<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-01T20:02:25Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 01 Nov 2023 20:02:25</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-01T20:02:25Z</published><updated>2023-11-01T20:02:25Z</updated><id>31f16c1b-4363-4416-9204-bccba945370a</id><summary type="html">Apple Sees Highest Ever Smartphone Shipments in India in Q3 2023; Market Records Flat YoY Growth (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Apple experienced its highest ever smartphone shipments in India during the third quarter of 2023.&lt;br&gt;- However, the overall smartphone market in India only saw flat year-on-year growth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XR (AR &amp; VR Headsets) Report on Market Insights and Trends, Q2 2023 (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- A report provides insights and trends on XR (AR &amp; VR) headsets in the second quarter of 2023.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Company news: Erica L. Masler hired by Hancock Estabrook law firm - syracuse.com (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Erica L. Masler has been hired by the Hancock Estabrook law firm, as reported by syracuse.com.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk and Sam Altman are expected to attend the UK's AI Safety Summit. Here's why it's taking place at a former top-secret WWII facility. (AI)&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk and Sam Altman are anticipated to attend the UK's AI Safety Summit, which will be held at a former top-secret WWII facility.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CD Rates and Savings Rates Today | Rates Remain Steady with Fed Meeting Imminent (Business)&lt;br&gt;- CD rates and savings rates are currently stable, with an imminent Federal Reserve meeting.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I would never recommend this to anybody': We accidentally bought a derelict Victorian apartment for $12,000 at an auction and transformed it into our dream home (Business)&lt;br&gt;- A story about accidentally purchasing a derelict Victorian apartment at an auction for $12,000 and renovating it into a dream home.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Personal Loan Interest Rates Today, November 1, 2023 | Rates Stall as Fed Meeting Looms (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Personal loan interest rates are currently stagnant as a Federal Reserve meeting approaches.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US economy is surging – but problems elsewhere could still torpedo profits for big companies like Apple and Tesla (Business)&lt;br&gt;- The US economy is experiencing growth, but challenges in other areas could still impact the profits of major companies like Apple and Tesla.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK household wealth has tanked and it's a sign of what could happen in the US (Business)&lt;br&gt;- The decline in UK household wealth serves as a warning of potential consequences in the US.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 3.5 million more American families went hungry after food prices spiked and the pandemic-era child tax credit ended (Business)&lt;br&gt;- The increase in food prices and the end of the pandemic-era child tax credit resulted in approximately 3.5 million more American families experiencing hunger.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mortgage Interest Rates Today, November 1, 2023 | Rates Down a Bit Ahead of Fed Announcement (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage interest rates have slightly decreased in anticipation of a Federal Reserve announcement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden Administration wants to close a retirement savings 'loophole' that could be costing you 20% on your investments (Business)&lt;br&gt;- The Biden Administration aims to eliminate a retirement savings loophole that may be causing individuals to lose 20% on their investments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I tried Walmart's self-checkout to see if it was as frustrating as some shoppers say. Here's what I found. (Business)&lt;br&gt;- An individual shares their experience of trying Walmart's self-checkout system and provides their findings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;From barbers to firefighters, the most AI-proof jobs are blue collar (AI)&lt;br&gt;- Blue-collar jobs, such as barbers and firefighters, are considered to be the most resistant to being replaced by AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Show HN: Clone someone and talk to them like in real life (AI)&lt;br&gt;- A project is showcased where individuals can clone someone and engage in realistic conversations with them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WeWork, a company once worth $47 billion, might soon go bankrupt (Business)&lt;br&gt;- WeWork, a company that was previously valued at $47 billion, is facing the possibility of bankruptcy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airline Apologizes for Forcing Disabled Man to Drag Himself Off Plane With No Wheelchair (Business)&lt;br&gt;- An airline issued an apology after a disabled man was forced to drag himself off a plane without a wheelchair.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;China wants to win the gene therapy race—and it’ll spend millions (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- China aims to lead the gene therapy race and is willing to invest significant funds to achieve this goal.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What are the hardest problems in tech we should be more focused on as a society? (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- A discussion on the most challenging problems in the tech industry that society should prioritize.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Western Digital Flash Business Spin Off Likely To Have Little Impact (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- The spin-off of Western Digital's flash business is expected to have minimal impact.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baltimore buried this river a century ago. Now, an artist is bringing it back to life (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- An artist is working to revive a river in Baltimore that was buried a century ago.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meet Dot, an AI companion designed by an Apple alum, here to help you live your best life (AI)&lt;br&gt;- Dot, an AI companion created by a former Apple employee, is introduced as a tool to enhance one's life.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wiley Laney Obituary - Bowser Family Funeral Home - Broken Bow ... - Legacy.com (Business)&lt;br&gt;- An obituary for Wiley Laney is featured on the Bowser Family Funeral Home website.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I got laid off from Amazon. They've tried 4 times to rehire me, but I can't go back. (Business)&lt;br&gt;- An individual shares their experience of being laid off from Amazon and declining multiple rehire attempts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos' net worth: How the ex-Amazon CEO went from startup founder to one of the richest people in the world (Business)&lt;br&gt;- The journey of Jeff Bezos, from a startup founder to becoming one of the wealthiest individuals globally, is explored.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bye California: 7 people who fled the state share the culture shocks they've experienced and why they have no regrets (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Seven individuals who left California discuss the cultural adjustments they have encountered and why they have no regrets about their decision.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I asked Meta's Kendall Jenner-inspired AI and ChatGPT for relationship advice. Only one actually responded like a friend. (AI)&lt;br&gt;- An individual sought relationship advice from Meta's Kendall Jenner-inspired AI and ChatGPT, with one providing a more friendly response.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I'm a girlfriend-for-hire. I use AI to help me satisfy customers, make more money, and feel better about my work. (AI)&lt;br&gt;- An individual who works as a girlfriend-for-hire discusses how they utilize AI to enhance their services and improve their job satisfaction.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charging, road trips, maintenance, and more: 8 EV owners reveal the realities of going electric (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Eight electric vehicle owners share their experiences and insights regarding charging, road trips, maintenance, and other aspects of owning an EV.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A popular tiny-home community near Tampa just added rentals under 400 square feet starting at $1,300 a month – take a look around (Business)&lt;br&gt;- A well-known tiny-home community close to Tampa has introduced rentals under 400 square feet, with prices starting at $1,300 per month.</summary></entry></feed>