<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-26T20:02:24Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 26 Aug 2023 20:02:24</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-26T20:02:24Z</published><updated>2023-08-26T20:02:24Z</updated><id>65ca676c-fa9f-491f-bcf6-7f49907ea55f</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers at Tencent AI Lab Introduces IP-Adapter: A Text-Compatible Image Prompt Adapter for Text-to-Image Diffusion Models&lt;br&gt;- Ngrok Starts Offering One Static Domain to All of its Free Users&lt;br&gt;- From Data to Frame: The Evolution of PDUs Across the OSI Model&lt;br&gt;- Overcoming Terraform Deployment Challenges: How to fix authorization issues using Service Principal on Azure Cloud&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- High-income Americans rarely mix with poorer people. Restaurants like Applebee's and Olive Garden are the exception.&lt;br&gt;- I spent most of my life without a penny in savings, but learning how much I can earn with high-yield savings completely changed my approach&lt;br&gt;- I'll make $140K driving for UPS this year. We deserve this pay &amp;mdash; it's not an easy job.&lt;br&gt;- Apple, Microsoft, Tesla, and Meta see a combined $625 billion wipeout in market value amid August's stock slump&lt;br&gt;- Startup extinction season is going to kick into high gear &amp;mdash; and there's likely going to be a bloodbath soon for some of the 50,000 VC-backed startups&lt;br&gt;- Wiley embraces a flexible future, empowering employees along the ... - HR Dive&lt;br&gt;- Merch, vinyl, hotels and credit cards: Taylor Swift's Eras Tour helped a bunch of companies &amp;ndash; but hurt others&lt;br&gt;- China's richest people are leaning hard into quiet luxury, wielding stealth wealth like a weapon and scorning their flashy, label-chasing peers&lt;br&gt;- 'Barbie' is about to pass 'Super Mario Bros.' and become the world's biggest movie of 2023&lt;br&gt;- 66% of Americans say they want extended European-style vacation policies at work&lt;br&gt;- Uncle Sam accuses SpaceX of not considering asylees and refugees for employment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- This AI Research from MIT Demonstrates How Machine-Learning System Based on Light Could Yield More Powerful and Efficient Large Language Models&lt;br&gt;- Stephen King won't forbid AI from training on his writing, and he's not afraid of AI ... yet&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Others:&lt;br&gt;- 200 monster hunters armed with drones join the biggest search in 50 years for Scotland's fabled Loch Ness creature&lt;br&gt;- The pedestrian detection systems in self-driving cars are less likely to detect children and people of color, study suggests&lt;br&gt;- Stormy Daniels leads mocking and disbelief that Trump weighs just '215 pounds,' as his Fulton County Jail booking record says&lt;br&gt;- I work as a fire lookout, living in a remote cabin with no plumbing or electricity. Here's why I want to be here as long as there are humans doing this job.&lt;br&gt;- Extreme heat could make photosynthesis impossible for tropical trees and plants that may all die as a result, a new study found.&lt;br&gt;- Apple Watch Is A Health Marvel, But Maybe A Health Hazard, Too, Report Claims&lt;br&gt;- Where to watch USA vs. New Zealand live stream basketball for free in FIBA World Cup&lt;br&gt;- Images from the Solar Orbiter spacecraft reveal tiny flares shooting from a 'hole' in the sun. They could explain how the sun blasts Earth with charged particles.&lt;br&gt;- 'Putin's vulture': Why the Ka-52 attack helicopter is one of Russia's most influential weapon systems&lt;br&gt;- Take a look at the $63 million F-16 fighter jet the West has pledged to help Ukraine win the war with Russia</summary></entry></feed>