<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-27T20:01:59Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:01:59</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-27T20:01:59Z</published><updated>2023-10-27T20:01:59Z</updated><id>dacd9031-9d3d-475f-bf0b-0a190cb08e5a</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Stimuli-responsive microlens arrays thinner than a human hair (John Wiley): Researchers have developed microlens arrays that can respond to external stimuli. These arrays are thinner than a human hair and have potential applications in various fields such as imaging and sensing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Automated identification of copy‐move forgery using Hessian and ... (John Wiley): A study proposes an automated method for identifying copy-move forgery in digital images. The method utilizes the Hessian matrix and other techniques to detect and localize manipulated regions in images.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The development of stimuli-responsive microlens arrays showcases advancements in microtechnology and its potential applications. The automated identification of copy-move forgery highlights the importance of digital image forensics in detecting image manipulation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Mark Zuckerberg's Meta has lost nearly $50 billion on the metaverse - more than Ford, Hershey, or Kraft Heinz are worth: Meta, formerly known as Facebook, has experienced significant losses in the metaverse market. The company's losses surpass the market value of well-established companies like Ford, Hershey, and Kraft Heinz.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The Kremlin plans to raffle off houses and holidays to shore up support for Putin ahead of an election: report: The Kremlin intends to boost support for President Putin by organizing raffles for houses and holidays. This strategy aims to garner public support ahead of an upcoming election.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The significant losses incurred by Meta in the metaverse market raise questions about the viability and profitability of this emerging industry. The Kremlin's plan to use raffles as a means of gaining support highlights the role of populist tactics in political campaigns.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Tsinghua University Researchers Propose Latent Consistency Models (LCMs): The Next Generation of Generative AI Models after Latent Diffusion Models (LDMs): Researchers from Tsinghua University propose Latent Consistency Models (LCMs) as the next generation of generative AI models. LCMs aim to improve upon the limitations of existing models like Latent Diffusion Models (LDMs).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- AI And The Future Of Work: Adapting To A Changing Landscape: This article discusses the impact of AI on the future of work and emphasizes the need for individuals and organizations to adapt to the changing landscape. It explores the potential benefits and challenges associated with AI integration in various industries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The proposal of Latent Consistency Models showcases ongoing research and advancements in the field of generative AI models. The discussion on AI and the future of work highlights the importance of adaptability and preparedness in the face of technological advancements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The development of stimuli-responsive microlens arrays and the automated identification of copy-move forgery demonstrate advancements in technology and its applications.&lt;br&gt;- Meta's losses in the metaverse market raise questions about the profitability of this emerging industry.&lt;br&gt;- The Kremlin's use of raffles to gain support highlights the role of populist tactics in political campaigns.&lt;br&gt;- The proposal of Latent Consistency Models and the discussion on AI and the future of work shed light on ongoing research and the need for adaptability in the face of technological advancements.</summary></entry></feed>