<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2023-12-14T20:02:13Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 14 Dec 2023 20:02:13</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-14T20:02:13Z</published><updated>2023-12-14T20:02:13Z</updated><id>a8e796e3-567c-4d86-bfc2-4b4a988cb240</id><summary type="html">In the world today, there are various interesting events taking place. Tesla has introduced Optimus Gen 2, a robot capable of taking care of eggs, showcasing the advancements in technology. Meanwhile, popular YouTuber MrBeast has been ordered to stop using the phrase 'Deez Nuts' on his candy bars due to its similarity to another phrase. A Gen Xer who relocated from Portland, Oregon to a small city in North Georgia expressed her inability to continue living there due to rising costs. In an effort to save money, a family of four has made several changes in their lifestyle. Additionally, it has been observed that Gen Z is increasingly obtaining news from TikTok, which may have positive implications. In the business world, Jack Altman has voluntarily stepped down from his CEO position at software unicorn Lattice. Let Them Live, an anti-abortion group, has been ordered to pay $10,000 that was promised but never given to women who agreed not to terminate pregnancies. Chris Smalls, the president of the Amazon Labor Union, is facing a battle to retain his job after agreeing to elections for the group's top positions. A former Google recruiter has shared insights on what makes job seekers appear desperate. The salaries of Wikimedia executives have sparked a debate about wages in the tech sector. In a personal account, a cruise performer reflects on their unique job experience traveling all over Europe. Threads, a messaging app, has expanded its user base to nearly half a billion users in Europe. Proton Mail has finally launched a desktop app for encrypted email and calendar services. Opera's gamer browser now features a 'panic button' for discreet browsing. AWS Management Console has introduced Intuitive Application Resource Management with myApplications. The Meta Ray-Ban glasses have encountered issues that cannot be solved by AI. The environmental impact of generative AI is being addressed, and a new system has been developed to teach robots household tasks within a short timeframe. Web3 is being hailed as a new paradigm for creativity and ownership in the artistic world. A company is making significant progress in decarbonizing the $444 billion industrial heat market. The Honest Company, despite the prevalence of 'clean' products, faces the challenge of standing out. A studio allows customers to design their dream Cadillac worth $340,000. Stone is making a comeback in architecture due to its strength, aesthetic appeal, and environmental benefits. Starbucks workers unionized two years ago, and there is hope that they will secure a contract in 2024. The art of interviewing is explored as a means to reveal the different facets of Elon Musk. Polymer molecular shape can now be quantitatively assessed using SEC with triple detection. AMD's new Threadripper chips have a hidden fuse that blows when overclocking, indicating potential issues. Hackers have discovered that trains were intentionally designed to break down after third-party repairs. Qogita, a wholesale marketplace, has raised $86 million in Series B funding to compete with Ankorstore in Europe. Lastly, Gartner predicts that by 2025, 50% of consumers will significantly limit their interactions with social media platforms.</summary></entry></feed>