<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-24T08:03:33Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 24 Aug 2023 08:03:33</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-24T08:03:33Z</published><updated>2023-08-24T08:03:33Z</updated><id>41030613-a6c6-4339-9d26-c20e53a7654b</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Nvidia just blew its results out of the water thanks to a technology spending wave that analysts haven't seen 'since the internet in 1995'&lt;br&gt;- Two years after Safari, Chrome plans to let you move the address bar to the bottom&lt;br&gt;- Nvidia’s Q2 earnings prove it’s the big winner in the generative AI boom&lt;br&gt;- Epic’s First Run offers 100% revenue share to game devs in exchange for exclusivity&lt;br&gt;- The AI Financial Crisis Theory Demystified: How To Create Resilient Global Ecosystems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: Nvidia has experienced exceptional results due to increased technology spending. Chrome is planning to introduce a feature that allows users to move the address bar to the bottom. Nvidia's Q2 earnings highlight its success in the generative AI market. Epic's First Run program offers game developers exclusive deals in exchange for 100% revenue share. The AI Financial Crisis Theory is explored, focusing on creating resilient global ecosystems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- CVS Health Launches Company To Produce Cheaper ‘Biosimilar’ Versions Of Expensive Biotech Drugs&lt;br&gt;- The SEC is introducing new rules for the quickly growing private fund industry&lt;br&gt;- Brazil proposes yuan guarantees in trade with Argentina amid dollar shortage&lt;br&gt;- China's Xi Jinping unexpectedly skipped a speech at a BRICS summit aimed at challenging dollar dominance&lt;br&gt;- California is considering offering unemployment to workers on strike as the Hollywood writers walkout approaches its 4th month&lt;br&gt;- US stocks surge as bond yields tumble amid signs of slowing growth in the US and Europe&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: CVS Health has launched a new company to produce more affordable versions of expensive biotech drugs. The SEC is implementing new rules for the private fund industry. Brazil proposes yuan guarantees in trade with Argentina due to a dollar shortage. China's Xi Jinping skipped a speech aimed at challenging the dominance of the dollar. California is considering offering unemployment benefits to workers on strike. US stocks have surged as bond yields decrease, indicating potential slowing growth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Nvidia just blew its results out of the water thanks to a technology spending wave that analysts haven't seen 'since the internet in 1995'&lt;br&gt;- Nvidia’s Q2 earnings prove it’s the big winner in the generative AI boom&lt;br&gt;- The AI Financial Crisis Theory Demystified: How To Create Resilient Global Ecosystems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: Nvidia's exceptional results and Q2 earnings highlight its success in the AI industry. The AI Financial Crisis Theory is explored, focusing on creating resilient global ecosystems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Membranous desquamation of the hand in a 7‐year‐old boy with ...&lt;br&gt;- The Truth About The ‘Blue Supermoon,’ The Biggest Full Moon Of 2023&lt;br&gt;- Latest ‘Alan Wake 2’ Trailer Is Filled With Unnerving Writerly Horror&lt;br&gt;- See the mugshots for Trump's co-defendants in the Georgia RICO case who have turned themselves in so far&lt;br&gt;- Ukrainian sniper ripped apart by a Russian shell says he had 16 operations to put his teeth and body back together so he could return to the front lines&lt;br&gt;- 5,000-year-old cauldrons of the Bronze Age are so well preserved they offer archeologists the 'first evidence' of an ancient feast consisting of milk and meat&lt;br&gt;- Here's Rudy Giuliani's mugshot, which he said authorities were 'going to degrade themselves' by making him take&lt;br&gt;- People in a genetic database have segments of DNA in common unexpectedly often&lt;br&gt;- Everlasting A-BONSAI Mini| Eternal Beauty that never changes by J-Wa International&lt;br&gt;- Ask Sophie: What are the visa options for a startup founder with family?&lt;br&gt;- Exactly When Apple Will Launch iPhone 15 Pro Max: New Date Claimed&lt;br&gt;- Presidential debates have always been political theater. Here are some of their most memorable moments.&lt;br&gt;- India's adorable, dog-sized moon rover is set to roll out any minute and collect the first samples of the lunar south pole ever&lt;br&gt;- Who is Yevgeny Prigozhin, the Wagner Group leader accused of 'betrayal' and 'treason' by Putin?&lt;br&gt;- No, you're not crazy. Pumpkin spice season is starting earlier this year, despite the ongoing sweltering heat.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: Various topics are covered in this section, including medical conditions, celestial events, entertainment, legal cases, historical discoveries, genetic research, product promotion, visa options, iPhone release, political debates, space exploration, military leaders, and seasonal trends. These topics provide a diverse range of information and insights.</summary></entry></feed>