<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-07T20:02:22Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 07 Dec 2023 20:02:22</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-07T20:02:22Z</published><updated>2023-12-07T20:02:22Z</updated><id>d24355a3-021c-4e7f-958b-97b5a48a5d65</id><summary type="html">In recent news, a radio station caused disappointment among fans when they announced Taylor Swift as a surprise guest at a concert, only for an impersonator to appear instead. Meanwhile, fraud investigators have made an arrest in the fake engine parts scandal that affected airlines like United and Delta. On a more positive note, AI models are predicted to have a significant impact in the near future, with the director of Google Cloud stating that they are just scratching the surface of their potential. Rolls-Royce has also unveiled a concept nuclear reactor that could potentially power a colony on the moon. In the entertainment industry, Gen Z and millennials have played a crucial role in the comeback of live events, which is expected to continue into next year. However, a new survey reveals that employees who feel pressured to work after hours are less productive compared to those who stick to a 9-to-5 schedule. The author of 'Rich Dad Poor Dad' warns that the exploding US debt will lead to inflation and the devaluation of the dollar. Additionally, Opal Security has raised $22 million to help companies manage access and identities. In international news, tens of thousands of Palestinians in Gaza are staying connected to the world through donated eSIMs. Ukraine's farmers are using drones and robots to clear the world's largest minefield, risking their lives in the process. On a personal note, someone shares their experience of moving their family from Milwaukee to New Zealand, highlighting the affordability of healthcare, better work-life balance, and the happiness of their children. Lastly, some individuals are capitalizing on the trend of tiny houses by setting them up in their backyards to earn extra income. Additionally, an app has been developed that allows Android users to send blue-bubble texts to iPhones, causing potential dissatisfaction for Apple.</summary></entry></feed>