<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-24T20:02:12Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 24 Sep 2023 20:02:12</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-24T20:02:12Z</published><updated>2023-09-24T20:02:12Z</updated><id>42909444-c076-46a0-9106-a54e941a2430</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Serum calprotectin can indicate current and future severity of COVID.&lt;br&gt;- Psychologist says there are 5 things that prompt us to tip more.&lt;br&gt;- This e-bike for 4-year-olds can do 15 miles an hour, costs $1,300, and sold out in a month.&lt;br&gt;- Citadel Securities is locked in a legal battle with 2 ex-staff who left to start a crypto firm and say they're victims of 'corporate bullying'.&lt;br&gt;- LeetCode, Hard++ (Acceptance 24%, Latest): 2867. Count Valid Paths in a Tree. DFS. O(n). Swift.&lt;br&gt;- The tech millionaire trying to live forever isn't afraid to drive as slowly as 16 mph in LA to avoid the 'beautiful irony' of dying in a car accident.&lt;br&gt;- How hydrogen bombs compare to atomic bombs, and how scientists created the most destructive weapon ever.&lt;br&gt;- Building a Sentiment Analysis App with Python and Hugging Face Transformers.&lt;br&gt;- 5 steps to build an authority for you and your repository.&lt;br&gt;- You may never become a better blockchain developer if you don’t read this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: &lt;br&gt;- Serum calprotectin can be a useful indicator for assessing the severity of COVID and predicting future outcomes.&lt;br&gt;- Understanding the psychological factors that influence tipping behavior can help improve service industry practices.&lt;br&gt;- The demand for e-bikes is increasing, even among younger age groups.&lt;br&gt;- Legal battles between established companies and startups in the crypto industry highlight the challenges and competition in the market.&lt;br&gt;- Continuous learning and problem-solving skills are essential for developers in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- The pursuit of immortality and the fear of death can influence personal choices and behaviors.&lt;br&gt;- The development and use of destructive weapons have significant implications for global security.&lt;br&gt;- Sentiment analysis and natural language processing technologies have practical applications in various industries.&lt;br&gt;- Building authority and expertise in a specific field can enhance professional growth and opportunities.&lt;br&gt;- Staying updated with the latest trends and developments is crucial for blockchain developers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Gas prices look like they'll get better — but not before getting worse first.&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine has 'completely defeated' a Russian naval infantry brigade of the Black Sea Fleet — for a second time, says think tank.&lt;br&gt;- Russia's desperate need for weapons in Ukraine could be a big win for the North Korean military.&lt;br&gt;- 10 cities where home prices are falling the most, as pandemic boomtowns cool down.&lt;br&gt;- Citadel Securities is locked in a legal battle with 2 ex-staff who left to start a crypto firm and say they're victims of 'corporate bullying'.&lt;br&gt;- The Cleanup of Seattle’s Only River Could Cost Boeing and Taxpayers $1 Billion. Talks Over Who Will Pay Most Are Secret.&lt;br&gt;- US commercial-property concerns keep mounting - experts warn of 'massive' debt refinancing risk and an economic 'doom loop'.&lt;br&gt;- Saudi Arabia and the UAE are battling to become the Middle East's economic superpower.&lt;br&gt;- The IRS is going to know if you made big money reselling tickets for tours by the likes of Taylor Swift or Beyoncé.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Fluctuating gas prices impact the economy and consumer spending.&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine's military success against Russia's naval infantry brigade highlights the ongoing conflict between the two countries.&lt;br&gt;- The arms trade and geopolitical dynamics have far-reaching consequences.&lt;br&gt;- The cooling down of home prices in certain cities indicates a shift in the real estate market.&lt;br&gt;- Legal disputes between companies can have significant financial implications and affect market competition.&lt;br&gt;- Environmental cleanup efforts can be costly and involve complex negotiations.&lt;br&gt;- The commercial-property sector faces potential risks and challenges in debt refinancing.&lt;br&gt;- Saudi Arabia and the UAE are competing for dominance in the Middle East's economy.&lt;br&gt;- The IRS is cracking down on ticket reselling for popular tours, potentially impacting the secondary ticket market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Deci AI Unveils DeciDiffusion 1.0: A 820 Million Parameter Text-to-Image Latent Diffusion Model and 3x the Speed of Stable Diffusion.&lt;br&gt;- Building a Sentiment Analysis App with Python and Hugging Face Transformers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Deci AI's new model showcases advancements in text-to-image generation and computational efficiency.&lt;br&gt;- Sentiment analysis using AI technologies has practical applications in various industries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;This report covers a range of topics including tech, business, and AI. Key insights include the potential of serum calprotectin as an indicator for COVID severity, the psychological factors influencing tipping behavior, the growing demand for e-bikes, legal battles in the crypto industry, the pursuit of immortality, the development of destructive weapons, the impact of gas prices on the economy, the ongoing conflict between Ukraine and Russia, the cooling down of home prices in certain cities, environmental cleanup costs, risks in the commercial-property sector, the economic competition between Saudi Arabia and the UAE, and the IRS crackdown on ticket reselling. Additionally, advancements in AI models for text-to-image generation and sentiment analysis are highlighted. Overall, this report provides valuable insights into various aspects of current affairs and technological advancements.</summary></entry></feed>