<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-10T20:01:11Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 10 Aug 2023 20:01:11</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-10T20:01:11Z</published><updated>2023-08-10T20:01:11Z</updated><id>b4d396d2-9836-4021-bead-b93da7f57090</id><summary type="html">Report: Global News Highlights&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's ChatGPT can write impressive code, experts say.&lt;br&gt;- AI companies are flocking to San Francisco, boosting the city's commercial real-estate market.&lt;br&gt;- The Yandex Leak: How a Russian Search Giant Uses Consumer Data.&lt;br&gt;- Get your staff's consent before you monitor them, tech inquiry warns.&lt;br&gt;- AI Is Only As Good As The Data That Trains It.&lt;br&gt;- AI could soon tell you the future value of your home.&lt;br&gt;- Months after an AI deepfake of the pontiff in a puffy coat went viral, Pope Francis is warning about the dangers of AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's change in label policy on X prompts a dramatic rise in the Kremlin's visibility, according to NATO.&lt;br&gt;- Manhattan renters are paying a record-breaking average of $5,588 per month, despite people leaving New York.&lt;br&gt;- Coach owner Tapestry acquires rival Capri Holdings for $8.5 billion, creating a US fashion giant.&lt;br&gt;- Hollywood's 100 days of strikes have likely dealt a $3 billion blow to California's economy.&lt;br&gt;- Bearish investor Boaz Weinstein is feeling the pain from this year's unexpected stock rally.&lt;br&gt;- The US FAST Market is growing, but ad experience is still lagging.&lt;br&gt;- HR Tech Funding falls to a 3-year low after a flurry of VC interest.&lt;br&gt;- Bootstrap, Sell Or Recapitalize? A Tech Entrepreneurs' Guide To Surviving A Capital Crunch In A Downturn.&lt;br&gt;- China's tech titans scramble to buy $5 billion of Nvidia chips as the US bans investment in key Chinese sectors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's ChatGPT can write impressive code, experts say.&lt;br&gt;- The Yandex Leak: How a Russian Search Giant Uses Consumer Data.&lt;br&gt;- Gates Foundation funds nearly 50 generative AI projects in low and middle-income countries.&lt;br&gt;- AI Is Only As Good As The Data That Trains It.&lt;br&gt;- Months after an AI deepfake of the pontiff in a puffy coat went viral, Pope Francis is warning about the dangers of AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's ChatGPT is making waves in the tech industry with its ability to write impressive code.&lt;br&gt;- The real estate market in Manhattan is experiencing a crisis, with record-breaking rents and a flatlining of new construction.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of AI on various industries, including tech, business, and society, is a recurring theme.&lt;br&gt;- The geopolitical tensions between Russia and Ukraine are causing ripple effects in international peace talks.&lt;br&gt;- The US-China trade war is influencing the tech industry, with Chinese companies scrambling to secure Nvidia chips.&lt;br&gt;- The importance of data in training AI systems is emphasized, as AI is only as good as the data it learns from.&lt;br&gt;- The potential risks and dangers of AI are highlighted, with Pope Francis warning about the dangers of deepfakes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report showcases the intersection of technology, business, and global affairs, highlighting key developments and insights in each category. The impact of AI, real estate trends, geopolitical tensions, and market dynamics are prominent themes throughout the report.</summary></entry></feed>