<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-21T20:02:14Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 21 Sep 2023 20:02:14</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-21T20:02:14Z</published><updated>2023-09-21T20:02:14Z</updated><id>08dd0c58-dd69-4f8a-a7af-d8f8eb8941c8</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. This AI Research Introduces Owl: A New Large Language Model for IT Operations&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Owl is a new language model designed specifically for IT operations, capable of understanding and generating code, providing solutions to complex problems, and improving efficiency in IT processes.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Owl has the potential to revolutionize IT operations by automating tasks, reducing human error, and increasing productivity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps Now Generally Available: Elevating Code Security to New Heights&lt;br&gt;- Key points: GitHub has launched Advanced Security for Azure DevOps, a new feature that enhances code security by providing vulnerability scanning, code analysis, and security alerts.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This integration between GitHub and Azure DevOps strengthens code security practices, ensuring that developers can identify and address vulnerabilities early in the development process.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Presentation: The Secret to Finding Impactful Projects to Land a Staff-Plus Engineer Role&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This presentation discusses strategies for engineers to identify and work on impactful projects that can help them advance their careers and land staff-plus engineer roles.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: By focusing on projects that have a significant impact on the business and aligning their skills with the company's goals, engineers can position themselves for career growth and increased responsibilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Expedia’s Project Explorer uses AI to curate trips based on budget and time of year (exclusive)&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Expedia has developed Project Explorer, an AI-powered tool that curates personalized travel itineraries based on user preferences, budget, and the time of year.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This AI-driven solution enhances the travel planning experience by providing tailored recommendations, saving users time and effort in researching and planning their trips.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. I’m an ER doctor: Here’s what AI startups get wrong about “ChatGPT for telehealth”&lt;br&gt;- Key points: An ER doctor shares insights on the limitations and challenges of using AI, specifically ChatGPT, in telehealth applications, highlighting the importance of human expertise and the need for context-aware AI systems.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: While AI can support healthcare professionals in certain aspects, it should not replace human judgment and expertise. Contextual understanding and the ability to handle complex medical scenarios are crucial for effective telehealth AI solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Six Ways Generative AI Can Help Companies Automate And Elevate Their CX&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Generative AI has the potential to transform customer experience by automating tasks, personalizing interactions, improving recommendation systems, enhancing chatbots, enabling virtual try-ons, and generating creative content.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: By leveraging generative AI, companies can streamline their customer experience processes, deliver personalized and engaging interactions, and gain a competitive edge in the market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights from all broader topics:&lt;br&gt;- The integration of AI in various industries, such as IT operations, travel planning, and customer experience, is driving innovation and improving efficiency.&lt;br&gt;- Code security is a critical concern, and advancements in tools like GitHub Advanced Security are essential for identifying and addressing vulnerabilities.&lt;br&gt;- Engineers can advance their careers by focusing on impactful projects that align with business goals.&lt;br&gt;- While AI has its benefits, it should be used as a tool to support human expertise rather than replace it, especially in fields like healthcare.&lt;br&gt;- Generative AI has the potential to automate and elevate customer experience, providing personalized and engaging interactions.&lt;br&gt;- The beauty industry is exploring innovative solutions to address its environmental impact and reduce pollution.</summary></entry></feed>