<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-17T10:04:24Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:04:24</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-17T10:04:24Z</published><updated>2023-08-17T10:04:24Z</updated><id>5c3874a9-1e47-4c3f-bd69-92d879322caa</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. How to Produce Green Hydrogen for $1/Kg – Terraform Industries Blog&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Discusses the production of green hydrogen at a cost of $1 per kilogram.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: Green hydrogen production at a low cost could revolutionize the renewable energy industry and contribute to a more sustainable future.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Leaked images reveal Lenovo’s Steam Deck competitor with a hint of the Switch&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Leaked images of a new Lenovo device that competes with Steam Deck and has similarities to the Nintendo Switch.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: The gaming industry is highly competitive, and companies are constantly innovating to capture market share.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Acronym’s new computer with Asus is bonkers, but that’s the point&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Acronym and Asus collaborate on a new computer that pushes the boundaries of technology.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: The partnership between fashion and technology companies can lead to unique and groundbreaking products.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Armed with new execs, dLocal rebounds from a short seller attack in a big way&lt;br&gt;- Key points: dLocal, a financial technology company, bounces back from a short seller attack with the help of new executives.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: Strong leadership and strategic decision-making can help companies overcome challenges and regain market confidence.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. 5 Best Real Estate Technology Trends to Look for in 2023&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Highlights the top five technology trends that will impact the real estate industry in 2023.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: Technology continues to disrupt various industries, including real estate, and staying ahead of these trends is crucial for success.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. Meet Embroid: An AI Method for Stitching Together an LLM with Embedding Information from Multiple Smaller Models Allowing to Automatically Correct LLM Predictions without Supervision&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Introduces Embroid, an AI method that combines multiple smaller models to improve predictions without supervision.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: AI advancements like Embroid have the potential to enhance the accuracy and efficiency of machine learning models.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. MLIR For Beginners: A series of articles on the MLIR framework&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Provides a beginner's guide to MLIR (Multi-Level Intermediate Representation), a framework for optimizing and transforming machine learning models.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: MLIR is a powerful tool that can help developers optimize and streamline their machine learning workflows.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Green hydrogen production at a low cost could revolutionize the renewable energy industry.&lt;br&gt;- The gaming industry is highly competitive, with companies constantly innovating to capture market share.&lt;br&gt;- Partnerships between fashion and technology companies can lead to unique and groundbreaking products.&lt;br&gt;- Strong leadership and strategic decision-making can help companies overcome challenges and regain market confidence.&lt;br&gt;- Staying ahead of technology trends is crucial for success in the real estate industry.&lt;br&gt;- AI advancements like Embroid and MLIR have the potential to enhance the accuracy and efficiency of machine learning models.</summary></entry></feed>