<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-20T22:01:04Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 20 Aug 2023 22:01:04</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-20T22:01:04Z</published><updated>2023-08-20T22:01:04Z</updated><id>de98b636-f0be-4f6f-92c8-0fe2f3dfd758</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine is re-engineering a Soviet-era missile system to strike inside Russia, according to UK intelligence.&lt;br&gt;- Russia's attempt to land on the moon after almost half a century ended in disaster.&lt;br&gt;- A glitch in X wiped out most pictures and links tweeted before December 2014.&lt;br&gt;- A Chinese AI paper proposes a Task Planning Agent (TaPA) for grounded planning with physical scene constraints.&lt;br&gt;- 20 VS Code extensions are recommended to enhance productivity.&lt;br&gt;- Chrome DevTools can be used to improve webpage performance.&lt;br&gt;- Custom directories and files can be created for Flutter projects with Go.&lt;br&gt;- Transitioning from the Options API to the Composition API in Vue 3 is discussed.&lt;br&gt;- Setting up PostgreSQL and replication between two servers on Ubuntu Server is explained.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Bond vigilantes are preparing to take action over the ballooning federal deficit.&lt;br&gt;- The resilience of Russia's stock market and economy is a mirage masking deeper pain, according to Yale researchers.&lt;br&gt;- A California-based Korean BBQ chain is expanding across the US, attracting Wall Street and meat lovers.&lt;br&gt;- An Amazon bestselling book was published during the Maui wildfires, raising concerns.&lt;br&gt;- Finland has ended homelessness and provides shelter for all in need.&lt;br&gt;- A Victorian mansion in Wisconsin, once called a "haunted house," was sold for $1.5 million.&lt;br&gt;- Borrowers are facing confusion as repayment looms, with incomplete debt relief and high monthly student loan bills.&lt;br&gt;- The dedollarization drive is facing a confidence crisis as the yuan, ruble, and Argentine peso simultaneously plummet, according to an analyst.&lt;br&gt;- Remote workers are struggling with social interactions and forgetting how to hang out with people.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- A Chinese AI paper proposes a Task Planning Agent (TaPA) for grounded planning with physical scene constraints.&lt;br&gt;- A US court denies AI image copyright, but the ruling has little significance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The geopolitical tensions between Ukraine and Russia are escalating, with Ukraine re-engineering missiles to strike inside Russia.&lt;br&gt;- Concerns over the ballooning federal deficit are leading investors to take action.&lt;br&gt;- Putin's invasion of Ukraine is considered a significant intelligence failure.&lt;br&gt;- Businesses are finding alternative solutions to dealing with crime, such as offering jobs instead of involving the police.&lt;br&gt;- Russia's stock market and economy may not be as resilient as they appear.&lt;br&gt;- Retirement planning and financial security are being reevaluated, with the realization that less cash may be needed to retire.&lt;br&gt;- In-N-Out has become a beloved fast-food dynasty in the US.&lt;br&gt;- Unique properties, such as a private island with a lighthouse toilet, are being sold.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of AI on copyright and legal issues is still being debated.&lt;br&gt;- The housing market and student loan debt continue to pose challenges for individuals.&lt;br&gt;- The transition to electric vehicles is gaining momentum, with considerations for tire selection.&lt;br&gt;- Lamborghini's first electric car is highly anticipated, boasting impressive horsepower.&lt;br&gt;- Gov. Ron DeSantis has faced backlash for his comments, drawing comparisons to previous political controversies.&lt;br&gt;- The dedollarization drive is facing challenges, impacting the yuan, ruble, and Argentine peso.&lt;br&gt;- Remote workers are experiencing social isolation and struggling with interpersonal interactions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;This report highlights various topics ranging from geopolitical tensions between Ukraine and Russia to the impact of AI and the challenges faced by remote workers. Concerns over the federal deficit, retirement planning, and the housing market are also discussed. The report provides insights into each topic, emphasizing key points and offering a comprehensive overview of the current landscape.</summary></entry></feed>