<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-07T08:03:42Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 07 Dec 2023 08:03:42</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-07T08:03:42Z</published><updated>2023-12-07T08:03:42Z</updated><id>0cbad7af-ddc7-4edb-908d-f8209e7d841f</id><summary type="html">In recent news, Wiley has announced that they will no longer be using the name "Hindawi" due to an $18 million decline in revenue. This decision comes as North and South Korea engage in a missile race underwater, with new missile-launching submarines being introduced. Meanwhile, McDonald's has unveiled the menu for CosMc's, a beverage-focused concept that could potentially compete with Starbucks. On a different note, Israel's highly accurate 2,000-pound SPICE bombs are being questioned for their potential overkill in Gaza. Additionally, a lawsuit alleges that Cecile de Jongh, former first lady of the US Virgin Islands, earned $200,000 a year on Jeffrey Epstein's payroll. In technology news, a robot dog has been introduced that doesn't instill fear of a robot uprising. Furthermore, the ex-security head of Twitter claims that he was fired to flout regulations. The National Institutes of Health's new chief, Monica Bertagnolli, aims for greater equity in biomedical research. The New England Journal of Medicine has also started a historical series examining its troubled past. In health-related news, the question of when it is too late to get a flu shot is addressed. In the business world, VC firm OpenView has reportedly collapsed due to the departure of two senior leaders. Additionally, Google's Gemini-powered phones may pose a challenge to Siri on the iPhone. TikTok's top videos of the year have been revealed, offering a different perspective from the usual dark and depressing content. Mortgage rates are falling at the fastest pace since the 2008 housing market crash. Lin Jiang has introduced Asian-inspired pancake mixes that promise to unveil a world of flavors. Urban Putt San Jose offers a mind-bending mini-golf experience along with a restaurant and bar. Pine Box Entertainment LLC has released the Bukana Bestiary, a 5E WakeSong Supplement. Fans of The Last of Us can look forward to the second season debuting in 2025. McDonald's plans to use Google AI to ensure the freshness of their fries. The surge in Bitcoin has reached the $44,000 threshold, prompting discussions on its future. In nature news, a rare "ghostly giant" jelly has been observed dancing in the deep ocean. CVS's simplified drug pricing plan has been criticized for being more confusing than ever. Artificial intelligence experts agree that regulation is necessary, but implementing it is the easy part. As the 2024 election approaches, the media faces the challenge of covering an election unlike any other. The creator economy continues to be a wild west for all involved. Finally, tensions between China and the rest of the world are being addressed. Wiley is also set to be arraigned on a manslaughter charge on December 13th, while the CEO of Young's Jersey Dairy has received a major award from the Ohio Restaurant Association.</summary></entry></feed>