<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-19T14:01:14Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 19 Aug 2023 14:01:14</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-19T14:01:14Z</published><updated>2023-08-19T14:01:14Z</updated><id>a504873a-d997-4cef-8285-7107f8028094</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- How to change your Facebook password: Reset your password to keep your account safe&lt;br&gt;- Create a systemd service script for running Gunicorn to serve your application&lt;br&gt;- HPC-AI Tech Raises 22 Million USD in Series A Funding to Fuel Team Expansion and Business Growth&lt;br&gt;- Show HN: Saf – simple, reliable, rsync-based, battle tested, rounded backup&lt;br&gt;- Implementing CI/CD pipeline with GitHub Actions, and GitHub Pages in a React app.&lt;br&gt;- Xbox’s new “8 strikes” mod rollout judges hate speech 3x worse than cheating&lt;br&gt;- Bored Ape Yacht Club creator to block OpenSea in fight over payments&lt;br&gt;- Apple Loop: Massive iPhone 15 Pro Upgrade, Apple Watch X Surprise, Disturbing iPhone Launch Details&lt;br&gt;- Android Circuit: Galaxy S24 Ultra Leaks, Oppo Reno10 Pro Prize, Honor Magic V2 Secrets&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk claims X users are about to lose an important safety feature—the ability to block trolls&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- PFL Playoffs NYC 2023 Results: Larissa Pachecho Obliterates Olena Kolesnyk In 14 Seconds&lt;br&gt;- PFL Playoffs NYC 2023 Results: Marina Mokhnatkina Makes Quick Work Of Amber Leibrock&lt;br&gt;- One in 5 Chinese young adults looking for work is unemployed. The lack of work slows down the whole economy&lt;br&gt;- TSMC – the world's most important company. And everyone wants control of it&lt;br&gt;- Express is laying off 150 workers. Here's the full list of major retailers making cuts, from Gap to Walmart.&lt;br&gt;- Analysis: Health care CEOs hauled in $4B last year as inflation pinched workers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- To-MAY-To, To-MAH-To: Why Digital Technology And Innovation Are Not The Same Thing&lt;br&gt;- Meet CipherChat: An AI Framework to Systematically Examine the Generalizability of Safety Alignment to Non-Natural Languages-Specifically Ciphers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- One in 5 Chinese young adults looking for work is unemployed. The lack of work slows down the whole economy&lt;br&gt;- Russian soldiers are fighting Ukraine high on amphetamines, a report claims. The Nazis did it first.&lt;br&gt;- On Maui, a perfect storm of climate, colonialism, and failed emergency systems made the deadliest US wildfire in over a century&lt;br&gt;- Radiation Spikes at Chernobyl: A Mystery Few Seem Interested in Solving&lt;br&gt;- Mister Rogers had a point – routinely greeting six neighbors maximizes wellbeing&lt;br&gt;- Exactly Where To Book Now For The U.S. ‘Ring Of Fire’ Solar Eclipse&lt;br&gt;- Today’s Wordle #791 Hints, Clues And Answer For Saturday, August 19th&lt;br&gt;- New Shows And Movies To Stream This Weekend On Netflix, Hulu, HBO Max, Disney+ And More&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section covers various topics such as Facebook password reset, creating a systemd service script, funding for HPC-AI Tech, implementing CI/CD pipeline, Xbox's new mod rollout, and disputes in the NFT space.&lt;br&gt;- The business section includes results from PFL Playoffs, unemployment issues in China, the importance of TSMC, layoffs in Express, and the earnings of health care CEOs.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section discusses the difference between digital technology and innovation, as well as an AI framework called CipherChat.&lt;br&gt;- The other section covers a range of topics including global unemployment, drug use in warfare, wildfires in Maui, radiation spikes at Chernobyl, the impact of social interactions on well-being, and upcoming solar eclipse events.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report highlights the latest developments in the tech, business, AI, and other sectors, providing insights into various trends and issues.</summary></entry></feed>