<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-06T20:02:30Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 06 Dec 2023 20:02:30</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-06T20:02:30Z</published><updated>2023-12-06T20:02:30Z</updated><id>a27ec735-2c8f-417c-a31a-256af116a839</id><summary type="html">In the world, there have been several significant events and developments. Cruise, a company specializing in driverless cars, has faced a major setback as it recalls its entire fleet. The new boss reportedly informed the staff about this "all-time low" for the company. On a different note, ChatGPT, an AI language model developed by OpenAI, has become the most viewed page on Wikipedia in 2023, surpassing popular figures like Taylor Swift, 'Oppenheimer,' and Elon Musk. This highlights the growing interest and impact of AI technology. Additionally, a chart suggests that buying groceries and cooking at home may once again be a better deal than dining out. This shift in consumer behavior could have implications for the restaurant industry. In education, there is a misconception about Gen Alpha, the youngest generation, being overstimulated by technology. However, one teacher argues that this perception is incorrect. Moving on to politics, it appears that corporate America is no longer afraid of President Joe Biden, as indicated by recent developments. Meanwhile, millionaires are returning to New York City, while individuals earning less than $172,000 are moving out. This shift in population dynamics could have economic implications for the city. In the tech industry, Intel has accused AMD of selling inferior CPUs, although the attack has since been deleted. Climate groups have criticized President Biden's AI order, claiming that it fails to address the environmental impact of artificial intelligence. Deloitte's chief futurist warns against becoming overly focused on AI and neglecting other important priorities. In the healthcare sector, emails have revealed how a hospital succumbed to political pressure and stopped treating transgender teenagers. The seafood industry is facing significant challenges, with China being largely blamed for its dangerous state. In the world of science and technology, Infocom's code-porting tools for games like Zork have been discovered, and advancements have been made in MR angiography and quantitative susceptibility mapping. Tragedy strikes as Dusty Miller's obituary is published, and the global smartphone market continues to evolve with new shipment and forecast trackers. Apple introduces its MLX machine learning framework, expanding the capabilities of its M Series. The chicken sandwich wars see a new competitor emerge as Chick-fil-A is compared to Pollo Campero. Jeff Bezos' relocation to Miami leaves behind a significant real estate empire in Seattle. The world witnesses the passage of the largest cruise ship under a bridge with minimal clearance. Elon Musk faces challenges but is expected to recover, while OpenAI's president expresses surprise at the success of ChatGPT. In Tokyo, a taxi driver is arrested for allegedly running over a pigeon. The impact of ChatGPT on e-commerce and customer experience is explored, and Tencent AI Lab introduces GPT4Video, a multimodal language model for instruction-followed understanding and safety-aware generation. Google AI Research presents Translatotron 3, a novel unsupervised speech-to-speech translation architecture. ViLa, an AI method utilizing GPT-4V, is developed for long-horizon robotic task planning. Lastly, investors focus on AI as startup funding faces challenges in the Asian market. These events and developments reflect the diverse and ever-changing landscape of the world.</summary></entry></feed>