<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-29T08:03:34Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 29 Sep 2023 08:03:34</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-29T08:03:34Z</published><updated>2023-09-29T08:03:34Z</updated><id>b4f31b2b-4e28-4b4d-b283-80d617667b0d</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Microsoft Tried to Sell Search Engine Bing to Apple Only 3 Years Ago&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft attempted to sell its search engine, Bing, to Apple in the past.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the potential challenges and changes in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. As Ukraine and Russia burn through artillery shells, the US Army is looking for new highly precise rounds to fire from its extra-long-range cannons&lt;br&gt;- The US Army is seeking advanced ammunition for its long-range cannons amidst the conflict between Ukraine and Russia.&lt;br&gt;- This emphasizes the continuous development and innovation in military technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Photos show the 3.86 billion-mile journey of OSIRIS-REx's asteroid sample mission from start to finish&lt;br&gt;- Images depict the extensive journey of OSIRIS-REx's mission to collect samples from an asteroid.&lt;br&gt;- This showcases the advancements in space exploration and the achievements of scientific missions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. 30 banks with 24/7 customer support either online or over the phone&lt;br&gt;- A list of 30 banks that offer round-the-clock customer support through various channels.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the importance of customer service in the banking industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Best High-Yield Checking Accounts of October 2023 - up to 7% APY&lt;br&gt;- A compilation of the top high-yield checking accounts available in October 2023.&lt;br&gt;- This provides valuable information for individuals seeking high-interest banking options.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. New California law raises minimum wage for fast food workers to $20 per hour&lt;br&gt;- California has implemented a new law that increases the minimum wage for fast food workers to $20 per hour.&lt;br&gt;- This reflects the ongoing discussions and changes in labor laws and workers' rights.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. OpenAI CEO Sam Altman and Sir Jony Ive may team up to create "iPhone of AI"&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's CEO and Sir Jony Ive are potentially collaborating to develop a groundbreaking AI product.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the convergence of technology and innovation in the field of artificial intelligence.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. AI sensors and WiFi networks that provide workplace insights are antidotes for some companies combating 'zombie offices'&lt;br&gt;- Companies are utilizing AI sensors and WiFi networks to gather workplace insights and address the issue of unoccupied offices.&lt;br&gt;- This demonstrates the application of AI in solving real-world problems and optimizing work environments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is constantly evolving, with companies exploring partnerships, advancements in military technology, and achievements in space exploration.&lt;br&gt;- The business sector focuses on customer service, high-yield banking options, and changes in labor laws.&lt;br&gt;- AI plays a significant role in various industries, from potential collaborations to workplace optimization.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report highlights the dynamic nature of the tech, business, and AI sectors, showcasing the latest developments, key points, and insights within each category.</summary></entry></feed>