<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-29T08:03:48Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 29 Nov 2023 08:03:48</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-29T08:03:48Z</published><updated>2023-11-29T08:03:48Z</updated><id>127036ec-0bf2-42a8-8ab0-1135ee1b7f32</id><summary type="html">In recent news, the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) has adopted rules that implement a provision of the Infrastructure Act. This move aims to improve the country's infrastructure and ensure its efficient implementation. In another story, a man accused of attempted murder testified that he did not intend to harm or kill an Upper Merion police officer during a shooting incident at a mall. The trial is ongoing, and the defendant is presenting his defense. Shifting gears, an article highlights the 60-year friendship between Warren Buffett and Charlie Munger, who both started their careers working in the same grocery store. Their enduring friendship and successful partnership in Berkshire Hathaway have been an inspiration to many. On a global scale, it is reported that Russia's Air Force remains largely intact, but there are concerns about its ability to build the necessary jets to secure victory on the ground in Ukraine. The situation in Ukraine continues to be a matter of international concern. In a more personal story, former President Jimmy Carter wore a blanket with his late wife Rosalynn Carter's image to her memorial service, showcasing their enduring bond. Shifting to the tech world, Amazon has introduced its Q AI assistant, allowing users to ask questions about their company's data. This development aims to enhance data analysis and decision-making processes. In the field of biomedical research, proposed changes to rules for policing fraud in U.S.-funded projects have received a mixed response. The potential impact of these changes on the integrity of research is being debated. In the business sector, scooter startup Tier has laid off 22% of its workforce in an effort to achieve profitability. This move reflects the challenges faced by many startups in achieving sustainable growth. In the media industry, the Sports Illustrated Union expresses its horror over the publication of AI-generated writers, raising concerns about the future of journalism and the role of human creativity. Tragically, Charlie Munger, Warren Buffett's longtime partner at Berkshire Hathaway, has passed away at the age of 99. Munger's contributions to the business world and his partnership with Buffett will be remembered. In the tech realm, Adobe's DMV3D has achieved state-of-the-art performance in generating high-fidelity 3D objects within seconds, showcasing advancements in computer graphics. On a somber note, an obituary for Christopher Barber has been published by Wiley Funeral Home, Granbury. In the field of science, researchers have made progress in generating red blood cells with a moustache-like structure, potentially leading to advancements in blood-related treatments. Additionally, the study of unstable metabolites in LC-MS/MS-based research is highlighted for its importance in understanding metabolic processes. In a fascinating development, dust from the Bennu asteroid has reached a UK museum, providing scientists with valuable insights into the composition of these celestial bodies. Shifting to a legal matter, Khazar Momeni, the sister of a suspect in the Bob Lee killing case, has been arrested and accused of DUI after an alleged hit-and-run incident. In an interview, Warren Buffett advises college students not to focus solely on money when choosing a career, emphasizing the importance of passion and fulfillment. In a disturbing incident, a woman is suing the Chop't salad chain, claiming that she found a portion of a human finger mixed into her arugula while eating. Moving to the real estate sector, Cher's former home on a private island in Miami has been sold for a staggering $35.35 million, offering a glimpse into the luxurious lifestyle of the rich and famous. In a significant discovery, a mine in Wyoming is believed to contain rare earth minerals worth $37 billion, which are crucial for the production of wind turbines, electric vehicles, and other technological advancements. In a heroic rescue operation, "rat miners" saved 41 men trapped in an Indian tunnel after the machines failed. Their bravery and resourcefulness are commendable. On the music front, Anna Indiana has become the world's first all-AI singer-songwriter, although her talent has been met with mixed reviews, with some considering her mediocre. In the culinary world, a person who initially found tending bar enjoyable faced a challenging situation when the entire kitchen staff quit, highlighting the difficulties faced by those in the restaurant industry. In the realm of artificial intelligence, Cloud TPU v5e is being utilized to power cost-efficient AI inference at scale, showcasing advancements in AI technology. In the field of science, researchers have successfully grown dolomite in the lab by dissolving defects during growth, offering new insights into the formation of this mineral. In the gaming industry, Dragon's Dogma 2 has been given a release date in March, along with the introduction of a new class, generating excitement among fans. Shifting to the energy sector, the extraction of oil and gas in the United States has reached a new high and is expected to remain near record levels until 2050, highlighting the country's reliance on these resources. In the world of coding, an article explores the hidden gems of Lisp, Clojure, and other programming languages, shedding light on their unique features and applications. In a thought-provoking study, scientists are examining the potential consequences if a rogue star were to crash through our solar system, offering insights into the dynamics of celestial bodies. Lastly, Sports Illustrated faces criticism for its use of AI-generated writers, with people roasting the publication for its ridiculous excuse. This incident raises questions about the future of journalism and the role of AI in creative industries.</summary></entry></feed>