<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-11T08:03:57Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 11 Dec 2023 08:03:57</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-11T08:03:57Z</published><updated>2023-12-11T08:03:57Z</updated><id>eac3683e-4ea5-4cd2-9bf7-3d9b59528ad6</id><summary type="html">In the world news, there have been several significant events. Firstly, former President Donald Trump accused Casey DeSantis of attempting to manipulate the Iowa caucuses after she unintentionally caused controversy by encouraging her husband's supporters to come to the state. Additionally, Senator Elizabeth Warren called out Apple for shutting down Beeper's 'iMessage to Android' solution. In the medical field, a study published by John Wiley suggests a link between metabolic dysregulations and the progression of Parkinson's disease. Furthermore, Senator Josh Hawley criticized GOP leaders for removing a measure compensating victims exposed to nuclear waste radiation from the latest defense bill, calling it a betrayal. In the business sector, a proposed merger between Cigna and Humana, which would have created a $140 billion healthcare conglomerate, has been called off. Meanwhile, McDonald's is planning new strategies for growth. In the technology realm, there have been developments such as the introduction of PC GEOS, a multitasking DOS-based GUI OS, and the unveiling of Mamba, a breakthrough SSM architecture for deep learning applications. Google DeepMind has also introduced AlphaCode 2, an AI system that utilizes the Gemini Model for competitive programming excellence. On a different note, cases of lead poisoning in children due to applesauce consumption have surged, raising questions about FDA oversight. In the financial sector, proposals have been made that would result in Columbia and NYU losing $327 million in tax breaks. Instead of a merger, Cigna has opted for a $10 billion stock buyback. In other news, Elon Musk has restored Alex Jones' X account, five years after he was banned. A Florida man who gained viral attention for his Joker face tattoos has accused GTA 6 of using his likeness. The US Air Force has announced retention bonuses of up to $600,000 in an effort to address a pilot shortage. Additionally, there have been concerns regarding stolen SSH keys by malicious PyPI and NPM packages. In the technology sector, AlaSQL, a JS SQL Database for browsers and Node.js, was featured in an interview. Lastly, it has been advised to delete 17 'dangerous' apps from phones, and a plane crash near Wiley Post in Oklahoma resulted in one fatality and one person being hospitalized. New York Attorney General Letitia James has stated that high-priced expert witnesses presented by Trump are aiding her civil fraud trial case.</summary></entry></feed>