<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-06T20:02:45Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 06 Sep 2023 20:02:45</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-06T20:02:45Z</published><updated>2023-09-06T20:02:45Z</updated><id>df2a007e-4da5-4dc0-b29e-9ccd5c59e3a2</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Hugging Face's new price calculator shows AI training doesn't come cheap.&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Hugging Face has developed a price calculator for AI training, highlighting the costs associated with it.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: AI training can be expensive, which may impact the accessibility of AI technology for smaller businesses or individuals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Google is about to turn 25. Its CEO thinks AI is the biggest tech development that we'll see in our lifetimes.&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Google's CEO believes that AI will be the most significant technological advancement in our lifetime.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: AI has the potential to revolutionize various industries and drive innovation in the future.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. My friend is on track to be a millionaire by 40, but ignoring their advice to automate my finances was the right move for 3 reasons.&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The author's friend is on a path to financial success, but the author explains why they chose not to automate their finances.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Automation may not always be the best solution for everyone, and personal financial decisions should be based on individual circumstances.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Vivek Ramaswamy's 'anti-woke' investment firm now manages assets worth more than $1 billion.&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Vivek Ramaswamy's investment firm, focused on opposing "woke" culture, has reached a significant milestone in managing assets.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: There is a growing market for investment firms that align with specific ideologies or values.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. Jeremy Grantham warns the AI boom won't stop a recession – and stocks are still likely to crash.&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Jeremy Grantham cautions that the AI industry will not prevent an economic downturn, and stock markets remain vulnerable.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: While AI has transformative potential, it does not guarantee immunity from economic fluctuations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Generative AI Is The Latest In The Growing Trend Of AI In Analytics.&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Generative AI is gaining popularity in the field of analytics, enabling the creation of new data and insights.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: AI technologies, such as generative AI, continue to advance and offer new possibilities for data analysis and decision-making.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;1. 'Barbie' is now the world's biggest movie of 2023 after overtaking 'Super Mario Bros.'&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The movie 'Barbie' has surpassed 'Super Mario Bros.' to become the highest-grossing film of 2023.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: The success of 'Barbie' highlights the popularity and influence of certain franchises in the entertainment industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. The head of the Anti-Defamation League says Elon Musk's behavior is 'dangerous and deeply irresponsible' after he threatened to sue the non-profit.&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The CEO of the Anti-Defamation League criticizes Elon Musk's behavior and considers it harmful and irresponsible.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Public figures and their actions can have significant impacts and may face criticism from organizations and individuals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of insights:&lt;br&gt;- AI training can be costly, potentially limiting its accessibility.&lt;br&gt;- AI is seen as a major technological development with the potential for significant impact.&lt;br&gt;- Personal financial decisions should be based on individual circumstances, and automation may not always be the best solution.&lt;br&gt;- Investment firms with specific ideologies or values are gaining traction.&lt;br&gt;- AI does not guarantee immunity from economic downturns.&lt;br&gt;- Generative AI is a growing trend in analytics, offering new possibilities for data analysis.&lt;br&gt;- The success of certain franchises can have a significant impact on the entertainment industry.&lt;br&gt;- Public figures' behavior can be subject to criticism and scrutiny.</summary></entry></feed>