<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-08T08:03:56Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 08 Dec 2023 08:03:56</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-08T08:03:56Z</published><updated>2023-12-08T08:03:56Z</updated><id>34b6fdc0-e812-44d4-bf9c-71712b807597</id><summary type="html">In the world, John Wiley &amp; Sons, a publishing company, released their quarterly earnings results and beat estimates by $0.17 EPS. This news was reported by MarketBeat multiple times. Another notable event is the upcoming release of the Tesla Cybertruck, with information about its delivery date, price, and specifications. FabFitFun, a subscription box company, faced backlash for a crude promo code in support of Elon Musk and their pledge to run ads on X. A Wall Street CEO demanded the resignation of Penn's president or threatened to withdraw a $100 million donation. An off-duty pilot named Joseph Emerson, who was accused of trying to crash a plane, will now receive mental health services that he previously avoided to keep his job. Google claims to have fixed data loss issues on Drive and has locked forum threads saying otherwise. The secrets of oobleck, a substance that behaves as both a liquid and a solid, are being unlocked through research. There are also various deals on headphones and wireless earbuds available. Biden wants the NIH to have the power to override patent rights for high-priced drugs. The Electronic Frontier Foundation is urging the Supreme Court to strike down laws in Texas and Florida that allow states to dictate what speech social media sites must publish. A new research hub aims to record life history through cells. Samira Wiley participated in a lip sync battle at the BET Soul Train Awards. Penn lost a $100 million donation after their president's poor performance in a congressional hearing. NASA found a stray tomato that went missing for 8 months in space, clearing the astronaut they initially suspected of eating it. A firefighter transformed a broken swimming pool into a sunken man cave with a full-service bar. The choice to replace George Santos, a Democrat, has lukewarm views on abortion and violated federal law multiple times with stock trades. Images from the Pearl Harbor attack 82 years ago are still unforgettable. A Californian claims to have achieved the American dream by moving to Canada. Placing conditions on US aid to Israel is no longer considered taboo. The impact of 5G technology is discussed, with insights into what's next for mobile tech. Saudi Arabia's Neom project aims to embrace green flying taxis, despite being the world's top oil exporter. A script for finding related posts with enhancements has been shared on Show HN. Ardent Worlds Publishing released "Ardent Tears: Awakening," an epic psychological fantasy. Mae Suramek published "Noodles, Drinks, World Peace: Recipes from Noodle Nirvana." Jennifer Roberson released "The Wonderful Wandering Wagon: Books One and Two." Some Android phones can automatically send medical data during 911 calls. The feasibility of battery swapping for EV consumers is being questioned.</summary></entry></feed>