<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-10T20:02:09Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 10 Dec 2023 20:02:09</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-10T20:02:09Z</published><updated>2023-12-10T20:02:09Z</updated><id>63bfe1bb-bd04-4b8d-b0b3-e7f6d3984cca</id><summary type="html">In recent news, the Resilient Communities Act has been introduced to assist communities that have been injured by unfair trade practices. This act aims to provide support and relief to those affected by such practices. In another story, the family of a victim speaks out after a guilty verdict was reached in the Wiley case, expressing their anguish and the impact it has had on their lives. Moving on to a different topic, the discovery of a massive skull belonging to a prehistoric sea monster, known as the 'ultimate killing machine,' has been made in the UK. This finding sheds light on the fascinating creatures that once roamed our oceans. Additionally, a group of superfans who consider Costco their 'happy place' share 11 surprising things they discovered while touring the store. Meanwhile, Elon Musk, under immense pressure from a significant gamble he has taken, is said to be cracking. The article explores the challenges he is facing and the impact on his mental state. As the winter season approaches, the fight against seasonal depression becomes a concern for many. 'Winter cities' are highlighted for their strategies in combating this issue. In other news, student-loan borrowers are on the verge of being one step closer to debt cancellation, with the article discussing what is expected to happen next. Megyn Kelly's recent statement about Donald Trump's mental sharpness is making headlines, as she claims he is increasingly confused. Shifting gears, chef Missy Robbins is reimagining the restaurant model one dish at a time, showcasing her innovative approach at Lilia. The rise of 'portfolio careers' is explored, with the article questioning whether it is simply a rebranding of hustle culture. Fan unions, which initially started as a joke, are now being considered as labor's next frontier, thanks to Taylor Swift's influence. The story of a divorced mom who went on to run a successful $34-million supplement company is shared, highlighting her journey of resilience and success. Additionally, a little-known way to obtain lower interest rates on mortgages is revealed, referred to as 'the mortgage cheat code.' Elon Musk's history with video games, from hating on GTA to playing Elden Ring until the early hours, is also discussed. The question of whether to subscribe to ChatGPT Plus is raised, considering its availability for free on Bing. The readiness of RISC-V for high-performance computing is evaluated, focusing on the 64-core Sophon SG2042 RISC-V CPU. Ancient Pompeii is depicted as a place of awful living conditions for the lowest class, shedding light on the harsh realities of life during that time. The Mavericks, an NBA team, are being sold as more than just a sports franchise, highlighting the broader impact they have on their community. The discrepancy between the number of cars bought by women and the macho designs of these vehicles is explored, raising questions about gender representation in the automotive industry. Meta AI presents EfficientSAM, a more efficient version of SAM with reduced parameters and faster runtime. The University of Hong Kong and Alibaba Group unveil 'LivePhoto,' an AI research breakthrough in text-controlled video animation and motion intensity customization. Tesla enthusiasts are given the opportunity to purchase a discounted Model 3 now or wait for the release of the Model 2. An artwork titled "Portrait of Tunji Adeniyi-Jones, 2023" by Kehinde Wiley is featured in Ocula Magazine. Kim Jong Un, known as a world dictator, is seen crying in a rare display of emotion. The best hardware for running small to medium models locally is discussed in response to a question posed by the HN community. Microsoft integrates Copilot with Azure Quantum Elements to advance scientific research. A new Tesla update allows users to customize their horn sound to resemble a screaming goat, adding a touch of humor to the world. ChatGPT users are warned that the AI might be tired of doing the heavy lifting when it comes to completing tasks at work. Lastly, Kevin McCarthy endorses Donald Trump for president in 2024, potentially eyeing a cabinet position in the future. The article concludes with a case study on cramming a tiny program into a tiny ELF file, showcasing a technical achievement.</summary></entry></feed>