<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-28T14:44:34Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 28 Jan 2024 14:44:34</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-28T14:44:34Z</published><updated>2024-01-28T14:44:34Z</updated><id>36e9cb6e-3108-4085-b828-f082660093da</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xiayanzheng/xiayanzheng.github.io/main/voice/36e9cb6e-3108-4085-b828-f082660093da.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, there has been a focus on the decline of hammerhead sharks, as local divers have been exploring the situation. These divers have been studying the population of hammerheads and have noticed a significant decrease in their numbers. This decline is concerning as hammerhead sharks play a crucial role in maintaining the balance of marine ecosystems. Additionally, there has been a nostalgic reflection on Unix desktops and the lessons we can learn from them. Unix desktops were once widely used and have left a lasting impact on the technology industry. By examining their history, we can gain valuable insights into the evolution of digital interfaces. Moving on, Adept AI has introduced a new multimodal model called Fuyu-Heavy, which is specifically designed for digital agents. This model aims to enhance the capabilities of digital agents in various tasks and interactions. In the realm of media literacy, classes focused on understanding and analyzing media content are gaining popularity. However, some conservatives have expressed concerns about a perceived "woke" agenda being pushed in these classes. Lastly, an individual shares their experience of creating a PalWorld server on AWS with a Discord bot in a two-part series. This guide provides insights into the technical aspects of setting up a server for the popular game PalWorld.
    </summary></entry></feed>