<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-20T18:01:03Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 20 Aug 2023 18:01:03</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-20T18:01:03Z</published><updated>2023-08-20T18:01:03Z</updated><id>15bf6e55-73b8-4329-8c7e-e8ba31f9d2f0</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- An artist used AI to create subversive images of Barbie in internet memes.&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI acquired a game studio working on a "Minecraft" clone.&lt;br&gt;- Apple Vision Pro's hand tracking feature is debated as a mistake or the future of gaming.&lt;br&gt;- NVIDIA introduced FlexiCubes, a new approach for generating high-quality meshes using neural workflows.&lt;br&gt;- INVE is an AI method that enables interactive neural video editing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- A "slum" landlord stuffed 40 tenants into a 4-bed house and made $450,000.&lt;br&gt;- Experts warn against sending emails on Sunday at 3:00 p.m. as it could be seen as a form of "techno-invasion."&lt;br&gt;- A simple playbook for new managers is provided.&lt;br&gt;- Lenny Rachitsky is discussed as a successful online writer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- An AI paper aims to transfer hand motion semantics among avatars.&lt;br&gt;- Large language models are compared to compilers for the 4th generation of programming languages.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- The US is identified as the biggest threat to the dollar, according to economist Benn Steil.&lt;br&gt;- A new immersive exhibit honors 50 years of hip hop.&lt;br&gt;- A 1954 Ferrari purchased for $2 million could be restored to its glory days.&lt;br&gt;- A 4-bedroom house in the English countryside is on the market for $11 million and includes a converted windmill guest house.&lt;br&gt;- Zelenskyy discusses talks with Sweden about receiving Gripen jets and producing "cool vehicles" like CV90s.&lt;br&gt;- A national security historian explains why aliens are unlikely to be found at Area 51.&lt;br&gt;- Recruitment of chalcone's potential in drug discovery for anti-SARS is discussed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The use of AI in various fields, such as art, gaming, and video editing, is expanding.&lt;br&gt;- Housing and real estate practices, including overcrowding and unique property listings, are highlighted.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of technology on communication, leadership, and email etiquette is explored.&lt;br&gt;- The future of programming languages and the potential of large language models are discussed.&lt;br&gt;- Geopolitical dynamics and military collaborations are mentioned.&lt;br&gt;- The intersection of science fiction and reality, such as aliens and historical artifacts, is touched upon.&lt;br&gt;- The potential of AI in drug discovery is mentioned.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, the report covers a range of topics including technology, business, AI, and other miscellaneous subjects. It provides insights into the current trends and developments in these areas, highlighting key points and offering analysis.</summary></entry></feed>