<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-12T22:01:20Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 12 Aug 2023 22:01:20</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-12T22:01:20Z</published><updated>2023-08-12T22:01:20Z</updated><id>38be88d1-99f8-4e5f-b032-878e0c3d3d40</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Harvard University Richest in World Encourages Students to Go on Food Stamps&lt;br&gt;- I feel like I made a mistake investing professionally into Flutter&lt;br&gt;- Mill’s ambitious smart trash can isn’t going to solve the food waste problem&lt;br&gt;- Can Large-Scale Language Models Replace Humans in Text Evaluation Tasks? This AI Paper Proposes to Use LLM for Evaluating the Quality of Texts to Serve as an Alternative to Human Evaluation&lt;br&gt;- Embracing the Magic of Dart: A Warm Welcome to Flutter's Loyal Companion 🚀&lt;br&gt;- Mastering Spring Data — A Step-by-Step Plan with free course Links&lt;br&gt;- Diablo 4’s 1.1.1 Patch Is Great, 1.1.2 Will Fix Something Annoying&lt;br&gt;- ‘Destiny 2’ Players Should Manage Expectations For ‘The Final Shape’ Showcase&lt;br&gt;- ‘Baldur’s Gate 3’ Has One Glaring Problem With Companions, And It’s Only Partly About Sex&lt;br&gt;- Virgin Galactic's first space tourism flight took off this week. Here are the players taking civilians to space.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft Continues Right to Repair About Face, Makes Its Hardware Easier to Fix&lt;br&gt;- tRPC – Move Fast and Break Nothing. End-to-end typesafe APIs made easy&lt;br&gt;- Train LLM with a Simple English Prompt! Meet gpt-llm-trainer: The Easiest Way to Train a Task-Specific LLM&lt;br&gt;- 🚀 Building an Invoice PDF system with React.js , Redux and Node.js&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI Deploys Crawler to Vacuum Up Your Posts and Train AI With Them&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Dear SaaStr: What Are The Characteristics of a Good SaaS Product?&lt;br&gt;- Buying my first house was a huge project, and my mortgage broker made all the difference&lt;br&gt;- I left my life in DC to live in a 400-square-foot tiny home near Tampa. I feel like I have more space and I'm saving money so I don't regret it.&lt;br&gt;- A small plane made a dramatic emergency landing on a busy British road at rush hour &amp;mdash; here's why pilots train to land on highways&lt;br&gt;- The average price of a resale ticket for the Eras Tour was $3,801. That's up 2,321% from Taylor Swift's last tour.&lt;br&gt;- China's economy is showing signs of serious trouble &amp;mdash; and the problems are still mounting&lt;br&gt;- College football players are smarter than you think . . .&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Can Large-Scale Language Models Replace Humans in Text Evaluation Tasks? This AI Paper Proposes to Use LLM for Evaluating the Quality of Texts to Serve as an Alternative to Human Evaluation&lt;br&gt;- Prompt Engineering Deciphers Riddle Of Show-Me Versus Tell-Me As Choice Of Best-In-Class Prompting Technique For Generative AI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Hurricane Dora Is Now A Typhoon But Did It Make The Maui Fires Worse?&lt;br&gt;- Current Climate: The Feds’ Billion Dollar Plan To Capture CO2 From The Sky&lt;br&gt;- Hurricane Dora Is Now A Typhoon But Did It Make The Maui Fires Worse?&lt;br&gt;- Current Climate: The Feds’ Billion Dollar Plan To Capture CO2 From The Sky</summary></entry></feed>