<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-20T20:02:14Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 20 Sep 2023 20:02:14</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-20T20:02:14Z</published><updated>2023-09-20T20:02:14Z</updated><id>9bd9f5a9-93cb-4eb9-ad64-7afc87f4c574</id><summary type="html">Report: International News Highlights&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Google Researchers Present a New Artificial Intelligence Approach to Modeling an Image-Space Prior to Scene Dynamics&lt;br&gt;- Harnessing the Power of SCSS in React: A Comprehensive Guide to Structuring and Styling Your Project&lt;br&gt;- WhatsApp Advances Towards Goal of 'Everything App' with New Business and Commerce Features&lt;br&gt;- Google researchers say you can tell AI to 'take a deep breath and work on this problem step by step' to improve its accuracy&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech industry continues to push boundaries in AI and software development. Google researchers are exploring new AI approaches, while React developers are leveraging SCSS for better project organization. WhatsApp is expanding its features to become an all-in-one app, and Google emphasizes the importance of step-by-step problem-solving for AI accuracy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Scholarly Journals: Wiley in European Hematology Association Deal - Publishing Perspectives&lt;br&gt;- The iPhone 15 launch in France could be disrupted after Apple store workers voted to strike on release day&lt;br&gt;- Russia's trade with the US plummets to a 3-decade low while its commerce with China surges toward a record $200 billion&lt;br&gt;- Rupert Murdoch has become a 'frothing-at-the-mouth' enemy of Donald Trump and often wishes for his death, new Michael Wolff book claims&lt;br&gt;- Hedge fund CEO says staff installed mirrors around the office to stop him from crashing into them while he rode a unicycle&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business landscape is diverse, with news ranging from publishing deals to labor strikes. Trade dynamics between countries are shifting, with Russia's trade with the US declining while its commerce with China grows. Personalities like Rupert Murdoch and hedge fund CEOs also make headlines, showcasing the unique aspects of the business world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Side hustles could become a $1.4 trillion industry by 2030 thanks to ChatGPT and AI, Morgan Stanley says&lt;br&gt;- Google Researchers Present a New Artificial Intelligence Approach to Modeling an Image-Space Prior to Scene Dynamics&lt;br&gt;Insights: AI continues to shape various industries, including the rise of side hustles driven by AI technologies like ChatGPT. Google researchers are at the forefront of AI advancements, exploring new approaches to modeling image-space and scene dynamics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is making strides in AI and software development, with Google researchers leading the way.&lt;br&gt;- Business news covers a wide range of topics, from publishing deals to labor strikes and shifting trade dynamics.&lt;br&gt;- AI is transforming industries, with side hustles projected to become a trillion-dollar industry by 2030.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the international news highlights the ongoing advancements and challenges in technology, business, and AI.</summary></entry></feed>