<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-22T20:01:51Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 22 Jan 2024 20:01:51</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-22T20:01:51Z</published><updated>2024-01-22T20:01:51Z</updated><id>db3aea8b-ca69-4269-848e-e19553f1f1ce</id><summary type="html">In recent news, Abercrombie, once considered America's most hated retailer, has managed to become a favorite among Gen Z consumers. The company's transformation has been remarkable, as it has successfully adapted to the changing preferences and demands of the younger generation. Meanwhile, the stock market is looking positive, with S&amp;P, Dow Jones, and Nasdaq all expected to extend their gains. Investors are eagerly awaiting earnings reports from major companies such as Netflix, Tesla, and IBM. In the tech world, design played a crucial role in driving $10 million in pre-orders for Rabbit R1 AI hardware. This highlights the importance of aesthetics and user experience in attracting customers. Additionally, a new image format called AVIF is set to replace JPEG, promising better quality and compression. However, amidst these developments, a woman has made headlines for stealing $2,500 worth of Stanley cups in a bold heist, reflecting an escalating national craze. In the political arena, Ron DeSantis, a candidate, ended his campaign on an optimistic quote attributed to Winston Churchill, only to later discover that it was actually fake. Lastly, following the issues with the 737 MAX 9, Boeing is now inspecting the 737-900ER model for any potential problems. On a different note, ChatGPT is being utilized to amplify software testing practices and assist in software delivery, showcasing the growing influence of AI in various industries.</summary></entry></feed>