<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-01T20:01:55Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 01 Oct 2023 20:01:55</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-01T20:01:55Z</published><updated>2023-10-01T20:01:55Z</updated><id>01f3a0af-3d42-4cf4-bedb-ff4b09302ecc</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Lensa's AI selfie app is back with new "Magic Avatars 2.0"&lt;br&gt;- In Digital Ocean, S3-like space keys can access all your buckets&lt;br&gt;- Twitter CEO Trying to Figure Out What to Tell Banks That Funded Elon's Disastrous Acquisition&lt;br&gt;- This smart Google tool can take notes in a meeting &amp;ndash; and let you catch up if you're late&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft Announces a New Azure SQL Database Free Offer in Public Preview&lt;br&gt;- Building a Firebase Authentication and Private Route System in a React App&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Lensa's AI selfie app has released an updated version called "Magic Avatars 2.0."&lt;br&gt;- Digital Ocean has a security vulnerability where S3-like space keys can access all buckets.&lt;br&gt;- Twitter CEO is facing a dilemma on how to address the banks that funded Elon's failed acquisition.&lt;br&gt;- Google has developed a tool that can take notes during meetings and allow latecomers to catch up.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft has introduced a new free offer for Azure SQL Database in public preview.&lt;br&gt;- A tutorial on building a Firebase authentication and private route system in a React app.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The advancement of AI technology is evident in the new features of Lensa's AI selfie app and Google's note-taking tool.&lt;br&gt;- Security vulnerabilities in platforms like Digital Ocean highlight the importance of robust security measures.&lt;br&gt;- The challenges faced by Twitter's CEO in handling the aftermath of a failed acquisition demonstrate the complexities of business decisions.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's continuous updates and free offers for Azure services show their commitment to attracting developers and users.&lt;br&gt;- Tutorials and guides on building authentication and route systems reflect the growing demand for web development skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Working Strategies: Business books for fall reading - St. Paul Pioneer Press&lt;br&gt;- Ski towns in the American West are getting swankier &amp;mdash; and pricing out frustrated locals&lt;br&gt;- I give my kids money through apps, not cash &amp;mdash; and I'm not alone&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett lost a bet on a college-football game. He paid up by shipping a decades-old $5 bill using FedEx.&lt;br&gt;- Biden's top economist says the key to ending the housing crisis is giving cities and developers monetary incentives to build more affordable homes&lt;br&gt;- We thought we avoided recession. Turns out we're not in the clear yet.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- St. Paul Pioneer Press recommends business books for fall reading.&lt;br&gt;- Ski towns in the American West are becoming more upscale, leading to affordability issues for locals.&lt;br&gt;- The use of apps for giving money to children is becoming increasingly common.&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett fulfilled a bet by shipping a $5 bill using FedEx.&lt;br&gt;- Biden's top economist suggests providing monetary incentives to address the housing crisis.&lt;br&gt;- Concerns arise about a potential recession despite initial optimism.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The book recommendations from St. Paul Pioneer Press indicate the ongoing interest in business-related literature.&lt;br&gt;- The gentrification of ski towns raises questions about the impact on local communities and affordability.&lt;br&gt;- The shift towards digital transactions, such as giving money through apps, reflects changing financial practices.&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's lighthearted bet settlement showcases his playful nature and attention to detail.&lt;br&gt;- The housing crisis remains a pressing issue, requiring innovative solutions and collaboration between cities and developers.&lt;br&gt;- Economic uncertainties highlight the need for continued vigilance and proactive measures to prevent a recession.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- A Ukrainian sniper called the Ghost of Bakhmut says he's personally killed 113 Russians. He explains how his elite unit hunts the enemy.&lt;br&gt;- All the ways student-loan borrowers can get help on their monthly payments &amp;mdash; and new relief to look out for next year&lt;br&gt;- Workers are worried about AI taking their jobs. Artists say it's already happening.&lt;br&gt;- AI chatbots let you 'interview' historical figures like Harriet Tubman. That's probably not a good idea.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- The Ghost of Bakhmut, a Ukrainian sniper, shares insights into his unit's tactics and achievements.&lt;br&gt;- Various options are available for student-loan borrowers to receive assistance with monthly payments, with new relief programs on the horizon.&lt;br&gt;- Concerns about AI replacing jobs are voiced by workers, while artists argue that it is already happening.&lt;br&gt;- The potential risks and ethical implications of using AI chatbots to interact with historical figures are discussed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The firsthand account of the Ghost of Bakhmut sheds light on the realities of warfare and the role of technology in modern conflicts.&lt;br&gt;- The availability of support for student-loan borrowers indicates efforts to alleviate the burden of debt.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of AI on employment is a topic of concern and debate, with differing perspectives from workers and artists.&lt;br&gt;- The use of AI chatbots raises questions about the boundaries of technology and the preservation of historical figures' legacies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of insights:&lt;br&gt;- The advancements in AI technology are evident in various applications, such as selfie apps, note-taking tools, and chatbots.&lt;br&gt;- Business trends include the rise of upscale ski towns, the shift towards digital transactions, and the need for innovative solutions in the housing market.&lt;br&gt;- The broader impact of AI is seen in warfare, employment concerns, and the ethical implications of interacting with historical figures.&lt;br&gt;- Ongoing vigilance is necessary to address potential economic challenges and prevent a recession.</summary></entry></feed>