<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-30T20:02:12Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 30 Aug 2023 20:02:12</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-30T20:02:12Z</published><updated>2023-08-30T20:02:12Z</updated><id>955b632e-8ce0-4434-8095-098b019cebe4</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Linux 6.6 to Protect Against Illicit Behavior of Nvidia Proprietary Driver&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft is using malware-like pop-ups in Windows 11 to get people to ditch Google&lt;br&gt;- The Fairphone 5 is a little more repairable and much more modern&lt;br&gt;- Budget for Project Users in Google Cloud Lowers the Barrier to Create and Manage Budgets&lt;br&gt;- Article: Streamlining Code with Unnamed Patterns/Variables: A Comparative Study of Java, Kotlin, and Scala&lt;br&gt;- css-loaders.com: The Biggest Collection of Loading Animations (more than 500 🤯)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Vin Fast suffered an $83 billion wipeout after the EV start-up's shares plunged 44% in a single day&lt;br&gt;- 4 Big Tech giants have plowed over $1 trillion into stock buybacks in 10 years &amp;mdash; more than Tesla or Meta's entire market value&lt;br&gt;- Burger King must face a lawsuit claiming it makes its Whoppers look much larger and meatier on its menus, a judge rules&lt;br&gt;- Employers need to stop treating workers like 7th graders, says ADP's talent chief&lt;br&gt;- The S&amp;P 500 could rally another 11% by year-end, Morgan Stanley Investment Management's Andrew Slimmon says&lt;br&gt;- Single people in Hawaii need to make an average of $112,411 to get by, a study has found. Here's how US living wages compare in the most expensive states.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from the University of Wisconsin–Madison Propose Eventful Transformers: A Cost-Effective Approach to Video Recognition with Minimal Loss in Accuracy&lt;br&gt;- Using measures of race to make clinical predictions: Decision making, patient health, and fairness&lt;br&gt;- PI3K block restores age-dependent neurovascular coupling defects associated with cerebral small vessel disease&lt;br&gt;- Elastocaloric signatures of symmetric and antisymmetric strain-tuning of quadrupolar and magnetic phases in DyB2C2&lt;br&gt;- The quorum-sensing peptidic inhibitor rescues host immune system eradication: A novel infectivity mechanism&lt;br&gt;- PtdSer as a signaling lipid determined by privileged localization of ORP5 and ORP8 at ER/PM junctional foci to determine PM and ER PtdSer/PI(4)P ratio and cell function&lt;br&gt;- A persistent major mutation in canonical jasmonate signaling is embedded in an herbivory-elicited gene network&lt;br&gt;- IL-15 synergizes with CD40 agonist antibodies to induce durable immunity against bladder cancer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- In the tech sector, there are advancements in operating systems, repairable smartphones, and code optimization.&lt;br&gt;- The business sector sees fluctuations in stock prices, legal issues, and discussions on fair treatment of employees.&lt;br&gt;- AI research focuses on video recognition, healthcare predictions, and advancements in neurovascular coupling and immune system responses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is evolving with new operating systems, repairable smartphones, and code optimization techniques.&lt;br&gt;- The business sector experiences market fluctuations, legal challenges, and discussions on fair treatment of employees.&lt;br&gt;- AI research explores video recognition, healthcare predictions, and advancements in neurovascular coupling and immune system responses.</summary></entry></feed>