<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-17T20:02:23Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 17 Nov 2023 20:02:23</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-17T20:02:23Z</published><updated>2023-11-17T20:02:23Z</updated><id>1e145518-1684-4679-bc21-d87dc60885e8</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Effects of low‐level Er:YAG laser irradiation on proliferation and ...&lt;br&gt;- epitoMAP Inc., Animal Allergy Clinical Laboratories Inc. and Nippon ... - BioSpace&lt;br&gt;- One in 5 teens who have heard of ChatGPT say they've used it for schoolwork, study finds&lt;br&gt;- Bellroy’s iPhone 15 Pro case has a proper Action Button now&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft Rebrands Bing Chat as "Copilot" in a Move to Unify AI Offerings&lt;br&gt;- How I optimized Portal to run on the Nintendo 64 [video]&lt;br&gt;- What's New in C# 12: Primary Constructors, Collection Expressions, and More&lt;br&gt;- Runway’s New ‘Motion Brush’ Feature in Gen-2 will Allow to Add Controlled Movement to Your Generations&lt;br&gt;- Meet Google’s Project Open Se Cura: An Open-Source Framework to Accelerate the Development of Secure, Scalable, Transparent, and Efficient AI Systems&lt;br&gt;- This AI Paper Introduces a Deep Learning Model for Classifying Stages of Age-Related Macular Degeneration Using Real-World Retinal OCT Scans&lt;br&gt;- This AI Paper from MIT Explores the Scaling of Deep Learning Models for Chemistry Research&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Bangladesh Smartphone Shipments May See Highest-ever Annual Decline in 2023, Modest Growth Expected in 2024&lt;br&gt;- It's time for retailers to stop blaming theft for so many of their problems&lt;br&gt;- Spiking mortgage rates are pricing poorer Americans out of the housing market – with a third of all homes bought in cash, Redfin says&lt;br&gt;- I quit teaching to work at Costco and I'm much happier. I never thought I'd leave my dream job, but these 5 things drove me out.&lt;br&gt;- Why a retiree planning to pay $1 million to live on a luxury cruise ship changed his mind: "Is this going to happen in my lifetime?'&lt;br&gt;- Online grocery startup Pricepally to expand in Nigeria backed by $1.3M funding&lt;br&gt;- Autodesk has ruled architecture for decades. These startups are trying to unseat it&lt;br&gt;- How Le Creuset picks the viral colors that will fill kitchens next year&lt;br&gt;- Disgraced Nikola founder's argument for why he should avoid jail: He's no Elizabeth Holmes&lt;br&gt;- China is helping the US deal with its massive fentanyl problem – sort of&lt;br&gt;- The stock market is edging toward extremes of Great Depression and dot-com eras&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- One in 5 teens who have heard of ChatGPT say they've used it for schoolwork, study finds&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft Rebrands Bing Chat as "Copilot" in a Move to Unify AI Offerings&lt;br&gt;- Meet Google’s Project Open Se Cura: An Open-Source Framework to Accelerate the Development of Secure, Scalable, Transparent, and Efficient AI Systems&lt;br&gt;- This AI Paper Introduces a Deep Learning Model for Classifying Stages of Age-Related Macular Degeneration Using Real-World Retinal OCT Scans&lt;br&gt;- This AI Paper from MIT Explores the Scaling of Deep Learning Models for Chemistry Research&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Low-level Er:YAG laser irradiation has shown positive effects on proliferation and...&lt;br&gt;- The use of ChatGPT among teens for schoolwork is more prevalent than expected.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's rebranding of Bing Chat as "Copilot" aims to streamline their AI offerings.&lt;br&gt;- Google's Project Open Se Cura aims to accelerate the development of secure and efficient AI systems.&lt;br&gt;- AI papers are exploring applications in various fields, such as age-related macular degeneration and chemistry research.&lt;br&gt;- The stock market is showing similarities to extreme periods in history, raising concerns.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall Summary:&lt;br&gt;This report covers various topics including tech, business, and AI. Key insights include the positive effects of low-level laser irradiation, the popularity of ChatGPT among teens, Microsoft's rebranding efforts, and the development of AI frameworks by Google. Additionally, AI papers are exploring applications in healthcare and chemistry research. The report also highlights concerns about the stock market reaching extreme levels.</summary></entry></feed>