<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-04T08:03:42Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 04 Oct 2023 08:03:42</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-04T08:03:42Z</published><updated>2023-10-04T08:03:42Z</updated><id>a82b2140-920e-49f6-a3e6-cab0abe547c5</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Samsung Galaxy S23 FE, Galaxy Tab S9 FE, and Galaxy Buds FE are now official, offering flagship features at lower prices.&lt;br&gt;- SP80 aims to have the fastest sailboat in the world next year.&lt;br&gt;- Intel plans to separate its Programmable Solutions Group (PSG) and potentially have an IPO in the next 2-3 years.&lt;br&gt;- Cruise, an autonomous vehicle company, faced an incident where one of its driverless taxis ran over a woman after a hit-and-run driver caused her to be launched into the car's path.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers used AI to analyze entries from an old drug forum.&lt;br&gt;- Puzzling objects found beyond Neptune hint at a second Kuiper belt.&lt;br&gt;- Generative AI is shaping the future of fraud prevention.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Eight GOP members voted to oust McCarthy from his position.&lt;br&gt;- Republicans have temporarily played themselves out of the presidential line of succession due to McCarthy's ouster.&lt;br&gt;- X has been ordered to pay $1.1 million in legal fees for ex-Twitter execs.&lt;br&gt;- Amex Member Week offers benefits to cardholders, including a Coachella presale and statement credits.&lt;br&gt;- Best deals on Visible phone plans offer Verizon-like service for $25.&lt;br&gt;- Best Mint Mobile plans offer unlimited data for $15 a month.&lt;br&gt;- Best AirPods sales and deals include AirPods Pro for $189.&lt;br&gt;- Best mattress sales in October offer discounts on Leesa, DreamCloud, and more.&lt;br&gt;- Hulu offers different monthly packages, including live TV.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers used AI to analyze entries from an old drug forum.&lt;br&gt;- Generative AI is shaping the future of fraud prevention.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Samsung's "fan editions" offer flagship features at lower prices, making them more accessible to consumers.&lt;br&gt;- The incident involving Cruise's driverless taxi highlights the challenges and risks associated with autonomous vehicles.&lt;br&gt;- The use of AI in various fields, such as analyzing drug forum entries and fraud prevention, showcases the potential of AI technology.&lt;br&gt;- The ousting of McCarthy from his position as House speaker is a historic event in US politics.&lt;br&gt;- The availability of various deals and discounts in the tech and business sectors provides opportunities for consumers to save money.&lt;br&gt;- The approval of Novavax's new Covid vaccine shows ongoing efforts to combat the latest strain of the virus.&lt;br&gt;- The introduction of Spotify's audiobook subscription plan expands the company's offerings beyond music streaming.&lt;br&gt;- The Edge Surf Game allows users to have entertainment while installing Windows 11.</summary></entry></feed>