<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-09T20:03:10Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 09 Dec 2023 20:03:10</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-09T20:03:10Z</published><updated>2023-12-09T20:03:10Z</updated><id>8d47b6e5-4697-42ee-a5a3-5ec5fbefaf74</id><summary type="html">In the world this week, there have been various news stories covering a wide range of topics. John Wiley &amp; Sons, a publishing company, had a strong week in the stock market, although it did not alleviate the pain of their five-year loss. The support for housing policies that are widely illegal in the United States has been shown to be the preference of the majority of Americans. Ukrainian tanks have played a crucial role in defending Avdiivka against Russian assaults, after previously taking a backseat in the fighting. A boomer decided to move from coastal Florida to a mobile home in a small Vermont town, expressing her eagerness to leave Florida behind. The concept of making jobs more enjoyable by transforming the workplace has been explored. Additionally, a homeowner in the British countryside renovated a 500-year-old home into an antique maximalist paradise. Airbnb hosts in Paris are scrambling to capitalize on the upcoming Summer Olympics, making it difficult for visitors to find affordable accommodations. Pollo Campero, a restaurant chain, aims to become the next chicken sensation in the US by offering a menu that combines the best elements of Chick-fil-A, Popeyes, and El Pollo Loco. A retired artist spent $70,000 to transform a vintage trailer into a retro tiny home on wheels. The popularity of private jets has led to the identification of the nine most popular airports for private jet travel. W4 Games, a video game development company, raised $15 million to support their work with the Godot Engine. The process of building a cloud-native monitoring application on Kubernetes and AWS ECR has been explored. The design of a memorial for the victims of the Pittsburgh synagogue attack was created by their families. The impact of university expansion and eminent domain on black land loss has been examined in the book "Uprooted." A study conducted by John Wiley focused on the characterization of multiple constituents in Valeriana jatamansi Jones using an online supercritical fluid. Marcellus Wiley, a former NFL player and ESPN host, is facing a lawsuit over an alleged rape at Columbia University in 1994. The European Union has reached a "historic agreement" on the world's first AI regulation, setting a global precedent. Tech executives like Bryan Johnson and Sam Altman are optimizing their diets to live longer, with experts recommending foods such as blueberries and red onions. A comparison of grocery prices at Costco, Walmart, and HEB for a family of four revealed surprising results, as Walmart was not the better bargain. A Gen Z office worker expressed their love for the structure provided by a 9-to-5 job, contrasting it with the frustration and demoralization experienced in a flexible job. The London EV show showcased a funky electric van and six other cool vehicles. In a tragic incident, a man was found half-eaten by zoo tigers after one of the apex predators was seen with a shoe in its mouth. AI doctor's offices at malls and gyms are allowing individuals to test their own blood without the presence of trained medics. The daily routine of Tim Cook, the CEO of Apple, includes waking up at 4 a.m. and reading hundreds of customer emails each day. A crisis PR expert criticized the testimony of elite college presidents, deeming it an embarrassment that could have been avoided. Apple AI Research has released MLX, an efficient machine learning framework specifically designed for Apple Silicon. Google AI Research has proposed TRICE, a new machine learning algorithm for tuning LLMs to be better at solving question-answering tasks using Chain-of-Thought (CoT) prompting. MVHumanNet, a large-scale dataset comprising multi-view human action sequences of 4,500 human identities, has been introduced. Lastly, the functioning of heat pumps, which have become a buzzword, has been explained.</summary></entry></feed>