<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-08T08:03:37Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 08 Nov 2023 08:03:37</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-08T08:03:37Z</published><updated>2023-11-08T08:03:37Z</updated><id>956048d8-583c-4450-87e0-7b1b7f5b6305</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- LG's new ultrawide monitors are smaller and cheaper.&lt;br&gt;- Apple updates iOS to prevent BMW's wireless charging from breaking iPhones.&lt;br&gt;- Revolutionary brain chips may have strange and troubling effects on the mind.&lt;br&gt;- AI and emerging technologies have the potential to mitigate the climate crisis caused by food production.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- US consumers have positive job outlook but negative views on the economy.&lt;br&gt;- Rivian seeks new electric van customers as its exclusive deal with Amazon ends.&lt;br&gt;- Top bitcoin miners sold their holdings as the price surged.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Revolutionary brain chips may have strange and troubling effects on the mind.&lt;br&gt;- AI and emerging technologies have the potential to mitigate the climate crisis caused by food production.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Belle man pleads guilty to voluntary manslaughter in a 2022 shooting.&lt;br&gt;- FCC examines increase in minimum broadband speed benchmark.&lt;br&gt;- Audrey Smith's obituary at Wiley Funeral Home.&lt;br&gt;- Baltimore artists inspire conversations on campus at Johns Hopkins.&lt;br&gt;- The US Army acknowledges the need for tanks in the Pacific but recognizes that the Abrams may not be suitable.&lt;br&gt;- Lawmakers push for 702 reauthorization requiring a warrant to access information on Americans.&lt;br&gt;- Four Color Comics History Cards: Mystery Men Comics by Christopher Irving.&lt;br&gt;- I Saw Blue Oyster Cult at the Sheboygan Armory in 1972 by David Sutton.&lt;br&gt;- The Old Ways Must Go: a tarot ritual game by Tim Rodriguez.&lt;br&gt;- John McGeoch: The Light Pours Out Of Me by Paul Sng.&lt;br&gt;- The Incredible Sensational Fiancée of Dr. Seyi Ajayi by Abbesi Akhamie.&lt;br&gt;- Gun deaths in children often occur in the line of fire of domestic violence.&lt;br&gt;- TCU Horned Frogs Offensive Players to Watch vs. Texas Longhorns - Sports Illustrated.&lt;br&gt;- Wiley accepts the 2023 Pro Bono Law Firm Award from DC KinCare.&lt;br&gt;- A discovery of more than 30,000 ancient Roman coins may lead to a hidden shipwreck.&lt;br&gt;- The best SSD for PS5 in 2023: Top M.2 solid state drives.&lt;br&gt;- What is a cash-out refinance? How to get money from your mortgage.&lt;br&gt;- The S&amp;P 500 experiences its best winning streak in 2 years as stocks extend gains amid falling bond yields.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is constantly evolving with new products and updates.&lt;br&gt;- The economy and job market have mixed sentiments among US consumers.&lt;br&gt;- The rise of cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin has attracted attention from investors.&lt;br&gt;- Emerging technologies like AI have both potential benefits and concerns.&lt;br&gt;- Various topics, including crime, art, literature, and sports, are covered in the news.&lt;br&gt;- The climate crisis is a pressing issue that requires innovative solutions.</summary></entry></feed>