<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-11T00:01:17Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:01:17</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-11T00:01:17Z</published><updated>2023-08-11T00:01:17Z</updated><id>73048018-b044-44f3-8bd4-4efc714339d0</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Launch HN: Rubbrband (YC W23) – Deformity detection for AI-generated images&lt;br&gt;- How ChatGPT and other AI tools are helping workers make more money&lt;br&gt;- Open-Source Large Autoregressive Vision-Language Models: Institutions Join Forces to Replicate DeepMind’s Flamingo Models&lt;br&gt;- Sonos’ $900 Dolby Atmos soundbar has a loud pop issue that’s taking years to fix&lt;br&gt;- Configurable typing of NPM packages. Typing may be stricter than you think&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Ingersoll Rand CIO Seeks New Ways To Drive Speed And Scale Via Tech&lt;br&gt;- Identity management platform Veza secures $15M from Capital One and ServiceNow&lt;br&gt;- The worst of the housing affordability crisis may be over, but that doesn't mean it'll get easier to buy a home soon&lt;br&gt;- Undergrad enrollment in petroleum engineering has dropped 75% over the past 10 years — even though they make 40% more than computer science grads&lt;br&gt;- Markets may be on a tear this year, but the economy is under the most pressure since 2008 and could still easily fall into recession, research firm says&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- How ChatGPT and other AI tools are helping workers make more money&lt;br&gt;- Launch HN: Rubbrband (YC W23) – Deformity detection for AI-generated images&lt;br&gt;- Open-Source Large Autoregressive Vision-Language Models: Institutions Join Forces to Replicate DeepMind’s Flamingo Models&lt;br&gt;- AI Is Coming For Your Data: 6 Steps To Ensure Cyber Resilience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Others:&lt;br&gt;- San Antonio punk band Piñata Protest touring with metal ... - San Antonio Current&lt;br&gt;- Exploding drone boats aren't hard to beat, but Russia's weak defenses are letting Ukraine blow up its ships&lt;br&gt;- I'm a 25-year-old with 2 master's degrees and $131,000 in student debt. I just left Paris and am getting ready to travel to Asia.&lt;br&gt;- Cher's former home on a private island in Miami is on the market for $42.5 million. Take a look inside.&lt;br&gt;- Clarence Thomas accepted previously undisclosed luxury vacations with rich friends that likely cost millions: report&lt;br&gt;- Trump's lawyers wanted Clarence Thomas to review their 2020 election lies, saying he was their 'only chance' of stopping Biden's victory&lt;br&gt;- Quinn-Finity: Welcome to Quinn-Landia Issue 1 2nd try by Nick Flair&lt;br&gt;- Exorcistic the Rock Musical Goes to New York! by Alli Chadd Emma and Michael&lt;br&gt;- FootRester™ | 3-in-1 Under Desk Foot Relief | by VILNO by VILNO&lt;br&gt;- Getting Started with Hy, the Python Lisp: a Matplotlib example (ep. 2)&lt;br&gt;- Author Annoyed to Find Amazon Selling AI-Generated Books Under Her Name&lt;br&gt;- Neptune Nanotechnologies Raises $1.8million To Revolutionize The Materials Industry By Transforming Waste Into Nanocrystals&lt;br&gt;- This Gen Z CEO is making sure TikTok and Instagram creators get paid&lt;br&gt;- The stock market's 'no recession' relief rally is over. Expect flat markets for the rest of the year.&lt;br&gt;- High-powered satellites have made blue-carbon credits a reality. But they still face accuracy and scalability issues.&lt;br&gt;- Ukrainian special forces surprised and killed dozens of Russians in a daring nighttime river raid, reports say&lt;br&gt;- Taylor Swift is slated to give a $320 million boost to a single US county - more than WeWork's entire market value&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- In the tech category, AI-related topics are prominent, indicating the growing influence and application of AI tools in various industries.&lt;br&gt;- The business category highlights the challenges and opportunities in the housing market and the impact of technology on driving speed and scale in businesses.&lt;br&gt;- The other category covers a wide range of topics, including music, travel, personal finance, and geopolitical conflicts.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report showcases the diverse range of news and trends in the tech, business, and other sectors, highlighting the intersection of technology and various aspects of life.</summary></entry></feed>