<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-21T18:01:21Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 21 Aug 2023 18:01:21</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-21T18:01:21Z</published><updated>2023-08-21T18:01:21Z</updated><id>b5b10758-746b-43ae-b674-fc74b31a2d03</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Insider Selling: Olin Co. (NYSE:OLN) VP Sells 800 Shares of Stock - MarketBeat&lt;br&gt;- Meet RAVEN: A Retrieval-Augmented Encoder-Decoder Language Model That Addresses The Limitations Of ATLAS&lt;br&gt;- Pinterest Revamps Its Asynchronous Computing Platform with Kubernetes and Apache Helix&lt;br&gt;- Learning Go by examples: part 12 - Deploy Go apps in Go with Pulumi&lt;br&gt;- What is routing and how to implement attribute routing in Asp.net MVC?&lt;br&gt;- How can Scala and Kotlin interact to build user-friendly DSLs (part two)&lt;br&gt;- How can Scala and Kotlin interact to build user-friendly DSLs (part one)&lt;br&gt;- Uncovering GAPS: a 3D experience map to identify and solve consumer problems with XR&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech section covers a range of topics, including insider selling, language models, computing platforms, programming languages, and consumer problem-solving. It highlights the advancements and innovations in the tech industry, showcasing the importance of staying updated with the latest technologies and techniques.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- I moved from New York City to Paris at age 79. Some people said I was crazy, but I wanted something new for this stage of my life.&lt;br&gt;- Some Walmart delivery drivers bringing groceries to customers' homes aren't who they say they are&lt;br&gt;- A pet wellness brand is offering dogs with 'bark-tastic social skills' and a tail that 'won't stop wagging' $100 an hour to be peanut butter ambassadors&lt;br&gt;- 10 common Facebook Marketplace scams, and how to avoid and report them&lt;br&gt;- Ecuador's runoff election is pitting a socialist against a banana baron&lt;br&gt;- Alibaba is so confident Beijing's tech crackdown has ended that it has just listed over 2,000 jobs for fresh graduates&lt;br&gt;- The year of 'global boiling' is creating an opportunity for winemakers in Sweden, and one winemaker says he can see things growing here that were unthinkable 30 or 40 years ago&lt;br&gt;- Russia's so desperate to get its billionaires and their massive wealth back that it just threatened to seize the assets of an oligarch worth $13 billion&lt;br&gt;- Why your team design is slowing your business down - and what to do about it&lt;br&gt;- Here's how government can accelerate their digital journey and empower citizens&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business section covers a wide range of topics, including personal stories, scams, elections, economic trends, and business strategies. It highlights the diversity and complexity of the business world, emphasizing the importance of adaptability, innovation, and ethical practices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Meet RAVEN: A Retrieval-Augmented Encoder-Decoder Language Model That Addresses The Limitations Of ATLAS&lt;br&gt;- Pinterest Revamps Its Asynchronous Computing Platform with Kubernetes and Apache Helix&lt;br&gt;- Embarking on a React Adventure? First, Master These 5 JS concepts! 🚀&lt;br&gt;- Learning Go by examples: part 12 - Deploy Go apps in Go with Pulumi&lt;br&gt;- How can Scala and Kotlin interact to build user-friendly DSLs (part two)&lt;br&gt;- How can Scala and Kotlin interact to build user-friendly DSLs (part one)&lt;br&gt;- Uncovering GAPS: a 3D experience map to identify and solve consumer problems with XR&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The AI section focuses on advancements in language models, computing platforms, programming languages, and problem-solving techniques. It highlights the growing importance of AI in various industries and the need for continuous learning and exploration in this field.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is constantly evolving, with advancements in language models, computing platforms, and programming languages. Staying updated with the latest technologies is crucial for success.&lt;br&gt;- The business world is diverse and complex, with stories ranging from personal experiences to economic trends. Adaptability, innovation, and ethical practices are key to thriving in this environment.&lt;br&gt;- AI is playing an increasingly important role in various industries, with advancements in language models, computing platforms, and problem-solving techniques. Continuous learning and exploration are essential in this field.</summary></entry></feed>