<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-01T20:02:02Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 01 Dec 2023 20:02:02</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-01T20:02:02Z</published><updated>2023-12-01T20:02:02Z</updated><id>0a3a73b0-e327-4cc6-a7b4-cf9e53a21da8</id><summary type="html">In the world, several notable events have taken place recently. In a dismemberment case, Sheganoski made a significant identification, providing crucial evidence. In Philadelphia, a man was convicted of attempted murder after shooting an Upper Merion police officer at the King of Prussia Mall. A woman who won a staggering $187 million in a lottery decided to sever ties with her family due to their demanding and greedy behavior. Tesla fans expressed disappointment and frustration with the Cybertruck's launch, criticizing its unexpected price hike. Surprisingly, Gen Z individuals are turning to TikTok for career advice, with creators sharing tips on workplace strategies like "corporate flirting" and being "delulu." There have also been concerns about scammy ads for Louis Vuitton bags on X, prompting questions to Elon Musk. Barcelona has found success in combating loneliness and pollution by encouraging people to give up cars and spend more time on the streets. Millennials have been vocal about their need for more than double the salary of previous generations to achieve happiness. Additionally, a professional cleaner shared five red flags to consider when choosing a new home. Telegram has introduced voice transcription for all users in its latest update. ClickHouse Keeper, a C++ and Raft-based alternative to Apache ZooKeeper, has been developed for efficient use. There is also information on removing git from a project and uploading it to a new repository. Cerbos v0.32 brings enhancements such as transitioning to OpenTelemetry and improved policy testing. 'DRESS,' a Large Vision Language Model (LVLM), has been introduced to align and interact with humans through natural language feedback. A high school's deepfake porn scandal has prompted US lawmakers to take action. The first CRISPR cure has sparked a potential patent battle. Shein, a popular brand among Gen Z, is going public, raising questions about which version of the company will be involved. There is also a discussion on Christian-based companies, both known and unknown. A former Lucasfilm executive has created a time-traveling chicken to help children cope with climate change. Columbia University scientists have discovered that soccer headers can diminish brain function over time. John Wiley has conducted studies on various topics, including detection in seized samples, impurities and composition measurement, gold nanocones for collocated tip-enhanced Raman, and the relationship between pellet size and shotgun dispersion patterns. ChatGPT has caused concern as it allegedly stole a client who brought in significant monthly revenue. Red Lobster's $20 promotion backfired, highlighting the desperation of diners for cheap deals. The Newsom-DeSantis debate, although focused on 2024, has set the stage for the 2028 political landscape. Benchmark, a renowned venture firm, has warned about potential pitfalls in the current AI funding frenzy. A tutorial on creating a before and after image slider with Vanilla JavaScript has been shared. Lastly, the World Climate Action Summit at COP28 is expected to address pressing global climate issues.</summary></entry></feed>