<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-21T20:02:06Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 21 Nov 2023 20:02:06</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-21T20:02:06Z</published><updated>2023-11-21T20:02:06Z</updated><id>6fa3c759-0379-4b59-a486-6083e4f8bc32</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Kirk Herbstreit reveals his top performing players from Week 12 - On3.com&lt;br&gt;- Emmett Shear's old tweet about interning at Microsoft might come back to haunt him&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's new CEO once compared working for Microsoft to selling his soul. It'll now be his biggest investor.&lt;br&gt;- Satya Nadella says OpenAI should've 'consulted' Microsoft before firing Sam Altman&lt;br&gt;- Nothing's iMessage app was a security catastrophe, taken down in 24 hours&lt;br&gt;- Finally, a guide for Node.js and TypeScript and ESM that works&lt;br&gt;- A Retrospective on Error Management: Where Do We Go From Here?&lt;br&gt;- Gartner IT Infrastructure, Operations &amp; Cloud Strategies Conference 2023 London: Day 2 Highlights&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech industry is filled with controversies and developments. From top-performing players in sports to CEOs' past tweets haunting them, there is always something happening. OpenAI's relationship with Microsoft is a topic of interest, with comparisons to selling one's soul and the need for consultation. Security issues and guides for programming languages are also discussed. The Gartner conference provides highlights and insights into IT infrastructure, operations, and cloud strategies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Linda Yaccarino is asking X staffers to be 'as fiscally responsible as possible' as advertisers bail from the site&lt;br&gt;- Millions of sustainability jobs are available to people with the right skills. The problem: Many don't have them, especially women.&lt;br&gt;- Walmart Black Friday crowds and chaos are a thing of the past&lt;br&gt;- Staff at Pure Barre and other boutique gyms say a major franchisee stiffed them on pay, sent bizarre emails, and talked about drinking his own urine&lt;br&gt;- Why Tod’s Is Joining LVMH And Prada Backed Aura Blockchain Consortium&lt;br&gt;- How a Top Mutual Fund Executive Made Millions for Himself Trading the Same Stocks His Giant Fund Was Trading&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business section covers a range of topics, from the financial challenges faced by companies to the availability of sustainability jobs. Advertisers leaving a site and the need for fiscal responsibility are highlighted. The changing dynamics of Black Friday shopping and the mistreatment of employees in boutique gyms are also discussed. The collaboration between Tod's and luxury brands in the blockchain consortium is explored. Additionally, the questionable practices of a mutual fund executive are brought to attention.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- The 'Magnificent 7' tech stocks add $150 billion of market cap in a day, with Microsoft leading the charge as investors zero in on the OpenAI psychodrama&lt;br&gt;- Satya Nadella says OpenAI should've 'consulted' Microsoft before firing Sam Altman&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The AI section focuses on the impact of tech stocks on the market, with Microsoft leading the charge. The OpenAI psychodrama and the need for consultation with Microsoft are emphasized.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;The tech industry is filled with controversies, developments, and the need for consultation between companies. The business section highlights financial challenges, job opportunities, changing consumer behaviors, and mistreatment of employees. The AI section focuses on the market impact of tech stocks and the importance of collaboration and consultation. Overall, the report showcases the dynamic nature of these industries and the various challenges and opportunities they present.</summary></entry></feed>