<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-28T14:08:04Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 28 Jan 2024 14:08:04</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-28T14:08:04Z</published><updated>2024-01-28T14:08:04Z</updated><id>cf0696aa-12a1-4c18-9152-0c5f68dd5850</id><summary type="html">In recent news, Adept AI has introduced a new multimodal model called Fuyu-Heavy, which is specifically designed for digital agents. This development aims to enhance the capabilities of digital agents and improve their performance in various tasks. In another story, media literacy classes are gaining popularity, but some conservatives perceive a 'woke' agenda behind them. This highlights the ongoing debate surrounding media education and its perceived political biases. Additionally, an individual who served as a US Air Force officer has reportedly spent $11 million in search of Amelia Earhart's long-lost plane and may have made a breakthrough in the investigation. This discovery could potentially shed light on the mysterious disappearance of the renowned aviator. Furthermore, a simulation of a China-Taiwan war assumes a scenario where former President Donald Trump returns to office in 2025, warning that Taiwan would face dire consequences. This simulation underscores the geopolitical tensions in the region and the potential risks involved. Lastly, Garry Tan, a tech CEO and campaign donor, has faced criticism for expressing a wish for the death of San Francisco politicians. This controversial statement has sparked a debate regarding the appropriate conduct of public figures and the boundaries of political discourse.</summary></entry></feed>