<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-17T18:01:38Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 17 Aug 2023 18:01:38</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-17T18:01:38Z</published><updated>2023-08-17T18:01:38Z</updated><id>c2726fd7-734e-482f-8535-b2fe99458919</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- I built my own app without knowing a single line of code. It was surprising how fast I got everything to work using AI and other tools.&lt;br&gt;- Salesforce AI Researchers Introduce the Evolution of LLM-Augmented Autonomous Agents and the Innovative BOLAA Strategy&lt;br&gt;- This Week In React #156: Server Actions, React Falls Behind, Expo Builds, Suspense Throttling, Obsidiosaurus, Expo DevTools...&lt;br&gt;- Effortless Containerization: Deploying Spring Boot and MySQL with Docker and Docker Compose&lt;br&gt;- Boost your Git Squash-Rebase Workflow with these Commands! (auto-squash, auto-commit, auto-rebase, auto-push)&lt;br&gt;- If ChatGPT had a brain, this is what it would look like&lt;br&gt;- ‘I sold my soul to the devil’: Background actors say they’re already losing work to AI&lt;br&gt;- How ‘heritage algorithms’ are shaping the future of art and design&lt;br&gt;- YouTube Ads May Have Led to Online Tracking of Children, Research Says&lt;br&gt;- An Iowa school district asked ChatGPT if a list of books contains sex scenes, and banned them if it said yes. We put the system to the test and found a bunch of problems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Forget AI - a $100 trillion investment opportunity awaits in clean energy, Schroders says&lt;br&gt;- Starbucks' $1.25 cold foam is the chain's most popular drinks add-on, and one of its most expensive. This is how it's made.&lt;br&gt;- Bud Light is winning over Americans again, 4 months after its collaboration with Dylan Mulvaney sparked a conservative boycott&lt;br&gt;- I started a blog and grew it into a $14 million business. Here's how I did it through affiliate marketing and social media.&lt;br&gt;- Paramount changed its mind about selling its majority stake in BET Media Group&lt;br&gt;- A distressed Rudy Giuliani made the hike all the way down to Mar-a-Lago to personally beg Trump to help pay off some of his legal bills: CNN&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- I built my own app without knowing a single line of code. It was surprising how fast I got everything to work using AI and other tools.&lt;br&gt;- Salesforce AI Researchers Introduce the Evolution of LLM-Augmented Autonomous Agents and the Innovative BOLAA Strategy&lt;br&gt;- ‘I sold my soul to the devil’: Background actors say they’re already losing work to AI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- The fight over 'return to office' policies has a dirty downside&lt;br&gt;- I rented a Tesla on Turo for a road trip. I own an EV, but 3 things about the Model 3 still surprised me.&lt;br&gt;- Gig workers are tracking customers who reduce tips after delivery by marking their homes on Google Maps&lt;br&gt;- US startup Joby is building an electric aircraft it wants to use to fly people between airports and cities for the price of an Uber &amp;mdash; take a look&lt;br&gt;- Forget Italy's 1 euro homes. You can buy a crumbling, 2-bedroom fixer-upper for $1 in Michigan.&lt;br&gt;- Getting a job at Apple without going to college or doing LeetCode&lt;br&gt;- The future of open source is still very much in flux&lt;br&gt;- Is The Way Many Cities Have Been Designed Making Them Even Hotter?&lt;br&gt;- The mystery of the social media disinformation war on plant-based meat&lt;br&gt;- You have a good excuse to turn off your camera during Zoom meetings—it’s better for the environment&lt;br&gt;- Of course the posters for the 2024 Paris Olympic Games are high art&lt;br&gt;- Use of UK plasma for the manufacture of albumins and vCJD risk - GOV.UK&lt;br&gt;- An Iowa school district asked ChatGPT if a list of books contains sex scenes, and banned them if it said yes. We put the system to the test and found a bunch of problems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Clean energy presents a significant investment opportunity, potentially worth $100 trillion.&lt;br&gt;- Starbucks' $1.25 cold foam is a popular and expensive add-on to their drinks.&lt;br&gt;- Bud Light's collaboration with Dylan Mulvaney helped win back American consumers.&lt;br&gt;- Building a successful blog through affiliate marketing and social media can lead to a $14 million business.&lt;br&gt;- Electric vehicles, such as the Tesla Model 3, continue to surprise consumers with their features.&lt;br&gt;- Gig workers are using Google Maps to track customers who reduce tips after delivery.&lt;br&gt;- US startup Joby aims to revolutionize air travel with its electric aircraft.&lt;br&gt;- The future of open source software remains uncertain.&lt;br&gt;- The design of cities may contribute to increased heat levels.&lt;br&gt;- Social media disinformation campaigns target plant-based meat.&lt;br&gt;- Turning off cameras during Zoom meetings can have environmental benefits.&lt;br&gt;- The use of AI in background acting is impacting job opportunities.&lt;br&gt;- The Paris Olympic Games posters are considered high art.&lt;br&gt;- The UK government is assessing the risk of vCJD in albumin manufacture.&lt;br&gt;- The use of AI systems to ban books based on content raises concerns about accuracy and reliability.</summary></entry></feed>