<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-05T08:03:49Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 05 Nov 2023 08:03:49</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-05T08:03:49Z</published><updated>2023-11-05T08:03:49Z</updated><id>95acafdd-1260-43e4-9f00-f280113c486f</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. The Olney Youth Arts Festival returned after a 4-year hiatus with new features and attractions. (The Philadelphia Inquirer)&lt;br&gt;2. Adaptive Learning Platforms Market 2029 – D2L, DreamBox... (Argyle Report)&lt;br&gt;3. GM's Cruise allegedly relies on human operators for "autonomous" driving.&lt;br&gt;4. Discord implements expiring file links to combat malware delivery.&lt;br&gt;5. AI companies argue against paying for copyrighted content.&lt;br&gt;6. A project onboarding process was reduced from 2 hours to 3 minutes.&lt;br&gt;7. OpenAI researchers develop advanced consistency models for high-quality data sampling.&lt;br&gt;8. DejaVu AI reduces costs without compromising AI capabilities.&lt;br&gt;9. Psychologist provides tips to avoid falling prey to online 'cockfishing.'&lt;br&gt;10. China's control of data raises concerns about digital sovereignty and trafficking.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Wiley College becomes Wiley University and announces new graduate programs.&lt;br&gt;2. Helpful reading list for executives.&lt;br&gt;3. AWS console explained as a central hub for managing Amazon Web Services resources.&lt;br&gt;4. Adam Kinzinger expresses concerns about the 2024 presidential election.&lt;br&gt;5. FTC Chair Lina Khan seeks allies in Silicon Valley.&lt;br&gt;6. Map shows states in favor of year-round daylight saving time.&lt;br&gt;7. Tech layoffs surge, Gaza internet collapses, and Apple hosts a Halloween event.&lt;br&gt;8. Building a distributed task scheduling and execution system using NoestJs, Docker, and RabbitMQ.&lt;br&gt;9. Pro-Palestinian protesters gather in front of the White House.&lt;br&gt;10. Elizabeth Warren praises John Fetterman's impact in the Senate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. Biden's cabinet explores the potential of ChatGPT in bioweapon development.&lt;br&gt;2. OpenAI researchers pioneer advanced consistency models for high-quality data sampling.&lt;br&gt;3. DejaVu AI reduces costs without compromising AI capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The Olney Youth Arts Festival's return after a hiatus indicates a revival of interest in the arts among the youth.&lt;br&gt;- The use of adaptive learning platforms in education is expected to grow in the coming years.&lt;br&gt;- The reliance on human operators for "autonomous" driving raises questions about the true autonomy of GM's Cruise.&lt;br&gt;- Discord's implementation of expiring file links shows a proactive approach to combating malware delivery.&lt;br&gt;- AI companies' resistance to paying for copyrighted content highlights ongoing debates about intellectual property rights.&lt;br&gt;- The significant reduction in project onboarding time demonstrates the potential of streamlining processes.&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's advanced consistency models contribute to improving data sampling quality in AI research.&lt;br&gt;- DejaVu AI's ability to cut costs without compromising AI capabilities is a promising development.&lt;br&gt;- The psychologist's advice on avoiding online 'cockfishing' provides valuable insights for internet users.&lt;br&gt;- China's control of data raises concerns about privacy and digital sovereignty.&lt;br&gt;- Blizzard's updates for Overwatch 2's competitive mode indicate ongoing efforts to enhance player experience.&lt;br&gt;- Wiley College's transition to Wiley University and the introduction of new graduate programs signify institutional growth.&lt;br&gt;- The reading list for executives offers valuable resources for professional development.&lt;br&gt;- Understanding the AWS console is crucial for effective management of Amazon Web Services resources.&lt;br&gt;- Adam Kinzinger's concerns about the 2024 presidential election highlight potential vulnerabilities in the electoral system.&lt;br&gt;- FTC Chair Lina Khan's charm offensive in Silicon Valley reflects the agency's efforts to build alliances.&lt;br&gt;- The map illustrating states in favor of year-round daylight saving time showcases regional preferences.&lt;br&gt;- The surge in tech layoffs, Gaza internet collapse, and Apple's Halloween event indicate diverse developments in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- The implementation of a distributed task scheduling and execution system using NoestJs, Docker, and RabbitMQ offers insights into efficient project management.&lt;br&gt;- The pro-Palestinian protests in front of the White House reflect ongoing geopolitical tensions.&lt;br&gt;- Elizabeth Warren's praise for John Fetterman highlights the impact of his presence in the Senate.&lt;br&gt;- Biden's cabinet's interest in ChatGPT's potential in bioweapon development raises ethical concerns.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The tech section of the report covers a range of topics, including the revival of the Olney Youth Arts Festival, the growth of adaptive learning platforms, concerns about the autonomy of GM's Cruise, Discord's measures against malware delivery, debates surrounding AI companies and copyrighted content, streamlining project onboarding, advancements in data sampling models, and cost-effective AI solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The business section highlights Wiley College's transition to Wiley University and the introduction of new graduate programs, a helpful reading list for executives, the importance of understanding the AWS console, concerns about the 2024 presidential election, FTC Chair Lina Khan's efforts to build alliances, regional preferences for daylight saving time, diverse developments in the tech industry, and the implementation of a distributed task scheduling and execution system.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The AI section focuses on Biden's cabinet's interest in ChatGPT's potential in bioweapon development, OpenAI's advanced consistency models, and DejaVu AI's cost-effective AI solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, the report provides insights into various tech, business, and AI topics, highlighting key points and offering a comprehensive summary of the gathered insights.</summary></entry></feed>