<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-14T22:01:23Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 14 Aug 2023 22:01:23</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-14T22:01:23Z</published><updated>2023-08-14T22:01:23Z</updated><id>697411fa-ac05-4a6c-94e8-2af8b79b3353</id><summary type="html">Report: Multilingual Insights on Tech, Business, and More&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. ChatGPT's Style Over Substance Trick:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers found that ChatGPT, an AI language model, has a trick that deceives people into thinking it's intelligent.&lt;br&gt;- The model's style may give the impression of intelligence, but its substance is lacking.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Language Models and Surface-Form Text:&lt;br&gt;- Language models can acquire impressive knowledge from surface-form text, such as learning how to draw.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the potential of language models to gain practical skills from textual data.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Generative AI's Dark Side:&lt;br&gt;- Generative AI can be a powerful tool for hackers to spread malware.&lt;br&gt;- The ability of AI models to generate content can be exploited for malicious purposes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. AMC's Meme Stock Dilution Concerns:&lt;br&gt;- AMC's stock price dropped by 35% due to fears of dilution caused by the conversion of APE units.&lt;br&gt;- Investors are concerned about the potential impact on the value of their shares.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Creator Economy Startups' Pitch Decks:&lt;br&gt;- Several creator economy startups have successfully raised millions of dollars.&lt;br&gt;- The pitch decks of these startups played a crucial role in attracting investment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Californians Fleeing to Texas:&lt;br&gt;- Many Californians are moving to Texas due to cheaper housing and a lower cost of living.&lt;br&gt;- The affordability of homes in Texas compared to California is a significant factor driving this migration.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. Knowledge Acquisition by Language Models:&lt;br&gt;- Language models can acquire knowledge from textual data, including practical skills like drawing.&lt;br&gt;- This showcases the potential of AI models to learn and apply information from various sources.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. The Impact of Generative AI:&lt;br&gt;- Generative AI poses a risk as it can be exploited by hackers to spread malware.&lt;br&gt;- The ability of AI models to generate content can be weaponized for malicious purposes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. The Deceptive Nature of ChatGPT:&lt;br&gt;- ChatGPT, an AI language model, tricks users into perceiving it as intelligent through its style.&lt;br&gt;- However, researchers found that the model lacks substantial intelligence behind its style.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;1. Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Language models have the potential to acquire practical skills from textual data, opening up new possibilities for AI applications.&lt;br&gt;- However, the deceptive nature of some AI models, like ChatGPT, highlights the need for critical evaluation and understanding of their limitations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Business:&lt;br&gt;- The success of creator economy startups demonstrates the growing interest and investment in this sector.&lt;br&gt;- The migration of Californians to Texas reflects the impact of cost of living and housing affordability on people's relocation decisions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. AI:&lt;br&gt;- The dual nature of AI models, with their potential for knowledge acquisition and misuse, underscores the importance of responsible AI development and usage.&lt;br&gt;- Understanding the limitations and potential risks associated with AI models is crucial for ensuring their ethical and secure deployment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall Summary:&lt;br&gt;This report provides insights into various topics, including tech, business, and AI, from different languages. It highlights the potential of language models to acquire knowledge and practical skills, the risks associated with generative AI, and the deceptive nature of certain AI models. Additionally, it discusses the concerns surrounding AMC's stock dilution, the success of creator economy startups, and the migration of Californians to Texas. These insights emphasize the need for responsible AI development, critical evaluation of AI models, and consideration of economic factors in decision-making processes.</summary></entry></feed>