<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-04T20:01:58Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 04 Jan 2024 20:01:58</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-04T20:01:58Z</published><updated>2024-01-04T20:01:58Z</updated><id>9afb1b03-a9da-42f9-b03c-cc631caf7627</id><summary type="html">In recent news, Microsoft has made a significant addition to PC keyboards with the introduction of an AI button for its Copilot tool. This marks the first major update to PC keyboards in 30 years, showcasing the company's commitment to advancing technology. Meanwhile, a federal lawsuit has been filed against an upmarket California restaurant, alleging that the establishment took thousands of dollars in tips from its staff to cover business expenses. The lawsuit sheds light on the challenges faced by employees in the service industry. On a different note, the combination of AI and satellite imagery has resulted in the creation of the clearest map of human activity at sea. This breakthrough provides valuable insights into human behavior and its impact on the oceans. In the world of technology, Perplexity AI, an AI-powered search engine, has recently raised $70 million in funding, bringing its valuation to $520 million. This highlights the growing interest and investment in AI-driven solutions. Shifting gears, a survey has revealed that managers are more inclined to continue working from home compared to their employees. This finding suggests a potential shift in work dynamics and preferences in the post-pandemic era. Finally, the chairman of Morgan Stanley has expressed his skepticism towards bitcoin, labeling it as speculative and volatile. He also predicts that the United States will be able to avoid a recession, providing his perspective on the country's economic outlook.</summary></entry></feed>