<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-14T00:01:25Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:01:25</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-14T00:01:25Z</published><updated>2023-08-14T00:01:25Z</updated><id>a525a735-bf2b-4210-bd5f-38e8c3661ee6</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Georgia prosecutors found texts and emails linking Trump's legal team to a voting breach.&lt;br&gt;- The 'Apple Watch X' is reportedly undergoing a major redesign, but it won't be released this year.&lt;br&gt;- Show HN: Broken Bear, an AI teddy bear that supports individuals going through tough times.&lt;br&gt;- Former VP claims Salesforce lied about software capabilities.&lt;br&gt;- Stability AI unveils Japanese StableLM Alpha, a breakthrough in Japanese language models.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's Xbox Series S parity demands are giving Sony an advantage.&lt;br&gt;- Crystal is making a comeback with a $150 million refurbishment of its ship and a new 2025 world cruise.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- I was at Goldman Sachs when I came out as a trans woman, reflecting on colleagues' perceptions.&lt;br&gt;- Disrupt is approaching, featuring fintech players taking the stage.&lt;br&gt;- Top SaaStr content for the week with CEOs from Cockroach Labs, Loom, and monday.com.&lt;br&gt;- Remote Work 2.0: Exploring the tools, trends, and challenges of the post-pandemic work era.&lt;br&gt;- The British navy is collaborating with the US to build a new 'Dreadnought' for a different battle at sea.&lt;br&gt;- The US is facing a debt storm, as shown by troubling charts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Sure AI is hot, but is it a market or a platform piece?&lt;br&gt;- 'Baldur's Gate 3' developers discuss the challenges of DLC.&lt;br&gt;- Learning produces a cognitive map in the form of a state machine.&lt;br&gt;- 75% of companies are considering banning ChatGPT and generative AI services, according to a survey.&lt;br&gt;- The CEO of Rewind AI receives mixed reviews on his performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Best mattress sales and deals in August, with savings of up to 50% on various brands.&lt;br&gt;- When should you get your next Covid-19 booster? How to decide.&lt;br&gt;- A video appears to show Ukraine's drones destroying a Russian 'Terminator' armored vehicle.&lt;br&gt;- Bad weather, natural disasters, and disease are impacting crops, affecting food commodity markets.&lt;br&gt;- See inside a test Boeing 777X as the planemaker races to certify its new jet by 2025.&lt;br&gt;- An introduction to the Conjugate Gradient Method without the agonizing pain [pdf].&lt;br&gt;- Tipping 'nudges' are now popping up on DoorDash, encouraging customers to leave a gratuity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The connection between Trump's legal team and a voting breach raises concerns about election integrity.&lt;br&gt;- The anticipation for the redesigned 'Apple Watch X' builds excitement among tech enthusiasts.&lt;br&gt;- AI applications like Broken Bear and StableLM Alpha showcase the potential for emotional support and language advancements.&lt;br&gt;- The challenges and opportunities of remote work 2.0 are explored in the post-pandemic era.&lt;br&gt;- The debt storm faced by the US highlights the need for fiscal responsibility.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of AI on various industries, including finance and customer service, is a topic of discussion.&lt;br&gt;- The travel industry, represented by Crystal's refurbishment and world cruise, is making a comeback.&lt;br&gt;- The importance of data privacy and ethical considerations in AI development is evident in the potential banning of generative AI services.&lt;br&gt;- The performance and leadership of CEOs in the tech industry are subject to scrutiny and praise.&lt;br&gt;- The decision-making process for Covid-19 boosters requires careful consideration of individual circumstances.&lt;br&gt;- The ongoing conflict between Russia and Ukraine is showcased through military advancements.&lt;br&gt;- The effects of climate change and disease on food commodity markets highlight the vulnerability of global food supply.&lt;br&gt;- The development of new aircraft models, such as the Boeing 777X, demonstrates the continuous innovation in the aviation industry.&lt;br&gt;- The Conjugate Gradient Method offers a mathematical approach to problem-solving.&lt;br&gt;- The emergence of tipping 'nudges' reflects the growing importance of gratuities in the gig economy.</summary></entry></feed>