<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-09T08:03:59Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 09 Dec 2023 08:03:59</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-09T08:03:59Z</published><updated>2023-12-09T08:03:59Z</updated><id>9a72ec85-9404-4dcb-9bcf-c9753a19d762</id><summary type="html">In recent news, billionaire investor Bill Ackman has called for Harvard University to address allegations of antisemitism, while simultaneously defending Elon Musk's controversial comments. Ackman argues that Harvard needs to be held accountable for any instances of antisemitism within its community. Meanwhile, former President Donald Trump's defense in his New York fraud trial is reportedly costing millions of dollars, particularly due to the expenses associated with expert witnesses. In Europe, the European Union has reached a provisional agreement on the AI Act, a groundbreaking law that will regulate artificial intelligence. This development paves the way for significant advancements in AI governance. On the scientific front, budget constraints are forcing U.S. particle physicists to scale down their ambitious projects. Despite their dreams of major breakthroughs, they are now focusing on smaller-scale initiatives. Additionally, a report suggests that the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) should enhance its investigation process following a rocket launch failure. OpenAI, a prominent AI research organization, is currently facing internal turmoil as one of its co-founders, who played a role in removing Sam Altman, finds themselves in a confusing situation. The ethical implications of AI are also being discussed, with a conversation featuring Diya Wynn, AWS Responsible AI Lead, shedding light on the subject. In the entertainment realm, various streaming platforms such as Netflix, Hulu, and Amazon Prime Video offer new shows and movies for viewers to enjoy over the weekend. The need for honest global action in combating fossil fuel influence and addressing climate change is emphasized, particularly in light of the upcoming COP28 conference. In the realm of technology, Apple faces challenges with its iPhone 16, leaks regarding its iPad, and a surprising development in its MacBook Air. AMD, a leading technology company, unveils AI accelerators that span from cloud to client, with the MI300 taking the lead. CX teams are advised to prepare for the long-term impacts of AI, as it continues to shape customer experiences. Android enthusiasts can look forward to updates on the Pixel 8 Pro and improvements in Genshin Impact, while OnePlus 12 details have been confirmed. In a significant milestone, the FDA has approved the first CRISPR gene-editing drug in the United States, marking a breakthrough in medical technology. An AI tool has also been developed to assist in demystifying paid leave claims for both employers and workers. The internet community expresses outrage over a Nike scholarship that asks teachers to grade essays for free, sparking a debate on fair compensation. In legal news, a law firm has prepared both Penn and Harvard for a hearing on antisemitism, highlighting their involvement in addressing this issue. Wiley, a publishing company, receives the 2023 Diversity Award from AT&amp;T, recognizing their commitment to diversity and inclusion. NVIDIA introduces AI accelerated DGL and PyG containers for graph neural networks, providing enhanced capabilities for researchers and developers. Starbucks announces a major reversal in its stance on workers' unions, expressing a commitment to reaching a deal after two years of conflict. The US Naval Academy showcases its impressive ability to prepare thousands of meals daily for midshipmen, demonstrating their logistical prowess. A 21-year-old Roblox creator gains attention for their unique room, which both fascinates and horrifies fans due to its roach-infested and trash-filled state. Rashida Tlaib, a member of the US House of Representatives, suggests that House leadership refused to authorize a vigil on the Capitol steps to mourn the deaths of Palestinians and Israelis, sparking controversy. Lastly, a 27-year-old individual known as the "water buffalo" is negotiating California's claim to the diminishing Colorado River, highlighting the complex water rights issues in the region. Apple has seemingly found a way to block Android's new iMessage app, while also cutting off Beeper Mini's access to iMessage after the launch of their service that brought iMessage to Android. Dollar General, a popular retail chain, is investing $150 million to bring back employees, as self-checkout technology proves insufficient for certain tasks. Meta, formerly known as Facebook, introduces a new AI that generates images based on users' Instagram and Facebook posts, raising concerns about privacy and data usage. Finally, NVIDIA presents a research paper introducing a novel AI model called Diffusion Vision Transformers (DiffiT), which leverages the effectiveness of vision transformers in diffusion-based generative learning.</summary></entry></feed>