<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-27T20:02:09Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 27 Nov 2023 20:02:09</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-27T20:02:09Z</published><updated>2023-11-27T20:02:09Z</updated><id>991f959d-95e0-47e8-9e13-de18cf17be3b</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- An artist has taught three robot dogs to paint, and they are now featured in an art exhibition.&lt;br&gt;- School children are using AI image generators to create inappropriate fake images of their classmates, raising concerns about internet safety.&lt;br&gt;- Jack Dorsey is eliminating annual reviews and PIPs at Block, prompting discussions about whether this is a trend in the workplace.&lt;br&gt;- Beijing is reportedly preventing big shareholders from selling stocks to sustain a market rally.&lt;br&gt;- Swift 5.9 Backtracer has become concurrency-aware, improving readability and Linux support.&lt;br&gt;- A digital theme park is being developed where people can live in a video game-like environment.&lt;br&gt;- A new AI tool called "Lightning Cat" has been introduced for detecting vulnerabilities in smart contracts.&lt;br&gt;- In a generative AI world, analog film photography is experiencing a resurgence.&lt;br&gt;- Companies are being criticized for not fully complying with data deletion requests from users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech industry is witnessing advancements in AI, robotics, and digital experiences. There are concerns about the misuse of AI technology, as well as discussions about changing workplace practices. The market rally in Beijing and the resurgence of analog film photography are notable trends. Data privacy and compliance remain important issues for companies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Best Cyber Monday MacBook deals offer up to $250 off on new Apple laptops.&lt;br&gt;- Best Cyber Monday AT&amp;T deals include savings on iPhone 15, Galaxy S23, and more.&lt;br&gt;- Americans who left big cities during the pandemic are now regretting their decision.&lt;br&gt;- Secretlab Cyber Monday deals provide savings on gaming chairs and desks.&lt;br&gt;- A $10 billion firm backed by WhatsApp billionaire Jan Koum is quietly building a startup portfolio.&lt;br&gt;- An Amazon senior leader advises caution before relocating for a new job, as regrets may arise.&lt;br&gt;- Several companies, including Nvidia and Meta, are hiring generative AI talent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The Cyber Monday deals for MacBook and AT&amp;T products are attracting customers. The regret of leaving big cities during the pandemic highlights the changing preferences of individuals. The presence of a secretive firm backed by a prominent billionaire indicates potential growth in the startup sector. The cautionary advice from an Amazon senior leader emphasizes the importance of considering job relocations carefully.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- An artist has trained robot dogs to paint, showcasing their abilities in an art exhibition.&lt;br&gt;- School children are using AI image generators to create inappropriate fake images, raising concerns about online safety.&lt;br&gt;- A new AI tool called "Lightning Cat" has been developed for detecting vulnerabilities in smart contracts.&lt;br&gt;- Companies are hiring generative AI talent, with several prominent names actively recruiting.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: AI is being utilized in various fields, such as art and contract security. However, concerns about the misuse of AI technology, particularly by children, highlight the need for responsible usage and online safety measures. The demand for generative AI talent indicates the growing importance of AI in business operations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The tech industry is witnessing advancements in AI, robotics, and digital experiences. Concerns about the misuse of AI technology and data privacy are prevalent. Changes in workplace practices, such as eliminating annual reviews, are being discussed. The market rally in Beijing and the resurgence of analog film photography are notable trends. Cyber Monday deals for MacBook, AT&amp;T products, and gaming chairs are attracting customers. The regret of leaving big cities during the pandemic and the cautionary advice regarding job relocations highlight changing preferences and considerations. The presence of a secretive firm backed by a prominent billionaire indicates potential growth in the startup sector. The demand for generative AI talent emphasizes the increasing importance of AI in various industries.</summary></entry></feed>