<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-18T10:05:34Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:05:34</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-18T10:05:34Z</published><updated>2023-08-18T10:05:34Z</updated><id>a11ae08c-a745-471d-9d3a-9ad77ba04bd1</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Amazon’s New Fee on Third-Party Sellers: A Strategic Move or Coercive Tactic?&lt;br&gt;- Apple Abandons Plan to Move “End Call” Button in iOS 17&lt;br&gt;- Parmigiano-Reggiano makers are putting edible microchips the size of a grain of sand into their 90-pound cheese wheels to combat counterfeiters&lt;br&gt;- Threads gets retweets — sorry, reposts — in the reverse-chronological feed&lt;br&gt;- Cruise Robotaxi Drives Into Wet Concrete; Waymo Shows Off Same Route&lt;br&gt;- Blue Light Glasses May Not Help With Eye Strain Or Improve Sleep Quality, Study Says&lt;br&gt;- Razer’s new BlackWidow V4 75 could be a great starter mechanical keyboard&lt;br&gt;- Never write tests or docs again! - Amalgam could change everything.&lt;br&gt;- YouTube Ads May Have Led to Online Tracking of Children, Research Says&lt;br&gt;- How the Army tried and failed to build a bicycle corps (2020)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- CRO Confidential LIVE with Sam Blond and Gong’s SVP Sales at SaaStr Annual 2023!!&lt;br&gt;- US Courseware Market: Unlocking a USD 1061.45 Million Growth ... - PR Newswire&lt;br&gt;- Some people say they're angry that UPS workers could make $170,000 including benefits. Members of Congress make more than that for working a lot less.&lt;br&gt;- Whole Foods is attracting extreme couponers who are sharing tips on TikTok for saving money at the supermarket once known as 'whole paycheck'&lt;br&gt;- Fubo TV price and channels: A complete breakdown of streaming plans, networks, and upgrade packages in 2023&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- When To See Saturn At Its Biggest, Brightest And Best This Week&lt;br&gt;- When To See Saturn At Its Biggest, Brightest And Best This Week&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- This archive broadened access during the pandemic. Then ... - Fronteras: The Changing America Desk&lt;br&gt;- Why is RFK Jr.'s voice raspy? He has a neurological disorder called spasmodic dysphonia&lt;br&gt;- South Africa to ban fishing around African penguin colonies for 10 years&lt;br&gt;- Dolphins are dying in droves in the Black Sea, and Ukraine says it's evidence that Russia is committing a new kind of war crime&lt;br&gt;- 9 techniques villagers used starting in the 14th century to bury people they feared were 'vampires' to keep them from coming back from the dead&lt;br&gt;- Bill Barr rejects Trump's plea that it's unfair to try him while he's running: 'You don't get immunity' by being a presidential candidate&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine says it can shoot down Ka-52 attack helicopters but Russia needs to be stopped from making new ones&lt;br&gt;- Maui wildfires made Hawaii's housing market crisis worse &amp;mdash; residents already feared being priced out&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section covers a range of topics including e-commerce, smartphone features, counterfeit prevention, autonomous vehicles, and the impact of technology on health.&lt;br&gt;- The business section focuses on sales strategies, market growth, income disparities, and consumer behavior.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section highlights celestial events and their significance.&lt;br&gt;- The other section includes various topics such as archives, health conditions, environmental conservation, historical practices, legal matters, and regional issues.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report provides a diverse range of insights into technology, business, AI, and other areas, showcasing the impact of these topics on society and the world.</summary></entry></feed>