<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-30T20:02:00Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 30 Nov 2023 20:02:00</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-30T20:02:00Z</published><updated>2023-11-30T20:02:00Z</updated><id>2c2ccfca-fa00-4f5a-9fbe-9ea8b0776de5</id><summary type="html">In the world, there have been several notable events. Deepmind's GNoME AI tool has made significant progress in crystal research, speeding up the process by 800 years. However, tensions between Russia and Ukraine continue to escalate, with Ukraine claiming that Russian troops are being harmed by their own minefields due to a lack of communication from their leaders. In the tech industry, OpenAI employees are reportedly feeling uneasy despite Sam Altman's return as CEO, and some are actively seeking other job opportunities. On a lighter note, Henry Kissinger celebrated his 100th birthday, although he admitted to having no idea how he managed to live for so long. Additionally, a person decided to leave their corporate job and big-city life behind to find solace in a remote cottage in the woods. In other news, the Iowa Lottery accidentally published the wrong numbers, but the mistaken "winners" will still be able to keep their money. Car dealers are concerned about the future of electric vehicles, and Elon Musk denies allegations of gruesome deaths among Neuralink monkeys. The cofounder of Allbirds shared advice for startups looking to go public, emphasizing the importance of making money beforehand. A comparison between Singapore and NYC highlighted the advantages and disadvantages of each city. There are also lesser-known but well-paying jobs that were discussed in a viral Reddit thread. Walmart's "store of the future" gave off vibes similar to Target, and a hidden expense is reportedly draining $74 billion from the economy. In the tech world, Ripgrep has proven to be faster than other search tools. An individual who worked in Amazon HR expressed disgust at the company's performance improvement plans. Adobe's acquisition of Figma raised concerns among UK regulators regarding its impact on developers. It is advised to update the Chrome browser to avoid a known exploit. Voicemod now allows users to create and share their own AI voices, and Firefox's Android browser will soon support extensions again. Researchers from Tokyo University of Science have developed a deep learning model capable of detecting a previously unknown quasicrystalline phase in materials science. The University of California has largely abandoned carbon offsets and encourages others to do the same. Google has started deleting Gmail and photo content within 24 hours. Warren Buffett sought investment advice from Charlie Munger, who had a unique approach among corporate executives. The importance of hardware in solving climate tech challenges was highlighted. Lastly, Chick-fil-A is envisioning a drive-through of the future that could serve up to 720 cars per hour, and Detroit is developing a road that can charge electric vehicles while they drive on it.</summary></entry></feed>