<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-22T08:03:50Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 22 Oct 2023 08:03:50</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-22T08:03:50Z</published><updated>2023-10-22T08:03:50Z</updated><id>3b60c01f-9fed-4d70-b75a-415b0974bbf3</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Google and other search engines' use of generative AI threatens the $68B SEO industry.&lt;br&gt;- Hackers leaked more 23andMe data, leading to increased security measures.&lt;br&gt;- Apple is rumored to release a new iPad Air in 2023.&lt;br&gt;- Web Summit CEO Paddy Cosgrave steps down following controversy over his comments about Israel.&lt;br&gt;- Google implemented targeted job cuts, including several "director decapitations."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- BuildZoom, a platform for building custom homes, is hiring a Growth Associate.&lt;br&gt;- Ferrari sued a used car dealer for $2.2M over a replica, but the case did not go well for Ferrari.&lt;br&gt;- The Worst Show On TV is given one more chance at redemption before being canceled.&lt;br&gt;- Markets are looking to Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell amid rising tensions in the Middle East.&lt;br&gt;- More people are missing car payments, indicating potential economic troubles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Google's use of generative AI threatens the SEO industry.&lt;br&gt;- Viral photos of Hamas leaders accused of being AI fakes were actually poorly upscaled.&lt;br&gt;- The real science behind the mysterious "Devil Comet" is not fully understood by scientists.&lt;br&gt;- China is projected to have 1,000 nuclear warheads and missiles capable of hitting the US by 2030, according to a Pentagon report.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Canada has experienced a decline in the number of entrepreneurs over the past 20 years.&lt;br&gt;- The SEO industry faces a significant threat from the use of generative AI by search engines.&lt;br&gt;- The leaking of personal data by hackers highlights the need for improved cybersecurity measures.&lt;br&gt;- The automotive industry is facing challenges, with more people missing car payments.&lt;br&gt;- The potential development of 1,000 nuclear warheads by China raises concerns about global security.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report highlights various topics such as the decline in entrepreneurship, the impact of AI on industries, business developments, political dynamics, and scientific discoveries. It emphasizes the need for cybersecurity measures, economic stability, and international security.</summary></entry></feed>