<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-07T08:03:45Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 07 Oct 2023 08:03:45</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-07T08:03:45Z</published><updated>2023-10-07T08:03:45Z</updated><id>f408fb80-ece4-4ec6-ab5f-1fb2c66cff1e</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage Rates: Average Mortgage Interest Rates by State, Credit Score, Year, and Loan Type&lt;br&gt;- Show HN: A job application tracker with company reviews, recruiter autoresponder&lt;br&gt;- Sam Bankman-Fried’s cofounder describes FTX’s hidden cheat code to misuse customer funds&lt;br&gt;- Why did the Motorola 68000 processor family fall out of use in PCs?&lt;br&gt;- Fail2Ban – Daemon to ban hosts that cause multiple authentication errors&lt;br&gt;- A NY startup aims to build hundreds of chip factories with prefab parts and AI&lt;br&gt;- A 20MP Sensor in a Film Canister Reinvigorates Vintage Analog Cameras&lt;br&gt;- Genetics firm 23andMe says user data stolen in credential stuffing attack&lt;br&gt;- The best price ever on Sharge’s transparent batteries and retro Mac chargers&lt;br&gt;- Electric seaglider startup Regent takes flight with $60M in new funding&lt;br&gt;- QCon San Francisco 2023: Streamlining Cloud Development with Deno by Ryan Dahl&lt;br&gt;- Deploy a Full Stack Next.js App to a DigitalOcean VPS With Docker!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The mortgage rates vary by state, credit score, year, and loan type.&lt;br&gt;- A job application tracker with company reviews and recruiter autoresponder is introduced.&lt;br&gt;- Sam Bankman-Fried's cofounder reveals a hidden cheat code in FTX to misuse customer funds.&lt;br&gt;- The decline of the Motorola 68000 processor family in PCs is explored.&lt;br&gt;- Fail2Ban is a daemon used to ban hosts causing multiple authentication errors.&lt;br&gt;- A startup plans to build chip factories using prefab parts and AI.&lt;br&gt;- A 20MP sensor in a film canister brings new life to vintage analog cameras.&lt;br&gt;- Genetics firm 23andMe experiences a data breach through a credential stuffing attack.&lt;br&gt;- Sharge offers transparent batteries and retro Mac chargers at a discounted price.&lt;br&gt;- Electric seaglider startup Regent secures $60M in funding.&lt;br&gt;- QCon San Francisco 2023 features a talk on streamlining cloud development with Deno.&lt;br&gt;- A guide is provided on deploying a full stack Next.js app to a DigitalOcean VPS using Docker.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Kevin McCarthy strolled out of his former office just to insist to reporters that he's not resigning and will seek re-election in 2024: 'Not that I wanted to talk to you'&lt;br&gt;- Rep. Lauren Boebert is signaling that the fight over the speakership could get bogged down over Ukraine&lt;br&gt;- FTX co-founder Gary Wang agreed to cooperate in Sam Bankman-Fried case in his first meeting with prosecutors: 'I thought I was likely to be charged'&lt;br&gt;- Kaiser Permanente workers are set to extend their strike after talks hit a stalemate&lt;br&gt;- GM Agrees To Put EV Battery Plants Under National Union Contract, UAW Says&lt;br&gt;- Baseball’s Mets Investigation Will Seek to Answer What Steve Cohen Knew&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft’s $68.7 Billion Activision Blizzard Acquisition Nears Completion Amid Regulatory Twists&lt;br&gt;- US stocks jump, reversing up after bond yields come off highs&lt;br&gt;- Republicans are asking their Twitter followers to help them decide who should replace Kevin McCarthy&lt;br&gt;- Here's why it's so dangerous for Wall Street to bet against the American consumer&lt;br&gt;- The US Navy turned the tables on Iran, sending drones that look like speedboats to spy on its warships and troublesome gunboats&lt;br&gt;- CMO Insider's new advisory council includes marketing leaders from Mastercard, Sesame Workshop, Indeed and more&lt;br&gt;- Are banks open today? Here's a list of US bank holidays for 2023&lt;br&gt;- If Rep. Jim Jordan wins the race for House speaker, it could be the death knell for US aid to Ukraine&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Kevin McCarthy asserts that he is not resigning and plans to seek re-election in 2024.&lt;br&gt;- Rep. Lauren Boebert suggests that the speakership fight may become entangled with Ukraine.&lt;br&gt;- FTX co-founder Gary Wang agrees to cooperate in the Sam Bankman-Fried case.&lt;br&gt;- Kaiser Permanente workers plan to extend their strike due to a stalemate in talks.&lt;br&gt;- GM agrees to put EV battery plants under a national union contract.&lt;br&gt;- An investigation into the Mets aims to uncover what Steve Cohen knew.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard is nearing completion amid regulatory challenges.&lt;br&gt;- US stocks experience a jump after bond yields decrease.&lt;br&gt;- Republicans seek input from Twitter followers on who should replace Kevin McCarthy.&lt;br&gt;- Betting against the American consumer is deemed risky for Wall Street.&lt;br&gt;- The US Navy deploys drones resembling speedboats to spy on Iran's warships and gunboats.&lt;br&gt;- CMO Insider forms an advisory council with marketing leaders from various companies.&lt;br&gt;- A list of US bank holidays for 2023 is provided.&lt;br&gt;- The potential election of Rep. Jim Jordan as House speaker could impact US aid to Ukraine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- The BBC is blocking OpenAI data scraping but is open to AI-powered journalism&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The BBC blocks OpenAI data scraping but remains open to AI-powered journalism.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage rates vary based on factors such as state, credit score, year, and loan type.&lt;br&gt;- A job application tracker with company reviews and recruiter autoresponder is introduced.&lt;br&gt;- FTX's hidden cheat code to misuse customer funds is revealed by a cofounder.&lt;br&gt;- The decline of the Motorola 68000 processor family in PCs is explored.&lt;br&gt;- Fail2Ban is a daemon used to ban hosts causing multiple authentication errors.&lt;br&gt;- A startup plans to build chip factories using prefab parts and AI.&lt;br&gt;- A 20MP sensor in a film canister brings new life to vintage analog cameras.&lt;br&gt;- Genetics firm 23andMe experiences a data breach through a credential stuffing attack.&lt;br&gt;- Sharge offers transparent batteries and retro Mac chargers at a discounted price.&lt;br&gt;- Electric seaglider startup Regent secures $60M in funding.&lt;br&gt;- QCon San Francisco 2023 features a talk on streamlining cloud development with Deno.&lt;br&gt;- A guide is provided on deploying a full stack Next.js app to a DigitalOcean VPS using Docker.&lt;br&gt;- Kevin McCarthy asserts his intention to seek re-election in 2024.&lt;br&gt;- Rep. Lauren Boebert suggests the speakership fight may involve Ukraine.&lt;br&gt;- FTX co-founder Gary Wang agrees to cooperate in the Sam Bankman-Fried case.&lt;br&gt;- Kaiser Permanente workers plan to extend their strike due to a stalemate in talks.&lt;br&gt;- GM agrees to put EV battery plants under a national union contract.&lt;br&gt;- An investigation into the Mets aims to uncover what Steve Cohen knew.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard faces regulatory challenges.&lt;br&gt;- US stocks experience a jump after bond yields decrease.&lt;br&gt;- Republicans seek input from Twitter followers on who should replace Kevin McCarthy.&lt;br&gt;- Betting against the American consumer is deemed risky for Wall Street.&lt;br&gt;- The US Navy deploys drones resembling speedboats to spy on Iran's warships and gunboats.&lt;br&gt;- CMO Insider forms an advisory council with marketing leaders from various companies.&lt;br&gt;- A list of US bank holidays for 2023 is provided.&lt;br&gt;- The potential election of Rep. Jim Jordan as House speaker could impact US aid to Ukraine.&lt;br&gt;- The BBC blocks OpenAI data scraping but remains open to AI-powered journalism.</summary></entry></feed>