<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-28T08:03:36Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:03:36</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-28T08:03:36Z</published><updated>2023-11-28T08:03:36Z</updated><id>4902985b-5644-4051-bac1-50f8a6eb025a</id><summary type="html">In the world, there have been several notable events recently. The Kehinde Wiley MFAH showcase has captivated audiences with its provocative and awe-inspiring artwork. However, there is controversy surrounding HPD's revised vehicle pursuit policy after an innocent driver was involved in a pursuit. On a more heartwarming note, a tiny puppy abandoned in a park has made a miraculous recovery thanks to the BC SPCA. Scientists from the University of California San Diego have published a 37-year record of ocean acidification, shedding light on the impact of climate change. In Vermont, a shooting suspect named Jason James Eaton, who was known as a 'hippie' and loved farming, has shocked his ex-boss who claims the crime doesn't align with his character. Both Russia and Ukraine are beefing up their air defenses ahead of another winter of bombardment. Flight attendants are facing challenges with sporadic shifts, with some claiming it is in a legal gray zone. US stocks have ended lower as Black Friday and Cyber Monday sales come into focus. Archaeologists have made an exciting discovery using Google Earth, uncovering 3,000 square miles of prehistoric settlements in Central Europe. Popular Science magazine, after 151 years, will no longer be offering a print edition. In the tech world, a male conference founder is behind a popular woman coding influencer account. BYD is challenging Tesla with its impressive sales of over 300k electric cars in a month. Additionally, there have been advancements in 3D scene synchronization using Three.js and localStorage. A virtual garage sale has emerged, allowing users to haggle with AI to buy various items. The trial has begun for a man charged with attempted murder of a police officer during a shooting at a mall. The renowned Obama portraitist has turned his brush to African presidents, showcasing their leadership through art. The Giants exhibition, featuring art from the Dean Collection of Swizz Beatz and Alicia Keys, has attracted attention at the Brooklyn Museum. Dell Technologies and NVIDIA have achieved a new risk calculation record in financial services with their H100 System for HPC and AI. In the field of medical research, there have been advancements in evaluating brown adipose tissue using water and triglyceride. A writer has tried and recommended seven foods from Costco, with only one falling short of expectations. In politics, George Santos may still enjoy lawmakers-only perks, even if he's expelled. In Australia, beachgoers rescued a wallaby from crocodile-infested waters after it was chased into the ocean by a dog. Two strangers bonded during a turbulent flight, surviving the bumpy ride with whiskey and TikTok. Jonathan Braun, a drug smuggler pardoned by Trump, has faced allegations of violence. For those planning overnight train journeys, there are tips on what to pack to help sleep better. Lastly, Cyber Monday VPN deals are offering significant discounts, making it a no-brainer for streaming and online privacy in 2023.</summary></entry></feed>