<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-16T08:03:47Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 16 Oct 2023 08:03:47</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-16T08:03:47Z</published><updated>2023-10-16T08:03:47Z</updated><id>c1a9a4c9-9d98-4371-a9bc-217376d9b8c7</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- LL Cool J lends his Kehinde Wiley painting to a museum&lt;br&gt;- Reed Smith adds Wiley Gov't Contracts Partner in DC&lt;br&gt;- Freshpaint is hiring software engineers to protect patient privacy&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from Yale and Google introduce HyperAttention for efficient long-range sequence processing&lt;br&gt;- Meet PIXART-α, a competitive image generator&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Top US bankruptcy judge resigns due to undisclosed romantic relationship&lt;br&gt;- Par Equity targets £100M at UK startups in the north&lt;br&gt;- Modi's government and India's elites battle for control of a private club&lt;br&gt;- Vivek Ramaswamy discusses the blacklisting of Harvard students&lt;br&gt;- Finland to vote against EU mass surveillance and encryption ban directive&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers introduce HyperAttention for efficient long-range sequence processing&lt;br&gt;- Meet PIXART-α, a competitive image generator&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- London's Par Equity targets £100M at UK startups in the north&lt;br&gt;- The largest dam removal in history stirs hopes of restoring tribes' way of life&lt;br&gt;- Giants vs. Bills live stream of Sunday Night Football&lt;br&gt;- 'Shooting Stars' from Halley's Comet visible in the night sky&lt;br&gt;- Best Eclipse Photos: 'Ring Of Fire' wows Western States as all U.S. see solar eclipse&lt;br&gt;- From skeptic to viral sensation: How Koala Puffs became the queen of cannabis content&lt;br&gt;- Matt Gaetz dismisses idea of Kevin McCarthy's ouster fueling government dysfunction&lt;br&gt;- A part of Afghanistan experiences unprecedented number of earthquakes&lt;br&gt;- The Sycamore Gap tree holds deep meaning for people&lt;br&gt;- Cat vs. Dog Owners: Who is happier? A psychologist settles the debate&lt;br&gt;- Destiny Wiley's obituary&lt;br&gt;- Ranking of electric-car frunks from best to worst&lt;br&gt;- UK spy chief warns of trap as Israel prepares for urban warfare against Hamas&lt;br&gt;- Israel wants Palestinians to rise up against Hamas, but one who did says it's impossible&lt;br&gt;- Israel's No.1 Hamas kill target is Yahya Sinwar, the 'Butcher from Khan Younis'&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- LL Cool J's act of lending his painting shows his support for the arts and cultural preservation.&lt;br&gt;- The resignation of the top US bankruptcy judge highlights the importance of transparency and ethical conduct in the legal profession.&lt;br&gt;- Par Equity's investment in UK startups in the north demonstrates the growing potential of the region's tech ecosystem.&lt;br&gt;- The dam removal project signifies a commitment to environmental restoration and collaboration with indigenous communities.&lt;br&gt;- The unprecedented earthquakes in Afghanistan raise concerns about seismic activity in unexpected areas.&lt;br&gt;- The debate between cat and dog owners' happiness sheds light on the psychological benefits of pet ownership.&lt;br&gt;- The blacklisting of Harvard students raises questions about the consequences of free speech and cancel culture.&lt;br&gt;- Finland's decision to vote against the EU mass surveillance and encryption ban directive reflects concerns about privacy and civil liberties.&lt;br&gt;- The smaller mass of the Milky Way challenges previous cosmological expectations.&lt;br&gt;- The development of HyperAttention and PIXART-α showcases advancements in AI and image generation technology.&lt;br&gt;- The ongoing conflict between Israel and Hamas highlights the complexities and challenges of the situation in the Middle East.</summary></entry></feed>