<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-13T08:03:31Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 13 Sep 2023 08:03:31</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-13T08:03:31Z</published><updated>2023-09-13T08:03:31Z</updated><id>23d4dc1d-c2d2-4341-96fd-bb89e2145701</id><summary type="html">Report: Impact of AI on Various Industries and Environmental Concerns&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Gmail and Instagram are utilizing AI for various purposes, and users have limited control over it.&lt;br&gt;- Unity, a popular game development platform, has changed its pricing model, causing dissatisfaction among game developers.&lt;br&gt;- Apple's iPhone 15 is the first phone to almost support Qi2 charging, and the iPhone 15 Pro and Pro Max are the first smartphones with Thread technology.&lt;br&gt;- Apple's USB-C AirPods Pro will support lossless audio with the Vision Pro.&lt;br&gt;- Google provides more details on its Cloud Generative AI play at the Next Event.&lt;br&gt;- Google suggests that their Multi-Modal AI Gemini will be able to generate images.&lt;br&gt;- The Apple Watch Ultra 2 is available for preorder, offering new features.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: AI is revolutionizing the tech industry, with companies like Apple and Google incorporating AI into their products and services. However, changes in pricing models and limited user control over AI raise concerns among developers and users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Business:&lt;br&gt;- Best IRA CD rates for September 2023 are up to 5.15% APY, making it an attractive investment option for those nearing retirement.&lt;br&gt;- T-Mobile plans to buy more 5G airwaves from Comcast for up to $3.3 billion.&lt;br&gt;- Investors show high demand for US debt as Treasury bills are bought at a record pace.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The financial sector is impacted by AI, with attractive IRA CD rates and significant investments in 5G technology. The high demand for US debt reflects investor confidence in the economy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. AI:&lt;br&gt;- Building an AI SMS Chatbot with Replicate, LLaMA 2, and LangChain.&lt;br&gt;- Unlocking the potential of Large Language Models (LLMs) for business insights.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: AI is being utilized to develop advanced chatbots and unlock valuable business insights through Large Language Models.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Environment:&lt;br&gt;- AI is causing environmental damage.&lt;br&gt;- Rare photo shows a macaque riding a deer for fun in a Japanese forest.&lt;br&gt;- Effect of breathwork on stress and mental health: A meta-analysis of RCTs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: While AI brings advancements, it also has negative consequences for the environment. Additionally, nature and mental health-related topics highlight the importance of preserving the environment and promoting well-being.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conclusion:&lt;br&gt;AI is transforming various industries, including tech and business, with both positive and negative impacts. While it offers innovative features and investment opportunities, concerns about environmental damage and limited user control over AI persist. It is crucial to strike a balance between technological advancements and environmental sustainability.</summary></entry></feed>