<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-11T02:01:09Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 11 Aug 2023 02:01:09</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-11T02:01:09Z</published><updated>2023-08-11T02:01:09Z</updated><id>af18723c-463a-4b78-82ca-759c5140450f</id><summary type="html">Report: Tech and Business Insights&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's company, X, is hiring again after previously slashing its workforce.&lt;br&gt;- The EV plateau is approaching, which could negatively impact companies like Ford and Tesla.&lt;br&gt;- YouTube's link spam situation has become so severe that Shorts is banning links.&lt;br&gt;- Hugging Face Platform is now available on the AWS Marketplace, allowing users to pay with their AWS Account.&lt;br&gt;- WhatsApp is encroaching on Zoom's territory, coinciding with Zoom facing backlash regarding AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is constantly evolving, with companies like X experiencing fluctuations in their workforce.&lt;br&gt;- The EV market is facing challenges as it reaches a plateau, potentially impacting major players like Ford and Tesla.&lt;br&gt;- YouTube's efforts to combat link spam highlight the ongoing battle against online scams and fake goods.&lt;br&gt;- The availability of Hugging Face Platform on the AWS Marketplace provides convenience for users.&lt;br&gt;- The competition between WhatsApp and Zoom showcases the growing demand for communication and collaboration tools.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- A Florida state attorney, suspended by Ron DeSantis, criticizes the governor's actions as an attempt to salvage his presidential campaign.&lt;br&gt;- Disney has increased streaming prices, leading to positive reactions from Wall Street.&lt;br&gt;- Home-price appreciation may help consumers offset dwindling savings.&lt;br&gt;- The Last Voyage of the Demeter fails to live up to Dracula's legacy.&lt;br&gt;- The most valuable startups are moving closer to profitability, but at a cost.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Political motivations can influence decisions within the legal system, as seen in the case of the suspended state attorney in Florida.&lt;br&gt;- Disney's price hike indicates confidence in the streaming market and its potential for revenue growth.&lt;br&gt;- Home-price appreciation can serve as a financial cushion for consumers during times of economic uncertainty.&lt;br&gt;- The reception of The Last Voyage of the Demeter highlights the challenges of living up to established legacies.&lt;br&gt;- Startups' pursuit of profitability may require sacrifices and trade-offs in terms of resources and strategies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Tailoring the Fabric of Generative AI: FABRIC is an AI approach that personalizes diffusion models with iterative feedback.&lt;br&gt;- Marc Raibert and Gill Pratt will discuss state-of-the-art research at TechCrunch Disrupt.&lt;br&gt;- Oracle, SUSE, and CIQ launch the Open Enterprise Linux Association amid controversy surrounding Red Hat.&lt;br&gt;- Terrified Elon Musk suggests a "debate" with Zuckerberg instead of a cage fight.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- FABRIC's AI approach showcases the potential for personalization in generative AI models.&lt;br&gt;- Tech conferences like TechCrunch Disrupt provide platforms for sharing cutting-edge research and advancements in AI.&lt;br&gt;- The launch of the Open Enterprise Linux Association reflects the ongoing discussions and debates within the Linux community.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's suggestion of a debate instead of a physical confrontation highlights the intersection of technology and entertainment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is characterized by constant change and competition, with companies experiencing fluctuations in workforce and market challenges.&lt;br&gt;- Business decisions can be influenced by political motivations and market dynamics, impacting various sectors such as streaming and real estate.&lt;br&gt;- AI continues to advance, with personalized approaches and discussions on state-of-the-art research shaping the field.&lt;br&gt;- The intersection of technology and entertainment is evident in debates and conflicts involving prominent figures like Elon Musk and Mark Zuckerberg.</summary></entry></feed>