<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-27T20:01:35Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:01:35</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-27T20:01:35Z</published><updated>2024-01-27T20:01:35Z</updated><id>a3f8a0be-860c-460c-8663-d0bd8a584992</id><summary type="html">In the world today, there are several interesting developments taking place. Scientists have discovered that black holes are moving through our universe at an astonishing speed of over 2.2 million mph, and they believe they have finally uncovered the reason behind this phenomenon. Meanwhile, Google has announced an update revealing that their AI technology will now have the ability to read all private messages, raising concerns about privacy. On a more positive note, Apple is exploring ways to make life easier for elderly customers, which could benefit everyone. Additionally, Ikea has unveiled its vision for the office of the future, resembling a coworking space. In personal stories, a millennial shares her experience of quitting her corporate job in London and moving to Australia, discussing the pros and cons of her career switch and life down under. Meanwhile, a food reporter who had never been to Golden Corral visited the only location in NYC after it went viral, and was pleasantly surprised by her $25 meal. Another millennial shares their experience of moving from New York to Kansas City, highlighting the advantages of paying less rent for a larger apartment and not having to work multiple jobs. In a different perspective, Uber and Lyft drivers reveal that their motivation for driving goes beyond money, as it helps alleviate their loneliness. However, there are also concerning news items, such as China's air force being unprepared for a crucial mission involving Taiwan, and a video appearing to show Ukraine's new drone machine-gunning a Russian outpost. Lastly, the relentless harassment from "left NIMBYs" has forced a 27-year-old Berkeley city council member to resign, who had been advocating for more affordable housing. In the tech world, discussions arise about the polished nature of startups and the reasons behind it.</summary></entry></feed>