<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-12T08:03:46Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 12 Sep 2023 08:03:46</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-12T08:03:46Z</published><updated>2023-09-12T08:03:46Z</updated><id>5311fe2e-8b7a-4a99-8254-468f6524f572</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- MGM ‘cybersecurity issue’ shuts down slot machines and ATMs in Las Vegas casinos&lt;br&gt;- TikTok accidentally blocked Hollywood writers strike videos while casting a QAnon net&lt;br&gt;- Max Q: Elon says Starship is ready, FAA says not quite&lt;br&gt;- Meet PhysObjects: An Object-Centric Dataset of 36.9K Crowd-Sourced and 417K Automated Physical Concept Annotations of Common Household Objects&lt;br&gt;- This Context API Mistake Ruins Your Whole React App (All Components Re-Render)&lt;br&gt;- Internet Archive appeals loss in library ebook lawsuit - The Verge&lt;br&gt;- Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 5 review: A big improvement to the clamshell foldable phone, but it's still held back by battery life and usefulness&lt;br&gt;- Enhanced HLS live streaming at Daily, now with adaptive bitrate 1080P&lt;br&gt;- Michael Chabon, Other Literary Giants Sue OpenAI Over Alleged Copyright Infringement&lt;br&gt;- Google Pixel 6a review: Unbeatable value in a budget Android phone&lt;br&gt;- Epic Games taps former MCU character designer as new creative executive&lt;br&gt;- Meta Quest adds new avatar customization options, an unsend message feature and more&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- A UAW strike could drive up inflation, push Michigan into a recession, and even hurt Biden in the election&lt;br&gt;- What is the Google antitrust case all about? Search engine to face regulators in greatest showdown since Microsoft’s&lt;br&gt;- Voter concerns over abortion are shattering Trump's Electoral College advantage, boosting Biden's chances in 2024&lt;br&gt;- JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon says he wouldn't be 'a big buyer of a bank' and sounds the alarm on the economy&lt;br&gt;- Office sector collapse will cost US banks as much as $250 billion, hedge fund boss says&lt;br&gt;- Disney and Charter have just made nice: Here’s what Spectrum cable subscribers can expect next&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk and Bill Gates have argued over everything from climate change to the pandemic. Here's how their disagreements started &amp;mdash; and everything that's happened since.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Online Educational Publishing Market Size and Regional Outlook Analysis 2023-2030 - Benzinga&lt;br&gt;- In a US showdown with China, there are some missions with no special-operations 'easy button'&lt;br&gt;- Groundbreakers: The Women Changing the Culture of Coffee by Jen Roberts&lt;br&gt;- The Irish Dance Globe: Issue 001 by The Irish Dance Globe&lt;br&gt;- All the big conferences and events in tech, entertainment, and automotive coming this fall&lt;br&gt;- Popular Direct Review: Savings Accounts and CDs With Competitive Interest Rates&lt;br&gt;- Knowledge Unlatched Announces 283 Open Acces Books in 2023 - Publishing Perspectives</summary></entry></feed>