<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-09T17:50:47Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 09 Aug 2023 17:50:47</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-09T17:50:47Z</published><updated>2023-08-09T17:50:47Z</updated><id>9e325aed-3f92-4e0a-8dd1-39cecd8d8dc1</id><summary type="html">SEC chairman warns AI could be at the heart of future financial crises (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- The chairman of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has issued a warning about the potential risks of artificial intelligence (AI) in the financial industry. He believes that AI could be at the center of future financial crises if not properly regulated and monitored.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mega Millions drawing tonight (Business)&lt;br&gt;- There is a Mega Millions lottery drawing scheduled for tonight. This news is relevant to those interested in participating in the lottery and potentially winning a large sum of money.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protein Loss Linked to Growth Defects in Mice, Humans - Mirage News (Science)&lt;br&gt;- A study has found a link between protein loss and growth defects in both mice and humans. This research provides insights into the underlying mechanisms of growth disorders and could potentially lead to new treatment options.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Student-loan payments and steeper interest rates will pave way for a severe consumer-led recession, top economist David Rosenberg says (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Prominent economist David Rosenberg predicts that the combination of student loan payments and higher interest rates will contribute to a severe recession led by consumer spending. This analysis highlights the potential economic impact of these factors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Zuckerberg, wife Priscilla's relationship timeline, from dating to marriage (Entertainment)&lt;br&gt;- This article provides a timeline of the relationship between Mark Zuckerberg, the co-founder of Facebook, and his wife Priscilla. It covers their dating period leading up to their marriage, offering insights into their personal lives.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quote Post Maker (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Quote Post Maker is a tool or software related to creating visually appealing quote posts. This information is relevant to individuals interested in creating engaging social media content.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lofi &amp; Jazz Hip Hop Producing Handbook (Entertainment)&lt;br&gt;- The Lofi &amp; Jazz Hip Hop Producing Handbook is a resource or guide for individuals interested in producing music in the lofi and jazz hip hop genres. This content is relevant to music producers and enthusiasts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minimalist eCommerce (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Minimalist eCommerce refers to a business approach or strategy that focuses on simplicity and minimalism in the design and functionality of online stores. This topic is relevant to entrepreneurs and businesses looking to optimize their eCommerce platforms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Review My Design (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Review My Design is a platform or service that allows individuals to receive feedback and critiques on their design projects. This content is relevant to designers seeking input and improvement on their work.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Backendless (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Backendless is a technology or platform that provides backend services for mobile and web applications. It offers features such as database management, user authentication, and cloud storage. This information is relevant to developers and app creators.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reflecting on My Failure to Build a Billion-Dollar Company (2019) (Business)&lt;br&gt;- This article reflects on the author's personal experience and failure in attempting to build a billion-dollar company. It offers insights and lessons learned from this entrepreneurial journey.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon has more than half of all Arm server CPUs in the world (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Amazon, the e-commerce giant, currently holds over 50% of the market share for Arm server CPUs globally. This information highlights Amazon's dominance in the server CPU market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Llama from Scratch (or how to implement a paper without crying) (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- "Llama from Scratch" is a project or tutorial that explains how to implement a research paper or algorithm from scratch. This content is relevant to individuals interested in understanding and implementing complex algorithms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;絶滅危惧種の遺伝子を未来へ：国立環境研究所がクラウドファンディングで「タイムカプセル」の費用を募る理由 (Science)&lt;br&gt;- This article discusses the efforts of the National Institute for Environmental Studies in Japan to preserve the genes of endangered species for the future. They are using crowdfunding to raise funds for a "time capsule" project. This content is relevant to conservation and genetic preservation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;一句话完成繁琐操作：你可以试试的 8 个 Windows 命令行工具 (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article introduces eight Windows command-line tools that can simplify complex operations with just a single line of code. It provides practical tips and tools for Windows users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAS AI BECOME TOO HUMAN? Researchers At Google AI Find LLMs Can Now Use ML Models And APIs With Just Tool Documentation! (AI)&lt;br&gt;- Researchers at Google AI have discovered that language model learners (LLMs) can now utilize machine learning models and APIs with just tool documentation. This finding raises questions about the capabilities and potential risks of AI becoming too human-like.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pretiosum Ventures hits first close on its second fund to back infrastructure startups (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Pretiosum Ventures, an investment firm, has achieved its first close on its second fund. The fund aims to support infrastructure startups, indicating potential growth and investment opportunities in this sector.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to get more suggestions from GitHub Copilot (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article provides tips and strategies on how to maximize the suggestions and assistance provided by GitHub Copilot, an AI-powered coding assistant. It is relevant to developers seeking to enhance their coding productivity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cloud Providers Showdown: AWS vs. Azure vs. Google Cloud (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This content compares the cloud services offered by major providers such as Amazon Web Services (AWS), Microsoft Azure, and Google Cloud. It highlights the strengths and weaknesses of each platform, assisting individuals in making informed decisions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weekly web development resources #161 (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This resource or article compiles a list of web development resources for the week, including tutorials, tools, and frameworks. It is relevant to web developers seeking to stay updated with the latest trends and resources.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Introduction to CSS: Customizing with index.css and Classes (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This content serves as an introduction to CSS (Cascading Style Sheets) and focuses on customizing web pages using index.css and classes. It provides foundational knowledge for individuals interested in web design and development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone was wrong about antipsychotics (Science)&lt;br&gt;- This article challenges the conventional understanding and usage of antipsychotic medications. It suggests that the prevailing beliefs about these drugs may have been incorrect, highlighting the need for further research and reevaluation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;People-centered startups: making employees happy is a key ingredient to success (Business)&lt;br&gt;- This article emphasizes the importance of prioritizing employee happiness and satisfaction in startups. It argues that creating a people-centered culture is a crucial factor in achieving success and long-term growth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;康恩贝：公司经营一切正常，“公司放假两个月”等传闻均为谣言 (Business)&lt;br&gt;- This article addresses rumors and speculations about the Chinese company Kangmei Pharmaceutical. It states that the company's operations are normal and dismisses rumors of a two-month vacation. This information is relevant to investors and stakeholders of the company.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;天力锂能：与鹏辉能源签署《战略合作框架协议》 (Business)&lt;br&gt;- This news article announces a strategic cooperation framework agreement between Tianli Lithium Energy and Penghui Energy. The agreement is relevant to the energy sector and indicates potential collaborations and developments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;澳大利亚广播公司退出X，称该平台上“有害互动”愈发普遍 (Business)&lt;br&gt;- The Australian Broadcasting Corporation (ABC) has announced its withdrawal from a certain platform, citing an increase in "harmful interactions" on the platform. This decision reflects concerns about the negative impact of online interactions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;英国又一房企宣布裁员，因高利率打压新屋需求 (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Another British real estate company has announced layoffs due to high interest rates suppressing demand for new homes. This news highlights the economic challenges faced by the real estate industry in the UK.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;中国联通：上半年净利润54.44亿元，同比增长13.7% (Business)&lt;br&gt;- China Unicom, a telecommunications company, has reported a net profit of 5.44 billion yuan in the first half of the year, representing a year-on-year growth of 13.7%. This financial update provides insights into the company's performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;用非官方通讯软件沟通业务，华尔街金融机构已累计被罚超25亿美元 (Business)&lt;br&gt;- This article discusses the use of unofficial communication software for conducting business in Wall Street financial institutions. It highlights the significant fines imposed on these institutions, totaling over $2.5 billion. This information sheds light on regulatory issues and compliance in the financial industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;恒指收涨0.32%，恒生科技指数跌0.01% (Business)&lt;br&gt;- The Hang Seng Index (HSI) closed with a 0.32% increase, while the Hang Seng Tech Index (HSTECH) experienced a 0.01% decline. This financial update provides an overview of the performance of these indices.</summary></entry></feed>