<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-10T08:03:30Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 10 Oct 2023 08:03:30</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-10T08:03:30Z</published><updated>2023-10-10T08:03:30Z</updated><id>50494e9e-c85f-48fd-832e-bc5d57ac3bdf</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- The Future of CSS: Easy Light-Dark Mode Color Switching with Light-Dark()&lt;br&gt;- Meta Extends Its AI Messaging To The Quest 3 And More At Meta Connect 2023&lt;br&gt;- The Pixel 8A is curvy and colorful in these first-look leaks&lt;br&gt;- Gartner Says Worldwide PC Shipments Declined 9% in Third Quarter of 2023&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech section of the report highlights advancements in CSS, AI messaging, and PC shipments. It showcases the potential for easy light-dark mode color switching and the integration of AI messaging into virtual reality devices. The leaked images of the Pixel 8A generate excitement among tech enthusiasts. However, the report also notes a decline in worldwide PC shipments during the third quarter of 2023, indicating a potential shift in consumer preferences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- X CEO Linda Yaccarino drops out of the WSJ Tech Live conference&lt;br&gt;- Consumer payments startup Braid shuts down, cites struggles with ‘leveraging third-party software’&lt;br&gt;- John Riccitiello steps down as unity CEO with former Red Hat chief exec Jim Whitehurst taking over for now&lt;br&gt;- John Riccitiello steps down as CEO of Unity after pricing battle&lt;br&gt;- Buzzy social app Fizz sues rival Sidechat over unfair competition practices&lt;br&gt;- Amazon’s One Medical Looks To Add More Services In Existing Markets&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business section of the report covers various developments in the corporate world. It highlights the departure of X CEO Linda Yaccarino from the WSJ Tech Live conference, the shutdown of consumer payments startup Braid, and the leadership changes at Unity. The report also mentions a legal dispute between social app Fizz and rival Sidechat, as well as Amazon's plans to expand its services in existing markets through One Medical.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Mind-to-Speech: The New Frontier in Neuro Communication Through Perception From Non-Invasive Brain Signals&lt;br&gt;- Meta Extends Its AI Messaging To The Quest 3 And More At Meta Connect 2023&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The AI section focuses on cutting-edge advancements in the field. It explores the concept of mind-to-speech communication through non-invasive brain signals, highlighting the potential for a new frontier in neuro communication. Additionally, it discusses Meta's expansion of AI messaging to the Quest 3 and other platforms, showcasing the integration of AI technologies into everyday devices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;The report provides a comprehensive overview of various topics, including tech, business, and AI. It highlights the future of CSS, advancements in AI messaging, and the decline in worldwide PC shipments. It also covers significant developments in the business world, such as leadership changes and legal disputes. Additionally, the report explores the potential of mind-to-speech communication and the expansion of AI technologies. Overall, it showcases the dynamic and evolving landscape of technology, business, and AI.</summary></entry></feed>