<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-19T18:01:03Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 19 Aug 2023 18:01:03</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-19T18:01:03Z</published><updated>2023-08-19T18:01:03Z</updated><id>41a316e9-2f9c-4dc4-b3dd-f5d444c280cd</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Police in England installed an AI camera system along a major road. It caught almost 300 drivers breaking the law in its first 3 days.&lt;br&gt;- Tesla owners share their best tips for taking an EV on a road trip.&lt;br&gt;- A team of engineers turned a Toyota Land Cruiser into an EV and drove it underwater for 4 miles.&lt;br&gt;- Comparing Windows uninstallers, getting upset and then deciding to make my own.&lt;br&gt;- How to set up Meta Pay to quickly make payments on Facebook, Instagram, Messenger, and WhatsApp.&lt;br&gt;- How do you enforce &amp; ensure AWS S3 secured transit - AWS Config Rule.&lt;br&gt;- Mountpoint for Amazon S3 Now GA to Access Bucket Like Local File System.&lt;br&gt;- 6 Tips for Effective React Pagination: Building a User-Friendly Navigation Component.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- You can live like a coastal grandmother in Diane Sawyer's 20-acre Martha's Vineyard estate for $24 million &amp;mdash; see inside.&lt;br&gt;- Jewelry worth up to $63,000 was stolen from one of the world's top museums and sold on eBay for as little as $50, report says.&lt;br&gt;- Banks have a secret weapon known as synthetic data. Here’s how it works.&lt;br&gt;- How Index Ventures jumped to the front of the AI GPU line.&lt;br&gt;- If Elon Musk removes the block feature from X it wouldn't be the first time the billionaire skirted App Store rules.&lt;br&gt;- A Proud Boy who was supposed to be sentenced for his role in the Capitol riot is now missing, FBI says.&lt;br&gt;- Lucy Letby: U.K. Orders Inquiry After Nurse Found Guilty Of Killing Babies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Here's everything you need to know about ChatGPT, the chatbot everyone's still talking about.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk, who was accused of unblocking himself from people's accounts after buying Twitter, now says he's getting rid of the block feature altogether aside from DMs.&lt;br&gt;- Charisma AI uses proprietary LLMs for interactive storytelling in games and beyond.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The use of AI camera systems by the police in England has proven effective in catching drivers breaking the law.&lt;br&gt;- Tesla owners have shared valuable tips for taking electric vehicles on road trips.&lt;br&gt;- The development of an underwater electric vehicle demonstrates the potential for innovative engineering solutions.&lt;br&gt;- The importance of secure transit in AWS S3 and the implementation of rules to enforce it.&lt;br&gt;- The growing popularity of Meta Pay for quick payments on social media platforms.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of synthetic data in the banking industry and its role in enhancing security.&lt;br&gt;- The influence of Elon Musk in challenging app store rules and his potential removal of the block feature.&lt;br&gt;- The concerning disappearance of a Proud Boy involved in the Capitol riot.&lt;br&gt;- The inquiry ordered in the case of Lucy Letby, a nurse found guilty of killing babies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;This report covers a range of topics including tech, business, and AI. It highlights the implementation of AI camera systems by the police in England to catch law-breaking drivers, provides tips from Tesla owners for road trips, and showcases innovative engineering with an underwater electric vehicle. The report also discusses the use of Meta Pay for quick payments on social media platforms, the impact of synthetic data in banking, and the potential removal of the block feature by Elon Musk. Additionally, it addresses concerning events such as the disappearance of a Proud Boy involved in the Capitol riot and the inquiry ordered in the case of Lucy Letby, a nurse found guilty of killing babies. Overall, the report provides insights into various aspects of technology, business, and AI.</summary></entry></feed>