<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-29T08:03:30Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 29 Oct 2023 08:03:30</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-29T08:03:30Z</published><updated>2023-10-29T08:03:30Z</updated><id>58bb67b4-02b9-4795-8e48-8a50c51cacf9</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Arduino Builds a Bridge to the Raspberry Pi Ecosystem with Its New Portenta H&lt;br&gt;- Arduino has introduced the Portenta H, which allows users to connect Arduino and Raspberry Pi devices.&lt;br&gt;- This collaboration aims to provide a seamless integration between the two platforms, expanding the possibilities for developers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Skio (YC S20) is hiring – Subscriptions for Shopify, recharge migrations&lt;br&gt;- Skio, a startup backed by Y Combinator, is hiring for its subscription management platform for Shopify.&lt;br&gt;- The company focuses on helping businesses migrate their subscription services to Shopify, providing a streamlined solution.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Cruise ceases robotaxi operations, the Apple Watch gets a new feature and Carta tries to head off bad press&lt;br&gt;- Cruise, a self-driving car company, has decided to halt its robotaxi operations due to technical challenges.&lt;br&gt;- Apple Watch introduces a new feature that allows users to unlock their iPhones while wearing a mask.&lt;br&gt;- Carta, a financial technology company, is taking proactive measures to address potential negative publicity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Plaza Inn closes 'temporarily' on same day as consent decree ... - Oklahoman.com&lt;br&gt;- Plaza Inn, a hotel, has announced its temporary closure on the same day as a consent decree.&lt;br&gt;- The closure is likely related to legal issues or compliance matters.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. A top South Carolina Democratic official dismisses Dean Phillips' presidential bid as 'not serious,' says the Minnesota lawmaker has not yet contacted the party in the key early-voting state&lt;br&gt;- A South Carolina Democratic official criticizes Dean Phillips' presidential bid, stating that it is not being taken seriously.&lt;br&gt;- The official mentions that Phillips has not reached out to the party in South Carolina, a crucial state for early voting.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. McDonalds is giving free French fries in return for waiving the right to sue&lt;br&gt;- McDonald's is offering free French fries to customers who agree to waive their right to sue the company.&lt;br&gt;- This move is likely a legal strategy to protect McDonald's from potential lawsuits.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. Meet Eureka: A Human-Level Reward Design Algorithm Powered by Large Language Model LLMs&lt;br&gt;- Eureka is an algorithm powered by large language models (LLMs) that aims to design rewards for AI systems.&lt;br&gt;- The algorithm focuses on creating human-level rewards to improve the performance and behavior of AI models.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Former Vice President Mike Pence is suspending his 2024 presidential campaign: 'This is not my time'&lt;br&gt;- Former Vice President Mike Pence announces the suspension of his 2024 presidential campaign.&lt;br&gt;- Pence states that the current time is not suitable for his presidential bid.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Apple says BMW wireless chargers really are messing with iPhone 15s&lt;br&gt;- Apple claims that BMW's wireless chargers are causing issues with the iPhone 15.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights potential compatibility problems between Apple devices and third-party accessories.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The collaboration between Arduino and Raspberry Pi expands the capabilities of both platforms, benefiting developers.&lt;br&gt;- Skio's subscription management platform for Shopify simplifies the migration process for businesses.&lt;br&gt;- Cruise's decision to halt robotaxi operations showcases the challenges in developing self-driving cars.&lt;br&gt;- McDonald's strategy of offering free French fries in exchange for waiving the right to sue is a legal maneuver.&lt;br&gt;- Eureka's reward design algorithm aims to improve AI systems' behavior and performance.&lt;br&gt;- Mike Pence's decision to suspend his presidential campaign indicates his assessment of the current political landscape.&lt;br&gt;- Compatibility issues between Apple devices and third-party accessories can impact user experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report highlights various developments in the tech, business, and AI sectors. It showcases collaborations, challenges, legal strategies, and political decisions that shape these industries. The insights gathered emphasize the importance of innovation, adaptability, and understanding user needs in these rapidly evolving fields.</summary></entry></feed>