<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-14T08:03:28Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 14 Oct 2023 08:03:28</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-14T08:03:28Z</published><updated>2023-10-14T08:03:28Z</updated><id>50efe707-b452-4fc7-89ec-15f80a88c519</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- YouTube is facing scrutiny from the EU regarding the war in Israel.&lt;br&gt;- Apple Loop highlights iPhone 15 Pro battery problems and MacBook Pro delays.&lt;br&gt;- Android Circuit reviews Pixel 8 and 8 Pro, and discusses Pixel Watch problems.&lt;br&gt;- Supercharge Graph Analytics at Scale with GPU-CPU Fusion for 100x Performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- The World of Hyatt Business Card is ending its offer for 2 free nights at expensive hotels.&lt;br&gt;- John Wiley &amp; Sons stock dropped 12% this week.&lt;br&gt;- Ripcord, a file scanning startup backed by Steve Wozniak, is raising new cash.&lt;br&gt;- EV data startup Volteras aims to bring Tesla-level control to every vehicle and charger.&lt;br&gt;- 6 VCs provide insights on capturing and defending market share in the AI era.&lt;br&gt;- African startups are experiencing a decrease in capital availability in Q3.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- 6 VCs explain how startups can capture and defend market share in the AI era.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Montana State Library Commission votes to eliminate educational resources.&lt;br&gt;- The desert ghost town known as 'Mini Gaza' is used by the Israel Defense Forces for urban warfare training.&lt;br&gt;- 'The Walking Dead: Daryl Dixon' may need a new name now that Carol is returning.&lt;br&gt;- Solar eclipse path in 2023 shows where to see the 'ring of fire' across the United States.&lt;br&gt;- Antarctica has lost 8.3 trillion tons of ice since 1997.&lt;br&gt;- Russia is using 'human wave' tactics in eastern Ukraine, according to the White House.&lt;br&gt;- Jeff Bezos reportedly bought a $79 million home on a private island known as 'Billionaire Bunker.'&lt;br&gt;- Over 1 million people in Gaza were forced to evacuate within 24 hours due to an Israeli order.&lt;br&gt;- Kodable is hiring a Unity game developer to teach kids to code.&lt;br&gt;- Amid a breakup, Synapse and Evolve address allegations about their relationship.&lt;br&gt;- The FDA warns that "Ketamine Therapy" may just be partying.&lt;br&gt;- Female frogs pretend to be dead to deal with annoying males.&lt;br&gt;- A digital-only gaming future is inevitable.</summary></entry></feed>