<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-07T20:01:48Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 07 Oct 2023 20:01:48</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-07T20:01:48Z</published><updated>2023-10-07T20:01:48Z</updated><id>2ead8102-451d-4a62-ae35-ec2c0907c987</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- NOV Inc. shares acquired by Ceredex Value Advisors&lt;br&gt;- Shell using Fortnite, TikTok, etc. to convince kids fossil fuels are cool&lt;br&gt;- John Carmack and Rich Sutton partner to accelerate development of AGI&lt;br&gt;- Google DeepMind releases Open X-Embodiment to help advance how robots can learn new skills&lt;br&gt;- Apple iPhone 15, iPhone 15 Pro overheating fix&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Target closing 9 locations over crime, but New York City crime stats tell another story&lt;br&gt;- A couple bought a 1940s house owned by a family of hoarders&lt;br&gt;- Take a look inside Florida's new golf course with a $1 million membership fee and private yacht club&lt;br&gt;- You can buy an abandoned Colorado ski resort for $7 million&lt;br&gt;- The secretive company that might end privacy as we know it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- John Carmack and Rich Sutton partner to accelerate development of AGI&lt;br&gt;- Google DeepMind releases Open X-Embodiment to help advance how robots can learn new skills&lt;br&gt;- Study finds that police "crime predicting" AI fails miserably at predicting crimes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Jeremy Grantham predicts a crash in the S&amp;P 500, house price slide, and a recession&lt;br&gt;- Gen Z worker in Spain shares his savings strategy&lt;br&gt;- Personal loan and mortgage interest rates today&lt;br&gt;- The student loan payment restart puts pressure on the economy&lt;br&gt;- One in ten chatbot users are interested in sexual content&lt;br&gt;- Your evil car is filling the ocean with microplastics&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section highlights advancements in AI, partnerships, and product fixes.&lt;br&gt;- The business section covers store closures, unique real estate purchases, and privacy concerns.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section discusses the limitations of crime-predicting AI.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report showcases a mix of technology, business, and AI news, with insights on financial trends and societal impacts.</summary></entry></feed>