<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-17T16:01:21Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 17 Aug 2023 16:01:21</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-17T16:01:21Z</published><updated>2023-08-17T16:01:21Z</updated><id>dca22cec-06f5-43c9-8c03-5cccde6315cb</id><summary type="html">Report: Insights from Various Topics&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Tabnine introduces Tabnine Chat, an enterprise-grade, code-centric chat application that allows developers to interact with Tabnine's AI models using natural language.&lt;br&gt;- Establishing a PostgreSQL connection with Prisma in NestJS is a comprehensive guide with a bookmark API example.&lt;br&gt;- Acronym's new computer with Asus is bonkers, emphasizing the point of innovation and uniqueness.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech industry continues to evolve with advancements in AI, code-centric applications, and innovative computer designs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Business:&lt;br&gt;- Tesla is making cheaper, shorter-range Model S and Model X cars to revive demand.&lt;br&gt;- Burger King in India removes tomatoes from the menu due to inflation.&lt;br&gt;- Angry investors protest outside a Chinese shadow bank, indicating potential trouble in China's debt and housing sectors.&lt;br&gt;- Ford takes inspiration from Tesla and expands its services.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: Businesses are adapting to market demands, facing challenges such as inflation and debt, and learning from successful competitors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. AI:&lt;br&gt;- Cryo-EM provides insights into the rational design of anticonvulsants.&lt;br&gt;- MIT and Harvard's open-source FAn system enables real-time detection, tracking, and following of any objects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: AI is being utilized in various fields, including drug design and object detection, revolutionizing research and technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Miscellaneous:&lt;br&gt;- George Eliot reflects on what an author leaves behind besides their books.&lt;br&gt;- Rupert Murdoch, 92, is dating again after breaking off his engagement.&lt;br&gt;- Madden 24 responds to community feedback related to on-field audio.&lt;br&gt;- San Francisco's blockbuster Kehinde Wiley show will tour the US.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: Miscellaneous topics cover literature, personal relationships, entertainment, and cultural events, showcasing diverse aspects of society.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is focused on AI advancements and code-centric applications.&lt;br&gt;- Businesses are adapting to market demands and learning from successful competitors.&lt;br&gt;- AI is revolutionizing various fields, including drug design and object detection.&lt;br&gt;- Miscellaneous topics highlight cultural, personal, and entertainment aspects of society.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In conclusion, this report provides insights into various topics, showcasing the advancements, challenges, and cultural aspects of different industries. The tech industry, business sector, AI applications, and miscellaneous topics all contribute to the overall understanding of the current landscape.</summary></entry></feed>