<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-28T15:02:55Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 28 Jan 2024 15:02:55</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-28T15:02:55Z</published><updated>2024-01-28T15:02:55Z</updated><id>7b4e8740-6817-4025-ac8f-ed645e3e2f94</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xiayanzheng/xiayanzheng.github.io/main/voice/7b4e8740-6817-4025-ac8f-ed645e3e2f94.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        
    &lt;script type="text/javascript"&gt;
        (function(c,l,a,r,i,t,y){
            c[a]=c[a]||function(){(c[a].q=c[a].q||[]).push(arguments)};
            t=l.createElement(r);t.async=1;t.src="https://www.clarity.ms/tag/"+i;
            y=l.getElementsByTagName(r)[0];y.parentNode.insertBefore(t,y);
        })(window, document, "clarity", "script", "kssf4cm8i9");
    &lt;/script&gt;
    
        In the world today, there are several noteworthy events taking place. One concerning issue is the decline of hammerhead sharks, which is being explored through the perspective of local divers. These divers are shedding light on the challenges faced by these magnificent creatures, highlighting the need for conservation efforts. Additionally, there is a nostalgic reflection on Unix desktops, emphasizing the lessons we can learn from their history. The tweet from @blackleitus mentions the use of data from SEC filings and company reports, with visuals being manually created in-house. In the realm of artificial intelligence, Adept AI has introduced a new multimodal model called Fuyu-Heavy, specifically designed for digital agents. This development showcases advancements in technology and its potential impact on various industries. Lastly, media literacy classes are gaining popularity, but some conservatives perceive a "woke" agenda behind them. This highlights the ongoing debates and differing perspectives on education and media consumption in society.
    </summary></entry></feed>