<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-16T14:01:25Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 16 Aug 2023 14:01:25</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-16T14:01:25Z</published><updated>2023-08-16T14:01:25Z</updated><id>ab1e7ab2-8bbc-44e8-bbcc-454922341fe2</id><summary type="html">A WFH employee in Australia is hitting out at her ex-employer after it tracked how much she was typing — and then fired her&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- A work-from-home employee in Australia was fired by her ex-employer after they tracked how much she was typing.&lt;br&gt;- The employee claims that she was unfairly dismissed and that the tracking of her typing was an invasion of privacy.&lt;br&gt;- This incident raises concerns about the monitoring of employees in remote work settings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The incident highlights the need for clear guidelines and policies regarding employee monitoring in remote work environments.&lt;br&gt;- Employers should prioritize trust and open communication with their remote employees rather than resorting to invasive monitoring practices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google Finds It’s Underpaying Many Men as It Addresses Wage Equity&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Business&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Google has discovered that it is underpaying many male employees as it addresses wage equity.&lt;br&gt;- The company has been working to close the gender pay gap, but this new finding reveals a discrepancy in pay for male employees as well.&lt;br&gt;- Google is committed to rectifying this issue and ensuring fair compensation for all employees.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The case demonstrates the complexity of achieving wage equity and the importance of ongoing monitoring and analysis to identify and address pay disparities.&lt;br&gt;- It is crucial for companies to regularly review their compensation practices and make necessary adjustments to ensure fair and equal pay for all employees.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paid users of X, formerly Twitter, gets a new tab to highlight their posts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Paid users of X (formerly Twitter) now have a new tab that allows them to highlight their posts.&lt;br&gt;- This feature provides an opportunity for paid users to increase the visibility of their content and engage with a wider audience.&lt;br&gt;- The introduction of this tab aims to enhance the user experience and provide additional value for paid subscribers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The new tab for paid users reflects the growing trend of social media platforms offering premium features and benefits to monetize their services.&lt;br&gt;- This feature can be seen as a way for X to incentivize users to upgrade to a paid subscription and generate revenue.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;X (formerly Twitter) makes X Pro (formerly TweetDeck) a subscriber-only product&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- X (formerly Twitter) has made X Pro (formerly TweetDeck) a subscriber-only product.&lt;br&gt;- This means that users will need to pay a subscription fee to access the advanced features and functionalities of X Pro.&lt;br&gt;- The move is part of X's strategy to monetize its platform and generate revenue from its most dedicated users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The decision to make X Pro a subscriber-only product highlights the increasing importance of subscription-based models in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- By offering exclusive features to paying subscribers, X aims to create a sustainable business model and enhance user engagement and loyalty.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why is it not recommended to use email registration in China?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Business&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- It is not recommended to use email registration in China due to various reasons.&lt;br&gt;- The Chinese government has strict regulations and censorship policies regarding email communication.&lt;br&gt;- Email services in China are often unreliable and prone to hacking and security breaches.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Businesses operating in China should consider alternative registration methods that align with local regulations and preferences.&lt;br&gt;- Understanding the unique challenges and limitations of email registration in China is crucial for companies looking to establish a strong online presence in the Chinese market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Re-entering the world of tech after a career break: ‘virtual’ Vapasi program&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- The 'virtual' Vapasi program aims to help individuals re-enter the tech industry after a career break.&lt;br&gt;- The program provides training, mentorship, and networking opportunities to support participants in updating their skills and knowledge.&lt;br&gt;- It is designed to address the challenges faced by individuals who have taken a break from their tech careers and facilitate their successful return to the industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The 'virtual' Vapasi program highlights the importance of creating inclusive and supportive initiatives to encourage diversity and inclusion in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- Providing resources and opportunities for individuals who have taken career breaks can help bridge the talent gap and promote a more diverse and skilled workforce.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to select a Payment Gateway: [Part 2] Functions of Payment Gateways&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Business&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Selecting a payment gateway involves considering various functions and features.&lt;br&gt;- Payment gateways facilitate secure and seamless online transactions.&lt;br&gt;- Key functions to consider include payment processing, fraud prevention, and integration capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Choosing the right payment gateway is crucial for businesses to ensure a smooth and secure payment experience for their customers.&lt;br&gt;- Understanding the specific functions and features of payment gateways can help businesses make informed decisions and optimize their online payment processes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Concluding insights:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The report covers a range of topics including tech, business, and career development.&lt;br&gt;- Key insights include the importance of trust and communication in remote work settings, the complexity of achieving wage equity, the monetization strategies of social media platforms, the challenges of operating in the Chinese market, the need for inclusive initiatives in the tech industry, and the considerations in selecting payment gateways.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report highlights the evolving landscape of technology and business, emphasizing the need for adaptability, fairness, and innovation in various aspects of the industry.</summary></entry></feed>