<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-10T04:01:05Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 10 Aug 2023 04:01:05</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-10T04:01:05Z</published><updated>2023-08-10T04:01:05Z</updated><id>a3de5831-a59c-4692-9b38-b6fa020a97d7</id><summary type="html">Vite report on Thu, 10 Aug 2023 02:01:17&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft is conducting Red Teaming on GPT-4 and other AI models.&lt;br&gt;- Apple Watch Ultra review: It is praised for its durability, accurate GPS, and longer battery life, making it a must-have smartwatch for sports and outdoor activities.&lt;br&gt;- Everything we know about Elon Musk's Starlink satellites and future internet plans.&lt;br&gt;- Popular open source project Moq is facing criticism for quietly collecting data.&lt;br&gt;- When Did Postgres Become Cool? A discussion on the rise in popularity of the Postgres database.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- 11 Best Robo-advisors of August 2023.&lt;br&gt;- CSAA Car Insurance Review 2023.&lt;br&gt;- New DoorDash customers are using the app for grocery deliveries and flowers, expanding beyond restaurant meals.&lt;br&gt;- Auto executives still doubt the success of Tesla's sales model.&lt;br&gt;- California has found a way to bypass opposition and build more housing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's Red Teaming includes testing GPT-4 and other AI models.&lt;br&gt;- Highlighting the key points of Elon Musk's Starlink satellites and future internet plans.&lt;br&gt;- The potential impact of AI on various industries and the need for ethical considerations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Arizona Wildcats RB Michael Wiley named to Doak Walker Award.&lt;br&gt;- Ohio Dems. chair mocks Republican's complaint about lack of time to push anti-abortion efforts.&lt;br&gt;- How a sheep wagon became one man's doomsday survival plan.&lt;br&gt;- DC Democrats argue against ranked choice voting in predominantly Black areas.&lt;br&gt;- Natural gas prices are rising due to potential strikes by energy workers in Australia.&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine's navy is finding ways to disrupt Russia's sea supply lanes.&lt;br&gt;- The potential impact of fungi on the curse of Tutankhamun's tomb.&lt;br&gt;- The rise in 401(k) hardship loans and the potential regrets associated with them.&lt;br&gt;- Insights on the quote from 50 years ago and its relevance to Hollywood today.&lt;br&gt;- Insights on the challenges faced by open-source Chrome extension developers.&lt;br&gt;- Tencent's Sogou Input Method's request to keep information private.&lt;br&gt;- The Quite OK Audio Format for fast, lossy compression.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The advancements in AI models, such as GPT-4, and their testing through Red Teaming by companies like Microsoft.&lt;br&gt;- The growing popularity of smartwatches, like the Apple Watch Ultra, for sports and outdoor activities.&lt;br&gt;- The potential impact of Elon Musk's Starlink satellites on future internet connectivity.&lt;br&gt;- The expansion of services offered by platforms like DoorDash, including grocery deliveries and flower deliveries.&lt;br&gt;- The ongoing skepticism among auto executives regarding Tesla's sales model.&lt;br&gt;- The challenges and solutions in the housing market, particularly in California.&lt;br&gt;- The ethical considerations and potential impact of AI on various industries.&lt;br&gt;- The potential disruptions in global energy supply due to strikes by energy workers.&lt;br&gt;- The historical and cultural significance of artifacts like Tutankhamun's tomb and the potential role of fungi in the curse associated with it.&lt;br&gt;- The financial implications and potential regrets associated with 401(k) hardship loans.&lt;br&gt;- The insights gained from the experiences of open-source Chrome extension developers.&lt;br&gt;- The importance of privacy and data protection in popular software applications like Tencent's Sogou Input Method.&lt;br&gt;- The development of new audio formats for efficient compression.</summary></entry></feed>