<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-24T20:01:53Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 24 Jan 2024 20:01:53</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-24T20:01:53Z</published><updated>2024-01-24T20:01:53Z</updated><id>6bd5e29e-27fb-4b38-91dd-58ced67a1a54</id><summary type="html">In the world, Krafton, the company behind the popular game PUBG, has announced plans to extend its supremacy by focusing on franchise growth and revamping the game's graphics. They aim to further enhance the gaming experience for players. In another news, a 61-year-old man has filed a lawsuit against Macy's, claiming that he was wrongly identified as a store robber through facial recognition technology, leading to his arrest and assault. The man alleges that the false identification caused him significant harm. On the financial front, Elevance Health has reported a profit of $856 million, despite a decrease in Medicaid enrollment. The company's success is noteworthy considering the challenging circumstances. In the gaming world, 'The Finals' 1.5.5 Patch Notes have been released, addressing issues such as nerfing the revive meta and fixing bugs. This update aims to improve the overall gameplay experience for users. Additionally, it is becoming easier for creators to earn their first dollar, as various platforms offer opportunities and support for aspiring creators. The article provides insights into how individuals can start monetizing their creative endeavors. However, Netflix users may have to pay more to enjoy the streaming service without ads, as the cheapest Basic plan is being phased out. This change may impact users' subscription choices and pricing. On social media platform TikTok, pay transparency has become a trending topic, with Salary Transparent Street's Hannah Williams shedding light on its significance. The discussion around salary transparency aims to promote fairness and equality in the workplace. Lastly, Kia's new electric vehicle features a bold headlight design, with a blinking light that has caught people's attention. The article explores the reasons behind this unique feature and its potential impact on the automotive industry. Meanwhile, California Forever, a new billionaire-backed city in the Bay Area, is facing criticism for various reasons. The article delves into the real problems associated with this ambitious project.</summary></entry></feed>