<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2023-12-13T08:03:51Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 13 Dec 2023 08:03:51</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-13T08:03:51Z</published><updated>2023-12-13T08:03:51Z</updated><id>7e647635-1a1c-467c-9819-f2e339b58416</id><summary type="html">In the world, there have been several significant events and developments. Firstly, the obituary of Richard Mayden was announced by Guardian Funeral Home and Cremation Services in Corpus Christi. This news marks the passing of an individual who likely had an impact on the local community. Additionally, a smart nanotool has been introduced to accelerate the fight against cancer, as reported by John Wiley. This advancement in technology brings hope for more efficient and effective cancer treatments. In the realm of education, Harvard University's fundraising efforts have allowed it to maintain its position, while the University of Pennsylvania has faced challenges in this area. The closure of a highly anticipated game developer after receiving negative reviews upon releasing their game on early access is also noteworthy. Furthermore, Netflix has confirmed that it offers thousands of movies and shows that many users do not watch. Marvel's Black Panther Disney Plus series is set to delve into the history of Wakanda, providing fans with further insights into this fictional world. The FDA's potential crackdown on lab tests raises questions about patient protection versus limited access to care. The US pork industry is facing its least profitable year on record in 2023. Puma's decision to end its sponsorship of Israel's soccer team is not connected to pro-Palestinian boycotts, according to the company. Scientists have expressed skepticism about the Dubai Climate Conference, suggesting that it may not be effective in addressing climate change. In legal news, SBF's lawyer has made a damning statement about his client during cross-examination. Zara has faced criticism for a recent ad campaign that some customers believe resembles the war in Gaza. In the field of science, various studies have been conducted on topics such as molecule-metal relay catalysis, dopamine receptors, and the correlation between cognitive and physical effort. Mouse models of Stargardt disease have shown differences in pharmacological targeting and inflammatory responses. A correction has been issued for supporting information in a study on the material footprint of nations. The relationships between different subsets of colon T regulatory cells have been explored. The mechanisms of higher-order and lower-order interactions in complex networks have been investigated in the context of hyperedge prediction. Phenotypic plasticity has been identified as a missing element in the theory of vegetation pattern formation. The design of ionizable lipid nanoparticles for mRNA delivery has been optimized to minimize off-target effects. Socioeconomic networks have undergone reorganization in response to external shocks. The role of dynamics in heterogeneous catalysis, specifically surface diffusivity and N2 decomposition, has been examined. Integrin α5β1 has been found to contribute to cell fusion and inflammation mediated by the SARS-CoV-2 spike protein through an RGD-independent interaction. Mutations in ALPK1 have been linked to ROSAH syndrome and Spiradenoma, and it has been discovered that these mutations are activated by human nucleotide sugars. The coupling mechanism during collective cell migration has been identified as a vinculin mechanochemical switch. Lastly, a suppressor screen in C. elegans has identified a multiprotein interaction that stabilizes the synaptonemal complex. The hippocampus has been found to play a role in novel spatial learning, with both age-related and age-invariant contributions. Additionally, USP16 has been identified as a deubiquitinase that targets pro-ISG15 and ISGylated proteins involved in metabolism.</summary></entry></feed>