<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-19T16:02:51Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 19 Aug 2023 16:02:51</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-19T16:02:51Z</published><updated>2023-08-19T16:02:51Z</updated><id>53f06763-2a5f-487b-aa67-096fafb79b1b</id><summary type="html">COVID‐19 and tail risk contagion across commodity futures markets - John Wiley (Business)&lt;br&gt;- This article discusses the impact of the COVID-19 pandemic on commodity futures markets and the concept of tail risk contagion.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the increased volatility and correlation among commodity futures during the pandemic, as well as the role of government interventions in stabilizing the markets.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that tail risk contagion can have significant implications for commodity markets and highlight the need for risk management strategies in times of crisis.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Elon Musk removes the block feature from X it wouldn't be the first time the billionaire skirted App Store rules (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article discusses the possibility of Elon Musk removing the block feature from an undisclosed app, which would be a violation of App Store rules.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include previous instances where Musk has skirted App Store rules, such as with the Tesla app, and the potential consequences of such actions.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that Musk's actions could have implications for the relationship between app developers and app stores, as well as the overall regulation of app distribution.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Proud Boy who was supposed to be sentenced for his role in the Capitol riot is now missing, FBI says (News)&lt;br&gt;- This news article reports on a Proud Boy member who was supposed to be sentenced for his involvement in the Capitol riot but is now missing.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the FBI's investigation into the individual's disappearance and the potential implications for the ongoing legal proceedings related to the Capitol riot.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that the missing individual's case highlights the challenges faced by law enforcement in prosecuting individuals involved in the Capitol riot.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to watch a free Australia vs. Sweden live stream: Women's World Cup third place matchup (Sports)&lt;br&gt;- This article provides information on how to watch a free live stream of the Australia vs. Sweden Women's World Cup third place matchup.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the platforms and services that offer free live streaming of the match and the schedule of the game.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that free live streaming options provide accessible ways for fans to watch and engage with sports events.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ask HN: Why did Microsoft, Meta, and PayPal update their ToS today? (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This post on the Hacker News forum asks why Microsoft, Meta (formerly Facebook), and PayPal updated their Terms of Service (ToS) on the same day.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include speculation and discussion from forum users on the reasons behind the updates and potential implications for users.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the post suggest that coordinated updates to ToS by major tech companies could be related to legal or regulatory changes, user privacy concerns, or other business considerations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kernighan and Pike were right: Do one thing, and do it well (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article discusses the principle of "do one thing, and do it well" advocated by Brian Kernighan and Rob Pike, two influential computer scientists.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the benefits of focusing on a single task or functionality in software development and the potential drawbacks of trying to do too much.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that the "do one thing, and do it well" principle can lead to more modular and maintainable code, as well as improved overall system performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mountpoint for Amazon S3 Now GA to Access Bucket Like Local File System (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article announces the general availability of a mountpoint for Amazon S3 that allows users to access their S3 buckets as if they were a local file system.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the benefits of this feature for developers and the potential use cases for accessing S3 data more seamlessly.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that the mountpoint for Amazon S3 can simplify data management and integration workflows, making it easier to work with S3 data in various applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6 Tips for Effective React Pagination: Building a User-Friendly Navigation Component (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article provides six tips for implementing effective pagination in React applications, focusing on creating a user-friendly navigation component.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include considerations for handling large data sets, optimizing performance, and enhancing the user experience.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that implementing pagination in React requires careful planning and attention to user needs, and following these tips can lead to a more efficient and user-friendly application.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lucy Letby: U.K. Orders Inquiry After Nurse Found Guilty Of Killing Babies (News)&lt;br&gt;- This news article reports on the case of Lucy Letby, a nurse in the UK who has been found guilty of killing babies in her care.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the details of the case, the investigation process, and the response from authorities.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that the case raises concerns about patient safety and the need for robust oversight and accountability in healthcare settings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to change your Facebook password: Reset your password to keep your account safe (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article provides instructions on how to change your Facebook password to enhance the security of your account.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the steps to reset your password and additional tips for creating a strong and unique password.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article emphasize the importance of regularly updating passwords and taking proactive measures to protect personal information online.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;💡 Discover Your Life Goals and Make Your First Open Source Contribution with Before I Die Code 🚀 (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article introduces the "Before I Die Code" project, which aims to help individuals discover their life goals and make their first open-source contribution.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the motivation behind the project, the process of getting involved, and the potential benefits for participants.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that combining personal growth and open-source contributions can be a meaningful and fulfilling experience for individuals in the tech community.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Create a systemd service script for running Gunicorn to serve your application (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article provides a tutorial on creating a systemd service script for running Gunicorn, a Python web server, to serve your application.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the necessary configurations and commands to set up the service script and start Gunicorn.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article highlight the benefits of using systemd for managing and automating application processes, improving reliability and ease of deployment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PFL Playoffs NYC 2023 Results: Larissa Pachecho Obliterates Olena Kolesnyk In 14 Seconds (Sports)&lt;br&gt;- This article reports on the results of a PFL (Professional Fighters League) playoff match in NYC, where Larissa Pachecho defeated Olena Kolesnyk in just 14 seconds.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the details of the fight, the significance of the victory, and the implications for the tournament.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that Pachecho's quick victory showcases her skills and sets the stage for further competition in the PFL playoffs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cruise told by CA DMV to reduce robotaxi fleet 50% following crash (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article discusses the California Department of Motor Vehicles' (DMV) directive for Cruise, a self-driving car company, to reduce its robotaxi fleet by 50% following a crash.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the details of the crash, the DMV's concerns, and Cruise's response to the directive.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that the incident highlights the challenges and regulatory scrutiny faced by autonomous vehicle companies, as well as the importance of safety measures in the development and deployment of self-driving technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PFL Playoffs NYC 2023 Results: Marina Mokhnatkina Makes Quick Work Of Amber Leibrock (Sports)&lt;br&gt;- This article reports on the results of another PFL playoff match in NYC, where Marina Mokhnatkina defeated Amber Leibrock.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the details of the fight, Mokhnatkina's dominant performance, and the implications for the tournament.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that Mokhnatkina's victory solidifies her position as a strong contender in the PFL playoffs and adds excitement to the competition.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To-MAY-To, To-MAH-To: Why Digital Technology And Innovation Are Not The Same Thing (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article explores the distinction between digital technology and innovation, highlighting that they are not interchangeable terms.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include defining digital technology and innovation, discussing their relationship, and providing examples to illustrate the difference.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that understanding the nuances between digital technology and innovation can help organizations and individuals better navigate the rapidly evolving tech landscape and make informed decisions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;HPC-AI Tech Raises 22 Million USD in Series A Funding to Fuel Team Expansion and Business Growth (Tech, Business)&lt;br&gt;- This article announces that HPC-AI Tech, a company specializing in high-performance computing and artificial intelligence, has raised 22 million USD in Series A funding.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the purpose of the funding, the company's plans for team expansion and business growth, and the investors involved.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that the funding reflects the growing demand for HPC and AI technologies and the company's potential for further innovation and market expansion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in 5 Chinese young adults looking for work is unemployed. The lack of work slows down the whole economy (Business, News)&lt;br&gt;- This article highlights the high unemployment rate among Chinese young adults, with one in five individuals looking for work being unemployed.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the impact of youth unemployment on the overall economy, the challenges faced by job seekers, and potential solutions.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that addressing youth unemployment is crucial for sustainable economic growth and social stability in China.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian soldiers are fighting Ukraine high on amphetamines, a report claims. The Nazis did it first. (News)&lt;br&gt;- This news article reports on a claim that Russian soldiers fighting in Ukraine are using amphetamines, drawing parallels to similar practices by Nazi soldiers.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the allegations made in the report, the historical context of drug use in warfare, and the potential implications for the ongoing conflict.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that the alleged use of amphetamines by Russian soldiers raises concerns about the impact on their behavior and decision-making, as well as the ethical implications of drug use in warfare.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;TSMC – the world's most important company. And everyone wants control of it (Business)&lt;br&gt;- This article discusses TSMC (Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company), highlighting its significance as the world's most important company and the competition for control over it.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include TSMC's role in the global semiconductor industry, its technological leadership, and the geopolitical dynamics surrounding its operations.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that TSMC's position as a key player in the semiconductor supply chain makes it a strategic asset for countries and companies, leading to intense competition and potential implications for global technology development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Show HN: Saf – simple, reliable, rsync-based, battle-tested, rounded backup (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This post on the Hacker News forum introduces Saf, a backup tool that aims to provide a simple, reliable, and battle-tested solution based on rsync.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the features and benefits of Saf, as well as the author's motivation for creating the tool.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the post suggest that Saf offers a user-friendly and robust backup solution for individuals and organizations seeking to protect their data.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cruise told by regulators to ‘immediately’ reduce robotaxi fleet 50% following crash (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article reports on regulators' directive for Cruise to "immediately" reduce its robotaxi fleet by 50% following a crash.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the details of the crash, the concerns raised by regulators, and Cruise's response to the directive.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that the incident underscores the challenges and regulatory oversight faced by autonomous vehicle companies, highlighting the need for safety measures and accountability in the development and deployment of self-driving technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cruise Robotaxi Hit By On Call Fire Engine. Is It The Fire Truck’s Fault? (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article discusses a recent incident where a Cruise robotaxi was hit by an on-call fire engine, raising questions about fault and liability.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the details of the collision, the potential factors contributing to the accident, and the implications for the development of autonomous vehicles.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that determining fault in accidents involving autonomous vehicles requires careful investigation and consideration of various factors, including the actions of other vehicles and emergency response vehicles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Maui, a perfect storm of climate, colonialism, and failed emergency systems made the deadliest US wildfire in over a century (News)&lt;br&gt;- This article examines the factors that contributed to the deadliest wildfire in over a century in the United States, which occurred on Maui.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the role of climate change, historical colonial practices, and failures in emergency systems in exacerbating the wildfire's impact.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that addressing the root causes of wildfires requires a comprehensive approach that considers environmental, social, and systemic factors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meet CipherChat: An AI Framework to Systematically Examine the Generalizability of Safety Alignment to Non-Natural Languages-Specifically Ciphers (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This article introduces CipherChat, an AI framework designed to systematically examine the generalizability of safety alignment to non-natural languages, specifically ciphers.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the purpose and methodology of CipherChat, as well as the potential applications and implications for AI safety research.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that CipherChat can contribute to advancing our understanding of safety alignment in AI systems and inform the development of robust and reliable AI technologies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Implementing CI/CD pipeline with GitHub Actions, and GitHub Pages in a React app. (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article provides a guide on implementing a CI/CD pipeline using GitHub Actions and GitHub Pages in a React application.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the steps and configurations required to set up the pipeline, as well as the benefits of using these tools for automated deployment.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article highlight the advantages of CI/CD pipelines in streamlining the development and deployment process, improving collaboration, and ensuring code quality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exactly Where To Book Now For The U.S. ‘Ring Of Fire’ Solar Eclipse (Travel)&lt;br&gt;- This article provides recommendations on where to book accommodations for the upcoming U.S. 'Ring of Fire' solar eclipse.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the best locations to witness the eclipse, the dates and times of the event, and tips for planning a successful viewing experience.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that the solar eclipse presents a unique opportunity for travelers and astronomy enthusiasts to witness a rare celestial event and should be planned in advance to secure the best viewing spots.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today’s Wordle #791 Hints, Clues And Answer For Saturday, August 19th (Games)&lt;br&gt;- This article provides hints, clues, and the answer for Wordle puzzle #791, which was released on Saturday, August 19th.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the rules of the Wordle game, strategies for solving the puzzle, and the specific hints and clues for the given puzzle.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that Wordle puzzles can be a fun and challenging way to exercise language and problem-solving skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Shows And Movies To Stream This Weekend On Netflix, Hulu, HBO Max, Disney+ And More (Entertainment)&lt;br&gt;- This article highlights the new shows and movies available for streaming on various platforms, including Netflix, Hulu, HBO Max, and Disney+.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the titles and brief descriptions of the new releases, as well as recommendations for viewers.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that streaming platforms continue to offer a wide range of content options, catering to diverse audience preferences and providing ample entertainment choices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exactly Where To Book Now For The U.S. ‘Ring Of Fire’ Solar Eclipse (Travel)&lt;br&gt;- This article provides recommendations on where to book accommodations for the upcoming U.S. 'Ring of Fire' solar eclipse.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the best locations to witness the eclipse, the dates and times of the event, and tips for planning a successful viewing experience.&lt;br&gt;- Insights from the article suggest that the solar eclipse presents a unique opportunity for travelers and astronomy enthusiasts to witness a rare celestial event and should be planned in advance to secure the best viewing spots.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;- The COVID-19 pandemic has had a significant impact on commodity futures markets, leading to increased volatility and correlation among commodities. Risk management strategies are crucial in times of crisis.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's potential violation of App Store rules by removing the block feature from an undisclosed app raises questions about the relationship between app developers and app stores.&lt;br&gt;- A missing Proud Boy member who was supposed to be sentenced for his involvement in the Capitol riot highlights the challenges faced by law enforcement in prosecuting individuals connected to the event.&lt;br&gt;- The Australia vs. Sweden Women's World Cup third place matchup can be watched for free through various streaming platforms, providing accessible options for sports fans.&lt;br&gt;- The updates to the Terms of Service by Microsoft, Meta, and PayPal prompt speculation and discussion on the reasons behind the changes and their implications for users.&lt;br&gt;- The principle of "do one thing, and do it well" in software development, advocated by Kernighan and Pike, emphasizes the benefits of focusing on a single task or functionality.&lt;br&gt;- The availability of a mountpoint for Amazon S3 that allows users to access their S3 buckets as if they were a local file system simplifies data management and integration workflows.&lt;br&gt;- Implementing effective pagination in React applications requires careful planning and attention to user needs, leading to a more efficient and user-friendly application.&lt;br&gt;- The case of Lucy Letby, a nurse found guilty of killing babies in the UK, raises concerns about patient safety and the need for robust oversight and accountability in healthcare settings.&lt;br&gt;- Changing your Facebook password regularly and following password security best practices is essential for protecting your account and personal information online.&lt;br&gt;- The "Before I Die Code" project combines personal growth and open-source contributions, providing individuals in the tech community with a meaningful and fulfilling experience.&lt;br&gt;- Creating a systemd service script for running Gunicorn to serve your application improves reliability and ease of deployment in a React app.&lt;br&gt;- Larissa Pachecho's quick victory over Olena Kolesnyk in the PFL playoffs showcases her skills and adds excitement to the competition.&lt;br&gt;- The directive for Cruise to reduce its robotaxi fleet by 50% following a crash highlights the challenges and regulatory scrutiny faced by autonomous vehicle companies.&lt;br&gt;- Marina Mokhnatkina's victory in the PFL playoffs solidifies her position as a strong contender and adds further excitement to the tournament.&lt;br&gt;- Digital technology and innovation are not the same thing, and understanding their distinctions can help navigate the tech landscape and make informed decisions.&lt;br&gt;- HPC-AI Tech's successful Series A funding reflects the growing demand for high-performance computing and artificial intelligence technologies.&lt;br&gt;- The high unemployment rate among Chinese young adults poses challenges for the overall economy and emphasizes the need for solutions to promote sustainable economic growth.&lt;br&gt;- Allegations of Russian soldiers using amphetamines in the Ukraine conflict raise concerns about their behavior and decision-making, as well as the ethical implications of drug use in warfare.&lt;br&gt;- TSMC's position as the world's most important company and the competition for control over it highlight its strategic significance in the global semiconductor industry.&lt;br&gt;- Saf, a simple and reliable backup tool based on rsync, offers a user-friendly and robust solution for data protection.&lt;br&gt;- Determining fault in accidents involving autonomous vehicles, such as the collision between a Cruise robotaxi and an on-call fire engine, requires careful investigation and consideration of various factors.&lt;br&gt;- The Maui wildfire, fueled by a perfect storm of climate change, colonialism, and failed emergency systems, underscores the need for comprehensive approaches to address wildfires.&lt;br&gt;- CipherChat, an AI framework, contributes to AI safety research by systematically examining the generalizability of safety alignment to non-natural languages, specifically ciphers.&lt;br&gt;- Implementing a CI/CD pipeline with GitHub Actions and GitHub Pages in a React app streamlines the development and deployment process, improving collaboration and code quality.&lt;br&gt;- Planning in advance and securing the best viewing spots are crucial for witnessing the upcoming U.S. 'Ring of Fire' solar eclipse.&lt;br&gt;- Wordle puzzles provide a fun and challenging way to exercise language and problem-solving skills.&lt;br&gt;- Streaming platforms offer a wide range of new shows and movies, catering to diverse audience preferences and providing ample entertainment choices.</summary></entry></feed>