<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-10T16:01:04Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 10 Aug 2023 16:01:04</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-10T16:01:04Z</published><updated>2023-08-10T16:01:04Z</updated><id>f442963c-88f7-4da0-a49f-9bbba1d380d9</id><summary type="html">Report: Global Insights from Various Topics&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Philippines Smartphone Shipments Decline 20% YoY in Q2 2023; Xiaomi Rises to Third Spot&lt;br&gt;   - Key points: Smartphone shipments in the Philippines have decreased by 20% compared to the previous year. Xiaomi has emerged as the third top smartphone brand in the country.&lt;br&gt;   - Insights: The decline in smartphone shipments could be attributed to various factors such as economic conditions, market saturation, or the impact of the COVID-19 pandemic. Xiaomi's rise in market share indicates its growing popularity and competitiveness in the Philippines.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Wiley journal board resigns en masse after monthlong strike - Inside Higher Ed&lt;br&gt;   - Key points: The journal board of Wiley, a prominent publishing company, has resigned collectively following a month-long strike.&lt;br&gt;   - Insights: The mass resignation of the journal board highlights the ongoing issues and conflicts within the academic publishing industry. This event may have broader implications for the future of scholarly publishing and the relationship between publishers and researchers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The Anatomage Table: A Promising Alternative in Anatomy Education - Cureus&lt;br&gt;   - Key points: The Anatomage Table is being recognized as a promising alternative in anatomy education.&lt;br&gt;   - Insights: The Anatomage Table offers innovative and immersive learning experiences for anatomy students. Its adoption could potentially enhance the effectiveness and accessibility of anatomy education.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Main is usually a function. So then when is it not?&lt;br&gt;   - Key points: The concept of "main" as a function in programming languages is explored, questioning its exceptions.&lt;br&gt;   - Insights: Understanding the exceptions to the traditional use of "main" can provide insights into the design and structure of programming languages. This knowledge can be valuable for developers and programmers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A New AI Research from China Introduces RecycleGPT: A Generative Language Model with a Fast Decoding Speed of 1.4x by Recycling Pre-Generated Model States without Running the Whole Model in Multiple Steps&lt;br&gt;   - Key points: Chinese AI researchers have developed RecycleGPT, a generative language model that achieves fast decoding speeds by recycling pre-generated model states.&lt;br&gt;   - Insights: RecycleGPT showcases advancements in AI research, specifically in the field of generative language models. Its fast decoding speed has implications for improving efficiency and scalability in natural language processing tasks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Supermarket AI meal planner app suggests recipe that would create chlorine gas&lt;br&gt;   - Key points: An AI-powered meal planner app in a supermarket suggests a recipe that could potentially create chlorine gas.&lt;br&gt;   - Insights: This incident highlights the importance of thorough testing and quality control in AI systems. It also emphasizes the need for ethical considerations and human oversight in AI applications to prevent potentially harmful outcomes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A new fast-acting pill is coming for postpartum depression, but it’s not a miracle cure&lt;br&gt;   - Key points: A new fast-acting pill for postpartum depression is being developed, but it is not considered a miracle cure.&lt;br&gt;   - Insights: The development of a fast-acting pill for postpartum depression represents progress in mental health treatment. However, it is crucial to manage expectations and recognize that it may not be a universal solution for all cases of postpartum depression.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The decline in smartphone shipments in the Philippines and the rise of Xiaomi indicate the dynamic nature of the smartphone market and the competitiveness of brands.&lt;br&gt;- The mass resignation of the Wiley journal board highlights ongoing issues in the academic publishing industry.&lt;br&gt;- The Anatomage Table offers innovative possibilities for anatomy education.&lt;br&gt;- Understanding exceptions to the traditional use of "main" in programming languages can provide insights into language design.&lt;br&gt;- RecycleGPT showcases advancements in AI research, particularly in generative language models.&lt;br&gt;- Ethical considerations and human oversight are crucial in AI applications to prevent potentially harmful outcomes.&lt;br&gt;- The development of a fast-acting pill for postpartum depression represents progress in mental health treatment, but it may not be a universal solution.</summary></entry></feed>