<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2023-12-17T08:03:49Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 17 Dec 2023 08:03:49</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-17T08:03:49Z</published><updated>2023-12-17T08:03:49Z</updated><id>6893a0c4-68a4-42c6-8a29-64d66e484b8d</id><summary type="html">In recent news, a Mississippi cop who shot an 11-year-old in the chest will face no criminal charges, sparking outrage and raising concerns about police accountability. Meanwhile, scientists are questioning the existence of a black hole in the center of the Sun, challenging previous theories. On a positive note, new research suggests that immune cells play a crucial role in shaping lung tissue before birth, offering potential new avenues for treating diseases. In the tech world, a developer shares their experience of building a Santa Chatbot to prank their brother, highlighting the fun side of technology. However, not all news is lighthearted, as officers have rescued 150 animals from a small garage where they were living in squalor, leading to animal cruelty charges for the owner. In the world of sports, Tiger Woods' 16-year-old daughter acted as his caddie for the first time, creating heartwarming moments for the Woods family. On a more serious note, hackers have targeted the AI bot ChatGPT, demanding it stops "dehumanizing" Palestinians. Additionally, Twitch has reversed its decision to allow "artistic nudity" due to concerns over AI-generated deepfakes. Social issues continue to make headlines, with an alarming increase in homelessness among American veterans and a scandal involving a co-founder of Moms for Liberty, Bridget Ziegler. In politics, Kevin McCarthy's hand-picked successor faces obstacles in running for a vacant seat due to already being involved in another race. Job opportunities are also being advertised, with Tesorio hiring a Senior Data Engineer in Latam. In environmental news, the mayor of Paris plans to triple SUV parking tariffs to combat air pollution. The tech industry sees both positive and negative developments, with AI job losses on the rise and AMD FSR being seen as a building block for Apple's hybrid MetalFX upscaling tech. In the energy sector, solar and wind power are projected to surpass coal power in the US for the first time in 2024. Google's Gemini expands to more apps, while Cruise reduces its workforce and Tesla issues a recall. In international news, Russia's new war plan aims to occupy more Ukrainian territory by 2026, raising concerns about escalating conflicts. Apple responds to the Beeper iMessage saga, emphasizing their efforts to protect user security. The company also introduces updates to make it easier for app makers to compete for consumer spending. In the world of development, frontend developers share their thoughts on WordPress and its usage in corporate jobs. Google AI introduces MedLM, a family of foundation models tailored for healthcare industry use cases, while deep learning is revolutionizing cancer diagnosis by accurately identifying and reclassifying combined liver cancers. Apple releases an urgent update to protect iPhones from devastating attacks. Lastly, scientists claim that large AI models can now create smaller AI tools without human intervention, leading to concerns about the potential for an AI "big brother." In politics, Ron DeSantis predicts that if he loses the Iowa caucuses, Trump will claim they were "stolen" from him, potentially delegitimizing the results.</summary></entry></feed>