<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-11T20:01:26Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 11 Aug 2023 20:01:26</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-11T20:01:26Z</published><updated>2023-08-11T20:01:26Z</updated><id>ed4a7d7e-13f2-4553-882c-1c56c063737d</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Google AI Introduces AdaTape: A New AI Approach with a Transformer-based Architecture that Allows for Dynamic Computation in Neural Networks through Adaptive Tape Tokens&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft Warns Of Exchange Server Failures, Pulls August 8 Security Update&lt;br&gt;- ChatGPT and GPT-4 skew the most liberal &amp;mdash; and Meta's LLaMA is the most conservative AI model, a new study says&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Eagle Asset Management Inc. Raises Stake in John Wiley &amp; Sons ... - MarketBeat&lt;br&gt;- Country Garden, one of China's real-estate behemoths, could look at restructuring its debt after missing key interest payments this week: JPMorgan&lt;br&gt;- A German grocery store charged customers the 'true price' of their food, and one cheese was almost twice as expensive&lt;br&gt;- Saudi Arabia is about to send more oil to China, even though it's slashed crude supply levels&lt;br&gt;- Chinese online retailer Pinduoduo has a 'hyper-aggressive' culture with hours surpassing a '996' schedule, analysts write&lt;br&gt;- Victoria's Secret is getting slammed by Skims fans online. They're accusing the brand of ripping off Kim Kardashian's campaign.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Google AI Introduces AdaTape: A New AI Approach with a Transformer-based Architecture that Allows for Dynamic Computation in Neural Networks through Adaptive Tape Tokens&lt;br&gt;- ChatGPT and GPT-4 skew the most liberal &amp;mdash; and Meta's LLaMA is the most conservative AI model, a new study says&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Others:&lt;br&gt;- Epigenetic profiling of the D4Z4 locus: Optimization of the protocol ... - John Wiley&lt;br&gt;- How to change your Facebook password to protect your account security&lt;br&gt;- TikTokers are encouraging Gen Z workers to 'manage up' &amp;mdash; the latest workplace trend reaching millions on the platform&lt;br&gt;- The internet just went on a wild quest that could result in floating trains and cheap EVs&lt;br&gt;- A pair of major flying-taxi companies who've been locked in a legal battle for 2 years have buried the hatchet and agreed to work together&lt;br&gt;- Today's Mortgage and Refinance Rates: August 11, 2023 | Rates Increase as Inflation Rises&lt;br&gt;- Top economist David Rosenberg says Bill Ackman's bet against Treasurys could end as badly as his Herbalife wager&lt;br&gt;- IDC Future of X Scorecards: Empowering Enterprises to Achieve Business Outcomes&lt;br&gt;- Google has marked my website as harmful for a file that does not exist&lt;br&gt;- Robotaxis got the green light to operate in San Francisco 24/7&lt;br&gt;- Why is it so hard to create new types of pain relievers?&lt;br&gt;- America’s Social Safety Net Is Broken—Here’s How We Fix It With The Farm Bill&lt;br&gt;- Westone Audio Announces Its New AM Pro X Series Of In-Ear Monitors&lt;br&gt;- Can AI Bring Sales Out Of “The Paleolithic Age Of E-Commerce”?&lt;br&gt;- Why Some Wisconsin Lawmakers and Local Officials Have Changed Their Minds About Letting Undocumented Immigrants Drive&lt;br&gt;- Collective sensemaking within institutions: Control of the COVID‐19 ... - John Wiley&lt;br&gt;- We returned our used mattress to Costco and don't feel bad about it at all. We're just following the policy and plan on returning another one.&lt;br&gt;- My company runs on a 4-day workweek. Our days can be intense but revenue has increased and we're never going back.&lt;br&gt;- The remote work revolution is crashing into a cold reality: Research is finding workers are less productive at home</summary></entry></feed>