<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-20T12:01:04Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 20 Aug 2023 12:01:04</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-20T12:01:04Z</published><updated>2023-08-20T12:01:04Z</updated><id>5cfd1143-a7dc-4afa-aa81-21f5e897fd18</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Zelenskyy says Ukraine is working with Sweden to produce 'cool vehicles' like CV90s: 'Just what is needed at the front'&lt;br&gt;- AMD's 7900 XTX achieves better value for Stable Diffusion than Nvidia RTX 4080&lt;br&gt;- Part 2 - Building a Full Stack Contact Form: Node.js Backend 2023&lt;br&gt;- Part 1 - Full Stack Contact Form: Getting Started &amp; React Frontend 2023&lt;br&gt;- Mousetrap.jl: a GUI library for Julia and C++ that fully wrap GTK4&lt;br&gt;- Unlocking the Power of Context with Google AI: A Showdown Between prefixLM and causalLM in In-Context Learning&lt;br&gt;- Oil companies are approaching influencers and enlisting PR firms to reach younger generations on social media&lt;br&gt;- Apple devices spoofed, Musk eggs on Zuckerberg and Better.com goes public&lt;br&gt;- This AI Paper Introduces A Comprehensive RDF Dataset With Over 26 Billion Triples Covering Scholarly Data Across All Scientific Disciplines&lt;br&gt;- How 100 milliseconds cost Amazon 3 BILLION DOLLARS: Latency, Concurrency and Parallelism&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Grindr has a reputation for its hookup culture, but the company says a quarter of its users are there to network. The CEO says he even hired people through the app.&lt;br&gt;- Self-driving car company Cruise agreed to reduce its driverless fleet by 50% after a spate of recent crashes. San Francisco officials previously pushed for a slower rollout of robotaxis.&lt;br&gt;- Cellebrite asks cops to keep its phone hacking tech ‘hush hush’&lt;br&gt;- Little Rock Nine members slam restrictions on AP African American Studies course in Arkansas&lt;br&gt;- Pornhub's War With a Local Kebab Restaurant Isn't Helping Its Quest for a "Fresh Start"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Unlocking the Power of Context with Google AI: A Showdown Between prefixLM and causalLM in In-Context Learning&lt;br&gt;- People like human art more than AI art - but it's complicated&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Recruitment of chalcone's potential in drug discovery of anti‐SARS ... - John Wiley&lt;br&gt;- W. H. Auden’s 1954 review of The Fellowship of the Ring&lt;br&gt;- How to watch UFC 292: live streams for Sterling vs. O'Malley, Weili vs. Lemos title fights&lt;br&gt;- Sleep ALL NIGHT to Heavy Rain | Black screen, 10 hrs, No ads&lt;br&gt;- Today’s Wordle #792 Hints, Clues And Answer For Sunday, August 20th&lt;br&gt;- Stormzy at All Points East review: after a slow start the rapper gave fans a fast and furious thrill ride - Yahoo Canada Sports&lt;br&gt;- Stormzy at All Points East review: after a slow start the rapper gave fans a fast and furious thrill ride - Yahoo Eurosport UK&lt;br&gt;- The Rimac Nevera Has Broken the Production EV Nurburgring Lap Record&lt;br&gt;- How to watch Messi and Inter Miami vs. Nashville live stream in Leagues Cup final&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine continues to target Moscow with drone strikes, forcing the city to shut down its airports&lt;br&gt;- A judge dismissed a Wisconsin politician's defamation suit against a newspaper, but the legal fees may still shutter the paper.&lt;br&gt;- North Korea's new ICBM looks and works an awful lot like a Russian ICBM, experts say&lt;br&gt;- The 3 Best Record Players for Enjoying Your Favorite Albums - The Wall Street Journal&lt;br&gt;- A new way to identify chiral molecules with light could vastly improve detection&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section highlights advancements in hardware, software, and AI technologies. It showcases the collaboration between Ukraine and Sweden in producing advanced vehicles, the comparison between AMD and Nvidia graphics cards, the development of GUI libraries, and the impact of context in AI learning.&lt;br&gt;- The business section focuses on the intersection of technology and business, discussing the networking aspect of Grindr, the challenges faced by self-driving car company Cruise, the controversy surrounding phone hacking technology, and the restrictions on African American Studies courses.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section explores the capabilities and limitations of AI, including its role in context learning and the preference for human art over AI-generated art.&lt;br&gt;- The other section covers a wide range of topics, including drug discovery, entertainment (UFC fights, music reviews), weather sounds for sleep, puzzles, sports, electric vehicle records, legal disputes, international conflicts, and consumer recommendations (record players).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, the report highlights the rapid advancements in technology, the evolving landscape of business and technology integration, the potential and challenges of AI, and the diverse range of topics covered in various media sources.</summary></entry></feed>