<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-11T08:01:15Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 11 Aug 2023 08:01:15</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-11T08:01:15Z</published><updated>2023-08-11T08:01:15Z</updated><id>79bf2ec5-0e5c-471b-b3ff-8b6634fc3fd8</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- US Special Operations Command is developing a new mini-submarine for transporting SEALs to their targets.&lt;br&gt;- Git scraping allows for tracking changes over time by scraping data to a Git repository.&lt;br&gt;- Designing a DCPU-16 emulator involves incorporating elements of ST and IO.&lt;br&gt;- LG is providing a burn-in warranty for its OLED monitor.&lt;br&gt;- VR technology utilizes hidden forces and sliding screens to enhance the sense of reality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Home Depot released its holiday catalog, with some items already sold out.&lt;br&gt;- Mushroom leather could become a luxury material for brands like Hermès.&lt;br&gt;- Swatch's pride watches are banned in Malaysia due to crackdowns on the LGBTQ+ community.&lt;br&gt;- Amazon is discontinuing several in-house brands that were not widely known.&lt;br&gt;- Fizz, a social network, is gaining popularity on over 80 college campuses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- LK-99 would have had a significant impact on AI development.&lt;br&gt;- Augie allows users to create videos using an AI clone of their own voice.&lt;br&gt;- Rival air taxi startups, Wisk and Archer, settled their trade secret theft lawsuit.&lt;br&gt;- Insiders are showing confidence in Fizz, a social network that has expanded to college campuses.&lt;br&gt;- Idiot students are submitting answers stating "I Am an AI Language Model."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Spain vs. Netherlands Women's World Cup quarter-final can be watched via live stream.&lt;br&gt;- 'Eris' Covid variant EG.5 is driving an increase in cases.&lt;br&gt;- 'The Wire' writer David Simon sparked a debate over NYC traffic cameras in school zones.&lt;br&gt;- Archaeologists discovered a 17th-century 'vampire child' in a Polish graveyard.&lt;br&gt;- A safari led to the discovery of the ancient history of house cats.&lt;br&gt;- President Biden requested $24 billion in aid for Ukraine and other allies.&lt;br&gt;- Open Source Summit Europe 2023 announced its keynote speakers.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers criticize Brazil's Amazon Summit for lacking meaningful goals to protect the forest.&lt;br&gt;- Space station astronauts appear to be breathing concerning substances.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The development of new technologies, such as mini-submarines and AI clones, is advancing the capabilities of various industries.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of AI is evident in both positive and negative ways, from enhancing video creation to students attempting to deceive with AI-generated answers.&lt;br&gt;- Business trends include the rise of sustainable materials like mushroom leather and the growing popularity of social networks on college campuses.&lt;br&gt;- The COVID-19 pandemic continues to drive changes, with new variants and debates over safety measures.&lt;br&gt;- Environmental concerns, such as deforestation in the Amazon, remain significant global issues.&lt;br&gt;- The intersection of technology and archaeology reveals fascinating discoveries about the past.</summary></entry></feed>