<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-08T18:01:02Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Briefing with LLM on Tue, 08 Aug 2023 18:01:02</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-08T18:01:02Z</published><updated>2023-08-08T18:01:02Z</updated><id>0e8c01ae-2f6f-4896-9b12-39918391c038</id><summary type="html">Briefing with LLM on Tue, 08 Aug 2023 16:44:27&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the briefing, several topics were discussed, including the importance of split billing for connectivity management platforms in the automotive sector. It was emphasized that split billing is crucial for these platforms to effectively manage connectivity and ensure seamless communication within vehicles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other news, Jump Financial LLC has acquired shares of 11135 John Wiley &amp; Sons, indicating a significant development in the financial market. Additionally, there is anticipation for advancements in room-temperature superconductors and nuclear fusion, which are expected to have a significant impact on various industries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study has revealed that working from home results in 18% less productivity compared to working in an office, further supporting the argument for return-to-office mandates. However, the essay does not provide any details about the study or its methodology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The essay also mentions an individual's experience of living on a South Carolina island without cars, which creates a unique sense of being transported back in time. Despite the lack of cars, the convenience of services like Instacart is still available.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PayPal's latest venture involves the introduction of a stablecoin pegged to the US dollar, further expanding its presence in the cryptocurrency market. This development showcases the growing interest and adoption of cryptocurrencies in the financial sector.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's July exports have contracted significantly, indicating a challenging external market for the country's manufacturing industry. This decline comes at a time when China needs a strong external market the most.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The essay briefly mentions a parent's efforts to help their 10-year-old child learn coding, highlighting the availability of resources to support children in developing skills for future careers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 80% of Americans believe that it is currently a bad time to buy a house, reflecting the prevailing sentiment regarding the housing market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Rivian electric truck owner shares their experience and mentions some aspects they dislike about the vehicle. Despite these criticisms, the owner still considers it their favorite vehicle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wharton professor Jeremy Siegel has changed his stance on the Federal Reserve's handling of inflation, now expressing a more positive view. He also predicts that the United States will not experience a recession this year.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A YouTube live stream featuring testers repeatedly opening and closing flip smartphones has gained significant attention. The durability of Samsung's phone is praised, while Motorola's phone is reported to be broken.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An analyst predicts that the US government will accumulate $5 billion in debt every day for the next ten years, highlighting the concerning financial situation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla introduces a unique merchandise item, a Cybertruck-inspired cat bed, exclusively available in China. This demonstrates the company's creative approach to branding and marketing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The essay briefly mentions various topics, including the arGPT for Monocle, Aglide, 365 Design Tips, Soula Care, a UK man contracting a bacterial infection from a cat bite, the Richard Scarry Collection on Archive.org, Golay Code (2015), the PC and Internet Revolution in Rural America, and the longest-lasting incandescent light bulbs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The essay concludes by mentioning the addition of themed outfits and quests from the Jujutsu Kaisen anime to the popular game Fortnite. It also briefly discusses Norway's regulation of meta advertisements that monitor users and the development of an iOS app aimed at regaining control over one's life. Lastly, it mentions the use of active Bayesian inference in animal group movements and the success of AI research in revolutionizing protein design through deep learning enhancements.</summary></entry></feed>