<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-16T18:01:29Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 16 Aug 2023 18:01:29</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-16T18:01:29Z</published><updated>2023-08-16T18:01:29Z</updated><id>730b9e17-c026-41c0-9f56-8368360ff92d</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Meta AI’s Humpback! Making a Splash with Self-Alignment of LLMs with Instruction Backtranslation&lt;br&gt;- Tesla supplier CATL unveils battery that can add up to 400km of range in 10 minutes&lt;br&gt;- Presentation: Speed of Apache Pinot at the Cost of Cloud Object Storage with Tiered Storage&lt;br&gt;- Running Apache Flink Applications on AWS KDA: Lessons Learnt at Deliveroo&lt;br&gt;- Gartner Places Generative AI on the Peak of Inflated Expectations on the 2023 Hype Cycle for Emerging Technologies&lt;br&gt;- Fewer than one in 3 households create a budget. Can ChatGPT help?&lt;br&gt;- Ask HN: Why Linux development happens on mailing list instead of Git?&lt;br&gt;- From Task List to Mind Map: Generative AI's Role in Workflow Visualization&lt;br&gt;- Saudi Arabia and the UAE join the global quest for AI supremacy&lt;br&gt;- The Apple Watch X might get a new look in 2024&lt;br&gt;- Wing To Roll Out Drone Delivery For Medical Supplies In Europe&lt;br&gt;- Google Finds It’s Underpaying Many Men as It Addresses Wage Equity&lt;br&gt;- Paid users of X, formerly Twitter, gets a new tab to highlight their posts&lt;br&gt;- X (formerly Twitter) makes X Pro (formerly TweetDeck) a subscriber-only product&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- 'Big Short' investor Michael Burry's new bets against the S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq-100 are no surprise. Here's why.&lt;br&gt;- 2,000 barnacle-covered wine bottles worth hundreds of thousands of dollars destroyed after California company illegally aged them in the ocean&lt;br&gt;- Margot Robbie will reportedly earn $50 million in salary and box office bonuses for 'Barbie'&lt;br&gt;- Have your eye on a Tesla? It just got $10,000 cheaper to buy a Model S or Model X.&lt;br&gt;- A 200% EV IPO bonanza has boosted the wealth of Vietnam's wealthiest person eightfold to over $44 billion&lt;br&gt;- Judge blocks Internet Archive from sharing copyrighted books - The Seattle Times&lt;br&gt;- A bartender is going viral on TikTok for jokingly saying he'd snub a customer for a regular patron who 'tips 50% every time'&lt;br&gt;- Re-entering the world of tech after a career break: ‘virtual’ Vapasi program&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Meta AI’s Humpback! Making a Splash with Self-Alignment of LLMs with Instruction Backtranslation&lt;br&gt;- Gartner Places Generative AI on the Peak of Inflated Expectations on the 2023 Hype Cycle for Emerging Technologies&lt;br&gt;- Fewer than one in 3 households create a budget. Can ChatGPT help?&lt;br&gt;- From Task List to Mind Map: Generative AI's Role in Workflow Visualization&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Free Australia vs. England live stream: How to watch the Women's World Cup match online from anywhere&lt;br&gt;- Russia's top general Sergei Shoigu bragged that the Kremlin's war in Ukraine has 'debunked many myths' that NATO weapons and military standards are superior&lt;br&gt;- How to change your Facebook cover photo on desktop or mobile&lt;br&gt;- Why is it not recommended to use email registration in China?&lt;br&gt;- Why is it not recommended to use email registration in China?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- In the tech category, there is a focus on AI advancements, such as self-alignment of LLMs and generative AI's role in workflow visualization. There are also updates on companies like Tesla and Google addressing wage equity.&lt;br&gt;- The business category covers a range of topics, including investments, destroyed wine bottles, celebrity earnings, and the impact of EV IPOs. There are also discussions on copyright issues and the challenges of re-entering the tech industry after a career break.&lt;br&gt;- The AI category delves deeper into the advancements and expectations surrounding generative AI, with a specific focus on its potential role in workflow visualization and household budgeting.&lt;br&gt;- The other category includes topics like sports streaming, geopolitical conflicts, social media tips, and the challenges of email registration in China.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, the report highlights the ongoing developments in the tech industry, the various aspects of the business world, the advancements and potential of AI, and the diverse range of topics covered in other categories.</summary></entry></feed>