<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-19T20:02:22Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 19 Nov 2023 20:02:22</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-19T20:02:22Z</published><updated>2023-11-19T20:02:22Z</updated><id>f12762e1-488d-4674-83f7-6ba4fdf9dab0</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Meta splits Responsible AI team between generative AI and AI infrastructure&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's internal drama unfolds as investors and employees push for Altman's return&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk became so paranoid he banned meetings of more than 2 Twitter employees, fearing mutiny or sabotage, author says&lt;br&gt;- See inside Nvidia's giant 'Voyager' HQ — a futuristic office where work meets nature&lt;br&gt;- Unlocking Efficiency: A Deep Dive into Redis as an In-Memory Datastore&lt;br&gt;- Boston experimented with using generative AI for governing. It went surprisingly well&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI’s custom GPTs: Everything you need to know about how to use them and build your own&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI is 'optimistic' that it can bring ousted CEO Sam Altman and other senior figures back, The Information reported&lt;br&gt;- Boeing 787 capable of carrying 300 passengers lands in Antarctica in world first&lt;br&gt;- Meta Unveils Emu Video and Emu Edit: Pioneering Advances in Text-to-Video Generation and Precision Image Editing&lt;br&gt;- London’s O2 Will Host The ‘League Of Legends’ Worlds Final In 2024&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Baby boomers got rich off real estate and they are in perfect position to do it again&lt;br&gt;- Airlines will make a record $118 billion in extra fees this year—their websites are designed to get you to pay&lt;br&gt;- Used car prices are finally falling. Here are 6 tips to help make sure you don't pay too much.&lt;br&gt;- LinkedIn tried censorship against me in the worst possible way. No More Joke.&lt;br&gt;- The history of Cathedral Canyon: From dream to dust - Las Vegas Review-Journal&lt;br&gt;- Greg James and Jo Wiley share Bridgwater Christmas lights viral clip - Bridgwater Mercury&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Meta splits Responsible AI team between generative AI and AI infrastructure&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's internal drama unfolds as investors and employees push for Altman's return&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk became so paranoid he banned meetings of more than 2 Twitter employees, fearing mutiny or sabotage, author says&lt;br&gt;- Boston experimented with using generative AI for governing. It went surprisingly well&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI’s custom GPTs: Everything you need to know about how to use them and build your own&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI is 'optimistic' that it can bring ousted CEO Sam Altman and other senior figures back, The Information reported&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- College football: Aggies win big; Longhorns keep playoff hopes alive - Caller Times&lt;br&gt;- Jared Wiley sets TCU record on Senior Day in 42-17 victory over Baylor - Yahoo Movies Canada&lt;br&gt;- Mr. John W. Wiley Obituary - The Beaver County Times - The Times&lt;br&gt;- Influenza vaccination and major cardiovascular risk: a systematic ... - Nature.com&lt;br&gt;- Trump told a rally his wife Melania didn't believe claims that he engaged in 'golden showers' with sex workers because he is a 'germaphobe'&lt;br&gt;- I moved to Portugal after falling in love with my tour guide. It was a lonely and humbling experience.&lt;br&gt;- India and Australia World Cup final shatters streaming records on Hotstar&lt;br&gt;- Jared Wiley, Emani Bailey step up for TCU in win vs. Baylor - The Dallas Morning News&lt;br&gt;- Tirrell Wiley Obituary - Funerals by T. S. Warden - Jacksonville - 2023 - Legacy.com&lt;br&gt;- Florida scientists are giving coral IVF treatments to help bolster dying reef&lt;br&gt;- A Russian general who was critical of the army's operation was found dead&lt;br&gt;- Americans' Trust in Scientists, Positive Views of Science Continue to Decline&lt;br&gt;- 5 Common CSS Mistakes: What to Avoid for Clean &amp; Efficient Code | Part 1&lt;br&gt;- The history of Cathedral Canyon: From dream to dust - Las Vegas Review-Journal&lt;br&gt;- Greg James and Jo Wiley share Bridgwater Christmas lights viral clip - Bridgwater Mercury&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is experiencing internal drama and leadership changes, particularly in companies like Meta and OpenAI.&lt;br&gt;- AI is being used in various fields, including generative AI for governing and text-to-video generation.&lt;br&gt;- Business trends include the rise of extra fees in the airline industry and falling used car prices.&lt;br&gt;- College football and sports achievements are also highlighted.&lt;br&gt;- Other topics range from obituaries to political statements and scientific developments.</summary></entry></feed>