<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-10T20:02:23Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 10 Sep 2023 20:02:23</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-10T20:02:23Z</published><updated>2023-09-10T20:02:23Z</updated><id>2378ae3d-63ab-40a3-9cbe-7bc81768c3b2</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Architects are transforming empty NYC offices into apartments by cutting holes in skyscrapers and adding more floors.&lt;br&gt;- A second Nikola electric semi-truck caught fire during tests.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from Cornell and Tel Aviv introduce Doppelgangers, a method to disambiguate images of similar structures.&lt;br&gt;- AI21 Labs and Imbue AI raise triple-digit millions for more capable LLMs.&lt;br&gt;- eBay's new AI app generates listings based only on product photos.&lt;br&gt;- Incandescent light bulbs are largely banned, prompting one fan to stockpile 3,500 bulbs.&lt;br&gt;- Bill Ackman's first stock was Wells Fargo, influenced by Warren Buffett.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- If all the food wasted in the US came from a single farm, it would be the size of California and New York combined.&lt;br&gt;- A Gen Xer with $145,000 in student debt had to sell items on eBay to afford loan payments.&lt;br&gt;- Cash-strapped New Yorkers are moving to Jersey City.&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage interest rates are high ahead of this week's CPI report.&lt;br&gt;- The United Auto Workers union is poised to strike major US car makers.&lt;br&gt;- Saudi Arabia is investing billions in sports, tech, and more for a post-oil world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers are developing methods to disambiguate images of similar structures.&lt;br&gt;- AI21 Labs and Imbue AI have raised significant funding for more capable LLMs.&lt;br&gt;- eBay has introduced an AI app that generates listings based on product photos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The real estate market in NYC is adapting to the changing needs of residents by repurposing office spaces into residential units.&lt;br&gt;- Student debt continues to burden individuals, forcing them to find creative ways to make loan payments.&lt;br&gt;- Economic and political concerns are driving individuals to relocate to more affordable and politically aligned areas.&lt;br&gt;- Electric vehicle companies like Nikola are facing challenges with their vehicles catching fire during testing.&lt;br&gt;- The demand for cybersecurity professionals is high, with individuals able to secure well-paying jobs after completing boot camps.&lt;br&gt;- The release of new Apple products, such as the iPhone 15, generates significant anticipation and interest.&lt;br&gt;- The stock market is uncertain, with experts divided on whether there will be gains or losses.&lt;br&gt;- International events, such as the FIBA World Cup final, attract global attention and interest.&lt;br&gt;- The discovery of a large lithium cache in the US has the potential to impact the global lithium market.&lt;br&gt;- The ban on incandescent light bulbs has led to stockpiling by enthusiasts.&lt;br&gt;- The influence of prominent investors, such as Warren Buffett, can shape investment decisions.&lt;br&gt;- Wealth distribution varies across cities, with some having a higher concentration of ultra-wealthy individuals.&lt;br&gt;- Countries like Saudi Arabia are diversifying their investments to prepare for a post-oil future.&lt;br&gt;- Philanthropists like Priscilla Chan are making significant contributions to education and society.&lt;br&gt;- Poland is expanding its military to become a dominant force in Europe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;This report covers a range of topics including real estate, student debt, relocation, electric vehicles, cybersecurity, Apple products, the stock market, international sports events, natural resources, lighting regulations, investment decisions, wealth distribution, diversification, philanthropy, and military expansion. Key insights include the adaptation of NYC real estate, the challenges of student debt, the impact of economic and political concerns on relocation, the issues faced by electric vehicle companies, the demand for cybersecurity professionals, the anticipation surrounding Apple product launches, the uncertainty in the stock market, the global interest in sports events, the potential impact of lithium discoveries, the effects of lighting regulations, the influence of prominent investors, the concentration of wealth in certain cities, the diversification efforts of countries like Saudi Arabia, the philanthropic contributions of individuals like Priscilla Chan, and the military expansion of Poland.</summary></entry></feed>