<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-14T23:08:49Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 14 Aug 2023 23:08:49</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-14T23:08:49Z</published><updated>2023-08-14T23:08:49Z</updated><id>eaebe00e-1474-4861-a361-24b7278541b4</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- ChatGPT has a style over substance trick that researchers found to dupe people into thinking it's smart.&lt;br&gt;- Language Models Can Gain Impressive Knowledge From Surface-Form Text - Like How To Draw.&lt;br&gt;- Generative AI's Dark Side: How It's The Perfect Tool For Hackers To Spread Malware.&lt;br&gt;- Opening Up To Open Source: Why AI Needs To Become A Community Affair.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- AMC plunges 35% on fears the meme stock will be diluted by conversion of APE units.&lt;br&gt;- US stocks edge lower as August slump continues amid China property woes.&lt;br&gt;- Californians are fleeing to Texas, where homes and the cost of living are cheaper.&lt;br&gt;- Struggling property developer Country Garden's shares hit record low after suspending bond trading amid a severe cash crunch.&lt;br&gt;- Ford hires ex-Apple TV Plus chief Peter Stern to lead the customer software team.&lt;br&gt;- Why Finance Leaders In Midsize Businesses Are Stepping Up Cybersecurity Efforts.&lt;br&gt;- How French Esports Team Karmine Corp Plans To Sell Out An Arena.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- ChatGPT has a style over substance trick that researchers found to dupe people into thinking it's smart.&lt;br&gt;- Language Models Can Gain Impressive Knowledge From Surface-Form Text - Like How To Draw.&lt;br&gt;- Generative AI's Dark Side: How It's The Perfect Tool For Hackers To Spread Malware.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- A United Airlines pilot on vacation in Hawaii volunteered to fly a plane from Maui to mainland US to help 300 people escape the fire.&lt;br&gt;- A leading Ukrainian doctor says mines second only to artillery as a cause of soldier injuries.&lt;br&gt;- W. Jason Morgan, scientist at forefront of plate tectonics theory, has died.&lt;br&gt;- Police raid of a Kansas newsroom raises alarms about violations of press freedom.&lt;br&gt;- Hayden Christensen Is Doing A Great ‘Clone Wars Voice’ For ‘Ahsoka’ In New Trailer.&lt;br&gt;- This Week’s New Games, Game Pass And PS Plus Additions, And Free Games On Prime Gaming And Epic Games Store.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- In the tech category, the use of AI and its potential risks are highlighted, such as the deceptive nature of ChatGPT and the potential for generative AI to be used for spreading malware.&lt;br&gt;- The business category covers various topics, including the stock market performance, real estate trends, and corporate hires. It also emphasizes the importance of cybersecurity efforts for finance leaders in midsize businesses.&lt;br&gt;- The other category includes diverse topics, ranging from a pilot's heroic act to the impact of mines on soldier injuries. It also mentions the passing of a prominent scientist and concerns about press freedom.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report showcases the intersection of technology, business, and other aspects of life, highlighting key developments and insights in each category.</summary></entry></feed>