<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-14T16:01:20Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:01:20</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-14T16:01:20Z</published><updated>2023-08-14T16:01:20Z</updated><id>f0b04363-135f-4767-a908-e4798a0e88e9</id><summary type="html">Report: Tech and Business News Highlights&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. India Mobile Phone Cumulative Production Crosses 2 Billion Units Under ‘Make in India’ Initiative&lt;br&gt;- India has achieved a significant milestone in mobile phone production under the 'Make in India' initiative, with over 2 billion units produced.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the success of India's efforts to promote local manufacturing and reduce dependence on imports.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. South Korea's SK Telecom bets big on AI with $100 million investment in Anthropic&lt;br&gt;- SK Telecom, a leading South Korean telecommunications company, has invested $100 million in Anthropic, an AI research company.&lt;br&gt;- This investment reflects the growing importance of AI in various industries and SK Telecom's commitment to staying at the forefront of technological advancements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. ResearchGate and Wiley expand partnership to encompass majority...&lt;br&gt;- ResearchGate, a social networking site for scientists and researchers, has expanded its partnership with Wiley, a global publishing company.&lt;br&gt;- This collaboration aims to enhance the sharing and dissemination of research findings, benefiting the scientific community as a whole.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Watch the shocking moment pilots ejected from a Soviet-era fighter jet before it crashed at a Michigan air show&lt;br&gt;- A Soviet-era fighter jet crashed at a Michigan air show, but the pilots managed to eject safely.&lt;br&gt;- This incident highlights the risks associated with aviation and the importance of safety measures.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. 'Girl Math' is the latest financial trend going viral on TikTok...&lt;br&gt;- 'Girl Math' is a viral trend on TikTok where users redefine their approach to financial decisions.&lt;br&gt;- This trend emphasizes the importance of mindful spending and considering the long-term value of purchases.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The 'Make in India' initiative has been successful in promoting local manufacturing and reducing import dependence in the mobile phone industry.&lt;br&gt;- SK Telecom's investment in Anthropic reflects the increasing significance of AI in various sectors, indicating a growing trend towards AI adoption.&lt;br&gt;- The partnership between ResearchGate and Wiley demonstrates the importance of collaboration in advancing scientific research and knowledge sharing.&lt;br&gt;- The incident at the Michigan air show highlights the importance of safety protocols in aviation.&lt;br&gt;- The 'Girl Math' trend on TikTok reflects a shift in mindset towards more conscious spending and financial decision-making.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech and business news highlights indicate the rapid advancements in AI technology and its integration into various industries.&lt;br&gt;- Collaboration and partnerships play a crucial role in advancing research and knowledge sharing.&lt;br&gt;- Safety measures and protocols remain essential in high-risk industries like aviation.&lt;br&gt;- Social media platforms like TikTok continue to influence trends and shape consumer behavior.&lt;br&gt;- The 'Make in India' initiative has been successful in promoting local manufacturing and reducing import dependence in the mobile phone industry.</summary></entry></feed>