<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-08T20:01:53Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 08 Jan 2024 20:01:53</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-08T20:01:53Z</published><updated>2024-01-08T20:01:53Z</updated><id>3d542328-2a58-48ce-9849-05e39a6a3ed7</id><summary type="html">In recent news, an Alaska Airlines flight experienced a terrifying incident when a chunk of its fuselage was lost mid-flight. Passengers on board described the experience as being inside a gas canister, highlighting the fear and panic that ensued. In another report, it has been revealed that some jobseekers from Generation Z are bringing their parents to interviews, which is causing employers to be turned off. A survey conducted on this matter found that such behavior is not well-received by employers. Additionally, Alaska Airlines has been forced to cancel 230 flights due to the grounding of the 737 Max 9 aircraft following a mid-flight door blowout. This incident has raised concerns about the safety of the aircraft model. In the world of art, an artist for the popular game 'Magic: The Gathering' has decided to quit after the publisher admitted to using AI-generated art in recent images. This revelation has sparked a debate about the role of artificial intelligence in creative industries. On a lighter note, music enthusiasts are sharing their favorite songs for Music Monday, with this week's theme being "Good Memories Edition." Lastly, a federal agency has accused managers at Checkers restaurants in Alabama of unethical practices, alleging that they clocked staff out mid-shift and altered their timecards to pay them less. This claim raises concerns about workers' rights and fair treatment in the restaurant industry.</summary></entry></feed>