<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-14T08:04:12Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 14 Sep 2023 08:04:12</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-14T08:04:12Z</published><updated>2023-09-14T08:04:12Z</updated><id>1a40a026-cdf8-47bb-866a-4e4349f3f9bd</id><summary type="html">New Book in Chinese published in 2023 | CSUF News - CSUF News&lt;br&gt;- This news article announces the publication of a new book in Chinese in 2023. No further information is provided.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Al Gore and Lila Preston ask the tough questions in their firm’s new climate report&lt;br&gt;- Al Gore and Lila Preston have released a new climate report that addresses challenging questions related to climate change.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;UN Cybercrime Treaty Talks End Without Consensus on Scope And Deep Divides About Surveillance Powers&lt;br&gt;- The United Nations' talks on a cybercrime treaty have concluded without reaching a consensus on the scope of the treaty and have revealed significant divisions regarding surveillance powers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today’s New Moon Sets-Up A Rare, Risky ‘Ring Of Fire’ Solar Eclipse&lt;br&gt;- The occurrence of a new moon sets the stage for a rare and risky "Ring of Fire" solar eclipse.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft Testing GPT-4-Powered Generative Text Feature for Edge Browser (Will Comments Ever Be The Same?)&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft is currently testing a generative text feature powered by GPT-4 for its Edge browser. This feature may have implications for online comments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK Government Relents (for Now) on Demanding Broken Encryption from WhatsApp and iMessage&lt;br&gt;- The UK government has temporarily backed down from its demand for broken encryption from messaging platforms like WhatsApp and iMessage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Average American savings balance by age, household size, and education level&lt;br&gt;- This content provides information on the average savings balance of Americans based on age, household size, and education level.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A long list of tech companies are rushing to give themselves the right to use people's data to train AI&lt;br&gt;- Numerous tech companies are quickly seeking permission to use individuals' data for the purpose of training artificial intelligence systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk chalked up his baseless tweet about Nancy Pelosi's husband to a tendency to post 'some things that are going to be stupid'&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk attributed his baseless tweet about Nancy Pelosi's husband to his tendency to post things that may be considered stupid.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Update everything: Chrome, Firefox, Brave, and Edge just patched a big flaw&lt;br&gt;- Major web browsers like Chrome, Firefox, Brave, and Edge have released updates to address a significant flaw.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;RustRover is a New Standalone IDE for Rust from JetBrains&lt;br&gt;- JetBrains has developed a new standalone integrated development environment (IDE) called RustRover specifically for the Rust programming language.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a third of US pro sports teams are tied to private equity&lt;br&gt;- Over 33% of professional sports teams in the United States have connections to private equity firms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EFF to Michigan Court: Governments Shouldn’t Be Allowed to Use a Drone to Spy on You Without a Warrant&lt;br&gt;- The Electronic Frontier Foundation (EFF) has argued in a Michigan court that governments should not be permitted to conduct warrantless surveillance using drones.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Subsidies Broke Public EV Charging; $100M In New Ones Won’t Fix It&lt;br&gt;- The provision of subsidies has negatively impacted public electric vehicle (EV) charging infrastructure, and an additional $100 million in subsidies is unlikely to resolve the issue.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Gates, Elon Musk and Mark Zuckerberg are meeting in Washington to discuss future AI regulations - CBS Miami&lt;br&gt;- Prominent figures such as Bill Gates, Elon Musk, and Mark Zuckerberg are convening in Washington to discuss the regulation of artificial intelligence (AI) in the future.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk, Mark Zuckerberg, Bill Gates and other tech names head to Washington for a closed-door meeting on policing AI&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk, Mark Zuckerberg, Bill Gates, and other influential figures in the tech industry are attending a closed-door meeting in Washington to discuss the regulation of AI in law enforcement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin is so paranoid that he has armed divers swimming around his private beach looking for assassins, an ex-security officer says&lt;br&gt;- According to a former security officer, Russian President Vladimir Putin is extremely paranoid and employs armed divers to patrol his private beach in search of potential assassins.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mitch McConnell left Mitt Romney on read after Romney texted him before January 6 about concerns mobs would burn down McConnell's home and storm the Capitol: book&lt;br&gt;- According to a new book, Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell ignored a text message from Senator Mitt Romney expressing concerns about the January 6th events at the Capitol.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attack on Russian warships at a Black Sea naval base shows Ukraine's big offensive is more than meets the eye and making Crimea 'untenable' for Moscow's forces&lt;br&gt;- An attack on Russian warships at a Black Sea naval base indicates that Ukraine's offensive is more significant than initially perceived and is making the Crimean region difficult for Moscow's forces to maintain.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans laughed at Trump behind his back after he rambled during a Senate luncheon, according to Mitt Romney's new tell-all book&lt;br&gt;- Mitt Romney's tell-all book claims that Republicans mocked former President Donald Trump behind his back when he rambled during a Senate luncheon.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;List: All the weapons and ammunition provided to Ukraine by the US after Russia's invasion&lt;br&gt;- This content provides a list of the weapons and ammunition supplied by the United States to Ukraine following Russia's invasion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matt Gaetz can count on some progressives' support as he threatens to force a vote on ousting Kevin McCarthy&lt;br&gt;- Representative Matt Gaetz has garnered support from some progressives as he threatens to initiate a vote to remove Kevin McCarthy from his position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;US debt risks a 'slow-motion collision' with the fight against inflation, Goldman Sachs says&lt;br&gt;- Goldman Sachs warns that the increasing US debt poses a potential collision with efforts to combat inflation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mitch McConnell told Mitt Romney that Trump is an 'idiot' who 'doesn't think when he says things:' book&lt;br&gt;- According to a book, Mitch McConnell referred to Donald Trump as an "idiot" who speaks without thinking during a conversation with Mitt Romney.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;iPhone 12 emits too much radiation, France says. It rules Apple must take it off the market.&lt;br&gt;- France has determined that the iPhone 12 emits excessive radiation and has mandated that Apple remove it from the market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How much YouTube pays per view and what you can expect to earn for every 1,000 views&lt;br&gt;- This content provides information on the amount YouTube pays per view and the potential earnings for every 1,000 views.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;US stocks trade mixed as investors assess Fed outlook after August CPI comes in hotter than expected&lt;br&gt;- US stocks are experiencing mixed trading as investors evaluate the Federal Reserve's outlook following the release of higher-than-expected August Consumer Price Index (CPI) data.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creator of Stoner Cats animated series starring Ashton Kutcher and Mila Kunis is fined by SEC for selling NFTs&lt;br&gt;- The creator of the animated series "Stoner Cats," featuring Ashton Kutcher and Mila Kunis, has been fined by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for selling non-fungible tokens (NFTs).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Control USB power on a port by port basis on some USB hubs&lt;br&gt;- Certain USB hubs allow for the control of USB power on a port-by-port basis.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creating G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero Volume 13 by Steel City Publishing, LLC&lt;br&gt;- Steel City Publishing, LLC has released Volume 13 of the book series "Creating G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero." No further information is provided.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The climate report by Al Gore and Lila Preston highlights the importance of addressing challenging questions related to climate change.&lt;br&gt;- The lack of consensus on the scope of the UN cybercrime treaty and divisions regarding surveillance powers indicate the complexities surrounding international cybercrime regulations.&lt;br&gt;- The occurrence of a rare solar eclipse and the testing of GPT-4-powered generative text feature for web browsers are notable developments in the tech field.&lt;br&gt;- The UK government's temporary retreat from demanding broken encryption from messaging platforms reflects the ongoing debate on privacy and security.&lt;br&gt;- The average American savings balance and the rush of tech companies to utilize personal data for AI training raise concerns about privacy and data protection.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's tendency to post controversial tweets and the need for software updates to address security flaws in popular web browsers demonstrate the influence and impact of prominent figures and technology on society.&lt;br&gt;- The meetings involving Bill Gates, Elon Musk, Mark Zuckerberg, and other tech leaders in Washington highlight the growing importance of AI regulation and its potential implications.&lt;br&gt;- The revelations about Russian President Vladimir Putin's security measures and the internal dynamics within the Republican party shed light on the complexities of international politics and domestic politics in the United States.&lt;br&gt;- The ongoing conflict between Ukraine and Russia, the potential ousting of Kevin McCarthy, and the impact of US debt on inflation reflect significant geopolitical and economic challenges.&lt;br&gt;- France's ruling on the iPhone 12's radiation emissions and the SEC's actions against the creator of "Stoner Cats" NFTs demonstrate the intersection of technology, regulation, and consumer protection.&lt;br&gt;- The information on YouTube earnings and the control of USB power on specific ports provide insights into the digital content industry and technological capabilities.</summary></entry></feed>