<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-04T08:03:32Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:03:32</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-04T08:03:32Z</published><updated>2023-11-04T08:03:32Z</updated><id>4c6937b7-2f42-4486-827c-a2451a2e29d9</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft is extending firmware updates for many Surface PCs to at least six years.&lt;br&gt;- IBM has introduced Watsonx Code Assistant, an AI-powered tool to revolutionize enterprise coding.&lt;br&gt;- GitInsights is a tool that provides a weekly summary email of a team's GitHub activity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Capital One has opened a new airport lounge in Denver, offering free access to some credit cardholders.&lt;br&gt;- Amazon delivery drivers can earn up to $40,000 per year, along with benefits.&lt;br&gt;- The BRICS countries have the potential to challenge the dominance of the US dollar in the global economy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- IBM's Watsonx Code Assistant utilizes AI to assist with enterprise coding.&lt;br&gt;- The EU is attempting to gain new powers to intercept encrypted web traffic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Pomerantz Law Firm is investigating claims related to shareholder alerts.&lt;br&gt;- A former North Bergen official has changed their plea deal and may avoid prison time.&lt;br&gt;- Sika deer distribution and its impact on bioclimatic conditions are being studied.&lt;br&gt;- Mark Meadows' conservative book publisher is suing him for alleged lies in his memoir.&lt;br&gt;- Sam Bankman-Fried is facing potential prison time.&lt;br&gt;- Jeff Bezos is relocating to Miami, joining an exclusive neighborhood known as the "billionaire bunker."&lt;br&gt;- Swedish fintech company Klarna has reached an agreement with workers, avoiding a strike.&lt;br&gt;- Cup Noodles is switching to new microwave-safe packaging.&lt;br&gt;- Daylight saving time can disrupt sleep patterns.&lt;br&gt;- Huntley District 158 has appointed Dana Wiley to the board.&lt;br&gt;- Vivian Gamble's obituary has been published.&lt;br&gt;- The FDA has proposed banning brominated vegetable oil due to safety concerns.&lt;br&gt;- The best gaming chairs, iPhone 15 Pro deals, TVs, and Black Friday mattress deals are highlighted.&lt;br&gt;- US stocks have experienced a significant rally following a positive jobs report.&lt;br&gt;- The judge in Donald Trump's fraud trial has expanded the gag order due to threats.</summary></entry></feed>