<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-18T20:02:01Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 18 Nov 2023 20:02:01</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-18T20:02:01Z</published><updated>2023-11-18T20:02:01Z</updated><id>8dcd4bae-b9d0-4f84-8a5c-2e649539c25b</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- A YouTuber risked taking his Tesla through a 2-day dead zone during a road trip to Alaska&lt;br&gt;- Chinese electric car maker BYD is about to steal Tesla's crown. Here's why it's winning the race.&lt;br&gt;- After the driver of a Tesla in Autopilot suffered a medical emergency, his 10-year-old son was reportedly able to get the car off the freeway&lt;br&gt;- You shouldn’t be driving over 100 mph—and your car shouldn’t let you&lt;br&gt;- SpaceX Starship launch: Here’s how to watch the rocket’s second flight test&lt;br&gt;- Tech Glitch Makes People Think Sam Altman Is Running For President&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Coshocton company provided tote bags to conference attendees - Coshocton Tribune&lt;br&gt;- Bragar Eagel &amp; Squire, P.C. Is Investigating Wiley, and R1 RCM and ... - StreetInsider.com&lt;br&gt;- New York’s comptroller says Citi Bike service is lacking in low-income areas. Citi Bike disagrees&lt;br&gt;- A hedge fund exec is funding hunts for treasures in shipwrecks at the bottom of the ocean&lt;br&gt;- New York may ban noncompete employment agreements and Wall Street is not happy&lt;br&gt;- Table of Experts: Unlocking capital for growth and innovation ... - The Business Journals&lt;br&gt;- Monroe County Sheriff's Office makes two arrests after finding ... - Martins Ferry Times Leader&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Sacha Baron Cohen told TikTok bosses that the platform was creating the 'biggest antisemitic movement since the Nazis'&lt;br&gt;- Darren Aronofsky is the perfect director for A24’s Elon Musk biopic. Now comes the hard part&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- 'Workaholic' dad told his eight-year-old son has died while on ... - The Mirror&lt;br&gt;- Comprehensive study of allergenic tree species: Palynological ... - John Wiley&lt;br&gt;- College football | Akron Zips lose in OT at Eastern Michigan - Akron Beacon Journal&lt;br&gt;- Patrick Dai denied bail in charges stemming from threats at Cornell - USA TODAY&lt;br&gt;- Linda Robinson Obituary - O. W. Wiley Mortuary - Houston - 2023 - Legacy.com&lt;br&gt;- Here's why one Gen Xer likes working with his Gen Z colleagues&lt;br&gt;- Most Americans are oblivious to 'forever chemicals' and risks, research finds&lt;br&gt;- Sailors playing heavy metal to scare killer whales may be putting a target on their backs by telling the orcas exactly where to find them&lt;br&gt;- “Devastated”: Family seeks justice after man killed while sleeping in Lawrenceville home - Yahoo News&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section highlights various developments in the automotive industry, including Tesla's Autopilot feature and the competition from Chinese electric car maker BYD. It also discusses the importance of car safety features and the potential risks of driving at high speeds.&lt;br&gt;- The business section covers a range of topics, from company investigations to potential policy changes. It also explores the world of hedge funds and their investments in shipwrecks. The section highlights the importance of access to capital for growth and innovation.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section focuses on the impact of social media platforms and the potential for creating harmful movements. It also discusses the potential for a biopic on Elon Musk and the challenges of finding the right director.&lt;br&gt;- The other section includes a mix of news stories, from personal tragedies to sports updates and environmental risks. It highlights the importance of awareness and justice in various situations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, the report provides insights into different industries and their current developments, showcasing the intersection of technology, business, AI, and other areas of interest. It emphasizes the need for safety, access to capital, and responsible use of technology and social media.</summary></entry></feed>