<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-10T20:01:46Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 10 Jan 2024 20:01:46</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-10T20:01:46Z</published><updated>2024-01-10T20:01:46Z</updated><id>2a6df9eb-c3a2-4470-a5c3-ffaaa427df88</id><summary type="html">In recent news, concerns have been raised about the quality of clean energy jobs at a solar company on Long Island due to allegations of union-busting. This development has sparked worries about the treatment of workers in the renewable energy sector, which is crucial for combating climate change. Meanwhile, Avi Schiffmann's Tab AI necklace has managed to raise an impressive $1.9 million in funding. The necklace aims to replace the concept of God by providing users with an artificial intelligence companion. This innovative project has garnered significant attention and support. Additionally, a review paper delves into the design secrets that make airplanes less susceptible to catching fire. This research is essential for enhancing aviation safety and preventing accidents. Furthermore, there is growing interest in the potential of deep learning to revolutionize phase recovery in computational imaging. A review paper explores the impact and future implications of this technology, highlighting its potential to transform the field. Lastly, language-learning platform Duolingo has made the decision to lay off workers as it increasingly relies on AI tools to carry out various tasks. This shift towards automation raises questions about the future of human employment and the role of artificial intelligence in the workforce.</summary></entry></feed>