<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-22T20:02:22Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 22 Aug 2023 20:02:22</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-22T20:02:22Z</published><updated>2023-08-22T20:02:22Z</updated><id>594777ee-8dc1-4e1f-9143-a4bdb35ad6d8</id><summary type="html">Report: Language Translation and Insights&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Midjourney has released a new feature called "inpainting" which allows users to customize AI-generated images after they are generated.&lt;br&gt;- Golem has unveiled a resilient computing platform for serverless workers using a WebAssembly component model.&lt;br&gt;- Inside the V8 Engine: A look into the core of Chrome Browser's performance.&lt;br&gt;- Real-Time Updates with Server-Sent Events (SSE): A practical guide with code examples.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech industry continues to innovate and develop new technologies. AI advancements, resilient computing platforms, and real-time updates are all contributing to the evolution of technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk plans to remove news headlines from his posts, displaying only images, as he believes it looks better.&lt;br&gt;- Americans now need to spend 43% of their income to afford a home due to surging mortgage rates.&lt;br&gt;- A millennial manager quit their job over the return to office policy, highlighting the challenges of adapting to new work environments.&lt;br&gt;- Home Depot's popular 12-foot skeleton is already sold out online for the rest of the year.&lt;br&gt;- Amazon is facing accusations of calling the police on employees in a union-busting case.&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway owns over $1 trillion in assets, surpassing the combined value of Microsoft, Alphabet, and Meta.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business landscape is constantly changing, with challenges such as rising housing costs, workplace policies, and labor disputes. However, successful companies like Home Depot and Berkshire Hathaway continue to thrive.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk draws inspiration from science fiction stories in shaping his business choices.&lt;br&gt;- Three easy ways to use AI for increased productivity at work, according to an AI consultant.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: AI is becoming increasingly integrated into various industries, offering opportunities for improved productivity and decision-making. Elon Musk's interest in science fiction demonstrates the influence of imagination and creativity on technological advancements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Argentina's economist suggests that a recession, rather than dollarization, is needed to address the peso crash.&lt;br&gt;- Instagram is introducing a chronological feed for Reels and Stories in Europe.&lt;br&gt;- Russia's use of US tech to build cruise missiles for potential attacks on Ukraine despite sanctions is a concerning development.&lt;br&gt;- New York to Paris in 90 minutes? A startup aims to make it happen.&lt;br&gt;- Wall Street's premature declaration of victory overlooks the potential for a US recession.&lt;br&gt;- Costco's history and growth as a wholesale warehouse and major retailer.&lt;br&gt;- The life and career of Jeff Bezos, the founder of Amazon.&lt;br&gt;- A Udemy instructor shares their success in selling courses for virtual assistants.&lt;br&gt;- The first large cruise ship built in China, complete with a water park and brewery, will set sail this year.&lt;br&gt;- Mexico has surpassed China as America's top global trade partner.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The global landscape encompasses various economic, political, and technological developments. From economic challenges in Argentina to the growth of major retailers like Costco, these diverse topics highlight the interconnectedness of the world. Mexico's rise as a trade partner also showcases the shifting dynamics in global trade relationships.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;This report covers a range of topics including tech advancements, business updates, AI integration, and global developments. Key insights include the continuous innovation in the tech industry, the challenges and opportunities in the business world, the growing influence of AI, and the interconnectedness of the global landscape. These insights provide a comprehensive overview of the current trends and developments across various sectors.</summary></entry></feed>