<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-21T14:02:10Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 21 Aug 2023 14:02:10</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-21T14:02:10Z</published><updated>2023-08-21T14:02:10Z</updated><id>513a597b-fd78-41ac-8520-8e22e1e61319</id><summary type="html">Russia's so desperate to get its billionaires and their massive wealth back that it just threatened to seize the assets of an oligarch worth $13 billion&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Russia is desperate to regain the wealth of its billionaires and has threatened to seize the assets of a specific oligarch worth $13 billion.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This action by Russia highlights the government's determination to reclaim the wealth of its billionaires, potentially impacting the business landscape and investor confidence in the country.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why your team design is slowing your business down - and what to do about it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The design of a team can have a significant impact on the efficiency and productivity of a business. This article discusses how certain team designs can slow down a business and provides suggestions on how to address this issue.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Businesses should evaluate their team designs and identify any potential bottlenecks or inefficiencies. By making necessary changes and optimizing team structures, businesses can improve their overall performance and productivity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How can Scala and Kotlin interact to build user-friendly DSLs (part two)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Tech&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article explores the interaction between Scala and Kotlin in building user-friendly Domain-Specific Languages (DSLs). Part two of the series delves deeper into the technical aspects and implementation strategies.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: The combination of Scala and Kotlin can offer powerful capabilities in creating user-friendly DSLs. Developers can leverage the strengths of both languages to design intuitive and efficient DSLs that cater to specific application requirements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How can Scala and Kotlin interact to build user-friendly DSLs (part one)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Tech&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article introduces the concept of using Scala and Kotlin together to develop user-friendly Domain-Specific Languages (DSLs). Part one provides an overview of DSLs and their benefits.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: The integration of Scala and Kotlin can enable developers to build DSLs that are easy to understand and use. By leveraging the features of both languages, developers can create expressive and concise DSLs that enhance the user experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's how government can accelerate their digital journey and empower citizens&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Tech, Government&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article discusses the role of government in accelerating their digital transformation journey and empowering citizens. It highlights the importance of leveraging technology to provide efficient and accessible services to the public.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Governments should prioritize digital transformation initiatives to enhance citizen engagement and service delivery. By adopting innovative technologies and streamlining processes, governments can improve efficiency, transparency, and citizen satisfaction.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to deal with the five dysfunctions of a team? (part one)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article addresses the five dysfunctions commonly observed in teams and provides strategies to overcome them. Part one focuses on identifying and understanding these dysfunctions.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Recognizing and addressing the dysfunctions within a team is crucial for fostering a healthy and productive work environment. By implementing the suggested strategies, businesses can promote effective collaboration, communication, and problem-solving within their teams.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to deal with the five dysfunctions of a team? (part two)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article continues the discussion on dealing with the five dysfunctions of a team. Part two explores practical approaches and techniques to address these dysfunctions and improve team dynamics.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Overcoming team dysfunctions requires a combination of open communication, trust-building exercises, and effective leadership. By implementing the strategies outlined in this article, businesses can create a cohesive and high-performing team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uncovering GAPS: a 3D experience map to identify and solve consumer problems with XR&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Tech&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article introduces the concept of using a 3D experience map to uncover and address consumer problems using Extended Reality (XR) technologies. It highlights the potential of XR in enhancing user experiences and solving real-world challenges.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: By leveraging XR technologies and creating 3D experience maps, businesses can gain valuable insights into consumer pain points and develop innovative solutions. This approach can lead to improved product design, customer satisfaction, and competitive advantage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A guide for successful client assessments and discoveries (part 2) - delivery&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article provides a guide for conducting successful client assessments and discoveries, focusing on the delivery phase. Part two explores the key considerations and best practices for ensuring successful project delivery.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Effective client assessments and discoveries are essential for delivering successful projects. By following the guidelines outlined in this article, businesses can enhance their project management processes, mitigate risks, and ensure client satisfaction.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A guide for successful client assessments and discoveries (part 1) - people&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article offers a guide for conducting successful client assessments and discoveries, with a focus on the people involved. Part one emphasizes the importance of understanding client needs, building relationships, and aligning expectations.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Building strong relationships with clients and understanding their needs are crucial for successful project outcomes. By prioritizing effective communication, collaboration, and empathy, businesses can establish a solid foundation for client assessments and discoveries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOLID Principles: How to create a code that is easy to extend and maintain- Part 3&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Tech&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article explores the SOLID principles of software development, focusing on creating code that is easy to extend and maintain. Part three delves into the Open-Closed Principle and Liskov Substitution Principle.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Adhering to SOLID principles can significantly improve the maintainability and extensibility of software code. By following the guidelines provided in this article, developers can create robust and flexible codebases that are easier to maintain and evolve.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOLID Principles: How to create a code that is easy to extend and maintain- Part 1&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Tech&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article introduces the SOLID principles of software development, emphasizing the importance of creating code that is easy to extend and maintain. Part one provides an overview of the SOLID principles and their benefits.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: The SOLID principles offer a set of guidelines for writing clean, modular, and maintainable code. By understanding and applying these principles, developers can improve code quality, reduce technical debt, and enhance the overall software development process.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to select a Payment Gateway: [Part 2] Functions of Payment Gateways&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Business, Tech&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article discusses the factors to consider when selecting a payment gateway for business transactions. Part two focuses on the functions and features that payment gateways offer.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Choosing the right payment gateway is crucial for businesses to ensure secure and seamless payment processing. By evaluating the functions and features of different payment gateways, businesses can make informed decisions that align with their specific requirements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to select a Payment Gateway [Part 4]: Payment Gateways integration methods and other considerations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Business, Tech&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article provides guidance on selecting a payment gateway for business transactions. Part four explores the integration methods and additional considerations to keep in mind when choosing a payment gateway.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Integrating a payment gateway seamlessly into existing business systems is essential for efficient payment processing. By considering integration methods and other relevant factors, businesses can streamline their payment workflows and enhance the overall customer experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why don’t women ask? Bridging the gender pay gap (Part III)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Business, Gender Equality&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article addresses the gender pay gap and explores the reasons behind women's reluctance to negotiate for higher salaries. Part three focuses on bridging the gender pay gap and promoting equal opportunities.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Bridging the gender pay gap requires systemic changes in organizations, including promoting transparency, providing negotiation training, and addressing unconscious biases. By implementing these measures, businesses can create a more equitable and inclusive work environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why don’t women ask? Bridging the gender pay gap (Part II)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Business, Gender Equality&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article continues the discussion on the gender pay gap and explores the factors contributing to women's hesitation in negotiating for higher salaries. Part two delves deeper into the societal and cultural influences on women's negotiation behaviors.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Societal and cultural factors play a significant role in shaping women's negotiation behaviors and contributing to the gender pay gap. By raising awareness, challenging stereotypes, and providing support, businesses can empower women to advocate for fair compensation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authentication sidecar — a new experience in microservice architecture (Part one)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Tech&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article introduces the concept of an authentication sidecar in microservice architecture. Part one provides an overview of the authentication sidecar and its benefits in enhancing security and scalability.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Implementing an authentication sidecar can improve the security and scalability of microservice architectures. By offloading authentication-related tasks to a dedicated component, businesses can simplify development, enhance performance, and ensure consistent security measures.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We Don’t Need A Dreamcast Mini, We Need Lots Of Awesome Remasters&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Tech, Gaming&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article discusses the preference for remastered versions of classic games over the release of a Dreamcast Mini console. It emphasizes the demand for high-quality remasters that preserve the essence of beloved games.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: The popularity of remastered games highlights the nostalgia and appreciation for classic titles. By investing in remastering projects, game developers can cater to the desires of fans while introducing these games to a new generation of players.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's still a Sriracha shortage and third-party vendors are selling the sauce for up to $23 on Amazon&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Business, Food&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article highlights the ongoing shortage of Sriracha sauce and the inflated prices charged by third-party vendors on platforms like Amazon.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Shortages of popular products can lead to price gouging by third-party sellers, impacting consumer affordability and availability. Businesses should address supply chain challenges to ensure consistent product availability and prevent opportunistic price hikes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A glitch temporarily wiped out X images and links between 2011 and 2014 — including Ellen's Oscar selfie that broke Twitter&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Tech, Social Media&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article discusses a glitch that temporarily erased images and links from a specific time period, including notable moments like Ellen's Oscar selfie that went viral on Twitter.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Glitches and technical issues can have significant consequences, impacting the accessibility and preservation of digital content. Businesses should prioritize robust data management and backup strategies to prevent the loss of valuable information.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Threads to launch web version, one of its largest updates yet&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Tech, Social Media&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article announces the upcoming launch of a web version for the messaging app Threads, highlighting it as one of the platform's largest updates.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: The introduction of a web version for messaging apps can enhance accessibility and user convenience. By expanding their platforms to different devices, businesses can cater to a wider user base and improve overall user experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Build, Deploy, and Host Your Vite App on GitHub Pages with GitHub Actions CI/CD&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Tech, Development&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article provides a guide on building, deploying, and hosting Vite applications on GitHub Pages using GitHub Actions for Continuous Integration/Continuous Deployment (CI/CD).&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Leveraging CI/CD tools like GitHub Actions can streamline the development and deployment processes for web applications. By automating build and deployment tasks, developers can save time and ensure consistent application delivery.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods' 'little brother' Justin Thomas sells his $3.5 million 'starter' mansion and it's the ultimate bachelor pad&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Lifestyle, Real Estate&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article highlights the sale of golfer Justin Thomas' mansion, which is described as the ultimate bachelor pad.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Celebrity real estate transactions can provide insights into luxury property trends and lifestyle preferences. The sale of Justin Thomas' mansion showcases the appeal of high-end properties designed for single individuals or couples without children.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My talk with Kris Nova about being homeless. See you on the other side, friend&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Personal, Social Issues&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article shares a personal conversation with Kris Nova about her experience of homelessness and offers support and empathy.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Personal stories and discussions about social issues can raise awareness and foster empathy. By sharing experiences and providing support, individuals and communities can work towards addressing homelessness and related challenges.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Changing its name tanked X's downloads in App Store and Play Store&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Business, Branding&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article discusses the negative impact of changing a brand's name on its app downloads in the App Store and Play Store.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Rebranding efforts should be carefully planned and executed to minimize any negative consequences. Sudden name changes can confuse users and lead to a decline in app downloads. Businesses should consider the potential implications before making significant branding decisions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today’s Wordle #793 Hints, Clues And Answer For Monday, August 21st&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Games, Puzzles&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article provides hints, clues, and answers for Wordle puzzle #793, offering assistance to players.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Puzzle-solving games like Wordle can provide entertainment and mental stimulation. Sharing hints and clues can enhance the gaming experience and help players overcome challenges.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cell therapy repairs cornea damage with patient's stem cells gives trial results&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Science, Medical Research&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article discusses the results of a trial that used cell therapy to repair cornea damage using the patient's own stem cells.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Cell therapy holds promise for regenerative medicine and the treatment of various medical conditions. The successful trial results highlight the potential of stem cells in repairing cornea damage and improving vision.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meer Pyrus Base: A New Open-Source Python-Based Platform for the Two-Dimensional (2D) Simulation of RoboCup Soccer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Tech, Robotics&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article introduces Meer Pyrus Base, an open-source Python-based platform for simulating RoboCup Soccer in a two-dimensional (2D) environment.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Open-source platforms like Meer Pyrus Base facilitate the development and experimentation of robotics applications. By providing accessible tools and resources, developers can contribute to the advancement of robotics and artificial intelligence in various domains.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;See Saturn Shine And A Red Giant Eclipsed: The Night Sky This Week&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Topic: Science, Astronomy&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article highlights the astronomical events occurring in the night sky, including the visibility of Saturn and the eclipse of a red giant star.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Observing celestial events can inspire awe and curiosity about the universe. By staying informed about astronomical phenomena, individuals can appreciate the wonders of the night sky and deepen their understanding of the cosmos.</summary></entry></feed>