<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-13T08:03:39Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:03:39</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-13T08:03:39Z</published><updated>2023-11-13T08:03:39Z</updated><id>525b794b-3acd-4a72-a24a-b3df88d8e651</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- An OLED iPad Pro is highly anticipated by tech enthusiasts.&lt;br&gt;- Base editing, a new form of gene therapy, has shown promising results in lowering bad cholesterol.&lt;br&gt;- Using Webb data, researchers have measured a rapid increase in oxygen in the early universe.&lt;br&gt;- Create a streaming AI assistant with ChatGPT, FastAPI, WebSockets, and React.&lt;br&gt;- Console #183 features an interview with Stypox, the creator of New Pipe, a libre streaming front-end for Android.&lt;br&gt;- Google DeepMind researchers propose a framework for classifying the capabilities and behavior of Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) models and their precursors.&lt;br&gt;- This AI paper introduces Neural MMO 2.0, which aims to revolutionize reinforcement learning with flexible task systems and procedural generation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech section highlights advancements in various fields, including gene therapy, space exploration, and AI. These developments have the potential to improve healthcare, entertainment, and overall technological capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- A UK supermarket chain is replacing self-checkout stations with human cashiers.&lt;br&gt;- Maryland Gov. Wes Moore advises Joe Manchin against launching a White House campaign against Biden.&lt;br&gt;- Democrats' contrasting results in the Kentucky governor's race and Mississippi elections are analyzed.&lt;br&gt;- Donald Trump faces challenges to his mental sharpness from rivals.&lt;br&gt;- Cars downloading text messages from phones does not violate state privacy law.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business section covers a range of topics, including retail, politics, and privacy. It highlights the impact of human labor in the retail industry, political strategies, and legal considerations in the digital age.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers propose a framework for classifying AGI models and their precursors.&lt;br&gt;- The question of reliable sources for AI developments without falling for hype is raised.&lt;br&gt;- Neural MMO 2.0 is introduced as a revolutionary approach to reinforcement learning.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The AI section focuses on the classification of AI models, the need for reliable sources in AI reporting, and the potential of Neural MMO 2.0. It emphasizes the importance of responsible AI development and accurate information dissemination.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The report covers a wide range of topics, including tech advancements, business strategies, and AI developments. It highlights the potential of OLED iPad Pro, base editing in gene therapy, and the use of Webb data in measuring oxygen levels in the early universe. The report also discusses the impact of human cashiers in supermarkets, political campaigns, and privacy concerns. Additionally, it explores the classification of AGI models, the need for reliable AI sources, and the potential of Neural MMO 2.0 in reinforcement learning. Overall, the report showcases the ongoing progress and challenges in various fields and emphasizes the importance of responsible and informed decision-making.</summary></entry></feed>