<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-03T20:01:56Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 03 Sep 2023 20:01:56</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-03T20:01:56Z</published><updated>2023-09-03T20:01:56Z</updated><id>e58c9903-5419-4c8a-96b8-29408a60df27</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from the University in Yokohama have proposed VirSen1.0, a virtual environment for streamlining the development of sensor-based human gesture recognition systems.&lt;br&gt;- Deepmind founder Mustafa Suleyman sees great potential in AI for mental health.&lt;br&gt;- Meta AI has introduced License for DINOv2 and released FACET, two new endeavors for fairness in computer vision.&lt;br&gt;- AI project imagines adult faces of children who disappeared during Argentina's military dictatorship.&lt;br&gt;- Maxar's Chris Johnson discusses the evolution of the government's thinking around space.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- John Wiley discusses growth through corporate development and online platforms.&lt;br&gt;- Yeti's CEO shares his approach to building a brand for the long term.&lt;br&gt;- Aspiring Taiwan presidential candidate Terry Gou resigns from the board of Apple supplier Foxconn.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- A brain-inspired learning algorithm enables metaplasticity in artificial and spiking neural networks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine arrested the oligarch who owns the TV station that aired Volodymyr Zelenskyy's show before he became president.&lt;br&gt;- Whales swimming behind fishing vessels catch an easy feast of escaped fish, but experts warn this behavior is risky.&lt;br&gt;- A remote worker took a $35,000 pay cut in exchange for work-from-home freedom.&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage interest rates remain low compared to recent weeks.&lt;br&gt;- SEC's Gary Gensler's views on the crypto industry have evolved over the years.&lt;br&gt;- A Tesla got stuck in the middle of a busy road for 9 hours.&lt;br&gt;- A Dodge Charger is 60 times more likely to be stolen than any other vehicle in the US.&lt;br&gt;- Russia attacks a Ukrainian port before key grain deal talks between Putin and Turkey's president.&lt;br&gt;- The NYPD plans to use drones to spy on Labor Day parties.&lt;br&gt;- The safety of COVID-19 vaccination in immunocompromised individuals is discussed.&lt;br&gt;- What's at stake when Turkey's leader meets Putin to reestablish the Black Sea grain deal.&lt;br&gt;- Text messages hold clues to why a drug gang killed 43 students.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The development of sensor-based human gesture recognition systems is being streamlined through virtual environments.&lt;br&gt;- AI has great potential in the field of mental health.&lt;br&gt;- Efforts are being made to ensure fairness in computer vision.&lt;br&gt;- The government's thinking around space has evolved.&lt;br&gt;- Building a brand for the long term requires a low-and-slow approach.&lt;br&gt;- The safety of COVID-19 vaccination in immunocompromised individuals is a topic of concern.&lt;br&gt;- Text messages can provide valuable clues in criminal investigations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report covers a range of topics including tech advancements, business developments, AI applications, and current events. It highlights key points within each section and provides insights into the significance of these topics. The report concludes that there is ongoing progress in various fields, such as AI and space exploration, while also addressing important issues like fairness and safety.</summary></entry></feed>