<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-12T20:02:17Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 12 Sep 2023 20:02:17</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-12T20:02:17Z</published><updated>2023-09-12T20:02:17Z</updated><id>e10e12a1-0428-445f-a0f6-2585da81a66b</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Arm checks assembly expert's book for trademark issues&lt;br&gt;- Instagram's Threads blocking searches about COVID-19&lt;br&gt;- Google DeepMind Researchers propose Optimization by PROmpting (OPRO): Large Language Models as Optimizers&lt;br&gt;- Detecting changes in JavaScript and CSS isn't an easy task, Part 3&lt;br&gt;- Robots that learn as they fail could unlock a new era of AI&lt;br&gt;- How software that tracks COVID variants could protect us against future outbreaks&lt;br&gt;- This startup plans to power a tugboat with ammonia later this year&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech industry is constantly evolving and facing challenges in various areas such as trademark issues, content moderation, and AI optimization. The development of technologies like robots and software for tracking COVID variants shows the potential for innovation and problem-solving in the tech sector.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Wiley Consumer Protection Download (September 11, 2023) - Dodd ... - Mondaq News Alerts&lt;br&gt;- The trusty American consumer is poised to run out of steam by early next year, investor survey says&lt;br&gt;- The S&amp;P 500 looks risky and expensive - and could plunge 25% if something shocks the system, Morgan Stanley's stock chief warns&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway sees its market value surge to a new record of almost $800 billion&lt;br&gt;- The typical NYC family is spending more than 25% of its income on childcare &amp;mdash; triple what's deemed affordable&lt;br&gt;- Walgreens In Deal With Tech Firm Pearl Health To Enhance Work With Primary Care Doctors&lt;br&gt;- Fast Company’s CEO Fair Pay report: The 15 ‘most fairly’ paid CEOs&lt;br&gt;- Fast Company CEO fair pay report: The 15 ‘least fairly’ paid CEOs&lt;br&gt;- Fast Company’s CEO Fair Pay Report: See how much corporate leaders make compared with their employees&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business landscape is influenced by consumer behavior, market risks, and the valuation of companies. The rising market value of Berkshire Hathaway and the challenges faced by American consumers highlight the dynamic nature of the business world. Additionally, issues such as childcare affordability and CEO pay disparities are important topics in the business sector.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Google DeepMind Researchers propose Optimization by PROmpting (OPRO): Large Language Models as Optimizers&lt;br&gt;- Robots that learn as they fail could unlock a new era of AI&lt;br&gt;- How software that tracks COVID variants could protect us against future outbreaks&lt;br&gt;- 8 More Companies Pledge to Make A.I. Safe, White House Says&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: Artificial intelligence continues to be a significant area of research and development. The proposed optimization method for large language models, the potential of robots that learn from failure, and the use of AI in tracking COVID variants demonstrate the wide-ranging applications and potential benefits of AI technology. The commitment of companies to ensure AI safety also reflects the growing importance of ethical considerations in AI development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is constantly evolving and facing challenges in various areas such as trademark issues, content moderation, and AI optimization.&lt;br&gt;- The business landscape is influenced by consumer behavior, market risks, and the valuation of companies.&lt;br&gt;- Artificial intelligence continues to be a significant area of research and development, with potential applications in various fields and a growing focus on ethical considerations.</summary></entry></feed>