<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-01T08:03:42Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 01 Sep 2023 08:03:42</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-01T08:03:42Z</published><updated>2023-09-01T08:03:42Z</updated><id>d0217837-5f7e-46c5-9d13-c01ddce364f5</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Russia and Ukraine are engaged in a drone war, highlighting concerns about future warfare.&lt;br&gt;- Delta Air Lines claims to have protected its planes against interference from 5G signals.&lt;br&gt;- US Army plans to mount a rifle on a robot dog.&lt;br&gt;- Startup Superframe raises $5 million to simplify Salesforce configurations with an AI chatbot.&lt;br&gt;- New Chrome feature makes it easier to grab full-resolution frames from videos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- South Korea is developing an 'arsenal ship' as a defense against North Korea.&lt;br&gt;- Barstool Sports reportedly lays off nearly 25% of staff after being sold for $1.&lt;br&gt;- Wall Street moguls gain an important backer in their fight over a hedge fund sale.&lt;br&gt;- New York subway system disables a feature that could allow stalkers to track trips.&lt;br&gt;- Owners of Scranton Times-Tribune and other Pennsylvania dailies sell to a publishing giant.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Startup Superframe raises $5 million to simplify Salesforce configurations with an AI chatbot.&lt;br&gt;- US Army plans to mount a rifle on a robot dog.&lt;br&gt;- New Chrome feature makes it easier to grab full-resolution frames from videos.&lt;br&gt;- Online Learning Platform Market - Global Industry Analysis, Size, Growth, Trends, and Forecast 2023 to 203.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The use of drones in warfare is becoming a significant concern, with Russia and Ukraine already engaged in a drone war.&lt;br&gt;- The integration of AI into various industries, such as Salesforce configurations and video editing, is gaining momentum.&lt;br&gt;- The business landscape is experiencing changes, with layoffs, sales, and legal battles affecting companies.&lt;br&gt;- Privacy concerns arise as technology advances, such as the disabling of a feature in the New York subway system to prevent stalking.&lt;br&gt;- The global market for online learning platforms is expected to grow significantly in the coming years.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report highlights the ongoing developments and challenges in the tech, business, and AI sectors. It emphasizes the need for preparedness in the face of evolving warfare tactics, the integration of AI in various industries, and the impact of legal and business decisions on companies. Additionally, it underscores the importance of addressing privacy concerns and the potential growth in the online learning market.</summary></entry></feed>