<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-06T08:03:30Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 06 Sep 2023 08:03:30</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-06T08:03:30Z</published><updated>2023-09-06T08:03:30Z</updated><id>3b310c96-d43c-40a1-a515-3311f136936b</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft files a patent on its new AI-powered smart backpack that can hear and see what you see.&lt;br&gt;- How Amazon uses chaos engineering to handle 80k requests per second.&lt;br&gt;- iPhone and iPad apps will be available in the Vision Pro App Store by default.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Global Medical Publishing Market valued at $9.7 billion in 2022.&lt;br&gt;- The shrinking number of primary care physicians is reaching a tipping point.&lt;br&gt;- Lawsuit claims mobile home park managers conspired to fix and inflate lot rental prices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft files a patent on its new AI-powered smart backpack that can hear and see what you see.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Remembering Doug Lenat (1950–2023) and his quest to capture the world with logic.&lt;br&gt;- I got my Amex Platinum for the clout, but I'm educating myself about the risks.&lt;br&gt;- The Capitol physician said Mitch McConnell's health scares may have been a result of dehydration, but Sen. Rand Paul doesn't believe it.&lt;br&gt;- Damaged tail rotor to blame for helicopter crash in 2018 that killed Leicester owner and 4 others.&lt;br&gt;- Air Canada apologizes for booting passengers who complained that their seats were smeared with vomit.&lt;br&gt;- Burning Man costs most people a minimum of $800 for just a ticket and a parking spot, with additional expenses pushing the total cost into the thousands.&lt;br&gt;- AOC says Biden must continue his outreach to progressives ahead of the 2024 election, similar to efforts after the 2020 Democratic primary.&lt;br&gt;- Republicans hired way more ex-lobbyists as congressional staffers in the last year than Democrats, analysis finds.&lt;br&gt;- Russian pilot who defected with stolen fighter jet spare parts gets $500,000 reward from Ukraine.&lt;br&gt;- Poor people 'surviving not living' as UK social contract collapses, says report.&lt;br&gt;- Emerge (YC W21) is hiring a lead front-end engineer (remote, small team).&lt;br&gt;- Ask HN: Is there a news source you read every day? If so, what is it?&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk paid for our attention, but the price to keep it is getting higher.&lt;br&gt;- These Steam Deck custom resin buttons look phenomenal and are for sale.&lt;br&gt;- After a historic strike, UC grad students say the university isn't honoring pay agreements.&lt;br&gt;- As a shutdown looms, will the U.S. Congress cut spending and restrict research?&lt;br&gt;- 'Ask Sophie' book excerpt: A startup founder's guide to O-1A visas.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The medical publishing market is experiencing significant growth, reaching a value of $9.7 billion in 2022.&lt;br&gt;- The shortage of primary care physicians is becoming a critical issue.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's new AI-powered smart backpack has the potential to revolutionize the way we interact with technology.&lt;br&gt;- There is a growing concern about the rising number of cancer cases among younger people, with scientists still unsure of the underlying causes.&lt;br&gt;- Student loans are a major concern for Gen Z, impacting their career choices.&lt;br&gt;- The social contract in the UK is collapsing, leading to poor living conditions for many.&lt;br&gt;- The influence of lobbyists in politics is evident, with Republicans hiring more ex-lobbyists as congressional staffers compared to Democrats.&lt;br&gt;- The cost of attending events like Burning Man can be substantial, with expenses easily reaching thousands of dollars.&lt;br&gt;- The need for continued outreach to progressives is emphasized by AOC, highlighting the importance of unity within the Democratic party.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of technology on our daily lives is evident, with companies like Amazon and Microsoft constantly innovating to handle increasing demands.&lt;br&gt;- The struggles faced by individuals in low-income communities are highlighted, emphasizing the need for social support and change.&lt;br&gt;- The importance of honoring agreements and fair treatment of workers is emphasized by the UC grad students' strike.&lt;br&gt;- The potential consequences of a government shutdown and its impact on spending and research are discussed.&lt;br&gt;- The challenges faced by startup founders in navigating visa processes are explored in the book excerpt.</summary></entry></feed>