<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-27T20:01:56Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 27 Aug 2023 20:01:56</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-27T20:01:56Z</published><updated>2023-08-27T20:01:56Z</updated><id>771455a6-b187-4bc8-8a87-7e14c266075d</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- A couple with over $250,000 in student debt had their balance wiped out after nearly 3 decades of repayment.&lt;br&gt;- A Tesla owner claimed that his Model 3 in Full Self-Driving mode crashed into a pond after not slowing down before hitting water on the road.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers at UCSF and UC Berkeley have developed a Brain-Computer Interface (BCI) that allows a woman with severe paralysis to speak through a digital avatar.&lt;br&gt;- Meta AI has released Code Llama, a state-of-the-art large language model for coding.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Your next apartment could be someone's old cubicle as developers rush to convert empty offices.&lt;br&gt;- Maui business owners rely on tourism to survive but believe visitors should rethink how they use resources.&lt;br&gt;- Vision 2030 is Saudi Arabia's plan to future-proof its oil-based economy, but experts say it's a huge risk.&lt;br&gt;- Silicon Valley elites have been revealed as investors behind an $800M Bay Area land grab.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Meta plans to take on GPT-4 with a rumored Llama 3, which is still free.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers at UCSF and UC Berkeley have developed a Brain-Computer Interface (BCI) that allows a woman with severe paralysis to speak through a digital avatar.&lt;br&gt;- Meta AI has released Code Llama, a state-of-the-art large language model for coding.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Old interview clip of Wagner chief Prigozhin sparks speculation about his death.&lt;br&gt;- I rented month-long Airbnb stays in 6 different cities before settling in San Diego, making my decision easy.&lt;br&gt;- A Soviet-style approach to war might be hindering Ukraine in its battles with Russia.&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage interest rates remain high despite dips.&lt;br&gt;- China's $10 trillion hidden debt mountain could be a ticking time bomb.&lt;br&gt;- 3 Marines were killed and 20 injured after a US helicopter crashed on a training exercise in northern Australia.&lt;br&gt;- Today's Wordle #799 hints, clues, and answer for Sunday, August 27th.&lt;br&gt;- Arizona's aspiring engineer and punter Ostendorp is back in 2023.&lt;br&gt;- 3 Ukrainian pilots died in a mid-flight collision days after Western allies announced a new training initiative.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The couple's student debt being wiped out after nearly 3 decades of repayment highlights the burden of student loans and the potential for relief.&lt;br&gt;- The Tesla crash raises concerns about the safety and reliability of Full Self-Driving mode.&lt;br&gt;- The development of the Brain-Computer Interface offers hope for individuals with severe paralysis to communicate.&lt;br&gt;- The conversion of empty offices into apartments reflects the changing needs and demands in the real estate market.&lt;br&gt;- The risks and potential benefits of Saudi Arabia's Vision 2030 plan for its economy are a topic of debate.&lt;br&gt;- The revelation of Silicon Valley elites as investors in a Bay Area land grab sheds light on the influence and investments of tech industry leaders.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;This report covers a range of topics including student debt relief, Tesla crashes, advancements in brain-computer interfaces, real estate trends, economic plans, and military incidents. Key insights include the impact of student loans, concerns about self-driving technology, the potential for improved communication for individuals with paralysis, changing real estate markets, the risks and benefits of economic plans, and the influence of Silicon Valley elites.</summary></entry></feed>