<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2023-12-15T20:02:03Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 15 Dec 2023 20:02:03</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-15T20:02:03Z</published><updated>2023-12-15T20:02:03Z</updated><id>14c2aee5-517b-47a4-99fc-175f5abea7b5</id><summary type="html">In the world, there have been various developments and events. Jeff Bezos, the founder of Amazon, recently experienced floating at zero gravity and described it as a "return to the womb." Lyft President Kristin Sverchek expressed her excitement for the year 2024, stating her bias towards action. In Mexico, it has been reported that cartels are accessing a government database to monitor their victims in real-time. Bezos also expressed his admiration for Elon Musk and his desire to be friends with him, as they are "very like-minded." On social media platform TikTok, young users are expressing their struggles in finding corporate jobs, feeling that it is nearly impossible. Additionally, a shadowy firm has been accused of ripping off media websites to support NFT projects, Amazon hustlers, and a convicted tax cheat. In Israel, conscientious objectors from Generation Z are facing shunning and even imprisonment for refusing to join the army. Technological advancements have also been made, with Spring Boot 3.2 delivering support for virtual threads and modern RestClient and JdbcClient. Meta and IBM have joined forces to lead the formation of an AI alliance to drive open-source innovation. Researchers at CMU have unveiled RoboTool, an AI system that accepts natural language instructions and outputs executable code for controlling robots. The stock market is being analyzed, questioning whether this year's top-performing stock ETFs will remain successful in 2024. In the entertainment industry, Taylor Swift's blue and Beyonce's silver are highlighted as colors that defined 2023. Private insurance companies are profiting from government-backed flood insurance. There is a call to shift the narrative from the climate crisis to the climate opportunity. In Idaho, school buildings have not been assessed for 30 years, prompting students and educators to take matters into their own hands. Obituaries for Micikater Wiley and Hazel Wiley have been published. Elon Musk's AI company, Grok, expressed a desire to befriend Grimes' AI, also named Grok, and exchange ideas. Bill Ackman's efforts against antisemitism have gained him a new fan, Elon Musk. Various presentations and papers have been released, discussing topics such as visual templates, GPT chatbots, real-time technology, image segmentation, and vision and language understanding and generation. Digital privacy has seen advancements in 2023, thanks to companies like Apple, Google, and Meta. Microsoft's digital crime unit has delved deep into disrupting cybercrime. Lastly, FineControlNet and VL-GPT are introduced as advancements in text control for image generation and generative pre-trained transformers for vision and language understanding and generation, respectively.</summary></entry></feed>