<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-26T08:03:25Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 26 Aug 2023 08:03:25</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-26T08:03:25Z</published><updated>2023-08-26T08:03:25Z</updated><id>6d78384c-8a45-4205-903f-368a052a2814</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. X to use Israeli software to require selfie, govt-issued ID for verification&lt;br&gt;- X plans to implement Israeli software that will require users to provide a selfie and government-issued ID for verification purposes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Fifth Circuit: Law Enforcement Doesn’t Need Warrants to Search Phones at Border&lt;br&gt;- The Fifth Circuit has ruled that law enforcement does not need warrants to search phones at the border.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Instacart, readying an IPO, is a rare gig-economy company to turn a profit&lt;br&gt;- Instacart, a gig-economy company, is preparing for an IPO and stands out as one of the few companies in this sector to turn a profit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. How Europe's new digital privacy act will change Big Tech regulation&lt;br&gt;- The new digital privacy act in Europe is expected to bring significant changes to the regulation of Big Tech companies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. 🐦 Inventing Issues to Solve Real Problems: My Dive into Jira Connector Development&lt;br&gt;- This article discusses the author's experience diving into Jira Connector development and how it involves inventing solutions for real problems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. The real cost of a preventive health scan goes well beyond the price tag&lt;br&gt;- The true cost of a preventive health scan extends beyond its monetary value.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Instacart's profitability relies in part on batching orders together — something that its gig workers hate&lt;br&gt;- Instacart's profitability is partially dependent on batching orders together, a practice that is disliked by its gig workers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. It's the return of the tech IPO. Instacart says it's profitable — and this may be the necessary secret ingredient for a hot market debut in 2023.&lt;br&gt;- Instacart's profitability and potential for a successful market debut in 2023 indicate the resurgence of tech IPOs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Oliver Anthony slams use of song at debate: I wrote that song about those people&lt;br&gt;- Oliver Anthony criticizes the use of his song at a debate, stating that it was written about the individuals on the stage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. Empowering Confidence: Overcoming Math Anxiety In The Age Of Artificial Intelligence&lt;br&gt;- This article explores how artificial intelligence can help individuals overcome math anxiety and boost their confidence.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Apple Researchers Propose an End-to-End Network Producing Detailed 3D Reconstructions from Posed Images&lt;br&gt;- Apple researchers have proposed an end-to-end network that can generate detailed 3D reconstructions from posed images.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Ex-Meta Researchers Have Raised $40 Million From Lux Capital For An AI Biotech Startup&lt;br&gt;- Former researchers from Meta have secured $40 million in funding from Lux Capital for their AI biotech startup.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Others:&lt;br&gt;1. Government seizure of Nicaraguan university a blow to science, researchers say&lt;br&gt;- The government seizure of a Nicaraguan university is seen as a setback for science and researchers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Newly Discovered Colombian Orchids Might Be On The Edge Of Extinction&lt;br&gt;- Recently discovered Colombian orchids are at risk of extinction.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. How Daniel Ellsberg, who died at age 92, went from being a disillusioned member of the government-military elite to a hero of anti-war movements&lt;br&gt;- The article discusses the transformation of Daniel Ellsberg, who went from a disillusioned member of the government-military elite to a hero of anti-war movements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The use of Israeli software for verification purposes highlights the increasing importance of identity verification in various industries.&lt;br&gt;- The Fifth Circuit's ruling on phone searches at the border raises concerns about privacy rights and the power of law enforcement.&lt;br&gt;- Instacart's profitability in the gig economy sector sets it apart from other companies and may contribute to a successful IPO.&lt;br&gt;- The new digital privacy act in Europe is expected to have a significant impact on the regulation of Big Tech companies.&lt;br&gt;- The use of artificial intelligence can help individuals overcome math anxiety and improve their mathematical skills.&lt;br&gt;- Apple's proposed end-to-end network for 3D reconstructions showcases the potential of AI in generating detailed visual representations.&lt;br&gt;- The government seizure of a Nicaraguan university is detrimental to scientific research and progress.&lt;br&gt;- The discovery of endangered Colombian orchids highlights the need for conservation efforts.&lt;br&gt;- The transformation of Daniel Ellsberg serves as an example of an individual's journey from disillusionment to activism.&lt;br&gt;- The use of songs in political debates can spark controversy and raise questions about the intentions behind their selection.</summary></entry></feed>