<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-19T22:01:07Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 19 Aug 2023 22:01:07</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-19T22:01:07Z</published><updated>2023-08-19T22:01:07Z</updated><id>c7b13203-e723-464d-976d-aa44be3bf10b</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Simplified Micro Front-Ends: Mastering Global State Management with Redux and Redux Toolkit&lt;br&gt;- An AI Model Tested In The Ukraine War Is Helping Assess Damage From The Hawaii Wildfires&lt;br&gt;- Academic journals scramble to adapt as AI-assisted papers sneak into publications&lt;br&gt;- AI becomes the new traffic police, catching hundreds of UK drivers in the act&lt;br&gt;- As well as 24-hour robotaxis, San Francisco now has a driverless bus service too&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Pickleball went pro. Can it profit? - The New York Times&lt;br&gt;- Consumers have spent all of their excess savings from the pandemic. That's just one reason why stocks are poised to fall, JPMorgan says&lt;br&gt;- China's economy is flailing. Here's how its problems could spill into global markets.&lt;br&gt;- The decline of Boston Market: Why the chain that sparked the rotisserie chicken craze has closed dozens of stores&lt;br&gt;- The bad news for automakers in China is only getting worse&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett, Michael Burry, and other top investors revealed striking portfolio changes this week. Here are 4 key trades.&lt;br&gt;- A Colorado airpark is on the market for $4.1 million, and one prospective buyer wants to turn it into a community for private plane owners &amp;mdash; take a look&lt;br&gt;- These 6 shocking twists show just how bad China's economy is right now, says Bank of America&lt;br&gt;- America’s Obsession with Weight-Loss Drugs Is Affecting the Economy of Denmark&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Simplified Micro Front-Ends: Mastering Global State Management with Redux and Redux Toolkit&lt;br&gt;- An AI Model Tested In The Ukraine War Is Helping Assess Damage From The Hawaii Wildfires&lt;br&gt;- Academic journals scramble to adapt as AI-assisted papers sneak into publications&lt;br&gt;- AI becomes the new traffic police, catching hundreds of UK drivers in the act&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- 4 steps I took to figure out how much house I can afford&lt;br&gt;- 4 ways to save enough now to retire in 10 years&lt;br&gt;- The Maui wildfires already caused widespread damage in Lahaina, but more remains at risk&lt;br&gt;- Battlefield casualties in the Ukraine war have surged to almost 500,000 killed and wounded, US officials say&lt;br&gt;- I flew 20 hours from Australia to the US in United Airline's Polaris business class. The flight was a game changer and I'll definitely be flying it again &amp;mdash; here's why.&lt;br&gt;- Stormzy at All Points East review: after a slow start the rapper gave ... - Evening Standard&lt;br&gt;- A look at the history of All-American teams in college football - Times-West Virginian&lt;br&gt;- Effects of SARS‐CoV‐2 infection and COVID‐19 pandemic on ... - John Wiley&lt;br&gt;- Today's Mortgage and Refinance Rates: August 19, 2023 | Highest Rates in Decades&lt;br&gt;- Video of a Ka-52 attack helicopter being shot down in Ukraine hints Russia isn't learning what it should have by now, former US general says&lt;br&gt;- A tick bite gave me Alpha-gal syndrome. Now, I'm allergic to meat and its byproducts and only eat 1 meal a day.&lt;br&gt;- I'm an incoming Harvard freshman. I'm nervous I won't fit in with the rich kids on campus as a financial-aid student.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is rapidly advancing with the implementation of AI in various fields, such as state management and damage assessment.&lt;br&gt;- The global economy is facing challenges, particularly in China, which could have repercussions on the stock market and automakers.&lt;br&gt;- Personal finance topics, such as homeownership, retirement planning, and affording a house, are of interest to readers.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of war and conflicts, such as the Ukraine war, is significant and has resulted in a high number of casualties.&lt;br&gt;- Consumer trends, such as the decline of certain chains and the popularity of spiked drinks, reflect changing preferences.&lt;br&gt;- Academic publishing is adapting to the use of AI-assisted papers, while AI is also being utilized in traffic enforcement.&lt;br&gt;- Cultural events, such as music festivals and sports, continue to attract attention.&lt;br&gt;- The COVID-19 pandemic has had wide-ranging effects on various aspects of life, including the economy and healthcare.&lt;br&gt;- Personal stories, such as experiencing allergies or concerns about fitting in at college, resonate with readers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, the report highlights the diverse range of topics covered in the provided content, showcasing the intersection of technology, business, AI, and other areas of interest. The insights gathered reflect the current state of various industries and provide a glimpse into the challenges and opportunities they face.</summary></entry></feed>