<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-17T02:01:11Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 17 Aug 2023 02:01:11</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-17T02:01:11Z</published><updated>2023-08-17T02:01:11Z</updated><id>4cfdf7a4-eaa4-492b-964b-af18356f5702</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Target CEO reports an increase in thefts involving violence or threats of violence.&lt;br&gt;- Former campaign staffer indicted for wire fraud and identity theft after impersonating Kevin McCarthy's chief of staff.&lt;br&gt;- People prefer working outside the office, including at gyms.&lt;br&gt;- Automakers like Ford and GM may need to offer fewer options on new cars to compete with Tesla.&lt;br&gt;- An accountant explains who should apply for the Employee Retention Credit.&lt;br&gt;- A list of alcoholic drinks to avoid for calorie-cutting purposes.&lt;br&gt;- Sen. Tommy Tuberville still earning royalties from 'The Blind Side' as controversy surrounds the movie's truthfulness.&lt;br&gt;- Economist warns of potential deflation in the US due to real estate and stock market risks.&lt;br&gt;- Four Americans moved to New Zealand for safety and a small-town feel.&lt;br&gt;- Michael Cohen expresses satisfaction over Rudy Giuliani's RICO charges.&lt;br&gt;- Trader Joe's executives assure that employees will not be replaced by self-checkout and deny claims of flirtatious cashiers.&lt;br&gt;- Tesla's Cybertruck spotted in the wild, standing out among regular cars.&lt;br&gt;- Detroit's Big 3 automakers face potential conflict with workers' union during contract negotiation.&lt;br&gt;- Concerns about the impact of the climate crisis on retirement plans.&lt;br&gt;- China's banks reduce lending to the lowest level in 14 years due to economic troubles.&lt;br&gt;- Trump ordered to surrender to Georgia authorities following RICO indictment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Canada attracts 10,000 tech workers from the US in just 48 hours.&lt;br&gt;- A major Chinese trust firm misses payments, raising financial concerns in Beijing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Replit CEO discusses empowering the next billion software creators.&lt;br&gt;- Reallusion enhances character animation workflows with Two-Way Live Sync and OpenUSD Support.&lt;br&gt;- Startup develops models for detecting vehicle failure patterns.&lt;br&gt;- NVIDIA introduces new Studio Laptops for content creation, gaming, and education.&lt;br&gt;- Snap confirms glitch in Snapchat's AI, causing it to post to Stories without user input.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Theft involving violence or threats of violence is a growing concern for retailers.&lt;br&gt;- Impersonation and identity theft remain prevalent issues.&lt;br&gt;- Remote work preferences extend beyond traditional office spaces.&lt;br&gt;- Automakers face challenges in competing with Tesla's customization options.&lt;br&gt;- Understanding eligibility for tax credits is important for businesses.&lt;br&gt;- Calorie-conscious individuals should be mindful of their alcoholic drink choices.&lt;br&gt;- Controversies surrounding movies can have long-lasting effects.&lt;br&gt;- Economic risks may lead to deflation in the US.&lt;br&gt;- People seek safety and a sense of belonging in different countries.&lt;br&gt;- Legal consequences can bring satisfaction to those affected by past actions.&lt;br&gt;- The role of human employees in retail remains important.&lt;br&gt;- Tesla's Cybertruck continues to generate interest and attention.&lt;br&gt;- Negotiations between automakers and unions can be contentious.&lt;br&gt;- Climate change poses uncertainties for retirement planning.&lt;br&gt;- China's economic troubles impact lending practices.&lt;br&gt;- Legal actions have consequences for public figures.&lt;br&gt;- Canada's tech industry attracts talent from neighboring countries.&lt;br&gt;- Financial concerns arise from missed payments by major firms.&lt;br&gt;- Technology plays a significant role in empowering software creators.&lt;br&gt;- Advancements in animation workflows enhance creative processes.&lt;br&gt;- Predictive models can help detect vehicle failures.&lt;br&gt;- NVIDIA's new laptops cater to various content creation needs.&lt;br&gt;- Glitches in AI systems can lead to unintended consequences.</summary></entry></feed>