<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-06T08:03:55Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 06 Oct 2023 08:03:55</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-06T08:03:55Z</published><updated>2023-10-06T08:03:55Z</updated><id>65dd7519-99db-43c7-ad83-f8af63cd2a4a</id><summary type="html">Online Learning Market 2023 Trends with Analysis on Key Companies 2U, Wiley (Knewton), Pluralsight, etc - SeeDance News&lt;br&gt;- Tech: The report discusses the trends and analysis of the online learning market in 2023, focusing on key companies such as 2U, Wiley (Knewton), Pluralsight, and others. It highlights the growth and potential of the online learning industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here is When Wear OS 4 is Coming to the Original Google Pixel Watch&lt;br&gt;- Tech: The article provides information on the release date of Wear OS 4 for the original Google Pixel Watch. It discusses the updates and features of the new operating system.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cannibalistic Europeans likely ate their dead at funerals 15,000 years ago instead of burying them, study says&lt;br&gt;- Science/Anthropology: A study suggests that ancient Europeans practiced cannibalism during funerals 15,000 years ago, consuming the flesh of the deceased instead of burying them. The findings shed light on burial practices and cultural behaviors of early humans.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to Earn, Redeem, and Maximize Wells Fargo Rewards in 2023&lt;br&gt;- Business/Finance: The article provides a guide on how to earn, redeem, and maximize Wells Fargo rewards in 2023. It offers tips and strategies for getting the most value out of the rewards program.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The no-annual-fee Amex Blue Business cards almost never have welcome bonuses, but now you can earn up to $250 or 15k points&lt;br&gt;- Business/Finance: The article discusses the welcome bonuses offered for the no-annual-fee Amex Blue Business cards. It highlights the rarity of welcome bonuses for these cards and provides details on the current offer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Santos filed false campaign reports inflating his fundraising figures to garner national GOP support, prosecutors say&lt;br&gt;- Politics: Prosecutors accuse George Santos of filing false campaign reports to inflate his fundraising figures and gain support from the national GOP. The article highlights the alleged misconduct and its potential impact on his political career.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4chan users manipulate AI tools to unleash torrent of racist images&lt;br&gt;- Tech/AI: The article reports on how users on the online platform 4chan manipulated AI tools to generate and spread racist images. It raises concerns about the misuse of AI technology and its implications for online content moderation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bing’s AI image generator tries to block ‘twin towers’ prompts, but it’s not working&lt;br&gt;- Tech/AI: The article discusses Bing's AI image generator and its attempts to block prompts related to the "twin towers" due to their sensitive nature. However, it highlights that the system is not effectively filtering out such prompts, raising concerns about AI's ability to handle sensitive topics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;a16z-backed Castelion wants to mass produce defense hardware, starting with hypersonics&lt;br&gt;- Tech/Defense: Castelion, backed by a16z, aims to mass produce defense hardware, starting with hypersonic technology. The article highlights the company's goals and its potential impact on the defense industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How To Turn Awkward Silence Into Comfortable Moments In Your Relationship&lt;br&gt;- Relationships: The article provides tips on how to turn awkward silence into comfortable moments in a relationship. It offers advice on communication and creating a comfortable atmosphere.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk killing article headlines on X could offer Threads a second chance&lt;br&gt;- Tech: The article discusses how Elon Musk's controversial actions and statements could provide an opportunity for Threads, a social media platform, to regain attention and relevance. It highlights the potential impact of Musk's actions on the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These are the battle lines for the House GOP's chaotic future&lt;br&gt;- Politics: The article examines the battle lines within the House GOP and the challenges it faces in the future. It discusses the divisions and conflicts within the party and their potential implications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can you earn a 7% CD interest rate? The truth behind high CD rates&lt;br&gt;- Finance: The article explores the truth behind high certificate of deposit (CD) interest rates and whether it is possible to earn a 7% interest rate. It provides insights into the factors that affect CD rates and offers realistic expectations for investors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The SEC is investigating Elon Musk's purchase of Twitter and attempting to force him to sit for questioning&lt;br&gt;- Business/Legal: The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is investigating Elon Musk's purchase of Twitter and seeking to compel him to sit for questioning. The article highlights the legal scrutiny surrounding Musk's actions and the potential consequences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin says Russia got its troubled nuclear-powered cruise missile to work after years of failure and a deadly disaster&lt;br&gt;- Politics/Defense: Russian President Vladimir Putin claims that Russia has successfully made its troubled nuclear-powered cruise missile operational after years of failures and a deadly accident. The article discusses the implications of this development for Russia's defense capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bob Menendez's wife, Nadine Arslanian, racked up traffic violations – including using her phone while driving – before she struck and killed a pedestrian in 2018&lt;br&gt;- Politics/Legal: The article reveals that Senator Bob Menendez's wife, Nadine Arslanian, had a history of traffic violations, including using her phone while driving, before she was involved in a fatal accident in 2018. It raises questions about her driving behavior and potential legal consequences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to watch NFL games without cable: live stream every game of the season&lt;br&gt;- Sports/Entertainment: The article provides a guide on how to watch NFL games without cable and live stream every game of the season. It offers options and platforms for streaming NFL games.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former FTX developer says he confronted an 'anxious' Sam Bankman-Fried on Bahamas paddleball court while trying to fix bug that led to $8 billion hole&lt;br&gt;- Business/Tech: A former FTX developer claims to have confronted Sam Bankman-Fried, the CEO of FTX, on a paddleball court in the Bahamas while attempting to fix a bug that resulted in an $8 billion loss. The article highlights the incident and its impact on FTX.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;See inside the $35 million 'Orchid' penthouse Sam Bankman-Fried lived in, with floor-to-ceiling ocean views and a rooftop pool&lt;br&gt;- Lifestyle/Real Estate: The article provides a glimpse inside the $35 million 'Orchid' penthouse where Sam Bankman-Fried, the CEO of FTX, resided. It showcases the luxurious features and amenities of the property.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuildZoom (better way to build custom homes) Is hiring a Growth Associate&lt;br&gt;- Business/Job Market: BuildZoom, a company offering a better way to build custom homes, is hiring a Growth Associate. The article highlights the job opportunity and provides information on the company.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;HP fails to derail claims that it bricks scanners on printers when ink runs low&lt;br&gt;- Tech: HP's attempt to dismiss claims that it intentionally disables scanners on printers when ink runs low has been unsuccessful. The article discusses the ongoing controversy and the potential impact on HP's reputation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sea trials of new acoustic deterrent device to keep orcas at bay&lt;br&gt;- Science/Environment: Sea trials are being conducted on a new acoustic deterrent device designed to keep orcas away. The article discusses the device's purpose and its potential benefits for marine conservation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forza Motorsport looks and feels like Forza but with an RPG hiding under the hood&lt;br&gt;- Gaming/Tech: The article explores the upcoming game Forza Motorsport, highlighting its similarities to previous installments but with the addition of RPG elements. It discusses the game's features and potential appeal to gamers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk is stonewalling the SEC, and now he’s getting sued&lt;br&gt;- Business/Legal: Elon Musk is facing a lawsuit for allegedly stonewalling the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The article discusses the legal battle between Musk and the SEC and its implications for his reputation and legal standing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEC to compel Elon Musk’s testimony in Twitter stock purchase probe&lt;br&gt;- Business/Legal: The SEC plans to compel Elon Musk to testify in a probe related to his Twitter stock purchase. The article highlights the regulatory scrutiny surrounding Musk's actions and the potential consequences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stoke Space raises $100M Series B as it looks to reach orbit by 2025&lt;br&gt;- Tech/Space: Stoke Space has raised $100 million in a Series B funding round as it aims to achieve orbit by 2025. The article discusses the company's funding and its goals in the space industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Janet Yellen has a good point about government support of the chip industry&lt;br&gt;- Business/Politics: The article highlights a point made by Janet Yellen regarding government support for the chip industry. It discusses the importance of government intervention and investment in the industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple iPad 2023 Release Date: Exactly Which iPads Are Coming When&lt;br&gt;- Tech: The article provides information on the release date of Apple iPads in 2023 and discusses the specific models that are expected to be launched. It offers insights into the upcoming iPad lineup.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This Week In XR: Wearable AI That Can ‘See’ And ‘Talk,’ New Celeb Deep Fakes Denounced&lt;br&gt;- Tech/Entertainment: The article covers the latest developments in extended reality (XR), including wearable AI that can "see" and "talk" and the denouncement of new celebrity deep fakes. It discusses the advancements and controversies in XR technology.</summary></entry></feed>