<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-31T20:02:14Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 31 Oct 2023 20:02:14</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-31T20:02:14Z</published><updated>2023-10-31T20:02:14Z</updated><id>ee2102b5-df87-475d-85c4-ad403282b156</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Genotyping strategies for tissues fixed with various embalming fluids&lt;br&gt;- The suitability of using domestic pigs (Sus spp.) as human proxies&lt;br&gt;- Muro Box-N40 | Programmable Mechanical Music Box by Muro Box Global&lt;br&gt;- 8BitDo’s NES buttons are a big, red, Nintendo-themed invitation to experiment&lt;br&gt;- This proptech startup says generative building design can change the way cities are built&lt;br&gt;- Alibaba unveils GPT-4 competitor "Tongyi Qianwen 2.0" and eight industry-specific models&lt;br&gt;- 'It's not that Huawei is superior, it's that Apple is inferior': What the Chinese internet is saying about the iPhone 15&lt;br&gt;- Tesla Cybertruck Price In Play Ahead Of November 30 Delivery Event&lt;br&gt;- When you win a Nobel Prize, this illustrator beautifully explains your idea&lt;br&gt;- Tesla's enduring power is even clearer after the EV competition in Detroit falls flat&lt;br&gt;- The iPod is officially 'vintage retro tech' now, and restored models sold out at Gen Z-favorite Urban Outfitters&lt;br&gt;- Jensen Huang, who got an Nvidia tattoo when its share price hit $100, says he's not getting inked again&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- A North Carolina restaurant shut down after filing a lawsuit against a next door cigar bar&lt;br&gt;- CD Rates and Savings Rates Today | Get the Top Rate for Your Deposits&lt;br&gt;- Personal Loan Interest Rates Today, October 31, 2023 | Lowest Rates for Your Personal Loan&lt;br&gt;- The Fed probably won't cut interest rates just yet &amp;mdash; but its next move is expected to be good for Americans&lt;br&gt;- Gold is set to rack up its best month since November 2022 with the Israel-Hamas war boosting demand for safe havens&lt;br&gt;- Meet the typical millionaire: College-educated people in their 50s and 60s who own a home and lots of stocks&lt;br&gt;- There's an easy way cities can lure in more holiday shoppers: Get rid of street parking&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage Interest Rates Today, October 31, 2023 | Rates Remain Scary High, but Relief May Come Soon&lt;br&gt;- Don’t blame the pandemic for all the empty storefronts on your street. Blame big banks.&lt;br&gt;- Walmart Spark delivery drivers are sick of customers asking them to bring deliveries into their homes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Behold the Nebulous Smear: al-Sūfī's Illustrated Book of Fixed Stars (ca. 1430)&lt;br&gt;- People shouldn’t pay such a high price for calling out AI harms&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Genotyping strategies for tissues fixed with various embalming fluids can provide valuable information for medical research and understanding human proxies.&lt;br&gt;- The use of programmable mechanical music boxes and Nintendo-themed buttons showcases the intersection of technology and entertainment.&lt;br&gt;- Proptech startups are revolutionizing the way cities are built through generative building design.&lt;br&gt;- The unveiling of Alibaba's GPT-4 competitor and industry-specific models highlights the advancements in natural language processing and AI.&lt;br&gt;- The Chinese internet's perception of Huawei and Apple reflects the ongoing competition in the smartphone market.&lt;br&gt;- Tesla's Cybertruck event and enduring power in the EV industry demonstrate its influence and market presence.&lt;br&gt;- The popularity of restored iPods among Gen Z reflects the nostalgia and demand for vintage tech.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of AI on society raises concerns about the high price individuals may pay for calling out AI harms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The report covers various topics including genotyping strategies, tech innovations, business trends, and AI developments. It highlights the advancements in technology, the influence of major companies like Tesla and Alibaba, and the concerns surrounding AI. Overall, the report showcases the diverse landscape of the tech and business industries and the ongoing impact they have on society.</summary></entry></feed>