<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-02T08:03:38Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 02 Dec 2023 08:03:38</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-02T08:03:38Z</published><updated>2023-12-02T08:03:38Z</updated><id>fc7f364e-00a3-4dd6-bae1-ea3765aaa88c</id><summary type="html">In the world news, there have been several obituaries reported. Edna Stargell's obituary was published by Colbert-Wiley Funeral &amp; Cremation Service, while Robert Stringer's obituary was released by Wiley Funeral Home in Granbury. In other news, a judicial candidate is planning to challenge the ballot designation of a rival, as reported by the Metropolitan News-Enterprise. A video has surfaced showing a Russian soldier claiming that some troops mixed river water in a can of meat and drank it for a week to avoid starvation. Leaks about the Samsung Galaxy S24 suggest that it will have a titanium build, a flattened screen, and other features. OpenAI's board has fired Altman, aiming to maintain an element of surprise. 23andMe has announced that hackers accessed a significant number of files containing users' ancestry information. Fisker, an electric vehicle startup, has reduced its 2023 production target for the fourth time. Additionally, there are reports on how to add/embed stream chat to OBS Studio, Israel's use of AI to identify targets for a "mass assassination factory," and advertisers stating that they won't return to Elon Musk's X for now. Apple Loop discusses iPhone 16 Pro design problems, NameDrop safety concerns, and Apple's fight against Spotify Unwrapped. Alderwood Dance Spectrum's 'A Storybook Nutcracker' is set to return, and Julie Wiley's obituary has been published by Dusckas Funeral Home and Cremations. There is also an article on the identification and analysis of pathogenic bacteria causing outbreaks. Italy is fighting against Airbnb, aiming to save Florence after losing Venice. Russia is reportedly equipping its tanks with jamming technology to counter exploding drones. At Parade, a failed Gen Z underwear startup, employee firings were often announced to the entire staff on Slack. The best TVs of 2023 are listed, including top picks from LG, TCL, Sony, Samsung, and Hisense. Fitbit Versa 3 is reviewed, highlighting its impressive health and fitness tracking features and multi-day battery life. Israel is utilizing AI to determine bombing targets in war-torn Gaza, resulting in a significant increase in the number of targets. Elon Musk, Bill Gates, and other wealthy individuals would reportedly pay $1 billion for Mar-a-Lago, as testified by a Trump expert at a fraud trial in New York. CBS News conducted an investigation revealing that cocoa is harvested by children as young as 5 in Ghana. An article from 1980 explores the concept of mass storage being free. KAIST researchers have introduced Quatro++, a robust global registration framework utilizing ground segmentation for loop closing in LiDAR SLAM. AI research presents a physics-based deep learning approach for predicting IFP and liposome accumulation. Android Circuit covers the massive update of Pixel 8 Pro, Honor's folding strategy, and the confirmation of OnePlus 12. Lastly, there are recommendations for new shows and movies to stream on Netflix, Hulu, HBO Max, Disney+, and more this weekend. The Biden administration has announced that the U.S. is making progress on some climate goals ahead of expectations.</summary></entry></feed>