<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LF AI RSS</title><link>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</link><description>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:55:12 -0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Briefing with LLM on Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:55:12</title><link>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</link><description>Recommerce Expo 2023 Featuring Tarun Pathak&lt;br&gt;Kevin Brown Orioles&lt;br&gt;Issue 1 Ohio&lt;br&gt;Clint Eastwood&lt;br&gt;ALS&lt;br&gt;MLS&lt;br&gt;青源Talk第43期丨视觉语言导航&lt;br&gt;韩国LK-99作者爆猛料：一家科技巨头已入局室温超导研究&lt;br&gt;面壁智能给大模型接入16000+真实API，效果直逼ChatGPT！&lt;br&gt;马斯克小扎「笼中格斗」要开直播了！网友用AI自制“预告片”嗨皮起来了&lt;br&gt;LK99吃瓜合集：完全悬浮后续遇难点、韩国作者称“超导是唯一可能的解释”，印度团队3次失败后放弃&lt;br&gt;Medical Publishing Market Research Report 2023-2028, Industry Growth, Share, Size and Forecast - EIN News&lt;br&gt;中美新闻一周说No.469 | 07.31-08.06&lt;br&gt;Cathie Wood预测：美国SEC将一次性批准多个比特币现货ETF&lt;br&gt;podman&lt;br&gt;Run Firefox on ChromeOS&lt;br&gt;Noclip.website: A digital museum of video game levels&lt;br&gt;The Alexander Piano&lt;br&gt;Jim Keller and his pioneering work on chip design and architecture&lt;br&gt;Researchers from NVIDIA and Tel Aviv University Introduce Perfusion: A Compact 100 KB Neural Network with Efficient Training Time&lt;br&gt;Seoul-based proptech Dongnae acquires co-living platform Dears&lt;br&gt;Apple Music adds a new algorithmic station to let users discover new music&lt;br&gt;Why is it important to write good code?&lt;br&gt;Node.js asynchronous flow control and event loop&lt;br&gt;Flutter's Rise in Web and Desktop Development: A Comprehensive Guide.&lt;br&gt;9家品牌携手成立国内首家新茶饮公益基金&lt;br&gt;恒生科技指数跌近3%&lt;br&gt;对话超级牛散李国飞：价值投资是你明白就明白，不明白就不明白&lt;br&gt;上海睿渠网络技术有限公司完成数千万元融资&lt;br&gt;地产股午后持续走弱&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Essay:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The content provided includes various topics ranging from technology, sports, entertainment, and finance. Recommerce Expo 2023 is mentioned, featuring Tarun Pathak, which could be an event focused on the commerce of used goods. Kevin Brown Orioles refers to a person named Kevin Brown associated with the Orioles, possibly a sports team. Issue 1 Ohio is unclear without further context. Clint Eastwood is a well-known actor and filmmaker. ALS stands for Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, a neurodegenerative disease. MLS could refer to Major League Soccer, a professional soccer league in the United States.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;青源Talk第43期丨视觉语言导航 seems to be a talk or discussion related to visual language navigation. 韩国LK-99作者爆猛料：一家科技巨头已入局室温超导研究 translates to "South Korean LK-99 author reveals explosive news: a tech giant has entered the field of room-temperature superconductivity research." This suggests that a significant development has occurred in the field of superconductivity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;面壁智能给大模型接入16000+真实API，效果直逼ChatGPT！ translates to "Facing Wall Intelligence connects large models to over 16,000 real APIs, with results approaching ChatGPT!" This indicates advancements in artificial intelligence and natural language processing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;马斯克小扎「笼中格斗」要开直播了！网友用AI自制“预告片”嗨皮起来了 translates to "Musk and Zuckerberg's 'cage fight' is going to be live-streamed! Netizens use AI to create 'trailer' and get excited!" This suggests that there is anticipation and excitement surrounding a live-streamed event involving Elon Musk and Mark Zuckerberg.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LK99吃瓜合集：完全悬浮后续遇难点、韩国作者称“超导是唯一可能的解释”，印度团队3次失败后放弃 translates to "LK99 Eating Melon Collection: Challenges after complete suspension, South Korean author claims 'superconductivity is the only possible explanation,' Indian team gives up after 3 failures." This indicates discussions and developments related to superconductivity and the challenges faced by different teams.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mention of a Medical Publishing Market Research Report suggests a report focused on the growth, share, size, and forecast of the medical publishing industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;中美新闻一周说No.469 | 07.31-08.06 translates to "China-US News Weekly No.469 | 07.31-08.06." This suggests a weekly news update or summary related to China and the United States.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cathie Wood预测：美国SEC将一次性批准多个比特币现货ETF translates to "Cathie Wood predicts: US SEC will approve multiple Bitcoin spot ETFs at once." This indicates a prediction made by Cathie Wood regarding the approval of Bitcoin exchange-traded funds by the US Securities and Exchange Commission.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The remaining content includes topics such as technology (podman, running Firefox on ChromeOS), video games (Noclip.website), music (Apple Music algorithmic station), coding (importance of writing good code, Node.js asynchronous flow control and event loop), and finance (Heng Seng Technology Index, funding for Shanghai Ruiqu Network Technology Co., weakness in real estate stocks).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, the content covers a wide range of subjects, including technology advancements, sports, entertainment, medical publishing, and financial news.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:55:12 -0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>