<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-09T08:01:08Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:01:08</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-09T08:01:08Z</published><updated>2023-08-09T08:01:08Z</updated><id>94818e2e-1e8c-4bd1-955d-1a1de1fbbf97</id><summary type="html">Kareem Hunt - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;Only Murders in the Building' Season 3 - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;Dave Portnoy buys Barstool Sports back for next to nothing, years after selling it - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;Is McDonald's about to drop a 'Loki' sauce? A viral TikTok video says yes - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;WeWork warns it has 'substantial doubt' about whether it can keep going as a business - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;3 steps small-business owners can take to build successful (and affordable) influencer collaborations - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;Can you earn 7% interest on a savings account? The fact and fiction of high APYs - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;I moved from Atlanta to rural Montana and documented my move on TikTok. Here's why I'm glad I did it. - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;LK-99: Phonon Bands, Localized Flat Band Magnetism, Models, &amp; Chemical Analysis - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;Exoplanets Could Help Us Learn How Planets Make Magnetism - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;HârnWorld: Kingdom of Azadmere by Columbia Games - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;Rook and Rose Pattern Deck by Marie Brennan - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;Barstool Sportsbook operator rebrands as ESPN Bet in a new $1.5 billion licensing deal - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;Verizon is shutting down the videoconferencing app it bought for $400 million - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;AIが生成したコンテンツを見分けるには「専用の文字」をつくればいい - Translate to English: "To distinguish AI-generated content, you can create "dedicated characters"."&lt;br&gt;Singapore wealth management platform Endowus raises $35M - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;WeWork goes from a $47B valuation to ‘substantial doubts’ about its ‘ability to continue as a going concern’ - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;Configure Grafana Cloud SAML to work with JumpCloud - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;The Ultimate Guide to building a UI Library - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;Decoding Starknet Part One: What is Blockchain, and why Starknet? - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;JavaScript Abuse — Article 1. JS vs. Python: Battle Royale - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;Data Engineering: Create a Apache Iceberg based Data Lakehouse on your Laptop - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;Navigating How AI Impacts Society and Shapes the Future of Work: A Short Note - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;AI Knows What You’re Typing Just By Hearing It Over a Zoom - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;Immortal Mars Helicopter Still Soars After Emergency Landing, Takes Photo of Its Buddy - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;How AI Could Predict the Outbreak of Infectious Diseases like Ebola - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;Walking Just 4,000 Steps A Day Enough To Lower Risk Of Death, New Study Reveals - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;Six Things You Didn’t Know About The Perseids Meteor Shower, Which Peaks This Weekend - No translation needed, as it is already in English.&lt;br&gt;今年以来新成立基金逾600只，数量和份额同比均下滑 - Translate to English: "Since the beginning of this year, there have been over 600 newly established funds, with both the quantity and shares declining compared to the same period."&lt;br&gt;我国成功发射环境减灾二号06星 - Translate to English: "Our country successfully launched the Environmental Disaster Reduction No. 06 satellite."</summary></entry></feed>