<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-15T20:02:46Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:02:46</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-15T20:02:46Z</published><updated>2023-09-15T20:02:46Z</updated><id>7b6aa03e-7391-48d1-bc70-e7ea149504c7</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Wiley BROS. Aintree Capital LLC makes new investment in NVIDIA.&lt;br&gt;- Wiley BROS. Aintree Capital LLC invests $214,000 in PepsiCo, Inc.&lt;br&gt;- Thermally-Induced Isomerization of Prenucleation Clusters During.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech section highlights investments made by Wiley BROS. Aintree Capital LLC in NVIDIA and PepsiCo, Inc. It also mentions the thermally-induced isomerization of prenucleation clusters.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Savings Account and CD Rates Today | More Banks Add 5% Rates.&lt;br&gt;- Most Americans don't trust companies to use AI responsibly, study finds.&lt;br&gt;- Luxury tycoon Bernard Arnault dismissed comparisons between his family and the Roys in 'Succession' and hopes there's no 'duel' to take over power.&lt;br&gt;- Retail investors pile into Arm stock on the first day of trading, seeking greater exposure to the AI boom.&lt;br&gt;- Sam Bankman-Fried said he was one of the 'most hated people in the world' in an unpublished Twitter thread written after he was arrested, report says.&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage Interest Rates Today, September 15, 2023 | Rates Sticking Around 7% for Now.&lt;br&gt;- Arm's red-hot stock debut captures the AI hype but it doesn't mean the IPO market has rebounded.&lt;br&gt;- California legislature passes law aiming to protect children from abusers during custody disputes.&lt;br&gt;- Younger baby boomers are facing a homelessness crisis as rents skyrocket and outpace Social Security.&lt;br&gt;- Citadel CEO Ken Griffin says he feels 'anxious' about 2023's stock market rally and warns the impact of higher interest rates will soon hit hard.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business section covers various topics such as savings account rates, trust in AI, luxury tycoon Bernard Arnault's comments, retail investors' interest in Arm stock, Sam Bankman-Fried's Twitter thread, mortgage interest rates, the IPO market, child protection laws, the homelessness crisis among younger baby boomers, and Citadel CEO Ken Griffin's concerns about the stock market rally and higher interest rates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Most Americans don't trust companies to use AI responsibly, study finds.&lt;br&gt;- Retail investors pile into Arm stock on the first day of trading, seeking greater exposure to the AI boom.&lt;br&gt;- Meet BLIVA: A Multimodal Large Language Model for Better Handling of Text-Rich Visual Questions.&lt;br&gt;- Five Ways To Leverage AI To Safeguard A Smooth Customer Experience.&lt;br&gt;- Arm's red-hot stock debut captures the AI hype but it doesn't mean the IPO market has rebounded.&lt;br&gt;- Creating Role and Permission Schemas for My Blog API using Chat GPT-4.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The AI section emphasizes the lack of trust in AI among Americans, retail investors' interest in Arm stock for AI exposure, the development of a multimodal language model, leveraging AI for a smooth customer experience, the impact of Arm's stock debut on the AI market, and the use of Chat GPT-4 for creating role and permission schemas.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine's attack on a Russian air-defense system may point to 'systemic tactical failures' with Russia's air defenses in Crimea, experts say.&lt;br&gt;- Recent arrests suggest Putin is quietly trying to rein in some of his most effective promoters of the war in Ukraine.&lt;br&gt;- Putin is 'scrounging around' for low-quality weapons by doing a deal with North Korea, US official says.&lt;br&gt;- Lauren Boebert denied vaping at the 'Beetlejuice' performance she was kicked out of. Video clearly shows she did.&lt;br&gt;- Challenging Bugs and Solutions of the Week: Share Your Stories! 🐞.&lt;br&gt;- Tesla's Cybertruck speaks to a thoughtful question asked by Elon Musk's son Saxon.&lt;br&gt;- A Black innovator gave us the modern shoe industry. Now, he has his own sneaker.&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine: Europe clearly overtakes US, with total commitments now twice as large.&lt;br&gt;- Effects of Fluorinated functionalization of Linker on Quercetin.&lt;br&gt;- Beyond Rattling: Tetrahedrites as Incipient Ionic Conductors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The other section covers various topics such as the Ukraine-Russia conflict, Putin's actions in Ukraine, weapons deals with North Korea, controversies surrounding Lauren Boebert, bug challenges, Tesla's Cybertruck, a Black innovator in the shoe industry, Ukraine's commitments, and the effects of fluorinated functionalization and tetrahedrites.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Wiley BROS. Aintree Capital LLC made investments in NVIDIA and PepsiCo, Inc.&lt;br&gt;- Americans lack trust in companies' responsible use of AI.&lt;br&gt;- Retail investors are interested in Arm stock for AI exposure.&lt;br&gt;- Various business topics, including mortgage rates, IPO market, child protection laws, and the homelessness crisis among younger baby boomers.&lt;br&gt;- AI developments include a multimodal language model and leveraging AI for customer experience.&lt;br&gt;- The Ukraine-Russia conflict and Putin's actions are significant.&lt;br&gt;- Controversies, bug challenges, and innovations in the shoe industry.&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine's commitments and the effects of fluorinated functionalization and tetrahedrites.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, the report highlights the intersection of technology, business, AI, and other topics, providing insights into various aspects of these fields.</summary></entry></feed>