<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-08T20:02:03Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:02:03</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-08T20:02:03Z</published><updated>2023-11-08T20:02:03Z</updated><id>3d357026-dc58-4f3e-bab4-43a409ad2dd5</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Amazon tracking: How to follow your package through every step in the shipping process and view or hide recent orders&lt;br&gt;- Meta's new way to handle AI-generated political ads basically relies on the honor system. Which will definitely work.&lt;br&gt;- Meta will start requiring disclosures for political ads manipulated with AI&lt;br&gt;- Samsung unveils ChatGPT alternative Samsung Gauss that can generate text, code and images&lt;br&gt;- This AI Research Introduces Breakthrough Methods for Tailoring Language Models to Chip Design&lt;br&gt;- The New York Times got its content removed from one of the biggest AI training datasets. Here's how it did it.&lt;br&gt;- Bridgewater's employee-rating system tracked even the lowest-paid workers — who could get dinged if the office ran out of soda, a book says&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- We moved to Mexico from Texas and have never been happier. We're saving $2,000 a month and can even afford to go to the dentist.&lt;br&gt;- A California native recently moved to a Kentucky city with 26,000 residents. She's able to live a much more fulfilling life closer to family at a much lower cost.&lt;br&gt;- 'Shark Tank' star Kevin O'Leary warns of a 'downsized America' as rising prices and loan payments force consumers to cut back&lt;br&gt;- Student-loan forgiveness and cheaper monthly payments are on the line as the GOP's plan to slash Education Department funding moves forward&lt;br&gt;- Trouble Brewing for RISC-V as Issue of Technology Transfer Is Questioned&lt;br&gt;- Sam Bankman-Fried’s trial has ended, but the fallout has just begun&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- X and TikTok are both under fire from the EU over hate speech and Israel-Hamas disinformation&lt;br&gt;- Meta's new way to handle AI-generated political ads basically relies on the honor system. Which will definitely work.&lt;br&gt;- Meta will start requiring disclosures for political ads manipulated with AI&lt;br&gt;- Samsung unveils ChatGPT alternative Samsung Gauss that can generate text, code and images&lt;br&gt;- This AI Research Introduces Breakthrough Methods for Tailoring Language Models to Chip Design&lt;br&gt;- The New York Times got its content removed from one of the biggest AI training datasets. Here's how it did it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The use of AI in various industries, such as tech and business, is becoming more prevalent.&lt;br&gt;- Companies like Meta and Samsung are developing AI technologies for different purposes, including political ad handling and language model customization.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of AI on society, including concerns over hate speech and disinformation, is being addressed by regulatory bodies like the EU.&lt;br&gt;- The potential benefits and challenges of AI in different sectors, such as shipping and chip design, are being explored.&lt;br&gt;- The role of AI in media, including content removal from AI training datasets, is a topic of discussion.&lt;br&gt;- Economic factors, such as rising prices and loan payments, can have implications for businesses and consumers.&lt;br&gt;- The potential consequences of policy decisions, such as education funding cuts, are being debated.&lt;br&gt;- The relocation of individuals and the cost of living are factors influencing personal and professional decisions.&lt;br&gt;- The use of technology, such as tracking systems, is improving customer experiences in e-commerce.&lt;br&gt;- The sustainability and ethical considerations of industries like fashion are being examined.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of employee-rating systems on workplace dynamics and fairness is a subject of interest.&lt;br&gt;- The availability and accessibility of basic services for vulnerable populations, such as youth in lockups, is a concern.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The report highlights the advancements and challenges in the fields of tech, business, and AI. It explores topics such as AI-generated political ads, shipping tracking systems, language model customization, and the impact of economic factors on businesses and consumers. It also discusses issues related to hate speech, disinformation, education funding, relocation, sustainability in fashion, employee-rating systems, and access to basic services for vulnerable populations. Overall, the report provides insights into the current trends and developments in these areas and emphasizes the need for ethical considerations and regulatory measures.</summary></entry></feed>