<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-25T20:02:50Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 25 Sep 2023 20:02:50</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-25T20:02:50Z</published><updated>2023-09-25T20:02:50Z</updated><id>f9c60cdd-978c-447a-909f-90865b2bd04d</id><summary type="html">Saudi Arabia Smartphone Shipments Grow 35% YoY in Q2 2023 on Strong Ramadan Sales (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Smartphone shipments in Saudi Arabia experienced a 35% year-on-year growth in the second quarter of 2023, driven by strong sales during the Ramadan period.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon invests up to four billion dollars in OpenAI competitor Anthropic (Tech, Business, AI)&lt;br&gt;- Amazon has made a significant investment of up to four billion dollars in Anthropic, a competitor of OpenAI. This move highlights Amazon's commitment to the field of artificial intelligence.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gateway Investment Advisers LLC Sells 11789 Shares of Ovintiv Inc ... - MarketBeat (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Gateway Investment Advisers LLC has sold 11,789 shares of Ovintiv Inc, according to MarketBeat. This transaction indicates a change in the investment strategy of Gateway Investment Advisers LLC.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Alameda Research staff realized FTX had gone down when they tried to order takeout on a company card and it was declined, ex-employee says (Tech, Business)&lt;br&gt;- Former employees of Alameda Research revealed that they became aware of FTX's downtime when their attempts to order takeout using company cards were declined. This incident sheds light on the impact of technical issues on business operations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I paid more for my house than it's worth, but it saved me a fortune in the long run (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Despite paying more for their house than its current market value, the individual believes that this decision has ultimately resulted in significant long-term savings. This perspective challenges the conventional notion of property value.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;US investors can't place wagers on the 2024 election, financial watchdog rules (Business)&lt;br&gt;- The financial watchdog has ruled that US investors are prohibited from placing wagers on the outcome of the 2024 election. This decision has implications for the gambling industry and the involvement of investors in political events.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atlanta is the US city seeing the biggest surge in people setting up their own businesses, beating out the likes of Austin and Seattle, according to LinkedIn data (Business)&lt;br&gt;- According to LinkedIn data, Atlanta is experiencing the highest increase in individuals starting their own businesses compared to cities like Austin and Seattle. This trend highlights Atlanta's growing entrepreneurial ecosystem.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millennials looking to buy a home are worrying about climate risk. They're not wrong. (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Millennials who are in the market to purchase a home are expressing concerns about climate risk. This article acknowledges the validity of their worries and emphasizes the importance of considering climate-related factors in real estate decisions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expect $100 to be the new normal for oil prices thanks to production cuts, higher interest rates, and lack of investment, JPMorgan energy analyst says (Business)&lt;br&gt;- A JPMorgan energy analyst predicts that oil prices will stabilize at around $100 due to factors such as production cuts, higher interest rates, and a lack of investment. This projection has implications for the energy industry and global markets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian soldier says Russia is leaving booby traps on the bodies of its own soldiers in the hope they will kill advancing Ukrainians (Business)&lt;br&gt;- A Ukrainian soldier has reported that Russia is placing booby traps on the bodies of its own soldiers, with the intention of causing harm to advancing Ukrainian forces. This revelation sheds light on the tactics employed in the ongoing conflict.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Personal Loan Interest Rates Today, September 25, 2023 | Today's Top Personal Loan Rates (Business)&lt;br&gt;- This article provides an overview of the current personal loan interest rates as of September 25, 2023. It offers insights into the prevailing rates for personal loans.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway just dumped another $130 million of HP stock - and has now sold nearly $300 million worth this month (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Berkshire Hathaway, led by Warren Buffett, has sold an additional $130 million worth of HP stock, bringing their total sales for the month to nearly $300 million. This move indicates a shift in Berkshire Hathaway's investment strategy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's defensive line is 'bending but not breaking' after Ukraine breached it, analyst says (Business)&lt;br&gt;- An analyst suggests that Russia's defensive line is showing resilience despite Ukraine's breach. This analysis provides insights into the ongoing conflict and the strategies employed by both sides.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rupert Murdoch has been watching too much 'Succession,' Brian Cox — the actor who played Logan Roy — joked as he weighed in on the media tycoon stepping down (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Actor Brian Cox, known for his portrayal of Logan Roy in the TV series "Succession," jokingly commented on Rupert Murdoch's decision to step down from his media empire. This anecdote offers a lighthearted perspective on the media industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why the head of Campari Americas thinks lateral career moves are an underrated tool for success (Business)&lt;br&gt;- The head of Campari Americas believes that lateral career moves are often overlooked as a valuable tool for achieving success. This perspective challenges the traditional notion of career advancement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A millennial who quit teaching to be a full-time Uber and Lyft driver has made $36,000 so far this year — but thinks it's better as a part-time gig (Business)&lt;br&gt;- A millennial who left their teaching job to become a full-time Uber and Lyft driver has earned $36,000 thus far in the year. However, they express the belief that driving for these platforms is more suitable as a part-time endeavor.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mortgage Interest Rates Today, September 25, 2023 | Rates Steady, but Where Will They go Next? (Business)&lt;br&gt;- This article provides an update on the current mortgage interest rates as of September 25, 2023. It raises the question of where these rates may be headed in the future.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York employers must include pay rates in job ads under new state law (Business)&lt;br&gt;- A new state law in New York mandates that employers include pay rates in their job advertisements. This legislation aims to promote transparency and address wage disparities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baby boomers are becoming homeless at a rate not seen since the Great Depression (Business)&lt;br&gt;- The rate of homelessness among baby boomers is reaching levels comparable to those seen during the Great Depression. This article sheds light on the challenges faced by this demographic group.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hiroia Hikaru V60 Smart Coffee Brewer - Powered by Hario by Hiroia (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Hiroia has introduced the Hikaru V60 Smart Coffee Brewer, a coffee brewing device powered by Hario. This product represents a fusion of technology and coffee brewing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bayonetta director and Platinum Games co-founder Hideki Kamiya is leaving the studio (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Hideki Kamiya, the director of Bayonetta and co-founder of Platinum Games, has announced his departure from the studio. This news has implications for the gaming industry and the future projects of Platinum Games.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon will invest up to $4 billion into OpenAI rival Anthropic (Tech, Business, AI)&lt;br&gt;- Amazon has committed to investing up to $4 billion in Anthropic, a competitor of OpenAI. This investment underscores Amazon's interest in the field of artificial intelligence.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;UC Berkeley's latest contribution to innovation is an innovative way to finance it (Tech, Business)&lt;br&gt;- UC Berkeley has developed a novel approach to financing innovation. This article highlights the university's contribution to the field of innovation and entrepreneurship.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AWS - Red Hat OpenShift for Everyone series ( I - Intro) (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Amazon Web Services (AWS) has launched the Red Hat OpenShift for Everyone series, providing an introduction to this technology. This initiative aims to make OpenShift more accessible to a wider audience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Greatest Transformation Since The Lightbulb? Three Ways Generative AI Will Catalyze AI Adoption (Tech, AI)&lt;br&gt;- Generative AI is predicted to bring about a significant transformation in the field of artificial intelligence, comparable to the impact of the lightbulb. This article explores three ways in which generative AI will accelerate AI adoption.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SoftBank May Slowly Be Starting To Play 'Offense' In AI Arms Race After Son's Promise (Tech, AI)&lt;br&gt;- SoftBank is potentially shifting its focus to playing "offense" in the AI arms race, following a promise made by its CEO, Masayoshi Son. This development has implications for the competitive landscape of AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global Medical Education Publishing Market [2023-2030] | Advanced Research Report - Benzinga (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Benzinga has released an advanced research report on the global medical education publishing market for the period 2023-2030. This report provides insights into the trends and dynamics of this industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Chinese official is telling property developers to 'transform' their businesses as there are more than enough empty homes to house all of China (Business)&lt;br&gt;- A former Chinese official is urging property developers to transform their businesses, citing the abundance of vacant homes that could potentially address China's housing needs. This perspective challenges the conventional approach to real estate development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Savings Account and CD Rates Today | Earn 5.50% on Savings Accounts (Business)&lt;br&gt;- This article presents the current savings account and CD rates, highlighting the opportunity to earn 5.50% on savings accounts. It provides insights into the prevailing interest rates for these financial products.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I moved states 5 days before we got the return-to-office order at Amazon, so I quit. I had no idea we'd be forced back into the office. (Business)&lt;br&gt;- An individual shares their experience of quitting their job at Amazon after relocating to a different state, only to receive a return-to-office order shortly after. This anecdote sheds light on the challenges faced by employees in navigating remote work policies.</summary></entry></feed>