<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-05T20:02:49Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 05 Dec 2023 20:02:49</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-05T20:02:49Z</published><updated>2023-12-05T20:02:49Z</updated><id>fb8322e4-0eb6-4ff8-9d13-e24c399981fb</id><summary type="html">In the world, there have been several significant events and developments. Firstly, there is a growing interest in leveraging Indian pulse proteins for plant-based mock meat, as highlighted in a publication by John Wiley. This indicates a shift towards more sustainable and environmentally friendly food options. Additionally, the passing of Norman Lloyd, as mentioned in an obituary by Colbert-Wiley Funeral &amp; Cremation Service, marks the loss of a notable individual. On the scientific front, MALDI mass spectrometry imaging and semi-quantification have made advancements, as reported by John Wiley. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the technology sector, Meta, IBM, AMD, and over 50 other companies and universities have come together to form the Open Source AI Alliance, demonstrating the collaborative efforts towards advancing artificial intelligence. Meanwhile, Coca-Cola has been ranked as the best place to work for career growth in a study of America's largest companies, highlighting its positive work environment. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the automotive industry, Elon Musk expressed his disapproval of Tesla's strike in Sweden, which has now spread to Denmark, causing disruptions. On a different note, a popular cruise line is offering $50-a-day sailings, but with the condition that travelers must be flexible with their plans. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The value of AI skills in the job market has been emphasized, with individuals who possess these skills potentially earning higher salaries. However, China's economy has suffered another blow as Moody's slashes its credit outlook, indicating ongoing challenges. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Nepal, the modernization of villages has put mokha art on the verge of disappearing, highlighting the potential loss of cultural heritage. On a positive note, Farmless, a company focused on alternative protein products, has received a new capital infusion, indicating progress in the field. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Various articles have been published on different topics, such as creating a pricing table with Range Slider using Tailwind CSS and Alpine.js, and the use of GPT-4V for screenshot to code in web development. Additionally, concerns about privacy and blackmail have arisen in the UK, as the government demands photo ID to access porn sites. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fast Company has provided a guide for designing an office that workers actually want to return to in 2024, highlighting the importance of creating a conducive work environment. Luxury brands like Louis Vuitton, Tiffany, and Dior are also taking steps towards sustainability in their stores. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of insights, an ex-FBI agent explains how to recognize power dynamics in a room, shedding light on interpersonal dynamics. The OpenAI debacle has also provided a lesson on the importance of responsible AI development. Furthermore, climate change has prompted a need to overcome fears about gene-editing plants to address the challenges ahead. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Various scientific research papers have been published, including one on waveguide-based Raman enhancement strategies, indicating advancements in the field. Additionally, a Chinese blogger has gone viral for lamenting the solitary lives of men in his nation, sparking discussions on social issues. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In San Francisco, the office vacancy rate has reached a record high of 35%, reflecting the impact of remote work and changing work dynamics. The gaming industry has also seen developments, with the introduction of the new Astro A50 X headset that allows seamless switching between consoles and PC. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the startup world, Omniful, a supply chain and e-commerce enablement startup, has emerged from stealth mode with a funding of $5.85 million. Carbon Maps, an environmental accounting startup for the food industry, has also gained new backers, indicating support for sustainable practices. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, there have been advancements in the field of artificial intelligence, with the introduction of EDGI, a groundbreaking equivariant diffuser for advanced model-based reinforcement learning and efficient planning, as unveiled by Qualcomm AI Research. Additionally, MMMU, a new AI benchmark for expert-level multimodal challenges, is paving the path towards artificial general intelligence.</summary></entry></feed>