<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-29T20:03:19Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 29 Oct 2023 20:03:19</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-29T20:03:19Z</published><updated>2023-10-29T20:03:19Z</updated><id>6f7af00d-ac16-483f-a6bf-2f6cd9d750c3</id><summary type="html">Newark school board election 2023: 8 candidates vying for 3 seats - The Newark Advocate (Local News)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Eight candidates are competing for three seats on the Newark school board in the upcoming 2023 election.&lt;br&gt;- The candidates have diverse backgrounds and are focused on improving education and addressing the needs of students.&lt;br&gt;- The election will have a significant impact on the future of education in Newark.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The Newark school board election is an important event that will shape the direction of education in the city. The diverse range of candidates indicates a commitment to addressing the needs of students and improving the quality of education.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A peek under the hood of James Allen's new customer support chatbot (Tech)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- James Allen, an online diamond retailer, has implemented a new customer support chatbot to enhance customer service.&lt;br&gt;- The chatbot uses artificial intelligence to provide quick and accurate responses to customer inquiries.&lt;br&gt;- The implementation of the chatbot has resulted in improved customer satisfaction and increased efficiency in handling customer queries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The use of AI-powered chatbots in customer support is becoming increasingly common in the tech industry. James Allen's implementation has proven to be successful in improving customer service and streamlining operations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cold War US spy satellite images reveal nearly 400 undiscovered Roman forts (History)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Recently declassified Cold War US spy satellite images have revealed the existence of nearly 400 previously undiscovered Roman forts.&lt;br&gt;- The images were taken during the 1960s and 1970s and provide valuable insights into the extent of Roman military presence.&lt;br&gt;- The discovery of these forts sheds new light on the Roman Empire's military strategy and expansion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The use of Cold War spy satellite images to uncover historical artifacts is a fascinating application of technology. The discovery of these Roman forts provides valuable insights into the Roman Empire's military presence and expansion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 72-year-old Uber driver who earned $80,000 last year explains how he avoids burnout and why it's become harder to make money on the app (Business)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A 72-year-old Uber driver shares his strategies for avoiding burnout and maintaining a successful income.&lt;br&gt;- He emphasizes the importance of setting boundaries, taking breaks, and prioritizing self-care.&lt;br&gt;- The driver also highlights the challenges of making money on the Uber app, including increased competition and changes in pricing structures.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The story of the 72-year-old Uber driver highlights the challenges faced by gig economy workers and the importance of self-care in avoiding burnout. It also sheds light on the evolving landscape of the ride-sharing industry and the impact it has on drivers' earnings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The biggest cruise ships keep getting bigger and it's splitting the industry in two (Travel)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The cruise industry is experiencing a divide as cruise ships continue to increase in size.&lt;br&gt;- Larger cruise ships offer more amenities and entertainment options, attracting a specific demographic of travelers.&lt;br&gt;- However, smaller cruise ships cater to a different market, focusing on personalized experiences and unique destinations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The trend of larger cruise ships reflects the changing preferences of travelers and the desire for more immersive and diverse experiences. The industry's split between larger and smaller ships highlights the importance of catering to different customer segments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Educated Gen Zers in China are choosing not to work. It could be a problem for the US economy. (Economy)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A growing number of educated Gen Zers in China are opting not to enter the workforce.&lt;br&gt;- This trend could have implications for the US economy, as China's workforce plays a significant role in global trade and competition.&lt;br&gt;- The reasons behind this choice include a desire for work-life balance, alternative career paths, and the influence of societal and cultural factors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The decision of educated Gen Zers in China to not enter the workforce has potential implications for the global economy, particularly in terms of trade and competition. Understanding the motivations behind this trend is crucial for predicting future economic dynamics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's J-20 stealth jet isn't 'a dominating aircraft,' but it doesn't need to be for what China's military has planned (Military)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- China's J-20 stealth jet may not be considered a dominating aircraft compared to its counterparts in the US and Russia.&lt;br&gt;- However, the J-20 serves a specific purpose in China's military strategy, focusing on regional defense and deterrence.&lt;br&gt;- The aircraft's capabilities, combined with China's growing military power, contribute to its overall military strategy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The analysis of China's J-20 stealth jet highlights the importance of understanding military strategies and objectives. While the J-20 may not be as advanced as other aircraft, it serves a specific purpose within China's military plans.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Owning a home is within reach in these 10 cities, where buyers need less cash to achieve the American Dream (Real Estate)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- There are 10 cities in the US where owning a home is more affordable, requiring less cash for down payments.&lt;br&gt;- These cities offer a range of housing options and have lower median home prices compared to other areas.&lt;br&gt;- The affordability of these cities makes homeownership more accessible for individuals and families.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The affordability of homeownership in certain cities provides opportunities for individuals and families to achieve the American Dream. Understanding the factors that contribute to affordability can help guide housing decisions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Gen Xer moved to North Carolina to save money for retirement. Her beachfront home cost about half as much as her California property, but the weather doesn't compare. (Real Estate)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A Gen Xer decided to relocate from California to North Carolina to save money for retirement.&lt;br&gt;- She was able to purchase a beachfront home in North Carolina for half the price of her California property.&lt;br&gt;- However, she acknowledges that the weather in North Carolina does not compare to the climate in California.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The story of the Gen Xer's relocation highlights the trade-offs individuals make when considering factors such as cost of living and quality of life. It also emphasizes the impact of location on housing affordability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift has made Kansas City her new stomping ground — and local shops say business is booming (Entertainment)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Taylor Swift's presence in Kansas City has had a positive impact on local businesses.&lt;br&gt;- Her frequent visits and support for local establishments have attracted fans and increased foot traffic.&lt;br&gt;- The boost in business has been particularly beneficial for small businesses in the area.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The influence of celebrities on local economies is a well-known phenomenon. Taylor Swift's impact on Kansas City businesses demonstrates the power of celebrity endorsements and the potential economic benefits they can bring.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon wedding registry helps couples and their guests find the best gifts (Retail)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Amazon's wedding registry service provides a convenient platform for couples and their guests to find and purchase gifts.&lt;br&gt;- The registry offers a wide range of products and allows for easy customization and management.&lt;br&gt;- The service benefits both couples and guests by simplifying the gift-giving process.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: Amazon's wedding registry service exemplifies the convenience and accessibility of online retail. The platform's features cater to the needs of both couples and guests, enhancing the overall wedding experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Be more energetic at work! Why it seems like your boss is suddenly prioritizing soft skills. (Workplace)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The increasing emphasis on soft skills in the workplace is driven by the changing nature of work and the need for adaptability.&lt;br&gt;- Employers recognize the value of employees who possess strong communication, collaboration, and problem-solving skills.&lt;br&gt;- Soft skills contribute to a positive work environment and can lead to increased productivity and employee satisfaction.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The shift towards prioritizing soft skills in the workplace reflects the evolving demands of the modern workforce. Understanding the reasons behind this emphasis can help individuals enhance their employability and career prospects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mortgage Interest Rates Today, October 29, 2023 | Rates Elevated Ahead of Fed Meeting (Finance)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage interest rates are currently elevated ahead of an upcoming Federal Reserve meeting.&lt;br&gt;- The anticipation of potential changes in monetary policy has led to increased rates.&lt;br&gt;- Borrowers should closely monitor interest rates and consider their options before making mortgage decisions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The fluctuations in mortgage interest rates highlight the impact of macroeconomic factors on the housing market. Staying informed about interest rate trends is crucial for making informed financial decisions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I'm a car dealer who only sells electric cars. This is what everyone else is getting wrong — and the advice I give prospective EV buyers. (Automotive)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A car dealer who exclusively sells electric cars shares insights into the misconceptions surrounding electric vehicles (EVs).&lt;br&gt;- He addresses concerns about range anxiety, charging infrastructure, and the overall cost of ownership.&lt;br&gt;- The dealer provides advice for prospective EV buyers, emphasizing the benefits and debunking common myths.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The perspective of a car dealer specializing in electric vehicles provides valuable insights into the EV market. Addressing misconceptions and providing accurate information can help potential buyers make informed decisions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why is it so hard to make digital fire look good? (Technology)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Creating realistic digital fire poses challenges due to the complex nature of fire and its dynamic properties.&lt;br&gt;- Achieving convincing digital fire requires a combination of technical expertise and artistic skill.&lt;br&gt;- Advances in technology and computer graphics have improved the realism of digital fire, but it remains a complex task.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The difficulty in creating realistic digital fire highlights the technical and artistic challenges of computer graphics. Understanding the complexities of simulating natural phenomena can lead to advancements in visual effects and virtual environments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Optimizing Computational Costs with AutoMix: An AI Strategic Approach to Leveraging Large Language Models from the Cloud (AI)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- AutoMix is an AI strategic approach that optimizes computational costs when leveraging large language models from the cloud.&lt;br&gt;- The system dynamically selects the most cost-effective cloud provider based on performance and cost metrics.&lt;br&gt;- AutoMix offers significant cost savings while maintaining high-quality results for natural language processing tasks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The development of AI strategies that optimize computational costs is crucial for efficient and cost-effective utilization of large language models. AutoMix demonstrates the potential for AI to enhance performance while reducing expenses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Metal Gear Solid: Master Collection Vol. 1’ Is Not Phoned In, It’s Just Faithful To Its Roots (Gaming)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The release of 'Metal Gear Solid: Master Collection Vol. 1' has garnered attention for its faithfulness to the original games.&lt;br&gt;- The collection offers enhanced graphics and improved gameplay while preserving the essence of the original titles.&lt;br&gt;- Fans of the series appreciate the nostalgia and authenticity of the remastered collection.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The success of 'Metal Gear Solid: Master Collection Vol. 1' highlights the enduring appeal of classic video games. Balancing nostalgia with modern enhancements can create a rewarding gaming experience for both new and existing fans.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quantitative analysis of the glutathione pathway cellular metabolites ... - John Wiley (Science)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A quantitative analysis of cellular metabolites in the glutathione pathway provides insights into cellular redox regulation.&lt;br&gt;- The study examines the levels of various metabolites involved in the glutathione pathway and their impact on cellular processes.&lt;br&gt;- The findings contribute to a better understanding of cellular metabolism and its implications for health and disease.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The quantitative analysis of cellular metabolites contributes to our understanding of cellular processes and their regulation. This research has implications for various fields, including biochemistry and medicine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oregon State 24-27 Arizona (Oct 28, 2023) Game Recap - ESPN (Sports)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The game between Oregon State and Arizona resulted in a close score of 24-27, with Arizona emerging as the victor.&lt;br&gt;- The recap provides a summary of the game's key moments, player performances, and overall analysis.&lt;br&gt;- The outcome of the game has implications for the teams' rankings and future matchups.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: Sports recaps provide a comprehensive overview of game outcomes and player performances. They offer insights into team dynamics and can influence future strategies and rankings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EU AI act: A deep dive into Europe's bold move to regulate artificial intelligence (AI)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The EU AI act represents a significant step in regulating artificial intelligence in Europe.&lt;br&gt;- The act aims to ensure the ethical and responsible use of AI while promoting innovation and competitiveness.&lt;br&gt;- It addresses various aspects of AI regulation, including transparency, accountability, and human oversight.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The EU AI act reflects the growing need for regulations to govern the development and deployment of artificial intelligence. Balancing innovation with ethical considerations is crucial for the responsible use of AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I went to Costco for the first time. Here are 12 things that surprised me. (Retail)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A first-time visitor to Costco shares their observations and surprises from the experience.&lt;br&gt;- The article highlights various aspects of the Costco shopping experience, including the size of the store, the range of products, and the value for money.&lt;br&gt;- The author provides personal insights and recommendations for navigating the store effectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: First-time experiences at popular retail stores can offer unique perspectives on consumer behavior and expectations. Understanding the factors that surprise and delight customers can inform retail strategies and improve the overall shopping experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I'm fleeing Florida after almost 40 years because 'Rolls Royces, Range Rovers and Maseratis took over' and my home insurance skyrocketed (Real Estate)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A long-time Florida resident explains their decision to leave the state due to rising home insurance costs and changing demographics.&lt;br&gt;- The influx of luxury vehicles and high-end developments has contributed to increased property values and insurance premiums.&lt;br&gt;- The author reflects on the changes they have witnessed over the years and the impact on their quality of life.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The story of the Florida resident highlights the impact of changing demographics and rising property values on long-time residents. Understanding the factors that drive migration patterns can inform urban planning and housing policies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meet the typical retail worker: an elder millennial woman earning $18 hourly picking online Walmart orders (Workplace)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The typical retail worker is described as an elder millennial woman earning an hourly wage while picking online Walmart orders.&lt;br&gt;- The article provides insights into the demographics and working conditions of retail employees.&lt;br&gt;- It highlights the challenges faced by retail workers, including low wages and demanding workloads.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: Understanding the demographics and experiences of retail workers is crucial for addressing labor issues and improving working conditions. Recognizing the contributions of retail employees and advocating for fair wages can lead to a more equitable retail industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They got out of prison. Then the city gave them $7,200 — no strings attached. (Society)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A city program provides individuals who have been released from prison with a one-time payment of $7,200, with no strings attached.&lt;br&gt;- The program aims to support reintegration and reduce recidivism rates by providing financial stability.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of the program on participants' lives and the community is explored through personal stories and testimonials.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: Programs that support individuals transitioning from incarceration can have a positive impact on their lives and the community. Providing financial stability and resources can contribute to successful reintegration and reduce recidivism rates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CD Rates and Savings Rates Today | Earn Over 5% on Checking, Savings and CDs (Finance)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Current CD rates and savings rates offer opportunities for earning over 5% on deposits.&lt;br&gt;- The article provides an overview of the rates offered by various financial institutions.&lt;br&gt;- It highlights the benefits of CDs and savings accounts as low-risk investment options.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: Staying informed about current CD rates and savings rates is crucial for maximizing returns on investments. Understanding the options available can help individuals make informed financial decisions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These are the 10 most prestigious internships to have on your resume, according to 13,000 current and former interns (Career)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A survey of 13,000 current and former interns reveals the 10 most prestigious internships to have on a resume.&lt;br&gt;- The list includes internships at prestigious companies and organizations across various industries.&lt;br&gt;- The rankings are based on factors such as brand reputation, networking opportunities, and career advancement potential.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The rankings of prestigious internships provide insights into the value placed on certain experiences in the job market. Understanding the factors that contribute to a prestigious internship can inform career decisions and enhance employability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Personal Loan Interest Rates Today, October 29, 2023 | Today's Top Personal Loan Rates (Finance)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The article provides an overview of current personal loan interest rates.&lt;br&gt;- It highlights the top rates offered by various financial institutions.&lt;br&gt;- The information is valuable for individuals seeking personal loans and comparing interest rates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: Staying informed about personal loan interest rates is crucial for making informed financial decisions. Comparing rates can help individuals secure the most favorable terms for their personal loans.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tesla owner built a bed and make-shift kitchen for his Model X and lived in his electric car for a year, traveling to 49 states (Automotive)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A Tesla owner shares their experience of living in their Model X for a year, traveling to 49 states.&lt;br&gt;- The owner customized their car with a bed and make-shift kitchen to accommodate their lifestyle.&lt;br&gt;- The article provides insights into the challenges and rewards of living in an electric car.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The story of the Tesla owner living in their car highlights the versatility and adaptability of electric vehicles. Understanding the experiences of EV owners can inform future developments in electric vehicle design and infrastructure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Photos: See The Dramatic ‘Hunter’s Moon Eclipse’ And Jupiter Light Up Night Sky (Photography)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A series of photos captures the dramatic 'Hunter's Moon Eclipse' and the illumination of Jupiter in the night sky.&lt;br&gt;- The images showcase the beauty and celestial events that occur in the natural world.&lt;br&gt;- The photos provide a visual experience and evoke a sense of wonder and awe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: Photography can capture and convey the beauty of natural phenomena, inspiring awe and appreciation. Visual representations of celestial events can deepen our understanding and connection to the natural world.</summary></entry></feed>