<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-19T08:03:34Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 19 Oct 2023 08:03:34</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-19T08:03:34Z</published><updated>2023-10-19T08:03:34Z</updated><id>a2d92687-b7b7-4926-901a-51dd7078c289</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Thunder Promotes Katrina Wiley to Vice President, People and Culture - NBA.com&lt;br&gt;- Are CDs safe? Find out if a CD is a good place to store your money&lt;br&gt;- AlmaLinux stays Red Hat Enterprise Linux compatible without Red Hat code&lt;br&gt;- Ask HN: Why did the number of new GitHub repos crash in late 2022&lt;br&gt;- Only Nintendo DS lovers will fully appreciate this dual-screen handheld PC&lt;br&gt;- Here we go: all the news about Super Mario Bros. Wonder&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Zero to Employment Hero: HR unicorn nabs $167M to be Australia’s ‘biggest export since Atlassian’&lt;br&gt;- Made Renovation, which intrigued, then infuriated, its customers, is shutting down&lt;br&gt;- Enemy of the right, deserted by the left: Is ESG’s future grim in a new anti-woke society?&lt;br&gt;- Issa Rae talks launching her own prosecco and building a creative empire&lt;br&gt;- Harlan Crow, the GOP megadonor and pal to Clarence Thomas, maxed out his campaign donation to a self-described 'non-Marxist socialist' trying to defeat Joe Biden&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Humans have launched so much to space that it's actually polluting Earth's atmosphere, a new study found&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- "A long time coming" - The New Era - Sweet Home New Era&lt;br&gt;- Damian Perkins Obituary - O. W. Wiley Mortuary - Houston - 2023 - Legacy.com&lt;br&gt;- Personal Loan Interest Rates Today, October 19, 2023 | Today's Top Personal Loan Rates&lt;br&gt;- Judge in Sam Bankman-Fried trial reams out lawyers for having witnesses 'hauled up here' from across the country without much to say&lt;br&gt;- A rediscovered passageway in an Egyptian Pyramid has revealed hidden rooms that could hold riches from ancient royals&lt;br&gt;- An 87-year-old deal is keeping a lid on the naval war in Ukraine — for now&lt;br&gt;- Photos show daily operations aboard USS Gerald R. Ford in the eastern Mediterranean, where it's in place to support Israel&lt;br&gt;- Aftermath images from the Gaza hospital explosion are 'inconsistent' with an Israeli airstrike, former UN war crimes investigator says&lt;br&gt;- Emily Sings, a Video Recording and Premier Concert by Donald Skoog&lt;br&gt;- Elfin Fountain - Revolutionary Pumpless Fountain for Pets by Elfin Fountain&lt;br&gt;- Songs for the Bees: A Gay Woman's Journey of Faith by Linden Hope&lt;br&gt;- FRANKENSTEIN VISIONS - Deluxe Art Book. A MONSTER Gallery! by Slampress Tomes&lt;br&gt;- VOLFGANG TWINS ENTER VALHALLA &amp; RAGNARÖK Twin Pack Album Set by VOLFGANG TWINS&lt;br&gt;- Hit Snooze: More Sleep Could Boost Morning Alertness - Neuroscience News&lt;br&gt;- William R. “Bill” Wiley, 92 – Ellwood City, PA news - EllwoodCity.org&lt;br&gt;- Companies won't hire these women to drive trucks because of their gender, a new lawsuit says.&lt;br&gt;- What are conforming vs. non-conforming loans, and which of these mortgages is right for you?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section includes news about promotions, financial products, and developments in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- The business section covers funding, company closures, societal trends, and interviews with successful entrepreneurs.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section highlights the negative impact of space exploration on Earth's atmosphere.&lt;br&gt;- The other section consists of various topics such as obituaries, legal proceedings, archaeological discoveries, art, music, and social issues.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report provides a diverse range of news and insights across different categories.</summary></entry></feed>