<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-17T20:02:13Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 17 Sep 2023 20:02:13</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-17T20:02:13Z</published><updated>2023-09-17T20:02:13Z</updated><id>28b8ef05-8a9d-42c1-9887-8f5e906c1953</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- This AI Paper Introduces Agents: An Open-Source Python Framework for Autonomous Language Agents&lt;br&gt;- Tech Bros Lectured Congress About AI "Like Schoolchildren" Who Weren't Allowed to Raise Hands&lt;br&gt;- The OM System LS-P5 Is A Brilliant Pocket-Sized Recording Studio&lt;br&gt;- "Chain of Density" prompt aims to improve AI summaries by packing more info into fewer words&lt;br&gt;- SpaceX engineer risked drunk driving rather than ignore an Elon Musk order: book&lt;br&gt;- 8 major takeaways from the explosive new book about Elon Musk that lifts the lid on the world's richest person&lt;br&gt;- Wall Street is turning cautious on US stocks, while some experts warn of pain ahead. Here's what JPMorgan, Jeremy Grantham and others have said.&lt;br&gt;- Save some bytes when using multiple themes in angular material components&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- An AI paper introduces an open-source Python framework for autonomous language agents.&lt;br&gt;- Tech bros lectured Congress about AI in a condescending manner.&lt;br&gt;- The OM System LS-P5 is a compact recording studio.&lt;br&gt;- The "Chain of Density" prompt aims to improve AI summaries.&lt;br&gt;- A SpaceX engineer risked drunk driving to follow an order from Elon Musk.&lt;br&gt;- The explosive new book about Elon Musk reveals major insights into his life.&lt;br&gt;- Wall Street is becoming cautious about US stocks, with warnings of potential pain ahead.&lt;br&gt;- Tips for saving bytes when using multiple themes in angular material components.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The development of open-source frameworks for autonomous language agents shows progress in AI technology.&lt;br&gt;- The condescending behavior of tech bros towards Congress highlights the need for better communication and understanding between the tech industry and policymakers.&lt;br&gt;- The compact recording studio offers convenience and portability for musicians.&lt;br&gt;- Improving AI summaries can enhance the efficiency and effectiveness of information processing.&lt;br&gt;- The anecdote about the SpaceX engineer showcases the dedication and commitment of employees in the company.&lt;br&gt;- The book about Elon Musk provides valuable insights into his success and challenges.&lt;br&gt;- Cautiousness in the stock market indicates potential risks and uncertainties.&lt;br&gt;- Tips for optimizing code can help developers improve efficiency in their projects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Master Plan Going to Plan as Tesla Hits New Milestone with 5 Millionth EV&lt;br&gt;- The billionaire son of H&amp;M's founder owns a sprawling English country estate with over 100 cottages, a distillery, and a pub that sells his own beer&lt;br&gt;- Biden's economic policies have quietly made peoples' lives better &amp;mdash; and no one seems to care&lt;br&gt;- State Board of Administration of Florida Retirement System Buys ... - MarketBeat&lt;br&gt;- Reading Public Museum announces ‘Voyage to the Deep’ exhibition, film screening, bus trip - Reading Eagle&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Tesla achieves a new milestone with the production of its 5 millionth electric vehicle.&lt;br&gt;- The billionaire son of H&amp;M's founder owns an extensive estate with various amenities.&lt;br&gt;- Biden's economic policies have had positive impacts, but they have gone unnoticed.&lt;br&gt;- The State Board of Administration of Florida Retirement System makes a significant purchase.&lt;br&gt;- The Reading Public Museum announces an upcoming exhibition and events.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Tesla's achievement in reaching the 5 millionth EV milestone demonstrates the success of its master plan.&lt;br&gt;- The billionaire's estate showcases the wealth and lifestyle of affluent individuals.&lt;br&gt;- The lack of recognition for Biden's economic policies raises questions about public awareness and perception.&lt;br&gt;- The investment made by the State Board of Administration of Florida Retirement System indicates confidence in the market.&lt;br&gt;- The upcoming exhibition and events organized by the Reading Public Museum offer cultural and educational opportunities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- This AI Paper Introduces Agents: An Open-Source Python Framework for Autonomous Language Agents&lt;br&gt;- Tech Bros Lectured Congress About AI "Like Schoolchildren" Who Weren't Allowed to Raise Hands&lt;br&gt;- "Chain of Density" prompt aims to improve AI summaries by packing more info into fewer words&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- An AI paper introduces an open-source Python framework for autonomous language agents.&lt;br&gt;- Tech bros lectured Congress about AI in a condescending manner.&lt;br&gt;- The "Chain of Density" prompt aims to improve AI summaries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The development of open-source frameworks for autonomous language agents shows progress in AI technology.&lt;br&gt;- The condescending behavior of tech bros towards Congress highlights the need for better communication and understanding between the tech industry and policymakers.&lt;br&gt;- Improving AI summaries can enhance the efficiency and effectiveness of information processing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of insights:&lt;br&gt;- The advancements in AI technology are evident through the introduction of open-source frameworks and improvements in AI summaries.&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry's relationship with policymakers needs improvement to foster better understanding and collaboration.&lt;br&gt;- Positive economic impacts from Biden's policies may be overlooked, raising questions about public awareness and perception.&lt;br&gt;- Tesla's milestone achievement in EV production showcases the success of its master plan.&lt;br&gt;- The investment decisions made by the State Board of Administration of Florida Retirement System indicate confidence in the market.&lt;br&gt;- The upcoming exhibition and events organized by the Reading Public Museum offer cultural and educational opportunities.&lt;br&gt;- The book about Elon Musk provides valuable insights into his success and challenges.&lt;br&gt;- Cautiousness in the stock market indicates potential risks and uncertainties.&lt;br&gt;- Tips for optimizing code can help developers improve efficiency in their projects.</summary></entry></feed>