<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-09T12:00:52Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 09 Aug 2023 12:00:52</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-09T12:00:52Z</published><updated>2023-08-09T12:00:52Z</updated><id>411c1242-e2f6-4820-b9bc-3124310d8d5c</id><summary type="html">Vite report on Wed, 09 Aug 2023 10:14:07&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Categories and Highlights:&lt;br&gt;1. Technology:&lt;br&gt;   - supabase/postgres_lsp: A technology project related to Postgres database.&lt;br&gt;   - StanGirard/quivr: A technology project related to virtual reality.&lt;br&gt;   - Z4nzu/hackingtool: A technology project related to hacking tools.&lt;br&gt;   - The-Run-Philosophy-Organization/run: A technology project related to running.&lt;br&gt;   - gocolly/colly: A technology project related to web scraping.&lt;br&gt;   - AutomaApp/automa: A technology project related to automation.&lt;br&gt;   - tauri-apps/tauri: A technology project related to building desktop apps.&lt;br&gt;   - frappe/frappe: A technology project related to enterprise resource planning.&lt;br&gt;   - jamesmurdza/awesome-ai-devtools: A technology project related to AI development tools.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. International Relations:&lt;br&gt;   - France vs Morocco: Information about a match or event involving France and Morocco.&lt;br&gt;   - Ukrainian troops are getting just weeks of training on military equipment that takes months to master.&lt;br&gt;   - Russia accuses Ukraine of orchestrating a phone scam scheme to trick elderly Russians into setting military recruitment offices on fire amid string of arson attacks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Food and Beverage:&lt;br&gt;   - Phan's Gourmet: Wood-Fired Cashews - Crafted in Small Batch by Long (Ron) Phan.&lt;br&gt;   - Super Dirt Foods: Convenient Wellness in Snack Form by Kristin O'Connor.&lt;br&gt;   - Match Point Brewing: Asian American Inspired Craft Beers by Simon.&lt;br&gt;   - Jewish Cowboy: A Jewish+Southern Experience by The Jewish Cowboy.&lt;br&gt;   - A KW Collards Commercial Kitchen by Kizito Wademi.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The technology section highlights various projects related to different aspects such as databases, virtual reality, hacking tools, automation, web scraping, and AI development tools.&lt;br&gt;- The international relations section mentions the ongoing tensions between Ukraine and Russia, with accusations of phone scam schemes and arson attacks.&lt;br&gt;- The food and beverage section showcases different culinary experiences and products, including wood-fired cashews, wellness snacks, craft beers, and unique cultural experiences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conclusion:&lt;br&gt;This report provides a snapshot of various topics, including technology projects, international relations, and food and beverage offerings. It highlights the diversity of interests and developments in these areas.</summary></entry></feed>