<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-16T06:01:32Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 16 Aug 2023 06:01:32</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-16T06:01:32Z</published><updated>2023-08-16T06:01:32Z</updated><id>9d897c81-8d97-479d-8fae-c72637dd4eb3</id><summary type="html">Report: Global Insights on Tech, Business, and AI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Tech&lt;br&gt;1.1 Netflix Expands Gaming Experience to More Devices: A New Era of Streaming Entertainment&lt;br&gt;- Netflix is expanding its gaming experience to reach more devices, signaling a new era of streaming entertainment.&lt;br&gt;- This move aims to attract a wider audience and enhance user engagement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1.2 Best Mint Mobile plans and deals in August 2023: every plan is $15 a month, save $200 on a Pixel 7 Pro&lt;br&gt;- Mint Mobile offers affordable plans, with every plan priced at $15 per month.&lt;br&gt;- Customers can also save $200 on a Pixel 7 Pro smartphone through their deals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1.3 Apple’s third-gen AirPods are matching their best price to date right now&lt;br&gt;- Apple's third-generation AirPods are currently available at their best price ever.&lt;br&gt;- This presents an opportunity for consumers to purchase the popular wireless earbuds at a discounted rate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1.4 ReductStore 1.6.0 has been released with new license and client SDK for Rust&lt;br&gt;- ReductStore has released version 1.6.0, featuring a new license and client SDK for Rust.&lt;br&gt;- This update aims to improve the functionality and accessibility of the software.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1.5 The Industry Discussion About Standards For Bluetooth-Enabled Physical Trackers is Finally Getting Started&lt;br&gt;- The industry is finally starting to discuss standards for Bluetooth-enabled physical trackers.&lt;br&gt;- This development is crucial for ensuring interoperability and seamless integration of these devices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1.6 The Art Of Connectivity: What Art Can Teach Us About Data&lt;br&gt;- The intersection of art and data can provide valuable insights into connectivity.&lt;br&gt;- Artists can offer unique perspectives on how data can be visualized and understood.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1.7 Drawing Stuff: AI Can Really Cook! How Far Can It Go?&lt;br&gt;- AI has shown remarkable capabilities in various fields, including cooking.&lt;br&gt;- The potential of AI in culinary arts and food preparation is being explored.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Business&lt;br&gt;2.1 An ex-Mafia hitman says Trump and Giuliani shouldn't face RICO charges because they aren't real criminals like he was&lt;br&gt;- An ex-Mafia hitman argues that Trump and Giuliani should not face RICO charges as they do not meet the criteria of being "real criminals."&lt;br&gt;- This perspective sheds light on the complexities of legal definitions and perceptions of criminality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2.2 These 6 senators made more money from selling books than from their day jobs last year&lt;br&gt;- Six senators earned more money from book sales than from their primary occupations in the past year.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the potential financial opportunities for politicians through book publishing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2.3 Home Depot sees shoppers pulling back. So why is Warren Buffett bullish on home builder stocks?&lt;br&gt;- Despite Home Depot experiencing a decline in shopper activity, Warren Buffett remains optimistic about home builder stocks.&lt;br&gt;- This raises questions about the factors influencing Buffett's investment decisions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2.4 Chicken Soup for the Soul Entertainment cuts costs a year after buying Redbox&lt;br&gt;- Chicken Soup for the Soul Entertainment is implementing cost-cutting measures following its acquisition of Redbox.&lt;br&gt;- This strategic move aims to optimize operations and improve profitability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2.5 House Republicans were rewarded for supporting Donald Trump’s ‘stop the steal’ efforts&lt;br&gt;- House Republicans who supported Donald Trump's "stop the steal" efforts were rewarded politically.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the influence of loyalty and alignment with specific political narratives.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. AI&lt;br&gt;3.1 Hear a classic Pink Floyd song reconstructed from listeners’ brain waves&lt;br&gt;- Researchers have reconstructed a classic Pink Floyd song based on listeners' brain waves.&lt;br&gt;- This showcases the potential of AI in interpreting and recreating musical experiences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3.2 The autophagy machinery interacts with EBV capsids during viral envelope release&lt;br&gt;- The autophagy machinery plays a role in the release of EBV capsids during viral infection.&lt;br&gt;- This discovery contributes to our understanding of the mechanisms behind viral replication.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3.3 Unusual magnetotransport in twisted bilayer graphene from strain-induced open Fermi surfaces&lt;br&gt;- Strain-induced open Fermi surfaces in twisted bilayer graphene lead to unusual magnetotransport phenomena.&lt;br&gt;- This research expands our knowledge of the unique properties of graphene and its potential applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3.4 WASF3 disrupts mitochondrial respiration and may mediate exercise intolerance in myalgic encephalomyelitis/chronic fatigue syndrome&lt;br&gt;- WASF3, a protein, disrupts mitochondrial respiration and may be linked to exercise intolerance in myalgic encephalomyelitis/chronic fatigue syndrome.&lt;br&gt;- This finding provides insights into the underlying mechanisms of this debilitating condition.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Overall Insights&lt;br&gt;- The expansion of streaming entertainment platforms like Netflix into gaming signifies a convergence of media forms.&lt;br&gt;- Affordable mobile plans and deals continue to attract consumers in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- The intersection of art and data offers unique perspectives on connectivity and visualization.&lt;br&gt;- The complexities of legal definitions and perceptions of criminality are highlighted in the case of Trump and Giuliani.&lt;br&gt;- Financial opportunities through book publishing can be lucrative for politicians.&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's optimism about home builder stocks raises questions about market trends.&lt;br&gt;- AI's potential in music reconstruction and medical research continues to advance.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of political narratives and loyalty on rewards and consequences is evident.&lt;br&gt;- Advancements in graphene research contribute to our understanding of its properties and applications.&lt;br&gt;- Insights into the mechanisms of diseases like myalgic encephalomyelitis/chronic fatigue syndrome provide potential avenues for treatment and management.&lt;br&gt;- The report highlights the importance of standards and discussions in emerging technologies like Bluetooth-enabled physical trackers.</summary></entry></feed>