<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-04T08:03:45Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:03:45</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-04T08:03:45Z</published><updated>2023-12-04T08:03:45Z</updated><id>8e3ad897-d1db-4005-a5b8-3d31cc8ad96e</id><summary type="html">In recent news, the Sackler family, known for their involvement in the distribution of oxycontin, has filed for bankruptcy in an attempt to gain immunity from civil lawsuits. However, this move may be deemed illegal. Liz Cheney has accused now-Speaker Mike Johnson of being a collaborator in former President Trump's efforts to overturn the 2020 presidential election. A leak on TikTok suggests that a Rockstar Games employee's child may have revealed information about the highly anticipated Grand Theft Auto 6. DeepMind's cofounder, Demis Hassabis, who is also a chess champion, secured funding from Peter Thiel by discussing a key tension in the game. The Texas GOP voted against a proposed ban on members associating with Nazi sympathizers, sparking controversy. In another development, dozens of controversial figures who were pardoned by former President Trump are now contributing to his 2024 bid or spreading his false election claims. Three gaming-focused Linux operating systems have surpassed Windows 11 in gaming benchmarks. Additionally, there are discussions about the best websites for teens and college students to earn money online. The devastating El Niño rains in Kenya have caused flooding and claimed the lives of over 120 people. In the Red Sea, a US warship and multiple commercial vessels were attacked near Yemen, potentially escalating the conflict in the Middle East. Larry Page accused Elon Musk of favoring the human species over digital life forms during a debate about the dangers of artificial intelligence. The challenges of sleep becoming more elusive as we age are being explored, particularly in relation to shifts in "sleep architecture." Arm has launched the Cortex-M52, its smallest processor with Helium, for IoT applications. There is also a new tool called Report Phone Spam that aims to shut down robocallers and text spammers. COP28 has seen an artist collaborating with Google to create an interactive experience highlighting the freshwater crisis. The importance of copper to the future of electric vehicles was emphasized in the Extreme E Finale. Finally, Charlie Munger, an investing legend, is being remembered for his dedication to lifelong learning.</summary></entry></feed>