<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-18T20:01:10Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 18 Aug 2023 20:01:10</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-18T20:01:10Z</published><updated>2023-08-18T20:01:10Z</updated><id>a03d9412-c269-45e3-9a60-d3ab1ec23cb7</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- A driverless car in San Francisco got stuck in wet concrete after mistaking it for a regular road.&lt;br&gt;- Google DeepMind is testing an AI that can give life advice to users.&lt;br&gt;- Acronym and Asus have collaborated on a new computer.&lt;br&gt;- Google reminds users to clean their Pixel Buds regularly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- VinFast's shares plummeted after its market debut.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk believes Warren Buffett missed out on investing in Tesla.&lt;br&gt;- Uber and Lyft may face challenges in Minneapolis.&lt;br&gt;- A real-estate listing in Michigan went viral for its $1 price tag.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from MIT and Harvard propose a hypothesis on building a transformer using biological elements in the brain.&lt;br&gt;- Prompt Engineering Technique aims to bring certainty and uncertainty of generative AI to the forefront.&lt;br&gt;- The AI hype cycle experiences setbacks as some of this year's biggest winners face challenges.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Americans are depleting their excess savings and could run out of funds this quarter, according to a Fed study.&lt;br&gt;- Free live stream available for the Women's World Cup Final between England and Spain.&lt;br&gt;- A Russian-backed general admits his troops cannot win against Ukraine.&lt;br&gt;- A rare Ferrari 250 GTO could be auctioned for $60 million.&lt;br&gt;- The vulnerability of healthcare supply chains is highlighted by a chemo drug storage incident.&lt;br&gt;- Families of dead Russian soldiers are being charged $1,500 to retrieve their bodies.&lt;br&gt;- China's slashing of US bond holdings contributes to a bond rout.&lt;br&gt;- Former teachers share their reasons for leaving the profession due to unpaid work.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The AI industry continues to advance with applications in various fields.&lt;br&gt;- Economic challenges and market fluctuations impact businesses and investments.&lt;br&gt;- Geopolitical tensions and conflicts affect international relations and human rights.&lt;br&gt;- The real estate market can experience unusual and viral listings.&lt;br&gt;- Personal experiences and burnout can lead individuals to make career changes.</summary></entry></feed>