<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-20T20:02:12Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 20 Oct 2023 20:02:12</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-20T20:02:12Z</published><updated>2023-10-20T20:02:12Z</updated><id>071b953e-2c01-49eb-8549-e48575895bb9</id><summary type="html">Report: Language Translation and Insights&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Wiley Analytical Science Virtual Conference - 2023 - John Wiley &amp; Sons&lt;br&gt;- Stereochemistry of aminoacylated cardiolipins and ... - John Wiley &amp; Sons&lt;br&gt;- How to Sustain Quality and Velocity in a JavaScript or TypeScript Project?&lt;br&gt;- This AI tool can estimate the chances of survival for cancer patients&lt;br&gt;- CRISPR chickens hint at what’s next for the gene-modified food chain&lt;br&gt;- JetBrains Rider 2023.3 EAP 2 Is Out: Debugger Data Flow Analysis, All-In-One Diff Viewer and More&lt;br&gt;- How Recast AI Improves Your Daily Reading Lifestyle and Boosts Productivity&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft Researchers Propose DeepSpeed-VisualChat: A Leap Forward in Scalable Multi-Modal Language Model Training&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech section of the report highlights various advancements and developments in the field. Key points include the Wiley Analytical Science Virtual Conference, the use of AI tools in healthcare, the potential of CRISPR technology in agriculture, and the release of new software and tools by companies like JetBrains and Microsoft. These advancements have the potential to revolutionize industries and improve productivity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Wiley College, Texas Southern University form new partnership - Marshall News Messenger&lt;br&gt;- Personal Loan Interest Rates Today, October 20, 2023 | Today's Top Personal Loan Rates&lt;br&gt;- A millionaire who retired at 43 says he made 3 money mistakes on the road to financial independence&lt;br&gt;- CD Rates and Saving Rates Today | Earn top interest rates on your deposits&lt;br&gt;- Meet the candidates in the running to replace James Gorman as Morgan Stanley's CEO&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's fortune plunged by $16 billion in a single day - but he could lose a lot more and still be the richest person in the world&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage Interest Rates Today, October 20, 2023 | Rates Quickly Closing in on 8%&lt;br&gt;- So, You’re Thinking Of Taking Your Startup Public. Here’s What You Need To Know&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business section covers a range of topics including partnerships between educational institutions, personal finance, retirement strategies, banking rates, CEO transitions, and the financial status of prominent individuals like Elon Musk. These insights provide a glimpse into the current state of the business world and offer valuable information for decision-making.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Why E-A-T Principles Matter In The Age Of LLM-Powered Search Engines&lt;br&gt;- Meta apologized after Instagram's auto-translate tool added 'terrorist' to the bio of some Palestine supporters&lt;br&gt;- People are grieving the 'death' of their AI companions after a chatbot app abruptly shut down&lt;br&gt;Insights: The AI section focuses on the impact of AI on various aspects of society. It discusses the importance of E-A-T principles in search engines, the challenges of automated translation tools, and the emotional connection people can develop with AI companions. These insights shed light on the ethical considerations and potential pitfalls of AI technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- 2025 WR CJ Wiley holds early Georgia offer, talks recent visit to ... - 247Sports&lt;br&gt;- A Russian soldier was so weak from lack of food and water that he couldn't wear his bulletproof vest, Ukrainian intelligence says&lt;br&gt;- An opulent ancient Egyptian tomb containing 5,000-year-old wine may have belonged to a long-forgotten female pharaoh&lt;br&gt;- Car theft surged more than 10% in one year. See the most stolen models.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's next headache after Tesla's earnings flop could be users ditching X over Israel-Hamas misinformation, Nobel economist Paul Krugman says&lt;br&gt;- Traveling alone on a cruise could double the cost of your vacation — but this could soon change&lt;br&gt;- Airbus just unveiled the private jet version of its smallest airliner, which is estimated to cost $100 million — see inside the plane&lt;br&gt;- In Plane Sight: Drug agents searching passengers for cash at airport gates&lt;br&gt;- SwimXYZ: A Synthetic Dataset of Swimming Motions and Videos Containing 3.4M Frames Annotated with Ground Truth 2D and 3D Joints&lt;br&gt;Insights: The other section covers a diverse range of topics including sports, international conflicts, archaeology, crime, travel, and datasets. These insights provide a glimpse into various aspects of society and offer a well-rounded view of current events.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The report highlights advancements in technology, developments in the business world, the impact of AI, and various other topics. Key insights include the potential of AI in healthcare, the challenges of automated translation tools, the financial status of prominent individuals, and the diverse range of societal events. Overall, the report showcases the rapid pace of innovation and the interconnectedness of different fields in today's world.</summary></entry></feed>