<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-18T18:01:18Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 18 Aug 2023 18:01:18</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-18T18:01:18Z</published><updated>2023-08-18T18:01:18Z</updated><id>aee1f364-b8bc-4459-9232-ed59d5868f75</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Google DeepMind Researchers Propose 6 Composable Transformations to Incrementally Increase the Size of Transformer-based Neural Networks while Preserving Functionality&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Researchers at Google DeepMind have proposed six transformations that allow for the incremental growth of transformer-based neural networks without sacrificing functionality.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This research could potentially lead to the development of larger and more powerful AI models, enabling advancements in various fields such as natural language processing and computer vision.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. This UK startup engineered a clever way to reuse waste heat from cloud computing&lt;br&gt;- Key points: A UK startup has developed a technology that captures and reuses waste heat generated by cloud computing data centers, reducing energy waste and carbon emissions.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This innovation addresses the environmental impact of data centers and contributes to the sustainability of cloud computing infrastructure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Russia is charging families of dead soldiers $1,500 to get their bodies back, human-rights group claims&lt;br&gt;- Key points: A human-rights group alleges that Russia is charging families of deceased soldiers $1,500 to repatriate their bodies, raising concerns about the treatment of military personnel and their families.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This practice raises ethical questions regarding the treatment of fallen soldiers and the financial burden placed on their families.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. The story behind Uline, the packaging powerhouse whose reclusive billionaire owners use their fortune to influence American politics&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Uline, a packaging company, is owned by reclusive billionaires who have used their wealth to influence American politics, raising questions about the role of money in politics.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This case highlights the influence of wealthy individuals on political processes and the potential implications for democracy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. The AI hype cycle faces its first setback as summer doldrums drag on some of this year's biggest winners&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The AI industry is experiencing a setback as some of the previously successful AI companies face challenges and slower growth during the summer period.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This indicates that the AI industry is not immune to market fluctuations and that sustained success requires continuous innovation and adaptation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Microsoft has pulled an AI-written travel guide, which told tourists to visit the Ottawa Food Bank if they are hungry&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Microsoft had to remove an AI-written travel guide after it suggested tourists visit the Ottawa Food Bank if they were hungry, highlighting the limitations and potential risks of AI-generated content.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This incident underscores the importance of human oversight and ethical considerations when deploying AI systems, particularly in sensitive domains such as travel recommendations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The AI industry is facing challenges and setbacks, indicating the need for continuous innovation and adaptation.&lt;br&gt;- The treatment of fallen soldiers and the financial burden on their families raise ethical concerns.&lt;br&gt;- The influence of wealthy individuals on politics and the role of money in democracy are subjects of scrutiny.&lt;br&gt;- Sustainable practices in technology, such as reusing waste heat from data centers, contribute to environmental sustainability.&lt;br&gt;- AI-generated content requires human oversight and ethical considerations to avoid potential risks and limitations.</summary></entry></feed>