<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-29T08:03:29Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 29 Aug 2023 08:03:29</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-29T08:03:29Z</published><updated>2023-08-29T08:03:29Z</updated><id>da619613-7534-4bad-8741-f40226b51401</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Amazon CEO reportedly told remote employees: ‘It’s probably not going to work out’&lt;br&gt;- Meet Nous-Hermes-Llama2-70b: A State-of-the-Art Language Model Fine-Tuned on Over 300,000 Instructions&lt;br&gt;- How to get Sponsored by DigitalOcean for Your Open Source Project&lt;br&gt;- Apple, Long a Critic of Right to Repair, Comes Out in Support of California Bill&lt;br&gt;- Uber Eats is reportedly developing an AI chatbot that will offer recommendations, speed up ordering&lt;br&gt;- Connections is The New York Times’ most played game after Wordle&lt;br&gt;- Unlock Limitless Possibilities: Supercharge Your Azure Virtual Machine with Additional Disk Space!&lt;br&gt;- Poe’s new desktop app lets you use all the AI chatbots in one place&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech section highlights various developments in the tech industry. It includes news about Amazon's CEO addressing remote employees, advancements in language models, support for right to repair, AI chatbot development, and the popularity of a game by The New York Times. These insights showcase the evolving landscape of technology and its impact on different sectors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Nathan Latka Hosting Bootstrapping Track at SaaStr Annual 2023 Next Week!&lt;br&gt;- Janet Yellen's Treasury Department found that joining a union is among the most effective ways to get a raise&lt;br&gt;- Best Credit Cards for TSA PreCheck or Global Entry of September 2023&lt;br&gt;- Wiley paused Hindawi special issues amid quality problems, lost $9 ... - Retraction Watch&lt;br&gt;- Amazon increases its free shipping minimum to $35 for non-Prime members in some regions&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business section covers topics such as entrepreneurship, labor unions, financial services, and e-commerce. It highlights the importance of networking events, the impact of unions on wages, credit card recommendations, and challenges faced by publishing companies. Additionally, it discusses changes in Amazon's shipping policies, reflecting the dynamic nature of the business landscape.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Meet Nous-Hermes-Llama2-70b: A State-of-the-Art Language Model Fine-Tuned on Over 300,000 Instructions&lt;br&gt;- Uber Eats is reportedly developing an AI chatbot that will offer recommendations, speed up ordering&lt;br&gt;- Poe’s new desktop app lets you use all the AI chatbots in one place&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The AI section focuses on advancements in natural language processing and chatbot technology. It highlights the development of a state-of-the-art language model and the integration of AI chatbots in food delivery services. The introduction of a desktop app that consolidates AI chatbots showcases the growing integration of AI into everyday applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- A massive Iranian missile attack on a US base offered a glimpse of the long-lasting injuries US troops will face in a war with Russia or China&lt;br&gt;- In a bid to build buzz, a whole lot of AMC shows are coming to Max ad-free&lt;br&gt;- The Protecting Kids on Social Media Act is A Terrible Alternative to KOSA&lt;br&gt;- Applying to college? Here’s what to know about the new financial aid formula and revamped FAFSA&lt;br&gt;- California's attorney general is suing a school district that's forcing teachers to out transgender and nonbinary students to their parents&lt;br&gt;- Over half of Americans report being visited by dead family members. Here’s what they do&lt;br&gt;- Opening of West Point time capsule reveals what cynics said it would: Nothing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The other section covers a range of topics including international conflicts, entertainment, legislation, education, social issues, and paranormal experiences. These insights provide a diverse perspective on global events, cultural developments, and societal challenges. They highlight the importance of understanding various aspects of the world we live in.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Technology continues to shape various industries, with advancements in AI and tech infrastructure influencing business strategies and consumer experiences.&lt;br&gt;- Business dynamics are influenced by factors such as networking, labor unions, financial services, and e-commerce policies.&lt;br&gt;- AI is becoming increasingly integrated into everyday applications, enhancing efficiency and convenience.&lt;br&gt;- Broader topics such as international conflicts, entertainment, legislation, education, social issues, and paranormal experiences reflect the multifaceted nature of our world and the need for comprehensive understanding.</summary></entry></feed>