<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-30T20:02:04Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 30 Sep 2023 20:02:04</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-30T20:02:04Z</published><updated>2023-09-30T20:02:04Z</updated><id>3ed3195f-c3d9-4017-8286-0ccdf0f06ae2</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Here's how to stop Google from using your web content for generative AI&lt;br&gt;- A next-generation CLI tool for building amazing web apps in Go using htmx &amp; hyperscript&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft Needs So Much Power to Train AI That It's Considering Small Nuclear Reactors&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Watching my parents pay for help in their 80s made me consider long-term care insurance before it's too late&lt;br&gt;- I quit my job, so I asked financial planners how to save for retirement without a 401(k)&lt;br&gt;- A millennial couple increased their net worth from zero to $500,000 in 4 years by making 5 strategic money decisions&lt;br&gt;- Taco Bell, Chipotle, and other chains pay managers as much as $180,000. Here's what it takes to land a high-earning fast-food job.&lt;br&gt;- Some Walmart delivery drivers are buying their credentials online — letting anyone deliver goods to your door&lt;br&gt;- The pandemic broke the used car market — now shoppers are screwed&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft Needs So Much Power to Train AI That It's Considering Small Nuclear Reactors&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Things To Do This Week In London: 2-8 October 2023 - Londonist&lt;br&gt;- The 10 most neighborly cities in the US, where crime rates are low and voter turnout is high&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine appears to be modifying the UK Challenger 2 battle tanks to protect a 'notorious' weak spot, report says&lt;br&gt;- US Army engineers are dredging the dwindling Mississippi River 24/7 and battling seawater creeping upstream toward New Orleans' drinking water&lt;br&gt;- When I graduated college, my dad told me exactly what to do with every paycheck. More than a decade later, I'm still doing it.&lt;br&gt;- Police fined a car owner after a speed camera appeared to show a dog behind the wheel&lt;br&gt;- NYC and its suburbs won't build new housing, so New Yorkers are flooding into Jersey City and driving up prices&lt;br&gt;- Will US house prices soar or plunge? These 5 experts are divided.&lt;br&gt;- Elite Ukrainian commandos on jet skis conducted a daring raid on a Russian electronic warfare station in Crimea, report says&lt;br&gt;- Scientists finally finished mapping Earth's 8th continent Zealandia, helping them solve the lost continent's mysterious history&lt;br&gt;- White House warns of 'unprecedented' Serbian troop buildup on Kosovo border&lt;br&gt;- Hacktoberfest 2023 registrations start! - The complete guide to win a T Shirt, Learn and Contribute.&lt;br&gt;- Remember That Black Hole They Took a Picture of? It's Spinning&lt;br&gt;- In Photos: See The 'Super Harvest Moon' Set-Up America's 'Ring Of Fire' Solar Eclipse&lt;br&gt;- Personal Loan Interest Rates Today, September 30, 2023 | Today's Top Personal Loan Rates&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage Interest Rates Today, September 30, 2023 | Did Rates Peak This Month?&lt;br&gt;- China kicks off its plan to take on the cruise industry: 'There's no turning back'&lt;br&gt;- Russia picked the Black Sea naval fight it's now losing to Ukraine, which doesn't even have a fleet of its own&lt;br&gt;- I didn't want to move to a remote Texas city because I was scared of crime. I was wrong, and now we're happier than ever.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Google's use of web content for generative AI raises concerns about intellectual property rights and the need for consent from content creators.&lt;br&gt;- The development of a next-generation CLI tool for web app development in Go showcases the continuous innovation in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's reliance on large amounts of power for AI training highlights the energy demands of advanced AI technologies.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of the pandemic on various industries, such as the used car market and delivery services, has led to significant challenges and changes.&lt;br&gt;- The geopolitical tensions between Ukraine and Russia continue to escalate, with reports of military actions and raids.&lt;br&gt;- The mapping of Zealandia provides valuable insights into Earth's geological history and the understanding of lost continents.&lt;br&gt;- The housing market and interest rates remain uncertain, with experts divided on the future direction.&lt;br&gt;- The personal experiences shared in the articles highlight the importance of financial planning, long-term care insurance, and overcoming misconceptions about certain locations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, the report highlights the intersection of technology, business, geopolitics, and personal experiences, showcasing the diverse range of topics and insights gathered. It emphasizes the ongoing advancements and challenges in various industries and the importance of informed decision-making in personal finance and life choices.</summary></entry></feed>