<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LF AI RSS</title><link>https://air.novaspark.io/</link><description>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 21:03:27 -0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Briefing with LLM on August 07 2023 21・03・27</title><link>https://air.novaspark.io/</link><description>The content provided includes various topics ranging from sports to technology. The NASCAR race and Montgomery riverfront brawl are related to sports. The article on TRANSCOLOR investing in the first Robe iFORTES for Poland is about the latest technology in the entertainment industry. The decline in stroke hospitalization due to COVID-19 is a medical issue. The article on iBuyers discusses a new trend in the real estate industry. The US Army's plan to make hundreds of thousands of artillery shells each year is related to defense. Jeff Bezos and Lauren Sanchez's superyacht engagement party included business titans and celebrities. Taylor Swift's mini-residencies in LA for her Eras tour are a smart business decision. China's working population will shrink in the coming decades, which will affect the nation's economy. E. Jean Carroll is still no closer to pocketing Trump's $5 million from defamation verdict. The article on impending collapse discusses the current state of the system. The open-source canvas drawing web app is built using React. Zoom's TOS permit training AI on user content without opt-out. The beginner's guide to Git version control is a helpful resource for those new to programming. The combined power of F# and C# is discussed in another article. The article on Mach-O Binaries is related to computer science. Good Movies as Old Books / Vol.2 is an art project. Feral: The Beast Within is a book by Mike Connell. Spicy Reads is an enamel pin collection by Nerd Tea Creations. Netflix is making it easier to rate its movies and shows on mobile. Boeing's Starliner crew capsule will not be ready to fly crew until March 2024. Padle and squash are both related to Rails migration. The article on Token x Criptomoeda discusses the differences between the two. The article on embracing the power of community argues that mentors are not necessary. Tailscale vs WireGuard is a comparison of two VPN services. Best of Blind: July 2023 is a collection of popular posts from the Blind community.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 21:03:27 -0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>