<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-14T04:01:12Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 14 Aug 2023 04:01:12</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-14T04:01:12Z</published><updated>2023-08-14T04:01:12Z</updated><id>547fa187-111c-4edd-8e4b-f5799787155e</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Mozilla to reintroduce full Browser Extension support for Firefox Android app&lt;br&gt;- Diving into React and Redux Toolkit: A Comprehensive Glossary of Key Terms and Concepts&lt;br&gt;- DeepMind’s AlphaStar Benchmark Improves RL Offline Agent With 90% Win Rate Against SOTA AlphaStar Supervised Agent&lt;br&gt;- AI Researchers From Apple And The University Of British Columbia Propose FaceLit: A Novel AI Framework For Neural 3D Relightable Faces&lt;br&gt;- College professors are going back to paper exams and handwritten essays to fight students using ChatGPT&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Frankfurt Week: Wiley Opens Its 'Partner Solutions' Division - Publishing Perspectives&lt;br&gt;- A North Florida congressional district that was held by a Black Democrat before it was dismantled by Ron DeSantis could be restored in 2024 under a new agreement&lt;br&gt;- Boomers enjoy vacation while Gen Z feels guilty about being away from work, survey finds&lt;br&gt;- US inflation means families are spending $709 more per month than two years ago&lt;br&gt;- Gov. Kim Reynolds urged anti-DeSantis protesters to be 'Iowa nice' as they rallied against his presidential campaign at the state's iconic fair&lt;br&gt;- Massachusetts passed a 4% millionaire's tax last year. Now every public school student is going to get free lunch.&lt;br&gt;- Mark Zuckerberg says it’s ‘time to move on’ from the Elon Musk fight&lt;br&gt;- The Elite's War on Remote Work Has Nothing to Do with Productivity&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- DeepMind’s AlphaStar Benchmark Improves RL Offline Agent With 90% Win Rate Against SOTA AlphaStar Supervised Agent&lt;br&gt;- AI Researchers From Apple And The University Of British Columbia Propose FaceLit: A Novel AI Framework For Neural 3D Relightable Faces&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- New‐onset inflammatory arthritis after COVID‐19 vaccination: A ... - John Wiley&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine's river raiders defy mosquito-infested bogs and the fear of being drowned by their body armor to harass Russian invaders&lt;br&gt;- Metro 2033 author Dmitry Glukhovsky sentenced to 8 years in prison&lt;br&gt;- ‘I've got nothing to hide’ and other misunderstandings of privacy (2007)&lt;br&gt;- Downloading a video should be “fair use” as recording a song from the radio&lt;br&gt;- A video shows an advanced Russian T-90 tank destroyed by a $500 hobby drone fitted with explosives, says Ukraine military&lt;br&gt;- Klaus Schwab: “If you have nothing to hide you have no reason to be afraid.”&lt;br&gt;- Temu Is Losing Millions of Dollars to Send You Cheap Socks&lt;br&gt;- How to Roman Republic 101, Part IIIa: Starting Down the Path of Honors&lt;br&gt;- The COVID‐19 lockdown increased obesity disparities; will the ... - John Wiley&lt;br&gt;- Today I realized I now trust Microsoft more than Google. What is happening?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Tech: The reintroduction of full Browser Extension support for Firefox Android app by Mozilla is a significant development for users who rely on extensions for enhanced browsing experiences. Additionally, the exploration of React and Redux Toolkit provides a comprehensive understanding of key terms and concepts in these technologies. DeepMind's AlphaStar Benchmark showcases the advancements in reinforcement learning and AI agents' performance. The proposed FaceLit AI framework for neural 3D relightable faces demonstrates the ongoing research in computer vision and graphics.&lt;br&gt;- Business: The opening of Wiley's 'Partner Solutions' division highlights the company's focus on expanding its publishing services. The potential restoration of a congressional district in North Florida and the survey findings on vacation guilt among different generations shed light on political and workplace dynamics. The impact of US inflation on family expenses and the implementation of a millionaire's tax in Massachusetts reflect economic and social policy changes. The statements by Gov. Kim Reynolds and Mark Zuckerberg provide insights into political campaigns and corporate leadership.&lt;br&gt;- AI: DeepMind's AlphaStar Benchmark and the proposed FaceLit AI framework exemplify the advancements in AI research and its applications in various domains.&lt;br&gt;- Other: The reports on new-onset inflammatory arthritis after COVID-19 vaccination, the sentencing of Metro 2033 author Dmitry Glukhovsky, and the discussion on privacy and fair use highlight diverse topics of interest. The incidents involving Ukrainian river raiders and the destruction of a Russian tank by a hobby drone demonstrate the ongoing conflict between Ukraine and Russia. The article on trusting Microsoft more than Google raises questions about changing perceptions and trust in technology companies.</summary></entry></feed>