<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-21T00:01:16Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:01:16</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-21T00:01:16Z</published><updated>2023-08-21T00:01:16Z</updated><id>400e827f-3009-4318-a9b4-4102477eb052</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- X glitch wipes out most pictures and links tweeted before December 2014&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from Cornell Introduce Quantization with Incoherence Processing (QuIP): A New AI Method based on the Insight that Quantization Benefits from Incoherent Weight and Hessian Matrices&lt;br&gt;- Get your own WebRTC Audio and Video using Open Source, Self Hosted Coturn for your Turn Server!&lt;br&gt;- Line Open-Sources ‘japanese-large-lm’: A Japanese Language Model With 3.6 Billion Parameters&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech section highlights various developments and issues in the field of technology. The X glitch wiping out old tweets raises concerns about data loss and the need for robust data storage systems. The introduction of QuIP by researchers from Cornell showcases advancements in AI methods. The availability of open-source tools like Coturn for WebRTC audio and video enables developers to create their own communication platforms. Line's open-sourcing of 'japanese-large-lm' demonstrates the growing interest in language models for different languages.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- GOP presidential candidate Vivek Ramaswamy says he can bring in 'voters of diverse shades of melanin' to the party by focusing on the economy&lt;br&gt;- A Maui restaurant owner is 'praying visitors will start to come back soon'&lt;br&gt;- The owner of a 1,900-square-foot house next to the Masters golf course kept turning down millions of dollars to sell&lt;br&gt;- 'Neutral' China is supplying Putin's forces with helicopters, drones, and crucial raw materials, report says&lt;br&gt;- Mexico replaced China as America's top trade buddy &amp;mdash; and it shows how the global economy is rapidly transforming&lt;br&gt;- NFL Hall of Famer's career almost ended before it started because he didn't speak Japanese&lt;br&gt;- Someone in California is now driving a unique Rolls-Royce that cost more than $30 million&lt;br&gt;- The US Air Force is tinkering with an unusual design for its biggest planes as it prepares for a potential long-range war with China&lt;br&gt;- Artists behind Chewy's adorable pet portraits are revealing the ugly side of the program. 'The way they are treating us is like we are just machines of mass production.'&lt;br&gt;- Top SaaStr Content for the Week: Workshop Wednesday with Justworks’ CRO, Loom’s CEO and Co-Founder, Rippling’s CEO and more!&lt;br&gt;- Dear SaaStr: What Key Things Should a SaaS Startup Focus on To Grow from 100k to 1M ARR?&lt;br&gt;- Bond vigilantes are 'saddling up.' Here's how concerned investors might take action over the ballooning federal deficit.&lt;br&gt;- The resilience of Russia's stock market and its economy is a complete mirage masking deeper pain, Yale researchers say&lt;br&gt;- A man who 'hopes he runs out of money' before he dies explains why you may not need as much cash to retire as you think&lt;br&gt;- How In-N-Out became one of America's most beloved fast-food dynasties as it marks 75 years under the ownership of the Snyder family&lt;br&gt;- A tiny private island in Maine where the only toilet is inside a lighthouse is on sale for $400,000 &amp;mdash; just a year after its owner bought it 'on a whim'&lt;br&gt;- I always planned to retire at 65 &amp;mdash; until I started thinking differently about what it means to retire&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business section covers a wide range of topics, including politics, tourism, real estate, international trade, sports, and personal finance. It highlights the importance of economic policies in attracting diverse voters. The struggles faced by a restaurant owner in Maui due to the decline in visitors reflect the impact of the pandemic on the tourism industry. The decision of the house owner near the Masters golf course to turn down lucrative offers emphasizes the value of sentimental attachment. The report on China's supply of military equipment to Russia raises concerns about geopolitical dynamics. The shift in trade relations between Mexico and the US indicates the changing global economy. The story of an NFL Hall of Famer's language barrier showcases the challenges faced by athletes in international settings. The unique Rolls-Royce in California highlights luxury car enthusiasts. The US Air Force's design modifications reflect the evolving nature of military strategies. The Chewy pet portraits controversy sheds light on the treatment of artists in mass production programs. The SaaStr content and advice for SaaS startups provide insights into the business world. The discussion on bond vigilantes and the federal deficit raises concerns about the economy. The analysis of Russia's stock market and economy challenges the perception of resilience. The perspective on retirement challenges traditional notions and encourages alternative thinking.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from Cornell Introduce Quantization with Incoherence Processing (QuIP): A New AI Method based on the Insight that Quantization Benefits from Incoherent Weight and Hessian Matrices&lt;br&gt;- Line Open-Sources ‘japanese-large-lm’: A Japanese Language Model With 3.6 Billion Parameters&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The AI section focuses on the advancements in AI research. The introduction of QuIP by researchers from Cornell showcases a new method for quantization in AI models. The open-sourcing of 'japanese-large-lm' by Line demonstrates the development of language models for specific languages.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The world is changing rapidly, as seen in the projected population growth of a country and the transformation of the global economy.&lt;br&gt;- Technology developments include data loss concerns, advancements in AI methods, and the availability of open-source tools for communication platforms.&lt;br&gt;- Business topics cover politics, tourism, real estate, international trade, sports, personal finance, and the treatment of artists.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section highlights advancements in AI research, particularly in quantization and language models.&lt;br&gt;- The report challenges traditional notions of retirement and encourages alternative thinking.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the insights gathered from the broader topics showcase the diverse and evolving nature of the world, with a focus on technology, business, and AI.</summary></entry></feed>