<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-23T08:03:42Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 23 Oct 2023 08:03:42</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-23T08:03:42Z</published><updated>2023-10-23T08:03:42Z</updated><id>573e1122-ef3d-41c6-955a-d080889707a6</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. How to Make a CPU – A Simple Picture Based Explanation&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Provides a simplified explanation of how a CPU is made using visuals.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: This article aims to make complex technology more accessible to readers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Local Development with AWS Lambda and NestJS: Docker Debugging and Hot Reload&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Discusses the use of AWS Lambda and NestJS for local development, focusing on Docker debugging and hot reload.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: Demonstrates practical tips for developers working with AWS Lambda and NestJS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Console #180 - Interview with Niaz of LibrePhotos - self-hosted open source photo management service&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Features an interview with Niaz, the creator of LibrePhotos, a self-hosted open source photo management service.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: Highlights the importance of open source projects in the tech community.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Chinese Billionaire To Step Down As Chairman At Video Platform Kuaishou&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Reports on a Chinese billionaire stepping down as chairman of Kuaishou, a video platform.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: Indicates potential changes in leadership and strategy within the company.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Andy Jassy: Meet the Amazon CEO of the post-Jeff Bezos era&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Introduces Andy Jassy, the new CEO of Amazon following Jeff Bezos' departure.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: Explores the transition of leadership at one of the world's largest companies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Why Monday.com decided to build its new database instead of buying one&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Explains the decision of Monday.com to build their own database instead of purchasing one.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: Highlights the strategic considerations and advantages of developing proprietary technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. Meet OmniControl: An Artificial Intelligence Approach for Incorporating Flexible Spatial Control Signals into a Text-Conditioned Human Motion Generation Model Based on the Diffusion Process&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Presents OmniControl, an AI approach for incorporating flexible spatial control signals into a human motion generation model.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: Showcases advancements in AI technology for human motion generation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. This is how to futureproof your career in an AI world, says IBM's CEO&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Provides insights from IBM's CEO on how individuals can futureproof their careers in an AI-driven world.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: Offers guidance on adapting to the changing landscape of work due to AI advancements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Elon Musk acted like a 'little baby' and was 'almost in tears' on Tesla's 'terrible' earnings call, analyst says&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Reports on an analyst's criticism of Elon Musk's behavior during a Tesla earnings call.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: Examines the impact of public perception and leadership style on the reputation of AI-driven companies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section highlights the importance of simplifying complex concepts for better understanding.&lt;br&gt;- The business section emphasizes the significance of leadership transitions and strategic decision-making.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section showcases advancements in AI technology and the need to adapt to an AI-driven world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, the report provides a diverse range of topics, demonstrating the intersection of technology, business, and AI. It highlights key developments, insights, and potential implications within each category.</summary></entry></feed>