<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-01T20:02:11Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 01 Sep 2023 20:02:11</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-01T20:02:11Z</published><updated>2023-09-01T20:02:11Z</updated><id>09b32081-d094-4866-8a03-10f04da0ae25</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk stayed up playing video games in a Vancouver hotel until 5:30 a.m. after he offered to buy Twitter, because he was in 'stress mode'&lt;br&gt;- A MAGA news network isn't sure if it got duped by an AI version of Trump in a 17-minute call&lt;br&gt;- Apple Clarifies Why It Abandoned Plan to Detect CSAM in iCloud Photos&lt;br&gt;- Google pulls popular but controversial live video chat app Chamet from the Play Store&lt;br&gt;- Unlocking the Black Box: A Quantitative Law for Understanding Data Processing in Deep Neural Networks&lt;br&gt;- Podcast: Roi Ravhon on FinOps, Application Unit Economics, and Cloud Cost Optimization&lt;br&gt;- Tesla’s upgraded Model 3 has a new design, rear touchscreen, and range improvements&lt;br&gt;- Understanding the Dark Side of Large Language Models: A Comprehensive Guide to Security Threats and Vulnerabilities&lt;br&gt;- Presentation: 5 Principles for Enablement with (Almost) Nothing to do with Building Tools&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Companies are shuffling people around more than they were a year ago. Here's how to know what your reassignment really means.&lt;br&gt;- UBS made a $29 billion quarterly profit after rescuing Credit Suisse&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett and Vivek Ramaswamy are miles apart politically. But the investing icon and Republican upstart have a few things in common.&lt;br&gt;- Millions of student-loan borrowers' balances are now starting to grow again after over 3 years&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage Interest Rates Today, September 1, 2023 | 30-Year Rates Fall&lt;br&gt;- I earned up to $130K in tech roles, but the jobs felt fake. Here's why I think startups hire people to build a brand only to fire them later on.&lt;br&gt;- AMC Theatres, revived by Barbie, will get a fall boost from another blonde icon&lt;br&gt;- Wealthy Family Wants to Reopen Major Industrial Polluter in Alabama Despite Mounting Debts and Proposed Regulation&lt;br&gt;- China tries again to support its battered economy, bringing in new measures to boost the yuan&lt;br&gt;- Dollarization is the only way for Argentina to stop its 'death spiral', economist Steve Hanke says&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- A MAGA news network isn't sure if it got duped by an AI version of Trump in a 17-minute call&lt;br&gt;- Unlocking the Black Box: A Quantitative Law for Understanding Data Processing in Deep Neural Networks&lt;br&gt;- Understanding the Dark Side of Large Language Models: A Comprehensive Guide to Security Threats and Vulnerabilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- TCU Football vs. Colorado: Staff Predictions And Game Previews - Sports Illustrated&lt;br&gt;- My husband and I couldn't afford to buy a home in Nashville, so we moved into an RV instead. We've been able to upgrade our vehicle, but haven't made the leap to homeownership.&lt;br&gt;- The Hottest Summer Ever And The Water Crisis: Building A Sustainable Future&lt;br&gt;- Cyber Autumn: Captivating Cybersecurity Conferences To Dive Into This October 2023&lt;br&gt;- US will regulate nursing home staffing for first time, but proposal lower than many advocates hoped&lt;br&gt;- Muhammad Yunus, the father of microfinance, is facing a prison sentence&lt;br&gt;- Burning Man is underway. Here are the famous CEOs and billionaires who have attended tech bros' favorite party, from Elon Musk to Ray Dalio.&lt;br&gt;- I left NYC for Tulsa, Oklahoma. I only planned to stay for a year, but I love the lower cost of living and slower pace.&lt;br&gt;- Presentation: 5 Principles for Enablement with (Almost) Nothing to do with Building Tools&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is experiencing advancements in AI, with concerns arising about the use of AI-generated content and the security threats associated with large language models.&lt;br&gt;- The business sector is seeing shifts in company structures and profits, as well as discussions on student loans, mortgage rates, and economic measures.&lt;br&gt;- Other topics range from sports predictions and game previews to personal stories, environmental issues, cybersecurity, and lifestyle choices.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report highlights the intersection of technology, business, and various other aspects of life, showcasing the diverse landscape of current news and trends.</summary></entry></feed>