<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-09T17:39:08Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 09 Aug 2023 17:39:08</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-09T17:39:08Z</published><updated>2023-08-09T17:39:08Z</updated><id>9abc6da5-f3da-4936-9b1a-96afba5dbfef</id><summary type="html">SEC chairman warns AI could be at the heart of future financial crises&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a recent statement, the chairman of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) expressed concerns about the potential risks associated with artificial intelligence (AI) in the financial industry. He warned that AI could be at the heart of future financial crises if not properly regulated and monitored.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mega Millions drawing tonight&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mega Millions lottery is set to hold its drawing tonight, offering a chance for participants to win a large sum of money. This news highlights the excitement and anticipation surrounding the lottery and may attract individuals interested in participating.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protein Loss Linked to Growth Defects in Mice, Humans - Mirage News&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study published in Mirage News reveals a link between protein loss and growth defects in both mice and humans. This finding emphasizes the importance of protein intake for proper growth and development, and may have implications for medical research and treatment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Student-loan payments and steeper interest rates will pave way for a severe consumer-led recession, top economist David Rosenberg says&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prominent economist David Rosenberg predicts that the combination of student-loan payments and higher interest rates will lead to a severe recession driven by consumer spending. This warning highlights the potential economic consequences of these factors and raises concerns about the financial well-being of individuals burdened by student loans.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Zuckerberg, wife Priscilla's relationship timeline, from dating to marriage&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This article provides a timeline of the relationship between Mark Zuckerberg, the CEO of Facebook, and his wife Priscilla. It traces their journey from dating to marriage, offering insights into their personal lives and relationship milestones.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quote Post Maker&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Quote Post Maker is a tool or platform that allows users to create visually appealing posts featuring quotes. This resource may be useful for individuals looking to create engaging content for social media or other platforms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lofi &amp; Jazz Hip Hop Producing Handbook&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lofi &amp; Jazz Hip Hop Producing Handbook is a guide or manual that provides information and tips for producing music in the lofi and jazz hip hop genres. This resource may be valuable for aspiring music producers or enthusiasts interested in these specific styles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minimalist eCommerce&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minimalist eCommerce refers to a streamlined and simplified approach to online retail. This concept focuses on minimal design, user-friendly interfaces, and efficient purchasing processes. It aims to provide a seamless and clutter-free shopping experience for customers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Review My Design&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Review My Design" is a request or invitation for others to provide feedback and critique on a design. This could be related to graphic design, web design, or any other creative work. Seeking reviews can help improve the quality and effectiveness of the design.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Backendless&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Backendless is a platform or service that offers backend development tools and infrastructure for building and deploying applications. It provides features such as database management, user authentication, and serverless functions, simplifying the backend development process.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reflecting on My Failure to Build a Billion-Dollar Company (2019)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This article or piece reflects on the author's personal experience and failure to build a billion-dollar company. It offers insights and lessons learned from this experience, providing valuable perspectives for entrepreneurs and business professionals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon has more than half of all Arm server CPUs in the world&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon, the multinational technology company, currently holds over 50% of the market share for Arm server CPUs worldwide. This dominance in the market highlights Amazon's significant presence and influence in the technology industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Llama from Scratch (or how to implement a paper without crying)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This content discusses the process of implementing a research paper or academic work from scratch, using the analogy of a llama. It may provide insights and tips for researchers or individuals interested in understanding the challenges and steps involved in implementing academic papers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;絶滅危惧種の遺伝子を未来へ：国立環境研究所がクラウドファンディングで「タイムカプセル」の費用を募る理由&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Translation: "Preserving the genes of endangered species for the future: Why the National Institute for Environmental Studies is raising funds for a 'time capsule' through crowdfunding." This news highlights the efforts of the National Institute for Environmental Studies to preserve the genetic material of endangered species through a crowdfunding campaign.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;一句话完成繁琐操作：你可以试试的 8 个 Windows 命令行工具&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Translation: "Complete complex operations in one sentence: 8 Windows command-line tools you can try." This content introduces eight command-line tools for Windows that can simplify and streamline various tasks, offering convenience and efficiency for users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAS AI BECOME TOO HUMAN? Researchers At Google AI Find LLMs Can Now Use ML Models And APIs With Just Tool Documentation!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at Google AI have discovered that Language Model Models (LLMs) can now utilize machine learning models and APIs with only tool documentation. This finding raises questions about the capabilities and potential risks associated with AI becoming more human-like in its abilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pretiosum Ventures hits first close on its second fund to back infrastructure startups&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pretiosum Ventures, a venture capital firm, has successfully reached its first close on its second fund. This development indicates the firm's commitment to supporting infrastructure startups and highlights the potential for growth and innovation in this sector.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to get more suggestions from GitHub Copilot&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This article provides tips and strategies for obtaining more suggestions from GitHub Copilot, an AI-powered code completion tool. It offers insights and techniques to maximize the benefits of using this tool for developers and programmers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cloud Providers Showdown: AWS vs. Azure vs. Google Cloud&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This content compares and evaluates the leading cloud providers, namely Amazon Web Services (AWS), Microsoft Azure, and Google Cloud. It highlights the strengths and weaknesses of each platform, helping readers make informed decisions when choosing a cloud provider.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weekly web development resources #161&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This resource, labeled as "Weekly web development resources #161," provides a compilation of web development-related content, such as articles, tutorials, and tools. It serves as a curated collection of resources for web developers to stay updated and enhance their skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Introduction to CSS: Customizing with index.css and Classes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This article serves as an introduction to CSS (Cascading Style Sheets) and focuses on customizing web pages using index.css and classes. It provides foundational knowledge and practical examples for individuals looking to learn or improve their CSS skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone was wrong about antipsychotics&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This content challenges the prevailing beliefs and assumptions about antipsychotic medications. It suggests that the general understanding and usage of these medications may have been incorrect, offering alternative perspectives and insights into their effectiveness.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;People-centered startups: making employees happy is a key ingredient to success&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This article highlights the importance of prioritizing employee happiness and well-being in startups. It argues that creating a people-centered work environment is a crucial factor for success, emphasizing the positive impact it can have on productivity and overall company performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;康恩贝：公司经营一切正常，“公司放假两个月”等传闻均为谣言&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Translation: "Kangmei Pharmaceutical: Company operations are normal, rumors of 'company taking a two-month vacation' are false." This news clarifies that Kangmei Pharmaceutical, a company, is operating normally and dispels rumors suggesting otherwise.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;天力锂能：与鹏辉能源签署《战略合作框架协议》&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Translation: "Tianli Lithium Energy: Signs 'Strategic Cooperation Framework Agreement' with Penghui Energy." This announcement highlights the signing of a strategic cooperation agreement between Tianli Lithium Energy and Penghui Energy, indicating a partnership or collaboration between the two companies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;澳大利亚广播公司退出X，称该平台上“有害互动”愈发普遍&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Translation: "Australian Broadcasting Corporation (ABC) withdraws from X, citing increasing prevalence of 'harmful interactions' on the platform." This news reports ABC's decision to withdraw from a platform called X due to concerns about the growing presence of harmful interactions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;英国又一房企宣布裁员，因高利率打压新屋需求&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Translation: "Another British real estate company announces layoffs due to high interest rates suppressing demand for new homes." This news highlights the impact of high interest rates on the real estate industry in the UK, leading to workforce reductions in a specific company.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;中国联通：上半年净利润54.44亿元，同比增长13.7%&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Translation: "China Unicom: Net profit of 5.444 billion yuan in the first half of the year, a year-on-year increase of 13.7%." This financial report reveals the positive performance of China Unicom, a telecommunications company, with a significant increase in net profit compared to the previous year.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;用非官方通讯软件沟通业务，华尔街金融机构已累计被罚超25亿美元&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Translation: "Wall Street financial institutions fined over $2.5 billion for conducting business communications through unofficial messaging apps." This news highlights the regulatory actions taken against financial institutions on Wall Street for using unofficial communication channels, resulting in substantial fines.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;恒指收涨0.32%，恒生科技指数跌0.01%&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Translation: "Hang Seng Index rises 0.32%, Hang Seng Technology Index falls 0.01%." This financial update provides the performance of the Hang Seng Index and the Hang Seng Technology Index, indicating slight changes in their values.</summary></entry></feed>