<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-20T06:00:54Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 20 Aug 2023 06:00:54</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-20T06:00:54Z</published><updated>2023-08-20T06:00:54Z</updated><id>1e5c9533-b5e3-4246-8222-fc6862a5d381</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Oil companies are using influencers and PR firms to target younger generations on social media.&lt;br&gt;- Apple devices are being spoofed, Elon Musk taunts Mark Zuckerberg, and Better.com goes public.&lt;br&gt;- A comprehensive RDF dataset with over 26 billion triples covering scholarly data across all scientific disciplines has been introduced by an AI paper.&lt;br&gt;- Meta's news ban is preventing Canadians from sharing important information about wildfires in western Canada.&lt;br&gt;- Spotify considered banning white noise podcasts to increase profitability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- A judge dismissed a defamation suit against a newspaper, potentially leading to the closure of the paper due to legal fees.&lt;br&gt;- A nearly $200,000 fine threatens to shut down a Florida abortion clinic, but activists have already crowdfunded half of it.&lt;br&gt;- Kroger is using sushi as a secret weapon to attract customers and compete in the dining-out industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- People prefer human art over AI art, but the preference is complex.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Stormzy's performance at All Points East received mixed reviews, with a slow start but an exciting finish.&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine is targeting Moscow with drone strikes, causing airport closures.&lt;br&gt;- North Korea's new ICBM closely resembles a Russian ICBM, according to experts.&lt;br&gt;- The Little Rock Nine members criticize restrictions on an AP African American Studies course in Arkansas.&lt;br&gt;- Hurricane Hilary poses significant risks to the western US, with three important messages to be aware of.&lt;br&gt;- A 1954 Ferrari shell was sold for nearly $2 million.&lt;br&gt;- 70 years ago, an Anglo-US coup led to decades of oppression in Iran.&lt;br&gt;- July 4th is not the US's birthday, and there is a story about how Ben Franklin played a role in the creation of the US.&lt;br&gt;- The Air Force is funding the development of a 'blended wing body' design for fuel-efficient flight.&lt;br&gt;- Helidon Níma is the first Java microservices framework based on virtual threads.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Oil companies are adapting their marketing strategies to target younger demographics through social media influencers.&lt;br&gt;- The use of AI in scholarly research is expanding, with a comprehensive RDF dataset being introduced.&lt;br&gt;- The preference for human art over AI art highlights the complexity of human perception and appreciation.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of Meta's news ban on sharing vital information during emergencies is concerning.&lt;br&gt;- The battle for profitability in the streaming industry has led Spotify to consider banning certain types of podcasts.&lt;br&gt;- Legal battles and fines pose threats to media outlets and abortion clinics, but public support and crowdfunding efforts can provide relief.&lt;br&gt;- Kroger's innovative approach to attract customers through sushi demonstrates the competitive nature of the dining-out industry.&lt;br&gt;- Historical events, such as the Anglo-US coup in Iran, continue to have long-lasting effects on nations and their people.&lt;br&gt;- Natural disasters, like Hurricane Hilary, require effective communication and preparedness in affected regions.&lt;br&gt;- The value of collectible items, such as the rusted shell of a 1954 Ferrari, can reach significant prices in the market.</summary></entry></feed>