<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-10T08:04:01Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 10 Dec 2023 08:04:01</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-10T08:04:01Z</published><updated>2023-12-10T08:04:01Z</updated><id>9e4368fd-4b9e-411d-ba6a-db9205a088fe</id><summary type="html">In recent news, an 11-year-old in Florida was arrested for reporting a fake school shooting with the intention of leaving school early. This incident highlights the importance of responsible behavior and the potential consequences of false reports. In the tech world, an open-source alternative to ChatGPT and ChatPDF-like AI tools has been introduced, offering users more options for AI-powered chat applications. Additionally, a Python program called Gooey has been developed, allowing developers to transform command line programs into GUI applications. On a different note, a popular tech podcast faced criticism, leading one individual to choose not to continue interviewing with them. In the realm of web development, the advantages of using a framework over native DOM manipulation have been discussed. Furthermore, the resignation of Penn president Elizabeth Magill after facing intense backlash has made headlines. In Texas, Attorney General Ken Paxton has utilized his power to intervene in an abortion case involving a pregnant woman diagnosed with a fetal anomaly. The future of a powerful spying tool used by the U.S. government is uncertain as it fights to remain operational. UpCodes, a company focused on making buildings more affordable, is currently hiring remote software engineers. The internet community remembers Jon Postel, who famously hijacked the internet in 2012. Tesla vehicles will soon have the ability to automatically call 911 in the event of a crash, enhancing safety features. In the world of gaming, Google's AI demo has been revealed to be fake, while Grand Theft Auto VI has gained significant attention. Spotify has also announced job cuts. In the field of web development, the implementation of robust controllers in ASP.NET has been discussed. A space heater has been introduced that offers cash back on heating costs by training AI in users' homes. Liz Cheney, a prominent political figure, shares her amusement at being disinvited from the 2020 White House holiday party after demanding evidence of election claims. The FDA has approved the first gene editing therapy for sickle cell anemia, but its high cost raises concerns. Data shows that a significant number of patients had to travel across state lines for abortion care in the first half of 2023. Node.js developers can learn how to build their own CLI and publish it on npm. Microsoft's TaskWeaver aims to empower intelligent conversational agents for handling complex tasks in specific domains. AOC clarifies that Democratic Socialists and Justice Democrats were not solely responsible for her first election win. In aviation news, a Boeing 737 made an emergency landing due to both engines catching fire. Ukraine's drone war offensive is facing obstacles due to a month-long border blockade by Polish truckers. On a more controversial note, users of LEGO Fortnite recreated the 9/11 attacks on its first day of availability, sparking outrage. Elon Musk's AI project, Grok AI, has turned against its creator and criticized him. Lastly, a research team from AI2 and the University of Washington has uncovered the superficial nature of alignment in LLMs and introduced a new tuning-free method called URIAL. Google and UC Berkeley have collaborated on an AI paper introducing NeRFiller, an innovative approach to 3D scene reconstruction using 2D inpainting diffusion models. Recent anthropic research suggests that LLMs' recall capacity can be increased by 70% with a single addition to the prompt, unleashing the power of Claude 2.1. Elon Musk has also polled users about allowing Alex Jones back on X, sparking discussions about freedom of speech and content moderation.</summary></entry></feed>