<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-09T20:02:31Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 09 Nov 2023 20:02:31</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-09T20:02:31Z</published><updated>2023-11-09T20:02:31Z</updated><id>0d50a2b9-8cd0-426f-8c45-7eeb3a497f06</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Google's Search Generative Experience expands to 120 new countries and four new languages&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk screamed a profanity-laden jibe about Mark Zuckerberg when he signed the Twitter deal, author says&lt;br&gt;- Getting mocked for your green Android text bubbles to iPhone users could be a thing of the past in Europe if Google gets its way&lt;br&gt;- Ask HN: As a first-time solopreneur how would you go about hiring the first team&lt;br&gt;- Unemployed Man Uses AI to Apply for 5k Jobs, Gets 20 Interviews&lt;br&gt;- Show HN: I built a tool to get "Your app was approved/rejected " alerts on Slack&lt;br&gt;- Omegle is shutting down notorious video chat service as scrutiny grows&lt;br&gt;- Secure messaging app Signal moves a step closer to launching usernames&lt;br&gt;- Sharpening Your Toolbox: Staying Ahead In The Tech World [Testμ 2023]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Google's Search Generative Experience is expanding its reach to 120 new countries and four new languages, making it more accessible to a global audience.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk made a profanity-laden comment about Mark Zuckerberg during the signing of a Twitter deal, showcasing their ongoing rivalry.&lt;br&gt;- Google is working on eliminating the stigma associated with green Android text bubbles by proposing a change in Europe.&lt;br&gt;- As a first-time solopreneur, it is important to carefully consider the hiring process for building the first team.&lt;br&gt;- An unemployed individual successfully used AI to apply for jobs and secured 20 interviews.&lt;br&gt;- A new tool has been developed to receive real-time alerts on Slack regarding app approval or rejection.&lt;br&gt;- Omegle, a controversial video chat service, is shutting down due to increasing scrutiny.&lt;br&gt;- The secure messaging app Signal is making progress towards launching usernames, enhancing user experience and privacy.&lt;br&gt;- Staying ahead in the tech world requires continuous learning and skill development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The expansion of Google's Search Generative Experience demonstrates the company's commitment to providing access to information globally.&lt;br&gt;- The rivalry between Elon Musk and Mark Zuckerberg continues to generate attention and controversy.&lt;br&gt;- Google's proposal to change the color of Android text bubbles reflects the company's efforts to improve user experience and address user preferences.&lt;br&gt;- Hiring the first team as a solopreneur is a crucial step in building a successful business.&lt;br&gt;- AI technology has the potential to streamline the job application process and increase interview opportunities.&lt;br&gt;- Real-time alerts on Slack can improve communication and efficiency in app development.&lt;br&gt;- The shutdown of Omegle highlights the importance of addressing privacy and safety concerns in online platforms.&lt;br&gt;- Signal's focus on usernames aligns with its commitment to user privacy and security.&lt;br&gt;- Continuous learning and skill development are essential for professionals in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Wiley Edge partners with Cisco Networking Academy to train job ... - FE News&lt;br&gt;- Days of The Jackal: how Andrew Wylie turned serious literature into big business - The Guardian&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's company is so massive it's like a mini US economy - and its latest earnings may stoke recession fears&lt;br&gt;- You're probably not getting a big raise this year. But don't worry, it's for the good of the economy.&lt;br&gt;- Business banking interest rates vs. personal banking interest rates: Which are better?&lt;br&gt;- How H&amp;R Block and Intuit are banking on your mistrust of the IRS to keep you as a customer&lt;br&gt;- How Warren Buffett Privately Traded in Stocks That Berkshire Hathaway Was Buying and Selling&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Wiley Edge has partnered with Cisco Networking Academy to provide job training opportunities.&lt;br&gt;- Andrew Wylie's approach to literature has turned it into a lucrative business.&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's company, Berkshire Hathaway, is of significant economic importance and its latest earnings may impact recession concerns.&lt;br&gt;- Salary raises may be limited this year due to economic considerations.&lt;br&gt;- Comparing business banking interest rates with personal banking interest rates can help individuals make informed financial decisions.&lt;br&gt;- H&amp;R Block and Intuit capitalize on customers' mistrust of the IRS to retain their customer base.&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's private stock trading activities provide insights into Berkshire Hathaway's investment strategies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Partnerships between educational institutions and industry players like Wiley Edge and Cisco Networking Academy contribute to job training and skill development.&lt;br&gt;- The success of Andrew Wylie in turning literature into a profitable business highlights the evolving landscape of the publishing industry.&lt;br&gt;- Berkshire Hathaway's size and financial performance have implications for the overall economy.&lt;br&gt;- Limited salary raises may be a result of economic factors and the need for stability.&lt;br&gt;- Understanding the differences between business and personal banking interest rates can help individuals optimize their financial decisions.&lt;br&gt;- H&amp;R Block and Intuit's marketing strategies leverage customer concerns to maintain their market position.&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's trading activities provide valuable insights into the investment decisions of Berkshire Hathaway.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- A huge underwater volcano blast formed a new island off the coast of Japan&lt;br&gt;- Cats have almost 300 distinct facial expressions, and 45% of them are friendly&lt;br&gt;- ‘Air Twister’ (Xbox) Review: Yu Suzuki’s Surprising Link To The Past&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- An underwater volcano eruption resulted in the formation of a new island near Japan.&lt;br&gt;- Cats have a wide range of facial expressions, with a significant portion being friendly.&lt;br&gt;- The game "Air Twister" for Xbox has received a positive review, highlighting its connection to the past work of Yu Suzuki.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Natural phenomena like underwater volcano eruptions can lead to the creation of new landforms and have significant geological implications.&lt;br&gt;- The complexity of cat facial expressions showcases the depth of their communication abilities.&lt;br&gt;- The positive review of "Air Twister" demonstrates the impact of past work and the influence of game developers on the gaming industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of insights:&lt;br&gt;- The expansion of Google's Search Generative Experience demonstrates the company's commitment to providing access to information globally. The rivalry between Elon Musk and Mark Zuckerberg continues to generate attention and controversy. Google's proposal to change the color of Android text bubbles reflects the company's efforts to improve user experience and address user preferences. Hiring the first team as a solopreneur is a crucial step in building a successful business. AI technology has the potential to streamline the job application process and increase interview opportunities. Real-time alerts on Slack can improve communication and efficiency in app development. The shutdown of Omegle highlights the importance of addressing privacy and safety concerns in online platforms. Signal's focus on usernames aligns with its commitment to user privacy and security. Continuous learning and skill development are essential for professionals in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- Partnerships between educational institutions and industry players contribute to job training and skill development. The success of Andrew Wylie in turning literature into a profitable business highlights the evolving landscape of the publishing industry. Berkshire Hathaway's size and financial performance have implications for the overall economy. Limited salary raises may be a result of economic factors and the need for stability. Understanding the differences between business and personal banking interest rates can help individuals optimize their financial decisions. H&amp;R Block and Intuit's marketing strategies leverage customer concerns to maintain their market position. Warren Buffett's trading activities provide valuable insights into the investment decisions of Berkshire Hathaway.&lt;br&gt;- Natural phenomena like underwater volcano eruptions can lead to the creation of new landforms and have significant geological implications. The complexity of cat facial expressions showcases the depth of their communication abilities. The positive review of "Air Twister" demonstrates the impact of past work and the influence of game developers on the gaming industry.</summary></entry></feed>