<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-09T20:02:11Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 09 Sep 2023 20:02:11</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-09T20:02:11Z</published><updated>2023-09-09T20:02:11Z</updated><id>d2dd6dcb-403c-4143-92e4-b29b265e2f6b</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Midjourney Delivers on AI Promise by Hitting $200 Million Revenue Run Rate without VC funding&lt;br&gt;- Midjourney, an AI company, has achieved a revenue run rate of $200 million without relying on venture capital funding.&lt;br&gt;- This demonstrates the success and potential of AI technology in generating significant revenue.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Researchers from Microsoft Introduce Hydra-RLHF: A Memory-Efficient Solution for Reinforcement Learning with Human Feedback&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft researchers have developed Hydra-RLHF, a memory-efficient solution for reinforcement learning with human feedback.&lt;br&gt;- This innovation can enhance the efficiency and effectiveness of reinforcement learning algorithms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Detecting changes in JavaScript and CSS isn't an easy task, Part 2&lt;br&gt;- This article discusses the challenges involved in detecting changes in JavaScript and CSS.&lt;br&gt;- It provides insights into the complexities of web development and the need for efficient change detection mechanisms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Warren Buffett wrote to Leon Cooperman about stock buybacks, taxing the rich, and the presidency. Here are the 3 messages, from Cooperman's new memoir&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's correspondence with Leon Cooperman covers topics such as stock buybacks, taxing the rich, and the presidency.&lt;br&gt;- This provides insights into the perspectives of influential figures in the business world on these important issues.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Mortgage Interest Rates Today, September 9, 2023 | Will High Mortgage Rates Push Home Prices Down?&lt;br&gt;- This article discusses the current mortgage interest rates and their potential impact on home prices.&lt;br&gt;- It provides valuable information for individuals interested in the real estate market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Yelp says diners love to take pictures in these 25 restaurants around the US &amp;mdash; and it's easy to see why&lt;br&gt;- Yelp has identified 25 restaurants in the US where diners love to take pictures.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the influence of social media and visual appeal in the restaurant industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. Researchers from Microsoft Introduce Hydra-RLHF: A Memory-Efficient Solution for Reinforcement Learning with Human Feedback&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft researchers have developed Hydra-RLHF, a memory-efficient solution for reinforcement learning with human feedback.&lt;br&gt;- This innovation showcases the advancements in AI technology and its potential for improving various applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. How Does Ideogram Revolutionize Text-to-Image Conversion? The AI Platform that Goes Beyond DALL-E and Midjourney to Generate Letters&lt;br&gt;- Ideogram, an AI platform, is revolutionizing text-to-image conversion by going beyond existing models like DALL-E and Midjourney.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the continuous development and innovation in AI technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The success of Midjourney in generating significant revenue without VC funding demonstrates the potential of AI technology in driving financial success.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's Hydra-RLHF showcases the ongoing advancements in reinforcement learning algorithms, which can enhance various applications.&lt;br&gt;- The challenges in detecting changes in JavaScript and CSS highlight the complexities of web development and the need for efficient change detection mechanisms.&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's correspondence with Leon Cooperman provides insights into the perspectives of influential figures in the business world on important issues.&lt;br&gt;- The current mortgage interest rates and their potential impact on home prices are crucial considerations for individuals in the real estate market.&lt;br&gt;- The influence of social media and visual appeal in the restaurant industry is evident in Yelp's identification of popular photo-taking restaurants.&lt;br&gt;- The continuous development and innovation in AI technology, as seen in Ideogram, showcase its potential for various applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall Summary:&lt;br&gt;This report highlights the latest developments and insights in the fields of tech, business, and AI. It showcases the success of AI companies like Midjourney, the advancements in reinforcement learning algorithms, the challenges in web development, and the perspectives of influential figures in the business world. Additionally, it provides valuable information on mortgage interest rates, the impact on home prices, and the influence of social media in the restaurant industry. These insights collectively demonstrate the continuous growth and potential of these industries.</summary></entry></feed>