<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-20T08:03:39Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 20 Sep 2023 08:03:39</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-20T08:03:39Z</published><updated>2023-09-20T08:03:39Z</updated><id>32fe9870-c7fc-4a6e-9458-2aefc5b12d4f</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Amazon made a new version of its cashierless tech that doesn't need cameras&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft addresses the huge Xbox leaks: here's Phil Spencer's full memo&lt;br&gt;- Integrating Flutter {all 6 platforms} and Python: Part 2, Live Talk&lt;br&gt;- Magnestar wants to solve the satellite signal interference problem for the entire space industry&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Sen. John Fetterman is selling 'body double' T-shirts, leaning into the right-wing conspiracy theory&lt;br&gt;- Sam Bankman-Fried's parents are accused of siphoning millions of dollars from FTX&lt;br&gt;- Bankrupt Digital Health Company Babylon Sells U.K. Assets For Just $620,000&lt;br&gt;- Emerge (YC W21) is hiring a lead front end engineer (remote, small team)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- What is ChatGPT, and should we be afraid of AI chatbots?&lt;br&gt;- a16z's Arianna Simpson believes crypto will be just fine, thank you for asking&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Others:&lt;br&gt;- A giant eruption covered 'over half the sun,' then crashed into Earth nearly 12 hours earlier than forecast&lt;br&gt;- The group behind a viral abortion rights ad is back with a new spot in Ohio and Pennsylvania focused on the hypothetical rape of a 12-year-old girl&lt;br&gt;- Australia's rare pink-diamond mine formed from the clashing and stretching of continents, a new study found. The discovery could lead to more colorful diamonds.&lt;br&gt;- Humans Have Exceeded Six of the Nine Boundaries Keeping Earth Habitable&lt;br&gt;- Resident Evil Village on the iPhone 15 Pro actually looks pretty good&lt;br&gt;- Drone footage shows Bakhmut in ruins after months of some of the bloodiest fighting of the Ukraine war&lt;br&gt;- Why the sun has two giant holes, and what that means for Earth&lt;br&gt;- Donald Trump was indicted in New York. Here's what we know so far.&lt;br&gt;- Marjorie Taylor Greene once again teases running for Senate or governor of Georgia: 'I have options'&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's biographer says 'nothing hurt him more' than his relationship with Amber Heard&lt;br&gt;- US stocks slump as investors brace for the Fed's next interest rate decision&lt;br&gt;- Rep. Lauren Boebert has been in the national spotlight even before her election to Congress. Here's a timeline of her biggest controversies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section highlights advancements in cashierless technology, satellite signal interference solutions, and integration of Flutter and Python.&lt;br&gt;- In the business section, there are controversies surrounding politicians and accusations of financial misconduct.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section explores the implications and concerns surrounding AI chatbots and the belief in the stability of cryptocurrency.&lt;br&gt;- The other topics cover natural phenomena, political developments, and conflicts around the world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, the report provides a diverse range of news topics, showcasing advancements in technology, controversies in business and politics, and insights into various aspects of society and the environment.</summary></entry></feed>