<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-17T08:03:26Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 17 Jan 2024 08:03:26</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-17T08:03:26Z</published><updated>2024-01-17T08:03:26Z</updated><id>8269ee17-702a-4d6e-acd1-21c5ebd7fd43</id><summary type="html">In recent news, Apple has made a significant change to its App Store policies, allowing US developers to now link to outside payment options. This move is expected to provide more flexibility and options for developers and users alike. In another development, OpenAI, a prominent artificial intelligence research organization, has decided to drop its ban on military tools and has partnered with The Pentagon. This decision has sparked discussions and debates regarding the ethical implications of such collaborations. Meanwhile, Samsung's Galaxy S24 preorders are still ongoing, with customers receiving a $50 credit for one more day. This offer has attracted attention and is likely to influence consumer decisions. In the political realm, former President Donald Trump faced criticism as he attacked E. Jean Carroll once again during his defamation trial. Carroll's lawyers urged the jury to take action and put an end to Trump's remarks. Shifting gears, a member of the Hacker News community sought advice on managing a website for an 87-year-old yoga teacher. The community provided suggestions and guidance on where to begin. Lastly, Samsung is set to unveil its highly anticipated Galaxy S24, and enthusiasts are eagerly awaiting the event. Details on how to watch the unveiling and expectations for the new device have been widely discussed. These recent events highlight the diverse range of topics and developments occurring in the world.</summary></entry></feed>