<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-18T06:01:20Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 18 Aug 2023 06:01:20</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-18T06:01:20Z</published><updated>2023-08-18T06:01:20Z</updated><id>523613a3-f939-466f-9cbd-6480aa54f6a9</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Fubo TV price and channels: A complete breakdown of streaming plans, networks, and upgrade packages in 2023&lt;br&gt;- YouTube Ads May Have Led to Online Tracking of Children, Research Says&lt;br&gt;- How the Army tried and failed to build a bicycle corps (2020)&lt;br&gt;- Amazon tests new star ratings that are even harder to read&lt;br&gt;- New AWS Instances For HPC Enable Weather Forecasting, Crash Simulations And More&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft travel article, seemingly written by AI, suggests vacationers dine at a food bank&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Whole Foods is attracting extreme couponers who are sharing tips on TikTok for saving money at the supermarket once known as 'whole paycheck'&lt;br&gt;- Bill Barr rejects Trump's plea that it's unfair to try him while he's running: 'You don't get immunity' by being a presidential candidate&lt;br&gt;- Match Group pauses background checks on Tinder and other dating apps&lt;br&gt;- CVS Retains Blue Plan’s Specialty Pharmacy Business And That’s Where The Money And Costs Are&lt;br&gt;- AEG Study Predicts A UAW Walkout Could Cost Billions In Losses To Automakers, Workers&lt;br&gt;- Validea's Top Communication Services Stocks Based On Joel ... - Nasdaq&lt;br&gt;- US stocks tumble as 10-year yield keeps climbing to hit highest since 2007&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Top 5 Free AI Courses Every Enthusiast Should Consider: Have You Enrolled Yet?&lt;br&gt;- The Sotheby's NFT lawsuit demonstrates how difficult it is to regulate art as an asset class&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Dolphins are dying in droves in the Black Sea, and Ukraine says it's evidence that Russia is committing a new kind of war crime&lt;br&gt;- 9 techniques villagers used to bury people they feared were 'vampires' to keep them from coming back from the dead&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine says it can shoot down Ka-52 attack helicopters but Russia needs to be stopped from making new ones&lt;br&gt;- Maui wildfires made Hawaii's housing market crisis worse &amp;mdash; residents already feared being priced out&lt;br&gt;- How to Communicate When Trust Is Low Without Digging Yourself into a Deeper Hole&lt;br&gt;- Fuzz testing: the best thing to happen to our application tests&lt;br&gt;- Why does email development have to suck? – Explaining all the &lt;tr&gt;'s and &lt;td&gt;'s&lt;br&gt;- What I learned after managing a small team for 2 years&lt;br&gt;- Lab-grown diamonds may not be forever—but their rise is driving down prices&lt;br&gt;- Professor Says Elon Musk Locked Him Out of His Twitter Account&lt;br&gt;- Parts Of Florida Under Mosquito-Borne Illness Alert: What To Know About Dengue—And Why Cases Are Rising&lt;br&gt;- Abortion Pill Mifepristone Is Still Available, Despite Appeals Court Ruling—Here’s Where And What To Know&lt;br&gt;- Study: Extreme heat can cause cognitive decline. Here’s who it will hurt the most&lt;br&gt;- Arizona Wildcats RB Michael Wiley named to Earl Campbell Tyler ... - PrimePublishers.com&lt;br&gt;- Best AirPods sales and deals in August 2023: AirPods (3rd generation) fall to all-time low&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section covers various topics such as streaming services, online tracking, AI courses, and new advancements in technology.&lt;br&gt;- The business section includes news about companies like Whole Foods, Match Group, CVS, and the impact of a potential UAW walkout.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section focuses on the challenges of regulating art as an asset class and the popularity of AI courses.&lt;br&gt;- The other section covers a wide range of topics including war crimes, historical burial practices, housing market crises, communication strategies, and health-related issues.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, the report highlights the diverse range of news and topics covered, showcasing the intersection of technology, business, AI, and other areas of interest. It also emphasizes the importance of staying informed about current events and trends in various industries.</summary></entry></feed>