<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-13T12:01:20Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 13 Aug 2023 12:01:20</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-13T12:01:20Z</published><updated>2023-08-13T12:01:20Z</updated><id>ac7501fc-6a3d-4e98-bab1-45aa6937268b</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Cruise blames Outside Lands for driverless car traffic fiasco in San Francisco&lt;br&gt;- Cruise, a self-driving car company, blames the Outside Lands music festival for causing traffic issues in San Francisco.&lt;br&gt;- The company claims that road closures and increased pedestrian activity during the festival disrupted their autonomous vehicle operations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. We are a lot closer to the Landauer limit than I thought&lt;br&gt;- Researchers suggest that we are closer to reaching the Landauer limit than previously believed.&lt;br&gt;- The Landauer limit is a theoretical minimum amount of energy required to perform a computation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Researchers from USC and Microsoft Propose UniversalNER: A New AI Model Trained with Targeted Distillation Recognizing 13k+ Entity Types and Outperforming ChatGPT’s NER Accuracy by 9% F1 on 43 Datasets&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from USC and Microsoft introduce UniversalNER, an AI model trained to recognize over 13,000 entity types.&lt;br&gt;- The model outperforms ChatGPT's named entity recognition (NER) accuracy by 9% F1 on 43 different datasets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Monorepo vs Microrepo: How to Choose the Best Repository Structure for Your Code&lt;br&gt;- This article discusses the differences between monorepo and microrepo repository structures for code management.&lt;br&gt;- It provides insights on how to choose the best structure based on the specific needs of a project.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. You can win $50,000 if you successfully hack a US government satellite&lt;br&gt;- A challenge is announced where participants can win $50,000 if they successfully hack a US government satellite.&lt;br&gt;- The challenge aims to identify vulnerabilities in satellite systems and improve their security.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. NixOS RFC 136 approved: A plan to stabilize the new CLI and Flakes incrementally&lt;br&gt;- NixOS RFC 136, a proposal to stabilize the new command-line interface (CLI) and Flakes, is approved.&lt;br&gt;- The plan outlines a gradual approach to stabilize these features in the NixOS operating system.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Doctor GPT: A Large Language Model That Can Pass the US Medical Licensing Exam&lt;br&gt;- Doctor GPT is introduced as a large language model capable of passing the US Medical Licensing Exam.&lt;br&gt;- The model has potential applications in medical education and assessment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;1. Today’s Wordle #785 Hints, Clues And Answer For Sunday, August 13th&lt;br&gt;- This section provides hints, clues, and the answer for Wordle puzzle #785 on August 13th.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. What Venus Is Doing This Weekend Is Only Done By One Other Planet&lt;br&gt;- The article discusses a unique phenomenon happening with Venus over the weekend, which is only observed in one other planet.&lt;br&gt;- It highlights the significance of this event in planetary science.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- In the tech category, the challenges faced by autonomous vehicles during events and the progress towards the Landauer limit are notable.&lt;br&gt;- The business section provides insights into choosing the best repository structure for code management.&lt;br&gt;- AI advancements include the approval of a plan to stabilize new features in NixOS and the development of a language model capable of passing medical exams.&lt;br&gt;- The other topics cover a range of subjects, including puzzles, planetary science, and communication mistakes in the tech ecosystem.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report highlights the latest developments and insights across various fields.</summary></entry></feed>