<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-16T16:01:19Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 16 Aug 2023 16:01:19</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-16T16:01:19Z</published><updated>2023-08-16T16:01:19Z</updated><id>c7036638-75d3-4444-8fa2-907f8627daf0</id><summary type="html">Judge blocks Internet Archive from sharing copyrighted books - The Seattle Times&lt;br&gt;Category: Tech&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Points:&lt;br&gt;- A judge has issued a ruling that prevents the Internet Archive from sharing copyrighted books online.&lt;br&gt;- The Internet Archive is a digital library that provides free access to millions of books, movies, and other materials.&lt;br&gt;- The ruling comes after a group of publishers filed a lawsuit against the Internet Archive, claiming copyright infringement.&lt;br&gt;- The judge's decision is seen as a blow to the concept of digital libraries and the accessibility of knowledge.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- This ruling raises questions about the balance between copyright protection and the availability of information online.&lt;br&gt;- It highlights the challenges faced by digital libraries in navigating copyright laws and ensuring fair use of copyrighted materials.&lt;br&gt;- The case also underscores the need for a comprehensive review of copyright laws in the digital age.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bartender is going viral on TikTok for saying he'd snub a customer for a regular patron who 'tips 50% every time'&lt;br&gt;Category: Business&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Points:&lt;br&gt;- A bartender's TikTok video has gone viral, in which he states that he would prioritize serving a regular customer who consistently tips 50% over a one-time customer.&lt;br&gt;- The video has sparked a debate about tipping culture and the treatment of customers based on their tipping habits.&lt;br&gt;- Some argue that tipping should not determine the level of service a customer receives, while others believe that tipping is an important factor in the service industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- This viral video highlights the importance of tipping in the service industry and the impact it can have on customer service.&lt;br&gt;- It raises questions about the fairness of relying on tips as a significant portion of a worker's income.&lt;br&gt;- The video also brings attention to the power dynamics between customers and service workers, and the potential for bias in serving customers based on their tipping habits.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's top general Sergei Shoigu bragged that the Kremlin's war in Ukraine has 'debunked many myths' that NATO weapons and military standards are superior&lt;br&gt;Category: AI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Points:&lt;br&gt;- Russia's top general, Sergei Shoigu, has claimed that the Kremlin's war in Ukraine has disproven the belief that NATO weapons and military standards are superior.&lt;br&gt;- Shoigu's statement is seen as a propaganda tactic to boost Russia's image and undermine NATO's military capabilities.&lt;br&gt;- The conflict in Ukraine has been a testing ground for new military technologies and strategies, with both sides showcasing their capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- This statement by Russia's top general highlights the role of propaganda in shaping public opinion and perception of military capabilities.&lt;br&gt;- It underscores the importance of strategic messaging in conflicts and the use of technology to project power.&lt;br&gt;- The conflict in Ukraine serves as a reminder of the ongoing geopolitical tensions and the competition between global powers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to change your Facebook cover photo on desktop or mobile&lt;br&gt;Category: Tech&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Points:&lt;br&gt;- This article provides a step-by-step guide on how to change your Facebook cover photo on both desktop and mobile devices.&lt;br&gt;- It includes instructions and screenshots to help users navigate the process.&lt;br&gt;- The guide covers different methods for changing the cover photo, including using the Facebook app and the website.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- This guide demonstrates the importance of user-friendly interfaces and clear instructions in technology platforms.&lt;br&gt;- It highlights the need for accessible resources to help users navigate and customize their online experiences.&lt;br&gt;- The article also showcases the evolving nature of social media platforms and the constant updates and changes to their features.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The case of the Internet Archive highlights the challenges of copyright in the digital age and the need for a balance between access to information and copyright protection.&lt;br&gt;- The viral bartender video sparks a discussion about tipping culture and the treatment of customers in the service industry.&lt;br&gt;- Russia's claims in the Ukraine conflict shed light on the role of propaganda and the competition between global powers.&lt;br&gt;- The guide on changing Facebook cover photos emphasizes the importance of user-friendly interfaces and accessible resources in technology platforms.</summary></entry></feed>