<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-10T10:44:29Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 10 Aug 2023 10:44:29</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-10T10:44:29Z</published><updated>2023-08-10T10:44:29Z</updated><id>7d766314-9e19-4b37-afbe-485ee55bbdbe</id><summary type="html">Report: August 10th News Highlights&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Zoom assures users that it will not use their calls to train AI without consent, following backlash over its terms of service.&lt;br&gt;- Verizon announces plans to raise prices on certain unlimited plans.&lt;br&gt;- ELO introduces the ELO Vagabond, a device that turns smartphones into gaming consoles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Seattle becomes the first city in the US to protect gig workers from sudden deactivation.&lt;br&gt;- Top economist Paul Krugman attributes food inflation to Russia.&lt;br&gt;- Dollar General shopper recounts an incident where the store remained open after closing time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers identify a protein that may help protect against osteoporosis.&lt;br&gt;- Supreme Court rules in favor of Apple, allowing them to keep their App Store payment rules.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Joel Meyerowitz's photography career is showcased in a series of pictures.&lt;br&gt;- Norwegian's newest cruise ship, complete with a go-kart track and food hall, sets sail this week.&lt;br&gt;- Midland, Texas experiences an oil boom, attracting millennials in search of high-paying jobs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is facing scrutiny over privacy concerns, as seen with Zoom's backlash and the ongoing debate over AI training.&lt;br&gt;- Economic factors, such as inflation caused by external factors like Russia, can impact businesses and consumers.&lt;br&gt;- The gig economy is gaining attention, with Seattle taking steps to protect gig workers.&lt;br&gt;- The travel and tourism industry continues to evolve, with Norwegian's innovative cruise ship offering unique amenities.&lt;br&gt;- The oil industry remains a significant factor in attracting job seekers to certain regions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report highlights the intersection of technology, business, and various other topics, showcasing the diverse range of news and developments happening globally.</summary></entry></feed>