<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-15T08:03:33Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 15 Jan 2024 08:03:33</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-15T08:03:33Z</published><updated>2024-01-15T08:03:33Z</updated><id>d4bc99f1-244e-485b-a9b7-fa5c2ff60f46</id><summary type="html">In recent news, Google AI has introduced GRANOLA QA, a groundbreaking technology that revolutionizes question answering through multi-granularity evaluation. This development, in collaboration with researchers from UC Berkeley and Meta, showcases the power of artificial intelligence in enhancing our ability to find accurate answers to complex queries. Additionally, the team at UC Berkeley and Meta has presented AST-T5, a novel pretraining paradigm that utilizes abstract syntax trees (ASTs) to significantly improve the performance of code-centric language models. This advancement holds great potential for boosting the efficiency and effectiveness of coding processes. In another exciting development, mathematicians from RUDN University have successfully enhanced 5G and 6G networks using advanced machine learning techniques. Their pioneering work in traffic forecasting has led to smarter radio resource management, ultimately improving the overall performance and reliability of these networks. However, amidst these technological advancements, it is disheartening to witness the spread of misinformation by GOP presidential candidates regarding the fentanyl crisis. Blaming illegal migrants for the crisis, these candidates are misleading voters and diverting attention from the real causes and solutions. On a more personal note, I have always dreamt of driving my own car, but living in the world's most expensive city has shattered that dream. The high cost of living has made it clear that owning a car is an unattainable luxury for me. In other news, The New York Times has undergone a significant transition to digital subscriptions, adapting to the changing landscape of media consumption. However, the newspaper is currently involved in a legal dispute with OpenAI and Microsoft, which raises questions about the future of digital publishing and intellectual property rights. Lastly, DA Fani Willis has come forward to defend a prosecutor she hired for Trump's Georgia election case amid allegations of an 'improper' relationship. This situation highlights the complexities and controversies surrounding high-profile legal cases.</summary></entry></feed>