<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-14T02:01:12Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 14 Aug 2023 02:01:12</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-14T02:01:12Z</published><updated>2023-08-14T02:01:12Z</updated><id>d1a3e7fc-fc0f-45cc-a9e4-719b15f48860</id><summary type="html">Report: Emerging Trends in Tech and Business&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Tech&lt;br&gt;- College professors are resorting to traditional methods like paper exams and handwritten essays to prevent cheating using AI language models like ChatGPT.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft is gaining trust over Google, possibly due to concerns about privacy and data security.&lt;br&gt;- Apple's upcoming M3 Ultra Mac Studio is rumored to feature a powerful 32-core CPU and up to 80 GPU cores.&lt;br&gt;- Mitochondria, the powerhouse of cells, hold the key to understanding the origins of cellular complexity on Earth.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's AI-powered shopping tools offer potential savings and convenience for consumers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech industry is witnessing a shift towards traditional methods to address concerns related to AI and privacy. Apple's advancements in hardware highlight the ongoing pursuit of performance and efficiency. The exploration of mitochondria's role in cellular complexity showcases the continuous quest for understanding life at a fundamental level. AI-powered shopping tools demonstrate the integration of AI into everyday consumer experiences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Business&lt;br&gt;- Georgia prosecutors have discovered texts and emails linking Trump's legal team to a voting breach.&lt;br&gt;- A trans woman shares her experience of coming out at Goldman Sachs and the fear of being judged by colleagues.&lt;br&gt;- Broken Bear, an AI teddy bear, aims to provide emotional support to individuals.&lt;br&gt;- Disruptive fintech players are set to take the stage, showcasing innovation in the financial industry.&lt;br&gt;- Remote work tools, trends, and challenges are explored in the post-pandemic work era.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The intersection of politics and business is highlighted through the discovery of potential links between Trump's legal team and a voting breach. The personal narrative of a trans woman at Goldman Sachs sheds light on workplace inclusivity. The emergence of AI emotional support tools reflects the growing importance of mental health. Fintech continues to disrupt traditional financial systems, and remote work has become a significant aspect of the post-pandemic work landscape.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. AI&lt;br&gt;- The potential market for AI is questioned, raising concerns about its actual viability.&lt;br&gt;- Stability AI introduces Japanese StableLM Alpha, a significant advancement in Japanese language models.&lt;br&gt;- The Conjugate Gradient Method is explored as an approach to optimization without excessive complexity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The viability and sustainability of the AI market are subjects of debate, emphasizing the need for practical applications and tangible outcomes. The introduction of Japanese StableLM Alpha showcases the global expansion of AI language models. The exploration of optimization methods highlights the ongoing pursuit of efficiency and effectiveness in AI algorithms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary: The COVID-19 lockdown has had an impact on obesity disparities, emphasizing the need for health interventions. The tech industry is witnessing a shift towards traditional methods to address concerns related to AI and privacy. Business intersects with politics, inclusivity, mental health, and innovation in fintech. AI's market viability, language model advancements, and optimization methods continue to be areas of exploration. Overall, these trends reflect the ongoing evolution and impact of technology and business in various domains.</summary></entry></feed>