<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-04T20:02:11Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 04 Oct 2023 20:02:11</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-04T20:02:11Z</published><updated>2023-10-04T20:02:11Z</updated><id>e9c34d76-d0e0-4889-81ff-729fa4c0ec06</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Softbank chief says that those who don't adopt AI are 'goldfish' who will be 'left behind'&lt;br&gt;- In his first job, Sam Bankman-Fried designed a system that called Trump's 2016 win before major news outlets &amp;mdash; but the firm still lost $300 million on election night&lt;br&gt;- JavaScript and Functional Programming: A Dive into Pure Functions, Currying, and Functional Composition&lt;br&gt;- This AI Paper Unveils a Deep-Learning Framework Called DeepMB for Real-Time Optoacoustic Image Reconstruction with Adjustable Speed of Sound&lt;br&gt;- AI Governance Is Here—What Your Organization Needs To Know (Part 2)&lt;br&gt;- Not All Algorithms Are AI (Part 2): The Rise Of Real AI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech section highlights the importance of AI adoption and its impact on various industries. It also delves into the advancements in programming languages and deep-learning frameworks. The insights gathered suggest that AI governance is crucial for organizations to navigate the evolving landscape of artificial intelligence.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett has only topped Forbes' rich list once &amp;ndash; while Bill Gates ranked first for 24 years straight&lt;br&gt;- Wall Street's fear gauge spikes to a 4-month high as investors worry the market downturn will deepen&lt;br&gt;- EU lawmakers take aim at ‘arbitrary’ decisions by Big Tech in Media Freedom Act vote&lt;br&gt;- Biomaterials Firm Bolt Threads, Formerly A Unicorn, Plans SPAC Deal At A $250 Million Valuation&lt;br&gt;- Going ‘Glocal’: How Brands Can Adapt And Thrive In A Changing Global Landscape&lt;br&gt;- Delta Air Lines is yet again walking back changes after angering fans of the brand. Can it win them back?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business section highlights the dynamics of wealth accumulation, market volatility, regulatory actions, and brand management. The insights gathered suggest the importance of adaptability and customer satisfaction in the business landscape.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Softbank chief says that those who don't adopt AI are 'goldfish' who will be 'left behind'&lt;br&gt;- AI bias tests gloss over a crucial aspect of skin color, Sony research claims&lt;br&gt;- AI Governance Is Here—What Your Organization Needs To Know (Part 2)&lt;br&gt;- Not All Algorithms Are AI (Part 2): The Rise Of Real AI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The AI section emphasizes the significance of AI adoption, the challenges of bias in AI systems, and the need for effective AI governance. The insights gathered suggest that organizations should be aware of the ethical implications and limitations of AI technologies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Savings Account and CD Rates Today | New CD Provider Tops Our List with a 6.25% APY&lt;br&gt;- Tank battles in Ukraine are putting several generations of 'crappy Russian armored vehicles' and their flaws on display&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine is getting better at using NATO tanks and armored vehicles in its counteroffensive, CNN reports&lt;br&gt;- Can You Trust Those Awards You See in Auto Ads? (2010)&lt;br&gt;- Creators of quantum dots, used in TV displays and cell studies, win chemistry Nobel&lt;br&gt;- Trillions In G20 Fossil Fuel Subsidies Fuel Profits And Climate Change&lt;br&gt;- Louisiana Supreme Court Ruling Overturns Reform Law Intended to Fix “Three-Strikes” Sentences&lt;br&gt;- Wheels Of Justice Slow To Accept Legal Tech As Funding Falls&lt;br&gt;- Personal Loan Interest Rates Today, October 4, 2023 | Today's Top Personal Loan Rates&lt;br&gt;- The New Covid Updated Vaccine Is Now Available- Here’s What You Need To Know&lt;br&gt;- Notoriously scruffy Sam Bankman-Fried gets a makeover for his criminal trial with a new haircut and suit&lt;br&gt;- The GOP's new interim House speaker kicked Nancy Pelosi out of her hideaway office so he could use it himself&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The other section covers a wide range of topics including finance, geopolitics, climate change, legal reforms, and current events. The insights gathered suggest the need for transparency, sustainability, and adaptability in various sectors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall Insights:&lt;br&gt;- AI adoption is crucial for organizations to stay competitive and avoid being left behind.&lt;br&gt;- Ethical considerations and bias in AI systems need to be addressed for responsible AI development.&lt;br&gt;- Adaptability and customer satisfaction are key factors for business success in a changing global landscape.&lt;br&gt;- Transparency, sustainability, and accountability are important in finance, geopolitics, and legal reforms.&lt;br&gt;- The market volatility and wealth accumulation dynamics impact the business landscape.&lt;br&gt;- Technological advancements in programming languages and deep-learning frameworks drive innovation.&lt;br&gt;- Climate change and energy subsidies have significant implications for the environment and economy.&lt;br&gt;- Current events and political dynamics shape various sectors and industries.</summary></entry></feed>