<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-08T20:02:55Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 08 Dec 2023 20:02:55</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-08T20:02:55Z</published><updated>2023-12-08T20:02:55Z</updated><id>1d7c3227-7953-4af3-a480-ca60fd509a37</id><summary type="html">In the world today, there have been several noteworthy events. Google has taken a "fake it till you make it" approach to showcase Gemini's multimodal capabilities. However, there has also been a disturbing rise in people using AI apps to manipulate and undress women in photos, as revealed by data. Meanwhile, New York's 'Son of Sam' law has not deterred George Santos from making money through his Cameo videos. Investors have shown great interest in AI startups following the launch of ChatGPT, with 32 pitch decks used by AI founders to win over venture capitalists. In a surprising move, Elon Musk is asking the Supreme Court to remove his 'Twitter sitter,' arguing that it infringes upon his free speech rights and is unconstitutional. On a different note, parents today face the daunting task of paying $3.4 million to secure the American Dream for themselves and their children. Baby boomers seem to be dominating the housing market once again, making all-cash purchases. Sam Altman, after being fired from OpenAI, claimed that his iPhone broke due to an overwhelming influx of messages. In a unique side hustle, someone has managed to earn $27,000 by renting their clothes to strangers, dedicating just one hour a day to this endeavor. Elon Musk has expressed his willingness to consider bringing back Sandy Hook conspiracy theorist Alex Jones, who has been banned for five years, to his platform X. Additionally, a man accused of aiding North Korea in evading US sanctions using cryptocurrency once expressed his desire to create a "paradise society." The differences between US and UK education systems have been highlighted by an individual who had to adapt their writing style. An employment law attorney has shared three signs to watch out for that may indicate impending end-of-year layoffs. Tesla has faced a setback in Sweden as it lost a legal battle related to a dispute with Nordic unions. In the gaming world, Baldur's Gate 3 has emerged as the Game of the Year at the Game Awards. The UK's Competition and Markets Authority is currently examining whether the Microsoft and OpenAI tie-up constitutes a "relevant merger." Exciting advancements in medical technology are on the horizon, with the development of medical microrobots that can navigate inside the human body. Researchers have also made progress in unsupervised learning of pixel clustering to map microstructural features in pathological tissues. COP28 has brought attention to the Loss &amp; Damage Fund and its significance in the fight against climate change. The US rail industry has received a significant boost with $8 billion allocated to passenger and bullet train projects, marking a "watershed moment." Despite their diverse backgrounds, the current generation in the workplace has found common ground in one particular career-building aspect. The movie 'Poor Things' has garnered attention for its imaginative set designs. AI web browsers are gaining popularity for their ability to perform tasks that Chrome cannot. The NBA has triumphed over critics of its In-Season Tournament. Sadly, a former police chief who fought to rebuild after a devastating fire in New Mexico passed away before he could return home. In scientific research, studies have been conducted on the binding properties of synthetic cannabinoid receptor agonists and their interaction with plasma proteins. In terms of wealth, the world's richest families saw their fortunes increase by $1.5 trillion in 2023, with notable leaders being the owners of Hermès and the rulers of Abu Dhabi. Neighbors have shared their experiences of living next to Jeff Bezos, the renowned entrepreneur. Lastly, someone has fulfilled their dream of buying a house directly across the street from their best friend, allowing them to keep a close eye on each other. Additionally, a significant portion of consumers are so fed up with inflation that they are willing to risk a recession in order to obtain lower prices.</summary></entry></feed>