<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-16T20:02:05Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 16 Nov 2023 20:02:05</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-16T20:02:05Z</published><updated>2023-11-16T20:02:05Z</updated><id>691c0feb-bc9e-4587-b4dd-397609817f15</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Google Deepmind and YouTube unveil new Lyria AI model for music generation&lt;br&gt;- DOS_deck: Play DOS games in the browser with full controller support&lt;br&gt;- Windows is now an app for iPhones, iPads, Macs, and PCs&lt;br&gt;- YouTube teases AI tool that clones famous singers — with their permission&lt;br&gt;- Epic is going to let you report voice conversations in Fortnite&lt;br&gt;- With Muse, Unity aims to give developers generative AI that’s useful and ethical&lt;br&gt;- Build a Responsive Space Travel Agency Website | HTML , CSS And JavaScript&lt;br&gt;- Shopping Crate &amp; Barrel’s new virtual store feels like playing a video game&lt;br&gt;- Outer space is full of human trash. Now we have to get rid of it&lt;br&gt;- Antitrust lawsuits are piling up for Google. Here’s how they could change the company&lt;br&gt;- Spotify’s podcast and audiobook discovery will get a boost from Google Cloud’s AI&lt;br&gt;- ‘Armored Core VI’ Gets Its First Robot Damashii Toy And It’s An End Game Boss&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Investors Met With Slowing Returns on Capital At John Wiley &amp; Sons (NYSE:WLY) - Simply Wall St&lt;br&gt;- Rick Lang Obituary - Wiley Funeral Home - Granbury - 2023 - Legacy.com&lt;br&gt;- Real estate made China rich. Now it's looking more like kryptonite.&lt;br&gt;- Inside the Autumn issue: We decide what the future looks like&lt;br&gt;- The CEO of Ford is throwing shade at the Cybertruck's viral &amp;mdash;&amp;nbsp;and messy &amp;mdash; attempt to drive up a dirt hill&lt;br&gt;- Article: Agile Coaching as a Path toward a Deeper Meaning of Work and Life&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Google DeepMind wants to define what counts as artificial general intelligence&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- I left NYC and moved to Eastern Europe after my divorce &amp;mdash; but here's what I wish I would've done differently&lt;br&gt;- Why disinformation experts say the Israel-Hamas war is a nightmare to investigate&lt;br&gt;- This Youth Detention Center Superintendent Illegally Locks Kids Alone in Cells. No One Has Forced Him to Stop.&lt;br&gt;- A reporter drove a Rivian to 126 EV fast-chargers in LA and found out-of-order signs on dozens of them&lt;br&gt;- The Biggest Questions: Why is the universe so complex and beautiful?&lt;br&gt;- Planet Where It Rains Sand Is A ‘Pivotal Milestone’ Say Scientists&lt;br&gt;- Planet Where It Rains Sand Is A ‘Pivotal Milestone’ Say Scientists&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section highlights advancements in AI, gaming, virtual reality, and space travel.&lt;br&gt;- The business section discusses the financial performance of John Wiley &amp; Sons and the impact of real estate in China.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section focuses on Google DeepMind's efforts to define artificial general intelligence.&lt;br&gt;- The other section covers personal experiences, social issues, and environmental concerns.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report showcases the latest developments in technology, business, AI, and other areas, providing insights into various topics of interest.</summary></entry></feed>