<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-20T08:04:01Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 20 Nov 2023 08:04:01</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-20T08:04:01Z</published><updated>2023-11-20T08:04:01Z</updated><id>3f157c48-51ac-4935-838b-d331a5a9e731</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- OpenAl is building powerful tech and there are concerns about transparency and honesty from Sam Altman.&lt;br&gt;- Non-profit Matrix.org Foundation is allegedly moving funds to a for-profit company.&lt;br&gt;- Semantic Hearing is a machine learning-based capability for hearable devices.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk warns about the risks of advanced AI and the firing of Sam Altman by OpenAI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Wiley urges following Traynor's approach.&lt;br&gt;- VCs support Sam Altman and criticize OpenAI's board.&lt;br&gt;- The College Board is making money while promoting AP exams among low-income students.&lt;br&gt;- Companies are fighting against the US government to keep junk fees.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's board fired Sam Altman and there are questions about his potential return.&lt;br&gt;- Boston officials express concerns about limitations on AI benefits due to Biden's directive.&lt;br&gt;- ChatGPT is being tested and its potential benefits are being discussed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- TCU football shines against Baylor in the Bluebonnet Battle.&lt;br&gt;- Tampa Bay researcher works to save endangered smalltooth sawfish.&lt;br&gt;- Nearly 20 Hindawi journals have been delisted from a leading index.&lt;br&gt;- Defence against scientific fraud is proposed as a new MSc course.&lt;br&gt;- Rosalynn Carter, former first lady of the United States, passes away at 96.&lt;br&gt;- Italy's cultivated meat ban is seen as a strategic move ahead of EU elections.&lt;br&gt;- Top athletes become players in the art market off the court and field.&lt;br&gt;- Yemen's Houthi rebels hijacked a cargo ship in the Red Sea on Iran's orders, according to Israel.&lt;br&gt;- Steven Johnson discusses whether a win over Oklahoma can salvage TCU's season.&lt;br&gt;- How to identify mass tourism places before visiting them.&lt;br&gt;- A different approach to landing your first developer job without grinding LeetCode.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's transparency and leadership have come into question with the firing of Sam Altman.&lt;br&gt;- Concerns about the ethical use and limitations of AI are being raised.&lt;br&gt;- Financial interests and profit motives can impact non-profit organizations.&lt;br&gt;- The intersection of sports and art is explored through the involvement of top athletes.&lt;br&gt;- Political motivations may influence decisions such as banning cultivated meat.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of fees and financial practices on businesses and consumers is a contentious issue.&lt;br&gt;- The potential benefits and limitations of AI are being debated and tested.&lt;br&gt;- The importance of integrity and combating scientific fraud is emphasized.&lt;br&gt;- The influence of social media and public opinion on leadership decisions is evident.&lt;br&gt;- The significance of strategic moves and elections in various contexts is highlighted.&lt;br&gt;- The role of technology in scientific research and education is emphasized.&lt;br&gt;- The challenges and misconceptions surrounding personal finance are discussed.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of AI on various industries, including education and research, is explored.&lt;br&gt;- The connection between sports and community engagement is evident.&lt;br&gt;- The risks and benefits of advanced AI are debated, with concerns about transparency and accountability.</summary></entry></feed>