<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-28T08:03:33Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 28 Oct 2023 08:03:33</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-28T08:03:33Z</published><updated>2023-10-28T08:03:33Z</updated><id>653a4afe-f22e-4fff-a5b1-021d5de099d7</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Xbox Game Pass offers a variety of games for a monthly fee, with different plans and features.&lt;br&gt;- Google's Bard chatbot now responds in real time and can be silenced mid-sentence.&lt;br&gt;- A comprehensive review of video diffusion models in AI-generated content.&lt;br&gt;- Can proof assistants' language be used for general-purpose programming?&lt;br&gt;- Wired vs. wireless gaming headsets: pros and cons of each.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The gaming industry continues to evolve with subscription-based services like Xbox Game Pass. AI-generated content and proof assistants show potential for advancements in programming. The choice between wired and wireless gaming headsets depends on personal preferences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Disney accuses a district appointed by DeSantis of withholding lawsuit documents.&lt;br&gt;- Meta (formerly Facebook) plans to invest $2B in Anthropic as AI funding competition intensifies.&lt;br&gt;- Walmart and Amazon offer early Black Friday deals on various products.&lt;br&gt;- Jamie Dimon sells $140 million worth of JPMorgan shares but still maintains involvement.&lt;br&gt;- Two Morrison Foerster lawyers are recognized in Los Angeles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: Legal disputes, investments, and early Black Friday deals are prominent in the business world. Jamie Dimon's sale of shares raises questions about his continued involvement. Recognition of lawyers highlights their achievements in the industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Meta's Threads aims to become the leading platform for online public conversations.&lt;br&gt;- Google reportedly supports Anthropic with a $2B investment in the AI sector.&lt;br&gt;- Apple's missing AI and the launch of a mystery iMac raise curiosity.&lt;br&gt;- Android Circuit discusses Qualcomm's Snapdragon 8 Gen 3, Xiaomi 14's impressive screen, and Honor Magic 6's AI secrets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: Meta and Google's investments in AI highlight the growing competition in the field. Apple's focus on AI and the launch of new products generate interest. Qualcomm, Xiaomi, and Honor showcase advancements in AI technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;This report covers various topics such as gaming, business, and AI. Key insights include the popularity of subscription-based gaming services, the potential of AI-generated content, and the competition in the AI funding landscape. Additionally, legal disputes, Black Friday deals, and notable achievements in the legal industry are discussed. The report provides a comprehensive overview of recent developments in these areas.</summary></entry></feed>