<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-19T20:01:02Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 19 Aug 2023 20:01:02</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-19T20:01:02Z</published><updated>2023-08-19T20:01:02Z</updated><id>fe6bc367-ba87-4361-8a82-e6e4bafb2127</id><summary type="html">Report: AI Impact on Various Topics&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Academic journals are struggling to adapt to the presence of AI-assisted papers, which are making their way into publications.&lt;br&gt;- AI is being used as a traffic police system in the UK, catching hundreds of drivers in the act.&lt;br&gt;- San Francisco now has a driverless bus service in addition to 24-hour robotaxis.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft researchers have introduced SpeechX, a versatile speech generation model capable of zero-shot TTS and various speech transformation tasks.&lt;br&gt;- Scientists have built a drone that mimics birds by seeking air currents, flying with minimal power.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: AI is revolutionizing various industries, from academia to transportation. It is enhancing research capabilities, improving traffic management, and enabling autonomous vehicles. Additionally, AI is advancing speech generation models and drone technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Business:&lt;br&gt;- The bad news for automakers in China continues to worsen.&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett, Michael Burry, and other top investors have made significant portfolio changes.&lt;br&gt;- A Colorado airpark is up for sale, with a prospective buyer planning to turn it into a community for private plane owners.&lt;br&gt;- America's obsession with weight-loss drugs is affecting the economy of Denmark.&lt;br&gt;- Jewelry worth up to $63,000 was stolen from a top museum and sold on eBay for as little as $50.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business landscape is experiencing both challenges and opportunities. Automakers in China are facing difficulties, while investors are making strategic portfolio changes. Unique real estate opportunities and the impact of weight-loss drug consumption on international economies are also noteworthy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. AI:&lt;br&gt;- Chroma, an AI-native open-source vector database, is introduced for LLMs, enabling faster development of Python or JavaScript LLM apps with memory.&lt;br&gt;- Driverless cars are found to be biased against dark-skinned people and children, according to scientists.&lt;br&gt;- Identification and practical validation of spectrally efficient non-orthogonal frequency shaping waveform is explored.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: AI advancements are being made in various domains. The introduction of Chroma enhances AI development capabilities, while concerns about bias in driverless cars raise ethical considerations. Additionally, research on waveform identification contributes to the improvement of AI technologies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;AI is making significant impacts across different sectors. In the tech industry, AI is revolutionizing research and transportation. In the business world, it is influencing investment decisions, real estate markets, and international economies. In the field of AI itself, advancements are being made in database development, addressing biases, and waveform identification. Overall, AI is reshaping industries and presenting both challenges and opportunities.</summary></entry></feed>