<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-11T12:01:11Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:01:11</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-11T12:01:11Z</published><updated>2023-08-11T12:01:11Z</updated><id>a339efbe-d56d-4fe8-9d1c-2ab8e2dfe680</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Setting JavaScript framework standards (what's wrong with the React-set standard and why everyone should be like Svelte)&lt;br&gt;- Sensor Watch: a board swap for the classic Casio F-91W wristwatch&lt;br&gt;- Robotaxis score a huge victory in California with approval to operate 24/7&lt;br&gt;- Git scraping: track changes over time by scraping to a Git repository&lt;br&gt;- A bit of ST and a bit of IO: Designing a DCPU-16 emulator&lt;br&gt;- Hidden forces and sliding screens trick the senses to make VR feel more real&lt;br&gt;- The dream may be dead, but here's how LK-99 would've changed AI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- A Canadian woman mysteriously received over 50 packages of women's shoes she never ordered. She says she was asked to pay over $220 in collect-on-delivery fees.&lt;br&gt;- Proposed Cybercrime Treaty's International Cooperation Provisions Could Let Tyrants Run Amok&lt;br&gt;- Wisk and Archer Will Collaborate on Air Taxis and End Legal Fight&lt;br&gt;- US Special Operations Command is working on a new mini-sub to carry SEALs to their targets in style&lt;br&gt;- 'The Wire' writer David Simon ignites a debate over NYC traffic cameras in school zones&lt;br&gt;- Christmas in August? Home Depot just dropped its holiday catalog—and some items are already sold out&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Waymo And Cruise Get Permits For Full-Day Robotaxi For Money In SF, LA, Silicon Valley&lt;br&gt;- Hidden forces and sliding screens trick the senses to make VR feel more real&lt;br&gt;- The dream may be dead, but here's how LK-99 would've changed AI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- 🧠 How to come up with new ideas (Building 101 #1)&lt;br&gt;- Today's Wordle #783 Hints, Clues And Answer For Friday, August 11th&lt;br&gt;- How to Earn, Use, and Maximize United Miles — Even if You're Not a Frequent Flyer&lt;br&gt;- Why You Should Stop Building Communities on Slack w/ Domitrius Clerk&lt;br&gt;- The Only Sure-Fire Ways To See (And Hear) The Perseid Meteor Peak This Weekend&lt;br&gt;- Perseids: Best Meteor Shower Of 2023 Peaks This Weekend—How To See It, According To Experts&lt;br&gt;- What We Know About 'Eris' Covid Variant EG.5: The Dominant Stain Driving An Uptick In Cases&lt;br&gt;- Five Things I Wish I Knew Before Playing The 'Escape From Tarkov' Wipe&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- In the tech category, there is a focus on JavaScript framework standards, sensor technology, robotaxis, Git scraping, and designing emulators. These advancements showcase the ongoing development and innovation in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- The business category highlights various topics such as unexpected deliveries, cybercrime treaties, collaborations in the aviation industry, and the impact of traffic cameras. These articles shed light on different aspects of the business world and its challenges.&lt;br&gt;- The AI category explores the progress made in autonomous vehicles and virtual reality technology. It also discusses the potential impact of AI on various industries.&lt;br&gt;- The other category covers a range of topics including creativity, travel tips, community building, meteor showers, and the impact of different Covid variants. These articles provide diverse insights into various aspects of life and current events.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report showcases the latest developments and trends in technology, business, AI, and other areas. It highlights the importance of innovation, collaboration, and adaptability in today's rapidly changing world.</summary></entry></feed>