<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-04T20:02:09Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 04 Sep 2023 20:02:09</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-04T20:02:09Z</published><updated>2023-09-04T20:02:09Z</updated><id>a212359b-7067-45f4-b008-cf27baaf9198</id><summary type="html">Report: Global News Highlights&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Pretendo: A free and open source server replacement for the 3DS and Wii U&lt;br&gt;- This AI Research Presents Lucene Integration for Powerful Vector Search with OpenAI Embeddings&lt;br&gt;- What is Facebook Portal? How to use Meta's Alexa-enabled video-chatting devices and their features&lt;br&gt;- Final Fantasy XVI is getting a PC port and two DLC expansions&lt;br&gt;- Nigerian embedded finance platform Anchor raises $2.4M to expand product offerings&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- The UK's biggest grocery chain is offering body cameras to staff as it seeks to fight the 'scourge on society' of retail crime and abuse to staff&lt;br&gt;- Business guru Scott Galloway touts his Apple and Amazon bets - and trumpets the power of Warren Buffett-style investing&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage Interest Rates Today, September 4, 2023 | Rates Still High Despite Recent Drops&lt;br&gt;- Kaiser Permanente patients are siding with its workers as they vote on whether or not to strike&lt;br&gt;- We opened a restaurant with a no-tipping policy. We have to charge more, but it's been totally worth it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- This AI Research Presents Lucene Integration for Powerful Vector Search with OpenAI Embeddings&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Politics:&lt;br&gt;- Meet Zelenskyy's pick for Ukraine's new defense minister, who's been deeply involved with Russian negotiations and prisoner exchanges&lt;br&gt;- The US is growing increasingly frustrated with Ukraine's tactics. It could put the counteroffensive in jeopardy.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's dad says he's worried the Tesla CEO might be assassinated following a report about his influence on government decisions&lt;br&gt;- Biden heads to Philadelphia for a Labor Day parade and is expected to speak about unions' importance&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The use of body cameras by the UK's biggest grocery chain highlights the growing concern over retail crime and abuse towards staff.&lt;br&gt;- Scott Galloway's endorsement of Apple and Amazon showcases the enduring power of Warren Buffett-style investing.&lt;br&gt;- The US's frustration with Ukraine's tactics could have implications for the ongoing counteroffensive.&lt;br&gt;- The concerns raised about Elon Musk's safety highlight the potential risks associated with his influence on government decisions.&lt;br&gt;- Biden's focus on unions during the Labor Day parade emphasizes the importance of labor rights and collective bargaining.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;This report covers a range of topics including tech, business, AI, and politics. It highlights the use of body cameras to combat retail crime, Scott Galloway's investment recommendations, the US's frustration with Ukraine's tactics, concerns about Elon Musk's safety, and Biden's support for unions. Overall, the report provides insights into current global news trends and their potential implications.</summary></entry></feed>