<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-09T10:14:07Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 09 Aug 2023 10:14:07</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-09T10:14:07Z</published><updated>2023-08-09T10:14:07Z</updated><id>d0f47eb3-6f6f-4807-8b5c-1ec4f190f9c7</id><summary type="html">Dave Portnoy - No translation needed, as it is already in English. Dave Portnoy is a well-known American internet entrepreneur and founder of the sports and pop culture blog, Barstool Sports.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across the Spider-Verse - No translation needed, as it is already in English. "Across the Spider-Verse" is the title of an upcoming animated superhero film.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nick Cannon - No translation needed, as it is already in English. Nick Cannon is an American actor, comedian, and television host.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only Murders in the Building Season 3 - No translation needed, as it is already in English. "Only Murders in the Building" is a television series, and Season 3 refers to the third season of the show.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOP attempt to stymie abortion in Ohio backfires spectacularly - No translation needed, as it is already in English. This refers to a failed attempt by the Republican Party to restrict abortion rights in the state of Ohio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Best deals on Visible phone plans in August 2023: as low as $20 monthly for Verizon-like service - No translation needed, as it is already in English. This is a statement about the affordable phone plans offered by Visible in August 2023.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Testing Intel’s Arc A770 GPU for Deep Learning - No translation needed, as it is already in English. This refers to the testing of Intel's Arc A770 GPU for deep learning purposes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are Implicit Operators a Path to Clean Code or a Buggy Nightmare? - No translation needed, as it is already in English. This is a question about the use of implicit operators in coding and their impact on code quality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reimagining the Bioreactor - No translation needed, as it is already in English. This refers to a project or concept that involves rethinking or redesigning the bioreactor.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meet AnyLoc: The Latest Universal Method For Visual Place Recognition (VPR) - No translation needed, as it is already in English. This introduces a new method called AnyLoc for visual place recognition.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crocodiles are alarmingly attuned to the cries of human infants - No translation needed, as it is already in English. This statement highlights the sensitivity of crocodiles to the cries of human babies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zoom knots itself a legal tangle over use of customer data for training AI models - No translation needed, as it is already in English. This refers to a legal issue faced by Zoom regarding the use of customer data for training artificial intelligence models.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BlueJeans folds - No translation needed, as it is already in English. This statement suggests that the company BlueJeans has closed down or gone out of business.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ai4 2023 Day One Main Stage Recap - No translation needed, as it is already in English. This refers to a recap or summary of the main stage events on the first day of the Ai4 2023 conference.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to get a beautiful Github Profile - No translation needed, as it is already in English. This is a guide or tutorial on how to create an attractive GitHub profile.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Telegram Channel Developer Cheatsheet - No translation needed, as it is already in English. This refers to a cheatsheet or guide for developers who create Telegram channels.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple bank executives increase their holdings, pushing valuations back to reasonable levels - Translation: "多家银行股东高管出手增持，推动估值合理回归." This statement suggests that several bank executives have increased their holdings, leading to a return to reasonable valuations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;US media: TikTok's US e-commerce general manager to resign, two retail veterans from Amazon and Meta join - Translation: "美媒：TikTok美国电商总经理将离职，两位来自亚马逊、Meta的零售老兵加入." This statement reports that the general manager of TikTok's US e-commerce division is resigning, and two retail veterans from Amazon and Meta are joining the company.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After helping Shein gain millions of users, full outsourcing only looks good on the surface | Hard Core Analysis - Translation: "帮Shein增长百万用户后，全托管只是看上去很美｜硬氪分析." This statement suggests that after assisting Shein in acquiring millions of users, full outsourcing may not be as beneficial as it appears.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech100 | Harbin Institute of Technology Shenzhen team enters the multimodal large model field, self-developed "若愚-九天" tops the OpenCompass list - Translation: "Tech100 | 哈工大深圳团队入局多模态大模型，自研「若愚-九天」荣登OpenCompass榜首." This statement highlights the entry of the Harbin Institute of Technology Shenzhen team into the field of multimodal large models, with their self-developed "若愚-九天" ranking first on the OpenCompass list.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Banks' wealth management portfolio undergoes a significant reallocation of 25 trillion yuan: cash deposits increase sharply, bond assets gradually lose favor - Translation: "25万亿元银行理财大调仓：现金存款占比猛增，债券资产渐“失宠." This statement indicates that banks' wealth management portfolios have undergone a significant reallocation, with a sharp increase in cash deposits and a gradual decline in bond assets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Foreign media: Google and Universal Music Group are negotiating the use of AI-generated melodies and sounds by authorized artists - Translation: "外媒：谷歌和环球音乐公司正就授权艺术家使用人工智能生成的旋律及声音进行谈判." This statement reports that Google and Universal Music Group are in negotiations regarding the authorization of artists to use AI-generated melodies and sounds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former CFO sells 3,750 shares of Tesla stock - Translation: "前CFO出售特斯拉3750股股票." This statement states that a former CFO has sold 3,750 shares of Tesla stock.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CITIC Securities: Exports expected to maintain a slight positive growth this year - Translation: "中信证券：今年出口有望保持微幅正增长." This statement suggests that exports are expected to maintain a slight positive growth this year, according to CITIC Securities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Margin financing balance in the two markets decreased by 54 million yuan - Translation: "两市融资余额减少0.54亿元." This statement indicates that the margin financing balance in the two markets has decreased by 54 million yuan.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IATA: Air cargo demand slows down in June - Translation: "国际航协：6月航空货运需求放缓." This statement reports that air cargo demand slowed down in June, according to the International Air Transport Association (IATA).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early-stage project | iPaaS vendor "数环通" launches enterprise AGI product "LinkBot," combining AI with iPaaS - Translation: "早期项目 | iPaaS厂商「数环通」推出企业AGI产品「LinkBot」，AI+IPaaS结合时." This statement introduces the launch of an enterprise AGI (Artificial General Intelligence) product called "LinkBot" by iPaaS vendor "数环通," which combines AI with iPaaS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4 listed companies' stocks experience significant reduction by important shareholders, with Nan Tian Information having the highest reduction amount - Translation: "4家上市公司股票遭重要股东减持，南天信息减持金额最高." This statement states that the stocks of four listed companies have experienced significant reductions by important shareholders, with Nan Tian Information having the highest reduction amount.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CITIC Securities: Policy expectations help Hong Kong stock market valuation recovery - Translation: "中信证券：政策预期助力港股估值修复." This statement suggests that policy expectations are helping the valuation recovery of the Hong Kong stock market, according to CITIC Securities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple policy tools provide support, infrastructure construction has strong momentum - Translation: "多种政策工具托底，基础设施建设后劲足." This statement highlights the support provided by multiple policy tools and the strong momentum of infrastructure construction.</summary></entry></feed>