<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-23T08:03:15Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 23 Aug 2023 08:03:15</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-23T08:03:15Z</published><updated>2023-08-23T08:03:15Z</updated><id>43c985c3-28ae-4087-b2aa-387ea8541f06</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- How to Write Software with Zero bugs – 25 years after qmail 1.0 – D. Bernstein [pdf]&lt;br&gt;- Autenticação e Autorização de uma ASP .NET Web API com Keycloak&lt;br&gt;- Scientists Say New Device Can Scrub 99.9 Percent of Microplastics From Water&lt;br&gt;- ‘Rebel Moon’ Looks Way Better Than Modern ‘Star Wars’ And Yet I’m Filled With Doubt&lt;br&gt;- From C-Suite To Loading Dock, The Impact Of Artificial Intelligence Will Be Evenly Distributed&lt;br&gt;- ‘Delta Force: Hawk Ops’ Is A First-Person Shooter With An Identity Crisis&lt;br&gt;- Correction for Buyalskaya et al., What can machine learning teach us about habit formation? Evidence from exercise and hygiene&lt;br&gt;- A human monoclonal antibody combination rescues nonhuman primates from advanced disease caused by the major lineages of Lassa virus&lt;br&gt;- Reconstitution of phytochrome A-mediated light modulation of the ABA signaling pathways in yeast&lt;br&gt;- The apicoplast is important for the viability and persistence of Toxoplasma gondii bradyzoites&lt;br&gt;- A green edge-hosted zinc single-site heterogeneous catalyst for superior Fenton-like activity&lt;br&gt;- Orange/far-red hybrid voltage indicators with reduced phototoxicity enable reliable long-term imaging in neurons and cardiomyocytes&lt;br&gt;- Synaptic and cellular endocannabinoid signaling mechanisms regulate stress-induced plasticity of nucleus accumbens somatostatin neurons&lt;br&gt;- Phosphorylation of RhoGDI1, a Rho GDP dissociation inhibitor, regulates root hair development in Arabidopsis under salt stress&lt;br&gt;- CD44 acts as a coreceptor for cell-specific enhancement of signaling and regulatory T cell induction by TGM1, a parasite TGF-β mimic&lt;br&gt;- The mRNA stability factor Khd4 defines a specific mRNA regulon for membrane trafficking in the pathogen Ustilago maydis&lt;br&gt;- Roles for diacylglycerol in synaptic vesicle priming and release revealed by complete reconstitution of core protein machinery&lt;br&gt;- Remembering the Improbable Life of Ed Fredkin (1934–2023) and His World of Ideas and Stories&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Florida Democrats just landed one of their top recruits to take on Rick Scott, but it still might not be enough to win&lt;br&gt;- Ayala Coffee: New Jersey's Philippine Specialty Coffee Shop by Matt and Trixie&lt;br&gt;- Mass Layoffs Continue Across The Biotech Sector. What Does This Mean For Pharma’s Future?&lt;br&gt;- The UPS contract with a $21-an-hour minimum wage is now official&lt;br&gt;- A growing urban-farming movement has transformed dozens of vacant lots in Philadelphia. Now with city backing, some crucial green spaces can flourish without the threat of development.&lt;br&gt;- Highest bank account bonus today: Earn up to a $3,000 bonus to open a bank account&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- From C-Suite To Loading Dock, The Impact Of Artificial Intelligence Will Be Evenly Distributed&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk was reportedly working on his AI company while publicly calling for a pause on AI development&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Covid is here to stay—as a risk factor in regulatory filings&lt;br&gt;- Videos of an artillery ambush show Russian tanks and armor making 'opening day mistakes' and paying the price for them&lt;br&gt;- Prime Video lets you stream popular movies and original shows &amp;mdash; here's how to sign up with or without Amazon Prime&lt;br&gt;- Save $150 with a Sony PS5 and 4K TV bundle &amp;mdash; here's how to grab the limited-time deal&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section covers a range of topics including software development, water pollution, artificial intelligence, and gaming. It highlights advancements in technology and their potential impact.&lt;br&gt;- The business section focuses on political recruitment, coffee shop business, layoffs in the biotech sector, minimum wage contracts, and urban farming. It discusses the challenges and opportunities in various industries.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section explores the impact of artificial intelligence on different sectors and the actions of prominent figures in the field.&lt;br&gt;- The other section includes topics such as Covid-19's influence on regulatory filings, military incidents, streaming services, and deals. It provides a mix of news and consumer-related information.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report showcases the diverse range of topics and insights gathered from different areas, highlighting the intersection of technology, business, and current events.</summary></entry></feed>