<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-05T08:03:42Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 05 Dec 2023 08:03:42</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-05T08:03:42Z</published><updated>2023-12-05T08:03:42Z</updated><id>31484401-71fb-42a9-b32e-ba99e04b3d3c</id><summary type="html">In the world, there have been various developments and events. John Wiley has published a prediction and analysis of quality markers for Chuantieling gel, as well as the development of an effervescence-assisted dispersive liquid phase. In the obituary section, Rebecca Ellard's passing is mourned at Young's Funeral Home in Jonesville, while Daphene Tyler's obituary is listed at O.W. Wiley Mortuary in Houston. NVIDIA ACE has introduced the ability to create lifelike avatars with AI animation and speech features. Panagora Asset Management Inc. has sold a significant number of shares in Cummins, as reported by MarketBeat. Additionally, there is a discussion among governors about President Biden's involvement in infrastructure law projects. Apple has allowed reporters to film inside its secretive chip-testing lab for the first time. In politics, John Fetterman paid George Santos for a Cameo to troll Bob Mendendez. OpenAI's ChatGPT will no longer comply if asked to repeat a word 'forever' due to recent revelations of training data and personal information. The influences of Godzilla Minus One are explored beyond the atom bomb. OpenSSL 3.2 has brought support for QUIC, Windows Certificate Store, and more. OpenAI has delayed its chatbot store following the Sam Altman drama. A discussion on clean code and good practices with JavaScript is taking place. There is also a question about sending data to websites. In New York City, lawmakers are considering cracking down on illegal mufflers and exhaust systems with the use of noise cameras. The Walking Dead Universe RPG has been released, bringing the zombie franchise to life. The U.K. has been urged to act as patients die waiting for care, which is described as heartbreaking. Government ethics lawyers provide insights on gifts that are better not to give. UCLA Football sees a star lineman announcing his entrance into the transfer portal. LGBTQ+ cancer survivors are found to be at a higher risk of chronic health conditions. Wiley College has rebranded as Wiley University during their homecoming. Subway locations will no longer be allowed to reject digital coupons or avoid footlong sandwich deals. Student-loan borrowers may qualify for up to $20,000 in debt cancellation through Biden's relief efforts. Researchers have photographed giant guinea pig-sized rats that climb trees and chomp coconuts for the first time. A researcher suggests that Russia's economy faces obstacles to further growth. The US Navy has had to gun down more threats as American forces become more involved in conflicts fueled by Israel's war with Hamas. An OpenAI executive discusses the most overhyped and underhyped aspects of AI. Lastly, a bride who went viral for planning a purported $59 million wedding has shut down her social media due to her husband's criminal charges coming to light.</summary></entry></feed>