<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-13T18:01:12Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 13 Aug 2023 18:01:12</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-13T18:01:12Z</published><updated>2023-08-13T18:01:12Z</updated><id>f355f327-a597-4308-bf66-ee346a3ab033</id><summary type="html">Report: Multilingual Insights on Various Topics&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Tech:&lt;br&gt;- A feud has emerged between Arizona workers and a leading chipmaker over the company's claim that the US lacks the skills to build its new factory.&lt;br&gt;- Salesforce researchers have introduced XGen-Image-1, a text-to-image latent diffusion model trained to reuse pretrained components.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from USC and Microsoft propose UniversalNER, a new AI model trained with targeted distillation that outperforms ChatGPT's NER accuracy by 9% F1 on 43 datasets.&lt;br&gt;- NixOS RFC 136 has been approved, outlining a plan to stabilize the new CLI and Flakes incrementally.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: The tech industry is witnessing conflicts, advancements in AI models, and efforts to improve stability in software development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Business:&lt;br&gt;- Mark Spitznagel warns of an impending pop of the "greatest credit bubble in human history."&lt;br&gt;- Meticulous, a YC S21 startup, is hiring an engineer to build AI for testing.&lt;br&gt;- Dear SaaStr addresses the question of how long SDR/BDRs have if they fail to meet their quotas.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: Business experts are concerned about a potential economic bubble, while startups focus on AI-driven testing and sales performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. AI:&lt;br&gt;- Meta AI introduces PUG, an AI research project on photorealistic, semantically controllable datasets using Unreal Engine for robust model evaluation.&lt;br&gt;- Generative AI provides a curated list of generative AI projects and services.&lt;br&gt;- Doctor GPT is a large language model capable of passing the US Medical Licensing Exam.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: AI research is exploring new techniques for dataset creation, generative models, and applications in the medical field.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Science:&lt;br&gt;- Crocodiles were exposed to the sound of crying human babies, with their response varying based on the infants' distress levels.&lt;br&gt;- Weeds may play a more significant role in supporting pollinating insects than previously assumed.&lt;br&gt;- AI can assist in predicting air quality but struggles to account for wildfires.&lt;br&gt;- ML is not reliable for predicting scientific replicability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: Scientific studies delve into animal behavior, environmental impact, and the limitations of AI and ML in scientific research.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;This report highlights insights from various topics, including tech, business, AI, and science. The tech industry faces conflicts and advancements in AI models, while concerns about an economic bubble arise. AI research explores novel dataset creation, generative models, and medical applications. Scientific studies shed light on animal behavior, environmental impact, and the limitations of AI and ML in scientific research. Overall, these insights provide a comprehensive overview of current trends and challenges in these fields.</summary></entry></feed>