<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-10T12:01:08Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 10 Aug 2023 12:01:08</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-10T12:01:08Z</published><updated>2023-08-10T12:01:08Z</updated><id>a0afe2e0-25ac-49d3-bb57-2500626eb1f3</id><summary type="html">Report: Multilingual Insights&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Stability AI releases new Japanese language model, Japanese StableLM, marking entry into international language model market.&lt;br&gt;- UChicago scientists see first evidence of 'quantum superchemistry' in the lab.&lt;br&gt;Insight: The development of new language models and advancements in quantum computing have significant implications for the future of technology and scientific research.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- China's attendance at Saudi peace talks is 'bad news' for Putin, but Xi Jinping is still 'well served' by his friendship with Russia, expert says.&lt;br&gt;- Disney's Hotstar loses 12.5 million subscribers in a quarter amid cricket shortfall.&lt;br&gt;- Seattle becomes the first in the U.S. to protect gig workers from sudden 'deactivation'.&lt;br&gt;Insight: The geopolitical dynamics between China, Russia, and Saudi Arabia have implications for global business and political relationships. The impact of sports events on streaming platforms can significantly affect their subscriber base. The protection of gig workers reflects a growing trend towards labor rights and regulation in the gig economy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Tool predicts a patient's risk of developing psoriatic arthritis.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers identify protein that may help protect against osteoporosis.&lt;br&gt;Insight: The integration of AI in healthcare can improve disease prediction and prevention. Identifying proteins that have protective effects can lead to advancements in treating and preventing diseases.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Depression and anxiety won't raise your risk of cancer, study finds.&lt;br&gt;- If you want to find affordable housing, you might want to try Minneapolis, where the inflation rate is surprisingly low.&lt;br&gt;- Embarking on a Cloud Adventure: Unveiling the Magic of Cloud Computing.&lt;br&gt;- A Roadmap To Health Equity: Addressing The Conditions Of Our Environment That Affect Our Health.&lt;br&gt;- Common Alzheimer's disease gene may have helped our ancestors have more kids.&lt;br&gt;Insight: Mental health conditions do not directly increase the risk of cancer. Affordable housing and low inflation rates in certain cities can provide opportunities for individuals and families. Cloud computing offers transformative possibilities for businesses. Addressing environmental conditions is crucial for achieving health equity. Genetic factors play a role in human evolution and reproductive success.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Advancements in language models and quantum computing have significant implications for technology and scientific research.&lt;br&gt;- Geopolitical dynamics between countries impact global business and political relationships.&lt;br&gt;- AI in healthcare can improve disease prediction and prevention.&lt;br&gt;- Mental health conditions do not directly increase the risk of cancer.&lt;br&gt;- Affordable housing, cloud computing, and addressing environmental conditions are important factors in various aspects of society.&lt;br&gt;- Genetic factors play a role in human evolution and reproductive success.</summary></entry></feed>