<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-05T08:03:34Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 05 Sep 2023 08:03:34</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-05T08:03:34Z</published><updated>2023-09-05T08:03:34Z</updated><id>77e88c7f-ec87-4ea8-96f1-a530cce28013</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Apple and Microsoft are reportedly seeking to have iMessage and Bing removed from the EU's tech 'gatekeeper' list.&lt;br&gt;- Amazon is facing legal battles with landlords over its 'zombie' Amazon Fresh stores.&lt;br&gt;- Aviator, a startup from Y Combinator's summer 2021 batch, is hiring a senior engineer to work on their open-source application platform for Kubernetes.&lt;br&gt;- Wine 8.15 (Dev) allows users to run Windows applications on Linux, BSD, Solaris, and macOS.&lt;br&gt;- Spectrolite is a Mac app designed to make the process of creating colorful risograph prints and zines easier.&lt;br&gt;- Google is expanding its Duet AI in Google Cloud to enhance app development and DevOps.&lt;br&gt;- The Epic Games Store is accepting AI-generated content in games, challenging Valve's caution.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech industry is constantly evolving, with companies like Apple, Microsoft, and Amazon facing legal challenges and seeking new opportunities. Startups like Aviator are also making strides in open-source application platforms, while tools like Wine and Spectrolite aim to improve user experiences. Google and Epic Games are expanding their AI capabilities to enhance various aspects of their services.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Reynolds has appointed Wiley as a district judge.&lt;br&gt;- Biden criticized Trump's tenure in a Labor Day speech, highlighting his lack of accomplishments.&lt;br&gt;- Zionsville's Boy Scout Troop 358 celebrates its 100th year.&lt;br&gt;- John Wiley &amp; Sons, Inc. has seen an increase in stock position.&lt;br&gt;- Hero MotoCorp plans to increase its stake in Ather with a $66.5 million investment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business landscape involves various appointments, celebrations, and investments. Reynolds appointing Wiley as a district judge and Hero MotoCorp increasing its stake in Ather demonstrate strategic decisions being made. Biden's criticism of Trump's tenure highlights the political landscape's influence on business. The stock position of John Wiley &amp; Sons, Inc. indicates investor confidence, while the celebration of Zionsville's Boy Scout Troop 358 showcases community milestones.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from South Korea propose VITS2, a breakthrough in single-stage text-to-speech models.&lt;br&gt;- Signal's president doubts Elon Musk's ability to turn Twitter into a 'super app' like WeChat.&lt;br&gt;- Unconventional Ventures, a Nordic-based fund, is nearing a €30M fund close to support diverse European teams.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The field of AI continues to advance, with researchers proposing new models like VITS2 for enhanced naturalness and efficiency in text-to-speech. The skepticism surrounding Elon Musk's plans for Twitter highlights the challenges of creating a 'super app.' Unconventional Ventures' fund close showcases the growing support for diverse teams in the AI industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;This report covers various topics in the tech, business, and AI sectors. In the tech industry, companies like Apple, Microsoft, and Amazon face legal battles and seek new opportunities. Startups like Aviator are making strides in open-source application platforms, while tools like Wine and Spectrolite aim to enhance user experiences. Google and Epic Games are expanding their AI capabilities. In the business sector, appointments, celebrations, and investments are taking place, demonstrating strategic decisions and community milestones. The AI field sees breakthroughs in text-to-speech models and discussions about the future of social media platforms. Overall, the report highlights the dynamic nature of these industries and the ongoing advancements and challenges they face.</summary></entry></feed>