<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-21T16:01:06Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 21 Aug 2023 16:01:06</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-21T16:01:06Z</published><updated>2023-08-21T16:01:06Z</updated><id>8d1472fa-d909-4a7b-8473-72891a8df25d</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- How to implement attribute routing in Asp.net MVC?&lt;br&gt;- How can Scala and Kotlin interact to build user-friendly DSLs?&lt;br&gt;- Uncovering GAPS: a 3D experience map to identify and solve consumer problems with XR&lt;br&gt;- A guide for successful client assessments and discoveries&lt;br&gt;- SOLID Principles: How to create a code that is easy to extend and maintain&lt;br&gt;- Authentication sidecar — a new experience in microservice architecture&lt;br&gt;- Build, Deploy, and Host Your Vite App on GitHub Pages with GitHub Actions CI/CD&lt;br&gt;- Threads to launch web version, one of its largest updates yet&lt;br&gt;- Changing its name tanked X's downloads in App Store and Play Store&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Why your team design is slowing your business down - and what to do about it&lt;br&gt;- Here's how government can accelerate their digital journey and empower citizens&lt;br&gt;- How to deal with the five dysfunctions of a team?&lt;br&gt;- How to select a Payment Gateway: Functions of Payment Gateways&lt;br&gt;- Why don’t women ask? Bridging the gender pay gap&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- How can Scala and Kotlin interact to build user-friendly DSLs?&lt;br&gt;- Authentication sidecar — a new experience in microservice architecture&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- The year of 'global boiling' is creating an opportunity for winemakers in Sweden&lt;br&gt;- Russia's so desperate to get its billionaires and their massive wealth back&lt;br&gt;- There's still a Sriracha shortage and third-party vendors are selling the sauce for up to $23 on Amazon&lt;br&gt;- A glitch temporarily wiped out X images and links between 2011 and 2014&lt;br&gt;- Tiger Woods' 'little brother' Justin Thomas sells his $3.5 million 'starter' mansion and it's the ultimate bachelor pad&lt;br&gt;- My talk with Kris Nova about being homeless. See you on the other side, friend&lt;br&gt;- Today’s Wordle #793 Hints, Clues And Answer For Monday, August 21st&lt;br&gt;- Cell therapy repairs cornea damage with patient's stem cells gives trial results&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section focuses on topics such as web development, DSLs, and microservice architecture.&lt;br&gt;- The business section discusses team design, government digitalization, and payment gateways.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section explores the intersection of Scala, Kotlin, and user-friendly DSLs.&lt;br&gt;- The other section covers various topics including global warming's impact on winemaking, wealth redistribution, food shortages, and personal stories.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report highlights the diverse range of topics in the provided content, showcasing the intersection of technology, business, and societal issues.</summary></entry></feed>