<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-23T08:03:43Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 23 Nov 2023 08:03:43</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-23T08:03:43Z</published><updated>2023-11-23T08:03:43Z</updated><id>bedd54ef-b22a-44ec-9556-622ec991da6f</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Apple sells 4 different types of iPads &amp;mdash; here are the latest models you can buy&lt;br&gt;- The best iPads in 2023: Pick the right Apple tablet for you&lt;br&gt;- Hulu offers 6 months of Starz add-on for $0.99 in extended Black Friday deal&lt;br&gt;- PS5 vs. Xbox Series X: The PlayStation 5 edges out the Xbox Series X as the better buy for most gamers&lt;br&gt;- A look inside both the Legion Go and Steam Deck OLED&lt;br&gt;- 5 AI-powered tech gifts that are actually fun — and productive&lt;br&gt;- Web3 backend and smart contract development for Python developers Musical NFTs part 17: Deployment time!&lt;br&gt;- Western Digital Releases 24TB Ultrastar and Gold Hard Drives, 28TB SMR Ramping&lt;br&gt;- For RoR, see in production every method call, parameter and return value&lt;br&gt;- All design and engineering of the original Tesla Roadster is now open source&lt;br&gt;- Launched Playtoob, a simple YouTube companion, because my 5yo daughter loves it&lt;br&gt;- How to Resolve Merge Conflicts Using the Merge Editor Feature on VS Code&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Former ESPN Analyst &amp; 'RHOBH' Husband Marcellus Wiley Accused Of Sexual Assault &amp; Rape While At Columbia In ... - Deadline&lt;br&gt;- Democratic Rep. Nickel wavers on endorsing Biden in 2024 - CNN&lt;br&gt;- Ex-NFL star Marcellus Wiley accused of raping student in 1994 - Marca English&lt;br&gt;- NFL Player, Former ESPN Host Marcellus Wiley Accused of Rape - The Root&lt;br&gt;- A realtor says a $660 apartment listing asking tenants to share a bed proves how 'grim' the affordable housing crisis is&lt;br&gt;- Terry Richardson sexually abused a model after Trump's modeling agency dismissed her concerns about him, lawsuit says&lt;br&gt;- US stocks climb ahead of Thanksgiving as investors weigh lower oil prices and jobless claims&lt;br&gt;- Dean Phillips says he doesn't agree with the Kamala Harris gossip, but felt a need to pass along that lots of people say she 'doesn't have the right disposition' to be president&lt;br&gt;- Poor Charlie's Almanack: The Essential Wit and Wisdom of Charles T. Munger&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- 5 AI-powered tech gifts that are actually fun — and productive&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section provides information on the latest Apple iPads, including their different models and features. It also compares the PS5 and Xbox Series X gaming consoles.&lt;br&gt;- The business section includes news about Marcellus Wiley being accused of sexual assault and rape, as well as discussions on endorsing Biden in 2024 and the affordable housing crisis.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section highlights AI-powered tech gifts that are both enjoyable and useful.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report covers a range of topics in the tech, business, and AI sectors, providing insights into current events and trends.</summary></entry></feed>