<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-02T20:02:11Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 02 Nov 2023 20:02:11</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-02T20:02:11Z</published><updated>2023-11-02T20:02:11Z</updated><id>e89038fa-49ea-4b13-96ae-f1aedef0bf32</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Landis+Gyr Overcomes Supply Chain Challenges to Post Record H1 2023 Revenue&lt;br&gt;- New Facebook Stories API helps creators share directly from third-party desktop or web apps&lt;br&gt;- The GPT Site Assistant: A New Era of AI Integration with WordPress&lt;br&gt;- An Algorithm to Automatically Create and Optimize Robot Designs within Seconds&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Landis+Gyr has managed to overcome supply chain challenges and achieve record revenue in the first half of 2023.&lt;br&gt;- The new Facebook Stories API allows creators to share content directly from third-party desktop or web apps, expanding their reach.&lt;br&gt;- The GPT Site Assistant is a new AI integration with WordPress that aims to enhance website management and user experience.&lt;br&gt;- An algorithm has been developed that can automatically generate and optimize robot designs in a matter of seconds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Landis+Gyr's success in navigating supply chain challenges highlights the importance of adaptability and resilience in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- The introduction of the Facebook Stories API demonstrates the increasing integration of social media platforms with third-party applications.&lt;br&gt;- The GPT Site Assistant showcases the potential of AI in streamlining website management processes and improving user engagement.&lt;br&gt;- The development of an algorithm for rapid robot design optimization showcases the advancements in automation and AI in the field of robotics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon says he suspects the Fed isn't done with interest-rate hikes, just hours after Powell hit pause again&lt;br&gt;- Cigna Reports $1.4 Billion Profit On Health Plan And Evernorth Growth&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Jamie Dimon, CEO of JPMorgan, believes that the Federal Reserve may continue with interest-rate hikes despite the recent pause by Powell.&lt;br&gt;- Cigna has reported a $1.4 billion profit driven by growth in its health plan and Evernorth division.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Jamie Dimon's suspicion regarding further interest-rate hikes suggests ongoing uncertainty in the financial market and potential impacts on businesses and consumers.&lt;br&gt;- Cigna's strong financial performance highlights the growth potential in the healthcare industry, particularly in health plans and related services.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- The building blocks of community participation in local climate ... - Nature.com&lt;br&gt;- The GPT Site Assistant: A New Era of AI Integration with WordPress&lt;br&gt;- An Algorithm to Automatically Create and Optimize Robot Designs within Seconds&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Nature.com explores the building blocks of community participation in addressing local climate issues.&lt;br&gt;- The GPT Site Assistant is an AI integration with WordPress that aims to enhance website management and user experience.&lt;br&gt;- An algorithm has been developed that can automatically generate and optimize robot designs in a matter of seconds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The study on community participation in climate action highlights the importance of collective efforts and engagement in addressing environmental challenges.&lt;br&gt;- The GPT Site Assistant showcases the potential of AI in streamlining website management processes and improving user engagement.&lt;br&gt;- The algorithm for rapid robot design optimization demonstrates the advancements in AI and automation in the field of robotics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry continues to overcome challenges and achieve record revenue, showcasing the importance of adaptability and resilience.&lt;br&gt;- The integration of social media platforms with third-party applications and the advancements in AI highlight the ongoing evolution of technology.&lt;br&gt;- The financial market remains uncertain, with potential impacts on businesses and consumers.&lt;br&gt;- The healthcare industry shows growth potential, particularly in health plans and related services.&lt;br&gt;- Climate action and community participation are crucial in addressing environmental issues.&lt;br&gt;- AI advancements in website management and robotics have the potential to streamline processes and improve user experiences.</summary></entry></feed>