<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-02T20:02:12Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 02 Sep 2023 20:02:12</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-02T20:02:12Z</published><updated>2023-09-02T20:02:12Z</updated><id>a124e858-c6ed-4a08-b347-0527edd61a89</id><summary type="html">Salesforce makes it clear to customers that generative AI is not to blame (Tech):&lt;br&gt;- Salesforce reassures customers that their generative AI technology is not responsible for any negative outcomes or biases in their systems.&lt;br&gt;- The company emphasizes that the responsibility lies with the data and algorithms used, not the AI technology itself.&lt;br&gt;- Salesforce highlights their commitment to ethical AI practices and their ongoing efforts to improve transparency and accountability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: This article highlights the importance of clarifying the role of AI technology in any issues that arise. It emphasizes the need for companies to take responsibility for the data and algorithms they use, rather than blaming the AI itself. This transparency and commitment to ethical practices are crucial in building trust with customers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biblioracle on Potter-mania and reading books for fun - Chicago Tribune (Business):&lt;br&gt;- The article discusses the enduring popularity of the Harry Potter series and the impact it has had on the reading habits of both children and adults.&lt;br&gt;- The author reflects on the joy of reading for pleasure and the importance of finding books that bring enjoyment.&lt;br&gt;- The article also touches on the role of libraries in promoting reading and providing access to books.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: This article highlights the cultural phenomenon of the Harry Potter series and its influence on reading habits. It emphasizes the importance of reading for pleasure and finding books that bring joy. Additionally, it recognizes the role of libraries in fostering a love for reading.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affective Activism and Digital Archiving: Relief Work and Migrant ... - anthrosource.onlinelibrary.wiley.com (AI):&lt;br&gt;- The article explores the intersection of affective activism and digital archiving in the context of relief work and migrant activism.&lt;br&gt;- It discusses how digital platforms and social media have enabled activists to document and share their experiences, creating a digital archive of migrant activism.&lt;br&gt;- The article also examines the emotional labor involved in this type of activism and the potential impact it can have on both activists and the wider public.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: This article sheds light on the use of digital platforms and social media in documenting and sharing migrant activism. It highlights the emotional labor involved in this type of activism and the potential for creating a digital archive of these experiences. This intersection of affective activism and digital archiving has the potential to create greater awareness and understanding of migrant issues.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warren Buffett's toll roads, Elon Musk's bottlenecks, and why both men prize the same kinds of businesses (Business):&lt;br&gt;- The article discusses the similarities in investment strategies between Warren Buffett and Elon Musk.&lt;br&gt;- It highlights their preference for businesses with strong barriers to entry and long-term competitive advantages.&lt;br&gt;- The article also explores the concept of economic moats and how it contributes to the success of these types of businesses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: This article highlights the investment strategies of Warren Buffett and Elon Musk, focusing on their preference for businesses with strong barriers to entry. It emphasizes the importance of long-term competitive advantages and economic moats in building successful businesses. This insight provides valuable lessons for investors and entrepreneurs alike.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former generals weigh in on how much say the US should have in Ukraine's counteroffensive as Kyiv's frustration with critics boils over (Business):&lt;br&gt;- The article features insights from former generals on the level of involvement the US should have in Ukraine's counteroffensive against Russia.&lt;br&gt;- It discusses the frustration of Kyiv with critics who question the effectiveness of their military actions.&lt;br&gt;- The article explores the complexities of the situation and the potential implications of increased US involvement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: This article provides perspectives from former generals on the US's role in Ukraine's counteroffensive. It highlights the tensions and frustrations faced by Kyiv in dealing with critics. The insights from these military experts offer valuable perspectives on the complexities of the situation and the potential consequences of increased US involvement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The report covers a range of topics including tech, business, AI, and others.&lt;br&gt;- It highlights the importance of transparency and accountability in AI technologies.&lt;br&gt;- The report emphasizes the joy of reading for pleasure and the impact of popular book series like Harry Potter.&lt;br&gt;- It explores the intersection of affective activism and digital archiving in the context of migrant activism.&lt;br&gt;- The report discusses the investment strategies of Warren Buffett and Elon Musk, focusing on businesses with strong barriers to entry.&lt;br&gt;- It provides insights from former generals on the US's role in Ukraine's counteroffensive against Russia.</summary></entry></feed>