<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2023-12-16T08:03:36Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 16 Dec 2023 08:03:36</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-16T08:03:36Z</published><updated>2023-12-16T08:03:36Z</updated><id>6940c9ee-40e7-4ecb-a4bb-0d8c20ea0dfd</id><summary type="html">In the world, there have been various developments and events. John Wiley conducted a study on the replacement mechanism of older proteins in the brain, shedding light on our understanding of this process. Concerns were raised about the well-being of Gen Z, prompting a question about their state of mind. The Acer Chromebook Plus 515 received a review highlighting its power but also pointing out limitations due to clunky software. Tragically, Matthew Perry's cause of death was determined to be a result of the acute effects of ketamine and drowning, according to a toxicology report. The best iPhone 15 deals in December were announced, offering a free phone with trade-in offers. In a trial over the Georgia election conspiracy theory, Rudy Giuliani was ordered to pay $148 million in defamation damages. Apple's Family Sharing settlement made individuals eligible for compensation. A genetics group criticized a company for using its data to screen embryos' genomes. NASA faced scrutiny for refusing to disclose information about drug use at SpaceX. Disturbingly, young people in the U.K. have started taking up smoking again after years of decline. Cox faced backlash and deleted an ad pitch boasting about eavesdropping through phones. A study published by John Wiley revealed that airborne siloxanes from hair care products accumulate indoors, posing a risk to air quality. McKinsey identified the top eight priorities for CEOs in the coming year, with AI topping the list. Cats were found to be capable of playing fetch, although their motivations may differ from dogs. A marketing company made headlines by claiming it could listen in on people's whispers using phones and smart speakers to target ads. The housing market experienced a resurgence as sinking mortgage rates led to increased inventory and sales. A court ruled that suspects can refuse to provide phone passcodes to the police. The impact of climate change on coral reefs raised concerns, with the potential for AI to aid in their protection. Quest owners were given the ability to use Word in virtual reality. Balancing boulders along the San Andreas fault suggested that seismic activity may be less severe than previously feared. Apple agreed to pay $25 million to settle a lawsuit related to Family Sharing. Ubiquiti addressed a glitch that exposed private video streams to other customers. Mutative 1.0 was announced as a new era in efficient immutable updates. Mejorando Rendimiento y Escalabilidad released a guide on distributed cache in ASP.NET Core. The power of JavaScript in modern development was emphasized. A Thiel-backed startup's futuristic city project in Bhutan moved forward without their involvement. Various new movies and TV shows were made available for streaming on platforms like Netflix and Amazon Prime Video. Unfortunately, nearly 40% of companies still anticipated layoffs in 2024, dispelling hopes of a soft landing. The auto industry faced challenges as unsold electric vehicles accumulated at dealerships. Lastly, John Wiley published a study on monitoring immune cell migration, highlighting advancements in speed.</summary></entry></feed>