<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-19T00:01:58Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:01:58</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-19T00:01:58Z</published><updated>2023-08-19T00:01:58Z</updated><id>890d07bc-edb1-4522-961c-c69c74c93f81</id><summary type="html">Kentucky Retirement Systems Sells 1188 Shares of Walmart Inc ... - MarketBeat&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Kentucky Retirement Systems has sold 1188 shares of Walmart Inc.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This transaction indicates that Kentucky Retirement Systems is adjusting its investment portfolio and divesting from Walmart Inc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to connect your MacBook or Windows laptop to a TV&lt;br&gt;- Category: Tech&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The article provides a guide on how to connect a MacBook or Windows laptop to a TV.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This information is useful for individuals who want to enhance their viewing experience by connecting their laptops to a larger screen.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix's DVD service is going out with a bang and mailing customers one last mystery shipment of 10 movies&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Netflix's DVD service is ending and they are sending customers a final mystery shipment of 10 movies.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This move by Netflix signifies the decline of physical media and the company's focus on its streaming platform.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin plunges more than 10% after Elon Musk's SpaceX reportedly sold the cryptocurrency&lt;br&gt;- Category: AI&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Bitcoin's price dropped over 10% following reports that Elon Musk's SpaceX sold the cryptocurrency.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Elon Musk's influence on the cryptocurrency market is evident, as his actions can significantly impact Bitcoin's value.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas electricity prices soar 6,000% as a fresh heat wave is expected to shatter records&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Texas electricity prices have surged by 6,000% due to an upcoming heat wave.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This situation highlights the vulnerability of Texas' electricity infrastructure and the challenges it faces during extreme weather conditions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The $1 trillion of high yield debt that's piled up in the last 5 years is about to have a 'day of reckoning,' Bank of America says&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Bank of America warns that the $1 trillion of high yield debt accumulated in the past 5 years is approaching a critical point.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This indicates potential risks in the corporate debt market and the need for caution among investors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peloton wants to expand beyond at-home fitness with a push into gyms, businesses, and hotels. Here's how it went from a pandemic-era success story to losing money.&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Peloton aims to expand its business beyond at-home fitness and enter gyms, businesses, and hotels.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This shift in strategy suggests that Peloton is seeking new revenue streams and diversifying its offerings to sustain growth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Tommy Tuberville doubles down after blocking hundreds of military promotions: 'I don't care if they promote anybody'&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Senator Tommy Tuberville defends his decision to block hundreds of military promotions.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This controversy highlights the political tensions surrounding military promotions and raises questions about the role of politicians in military affairs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nation's top general says it's an 'overstatement' to say 'the entire military is woke' over a few drag shows on bases&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The nation's top general dismisses claims that the entire military is "woke" due to a few drag shows on bases.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This statement emphasizes the need for nuanced discussions about social issues within the military and challenges the perception of a widespread ideological shift.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney isn't going to let DeSantis walk away from their feud unscathed as the governor desperately tries to reboot his campaign&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Disney is engaging in a feud with Governor DeSantis and is taking actions to counter his campaign reboot efforts.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This conflict highlights the intersection of politics and corporate interests, showcasing the influence and power of major corporations like Disney.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deja Vu: The FBI Proves Again It Can’t Be Trusted with Section 702&lt;br&gt;- Category: Tech&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The article criticizes the FBI's handling of Section 702 and questions its trustworthiness.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This raises concerns about the government's surveillance practices and the potential misuse of surveillance powers by law enforcement agencies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Revealed: WHO aspartame safety panel linked to alleged Coca-Cola front group&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The article uncovers a connection between a World Health Organization (WHO) aspartame safety panel and an alleged Coca-Cola front group.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This revelation raises questions about the independence and integrity of scientific panels and their potential ties to corporate interests.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Show HN: A website for remote workers to find Airbnb's with good Internet&lt;br&gt;- Category: Tech&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The article introduces a website that helps remote workers find Airbnb accommodations with reliable internet connections.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This platform addresses a specific need for remote workers and enhances their ability to work effectively while traveling.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Broadband monopolies push bill that would crush your ability to stand up to them&lt;br&gt;- Category: Tech&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Broadband monopolies are advocating for a bill that would limit consumers' ability to challenge them.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This highlights the ongoing struggle between consumers and broadband providers, emphasizing the need for policies that protect consumer rights and promote competition.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worldcoin ignored initial order to stop iris scans in Kenya, records show&lt;br&gt;- Category: Tech&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Worldcoin disregarded an initial order to cease iris scans in Kenya, as revealed by records.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This raises concerns about privacy and the ethical implications of biometric data collection, particularly in developing countries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Irrigating more U.S. crops by mid-century will be worth it, researchers say&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Researchers argue that increasing irrigation for U.S. crops by mid-century will yield significant benefits.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This highlights the potential trade-offs and considerations involved in agricultural practices, including the need for sustainable water management.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Target is selling the Xbox Series S with a free $70 game right now&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Target is offering the Xbox Series S console with a free $70 game as a promotional deal.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This promotion aims to attract customers and boost sales of the Xbox Series S, providing added value to potential buyers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Withings Body Smart review: a flawed but thoughtful approach to weight&lt;br&gt;- Category: Tech&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The article provides a review of the Withings Body Smart scale, highlighting its strengths and weaknesses.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This review offers insights into the features and performance of the Withings Body Smart scale, helping consumers make informed decisions about their weight management tools.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Checkout.com cuts ties with Binance, which is mulling legal action in response&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Checkout.com terminates its partnership with Binance, and Binance considers legal action in response.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This development reflects the growing scrutiny and regulatory challenges faced by cryptocurrency exchanges, impacting their partnerships and operations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Founders Fund, Index Ventures, Canvas Ventures join TC Disrupt Startup Battlefield judges&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Founders Fund, Index Ventures, and Canvas Ventures join the judging panel for TC Disrupt Startup Battlefield.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This highlights the involvement of prominent venture capital firms in supporting and evaluating startups, showcasing their influence in the startup ecosystem.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bored Ape Investors Are Suing Paris Hilton as the Whole Thing Falls Apart&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Bored Ape investors are filing a lawsuit against Paris Hilton as the project faces challenges.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This incident sheds light on the risks and controversies surrounding non-fungible token (NFT) investments and the potential for legal disputes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Space Views Of Hurricane Hilary Reveal Intense Storm On The Move&lt;br&gt;- Category: AI&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Space views of Hurricane Hilary show a powerful storm in motion.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This demonstrates the use of satellite imagery and AI technology to monitor and analyze weather patterns, aiding in disaster preparedness and response efforts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Brutal Year Of Decline, Games Industry Dealmaking Poised To Bounce Back&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The games industry is expected to rebound in terms of dealmaking after a challenging year.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This indicates optimism and potential growth opportunities in the gaming sector, highlighting the resilience of the industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid-19 Vaccines Can Decrease Severe Disease In Children, According To New CDC Report&lt;br&gt;- Category: AI&lt;br&gt;- Key points: A new CDC report states that Covid-19 vaccines can reduce severe disease in children.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This underscores the importance of vaccination in protecting vulnerable populations, including children, against the impacts of the Covid-19 pandemic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overblown perceptions of 'wokeness' in the military are making it harder to recruit new people, top Pentagon leader says&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: A top Pentagon leader argues that exaggerated perceptions of "wokeness" in the military hinder recruitment efforts.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This highlights the challenges faced by the military in attracting new recruits and the impact of public perception on recruitment strategies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks are approaching a perfect buy-the-dip opportunity as the S&amp;P 500 faces August rout, Fundstrat says&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Fundstrat suggests that stocks are nearing a favorable buy-the-dip opportunity amid a potential August market decline.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This analysis provides insights into market trends and investor sentiment, indicating potential investment opportunities during market downturns.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;America's favorite weight loss drugs are impacting Denmark's currency and interest rates&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The article explores the impact of America's popular weight loss drugs on Denmark's currency and interest rates.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This unexpected connection highlights the interconnectedness of global markets and the potential ripple effects of specific industries on economies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;US stocks fall as Dow heads for worst week since March amid China fears, rising bond yields&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: US stocks decline, with the Dow heading for its worst week since March, driven by concerns over China and rising bond yields.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This reflects the volatility and sensitivity of the stock market to geopolitical events and economic indicators, signaling potential market trends.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;US intel believes Ukraine's counteroffensive will fail to reach Melitopol, one of its key goals: report&lt;br&gt;- Category: Business&lt;br&gt;- Key points: US intelligence suggests that Ukraine's counteroffensive will not achieve one of its key goals, reaching Melitopol.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This report sheds light on the ongoing conflict in Ukraine and the challenges faced by the country in achieving its military objectives.</summary></entry></feed>