<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-19T08:01:04Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 19 Aug 2023 08:01:04</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-19T08:01:04Z</published><updated>2023-08-19T08:01:04Z</updated><id>6f19bc74-2cd7-43cb-8609-7e36bfe126e9</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Xbox's new "8 strikes" mod rollout judges hate speech 3x worse than cheating.&lt;br&gt;   - Xbox has implemented a new moderation system that penalizes hate speech more severely than cheating in games.&lt;br&gt;   - This move aims to create a safer and more inclusive gaming environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Bored Ape Yacht Club creator to block OpenSea in fight over payments.&lt;br&gt;   - The creator of Bored Ape Yacht Club, a popular NFT collection, plans to block OpenSea, a leading NFT marketplace, due to payment disputes.&lt;br&gt;   - This highlights the ongoing challenges and disputes within the NFT space.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Elon Musk claims X users are about to lose an important safety feature—the ability to block trolls.&lt;br&gt;   - Elon Musk, CEO of Tesla, claims that users of a certain product (referred to as "X") will lose the ability to block trolls, which raises concerns about online safety and harassment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Express is laying off 150 workers. Here's the full list of major retailers making cuts, from Gap to Walmart.&lt;br&gt;   - Express, a retail company, is laying off 150 employees, joining a list of major retailers, including Gap and Walmart, that have also made cuts.&lt;br&gt;   - This reflects the challenges faced by the retail industry, particularly during the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Analysis: Health care CEOs hauled in $4B last year as inflation pinched workers.&lt;br&gt;   - Health care CEOs earned a combined $4 billion in compensation last year, while workers faced the impact of inflation.&lt;br&gt;   - This raises questions about income inequality and executive compensation in the health care industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. California Blue Shield Deal Exposes Amazon's And Mark Cuban's Pharmacy Limitations.&lt;br&gt;   - A deal involving California Blue Shield has shed light on the limitations of Amazon and Mark Cuban's involvement in the pharmacy industry.&lt;br&gt;   - This highlights the complexities and challenges faced by tech giants entering the healthcare sector.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. Cisco CEO says AI is already becoming a huge new market after it 'missed' the initial cloud computing boom.&lt;br&gt;   - The CEO of Cisco believes that AI is emerging as a significant market, following the initial boom of cloud computing.&lt;br&gt;   - This indicates the growing importance and potential of AI technologies in various industries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Meta's updated RTO mandate is as strict as Amazon's, with a few unique rules. Here are all the key details.&lt;br&gt;   - Meta (formerly Facebook) has implemented updated rules for its Responsible Technology Organization (RTO), which are comparable to Amazon's guidelines but with some unique aspects.&lt;br&gt;   - This showcases the efforts of tech companies to address ethical concerns and regulate their platforms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. ListenAI: Elevate Your Health Journey with Our Caring AI Chatbot Companion.&lt;br&gt;   - ListenAI offers an AI chatbot companion designed to enhance individuals' health journeys.&lt;br&gt;   - This demonstrates the increasing integration of AI in healthcare and its potential to provide personalized support.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry continues to face challenges related to moderation, online safety, and payment disputes in the NFT space.&lt;br&gt;- The retail industry is experiencing layoffs and cuts, highlighting the impact of the pandemic and changing consumer behavior.&lt;br&gt;- Income inequality and executive compensation are prevalent issues in the healthcare sector.&lt;br&gt;- Tech giants are navigating the complexities of entering the healthcare industry, facing limitations and challenges.&lt;br&gt;- AI is emerging as a significant market, with potential applications in various industries.&lt;br&gt;- Ethical considerations and regulation are becoming increasingly important in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- AI is being integrated into healthcare to provide personalized support and enhance individuals' health journeys.</summary></entry></feed>