<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2023-12-16T20:02:00Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 16 Dec 2023 20:02:00</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-16T20:02:00Z</published><updated>2023-12-16T20:02:00Z</updated><id>cd378442-fd9a-44cf-a3de-ef35f3f3582a</id><summary type="html">In the world news, Russia has taken measures to hide troop movements from Ukrainian drones by adding protective screens to its trenches. Meanwhile, Costco offers a range of unusual items for sale, including bars of 24-karat gold, freeze-dried emergency-survival food, and even caskets. As the holiday season approaches, a foolproof guide has been released on how much to tip during this time. Elon Musk's rival to OpenAI's ChatGPT, called Grok, is being introduced, providing users with a new AI chatbot experience. In other news, Rudy Giuliani has expressed no regrets after a $148 million defamation judgment against him. Female entrepreneurs can find valuable advice from the founders of SoulCycle, Poppi, Halfdays, and more. A UK court has allowed an ANN patent, stating that the exclusion of computer programs does not apply. Apple has announced that 25 hours of Xcode Cloud will now be included with the Apple Developer Program. However, the company has also faced failures in 2023, including issues with AI, iPads, and 8GB of RAM. The passing of Donald Wiley in Champaign, IL has been reported. A Parisian wine bar has banned TikTokers and hired a bouncer to control crowds after becoming an unwilling viral sensation. Elon Musk has started a war with Tesla workers, but it is unlikely that he will come out victorious. TikTok's parent company has been accused of copying OpenAI's homework when developing its AI chatbot. Additionally, researchers at Stanford have unveiled PLATO, a novel AI approach to tackle overfitting in high-dimensional, low-sample machine learning with knowledge graph-augmented regularization. Another AI paper introduces RTMO, a breakthrough in real-time multi-person pose estimation using dual 1-D heatmaps. OpenAI has suspended ByteDance's account after it used GPT to train its own AI model. The battle between Linux and Windows operating systems is explored in an article. The passing of Craig Jones in Houston has been announced. A nostalgic music player from the early 2000s is gaining attention. Researchers have developed a data assimilation method to track excitation-inhibition balance change using scalp EEG. Elon Musk has assured bankers that they won't lose money on the Twitter deal, despite expectations of at least a $2 billion loss. Apple researchers have unveiled DeepPCR, a novel machine learning algorithm that parallelizes typically sequential operations to speed up inference and training of neural networks. A Chinese AI paper introduces UniRepLKNet, pioneering large-kernel ConvNet architectures for enhanced cross-modal performance in image, audio, and time-series data analysis. Quaker Oats has issued a recall of granola bars and cereal due to a salmonella risk. John Wiley &amp; Sons, Inc. has declared a quarterly dividend of $0.35.</summary></entry></feed>