<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-13T08:01:27Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 13 Aug 2023 08:01:27</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-13T08:01:27Z</published><updated>2023-08-13T08:01:27Z</updated><id>50dc49d5-d40f-4a6e-b379-2f152e26267f</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers at UC Santa Cruz propose a novel text-to-image association test tool that quantifies implicit stereotypes between concepts and valence in images.&lt;br&gt;- Create an Emoji Selector for Next.js Forms using Tailwind + DaisyUI.&lt;br&gt;- Unlocking Real-Time Insights: Harnessing Lambda and SES to Supercharge S3 Bucket Alerts.&lt;br&gt;- Freshpaint (YC S19) is hiring engineers to build a HIPAA compliant data platform.&lt;br&gt;- iPhone 14, 14 Pro owners complain about falling battery capacity.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers jailbreak a Tesla, FCC fines robocallers, and WeWork faces trouble again.&lt;br&gt;- Moderation on a popular AI image generator can be easily circumvented to create conspiracy theory-driven images, according to a new report.&lt;br&gt;- 'The most stunning demo I've ever seen in my life': ChatGPT impresses Bill Gates by acing AP Bio exam.&lt;br&gt;- Yes, cold weather affects EV batteries, causing them to drain faster.&lt;br&gt;- Tracing the roots of the 8086 instruction set to the Datapoint 2200 minicomputer.&lt;br&gt;- A core plank of the SaaS economic model is under extreme pressure.&lt;br&gt;- Dissecting the UN Cybercrime Convention's threat to coders' rights at DEFCON.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Georgia Gov. Brian Kemp criticizes Trump for refusing to sign a loyalty pledge and emphasizes the importance of the 2024 race.&lt;br&gt;- James Carville dismisses concerns about Democrats lacking a strong presidential bench for 2028.&lt;br&gt;- The once-mighty Iowa Democratic Party struggles as the GOP dominates the state.&lt;br&gt;- Congressmen call on Biden to stop Greg Abbott from transporting migrants to Democratic-led cities after a child's death on a bus.&lt;br&gt;- An Uber Eats rider and YouTuber boycotts McDonald's due to mistreatment of delivery staff and spills.&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine banks on vintage Soviet rocket launchers to support the counteroffensive against Putin's invasion, according to a report.&lt;br&gt;- Paper investigates police chief prior to raids on his office and home.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers propose ConceptLab, a method to generate new concepts using diffusion prior constraints.&lt;br&gt;- Commercial ships advised to stay away from Iran due to a heightened possibility of attack or seizure.&lt;br&gt;- TikTokers promote castor oil as an eye remedy, but there are problems associated with it.&lt;br&gt;- TikTokers promote castor oil as an eye remedy, but there are problems associated with it.&lt;br&gt;- A psychologist lists 3 ways to end a problematic 'parasocial relationship'.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- In the tech category, there are advancements in text-to-image association testing, real-time insights, and AI image generation. However, there are also concerns about privacy and security.&lt;br&gt;- The business category highlights political dynamics, including loyalty pledges, presidential benches, and party struggles. It also addresses issues related to transportation, worker treatment, and international conflicts.&lt;br&gt;- The AI category explores creative concept generation, geopolitical tensions, and the influence of social media trends. It also addresses potential risks and ethical concerns.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report highlights the intersection of technology, business, and AI, showcasing both advancements and challenges in these areas. It emphasizes the importance of considering ethical implications and the impact on society.</summary></entry></feed>