<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-11T08:03:37Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:03:37</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-11T08:03:37Z</published><updated>2024-01-11T08:03:37Z</updated><id>764bcc85-d3a8-42bd-b177-4a756ff914dd</id><summary type="html">In recent news, it has been announced that The Andersen's Pea Soup in Buellton will be closing its doors after serving customers for an impressive 100 years. This closure marks the end of an era for the beloved restaurant, leaving behind cherished memories for its patrons. In the tech world, there is a new development in the field of data storage as systemd and a Rust allocator introduce permanent memory. This innovation promises to revolutionize the way data is stored and accessed, ensuring long-lasting memory retention. On the financial front, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has approved Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) from Grayscale, BlackRock, and other companies. This decision is expected to pave the way for the trading of Bitcoin ETFs to commence this week, opening up new investment opportunities in the cryptocurrency market. In the travel industry, there is speculation about a potential government crackdown on frequent flyer programs following the blowback received by Delta SkyMiles. The controversy surrounding these programs has raised concerns about their fairness and potential exploitation. In the world of celebrities, lawyers have placed a lien on Kanye West's Malibu home, asserting their claim over the property. This legal action signifies a potential obstacle for anyone interested in purchasing the property, as they would need to address the lawyers' claims first. Lastly, a new technology called Zoe Care has emerged, utilizing existing Wi-Fi signals to detect falls in care homes. This innovative approach aims to enhance the safety and well-being of residents in care facilities by providing an efficient and reliable fall detection system. These recent developments highlight the diverse range of events occurring in the world, from closures and innovations to financial approvals and legal disputes.</summary></entry></feed>