<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-14T20:02:17Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:02:17</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-14T20:02:17Z</published><updated>2023-11-14T20:02:17Z</updated><id>7dd125a6-b38c-4ed9-8534-8d54d1318c00</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Wiley Edge partners with Cisco Networking Academy to train job seekers in tech skills.&lt;br&gt;- Intelligent LC/MS tools for quantitation and characterization of substances.&lt;br&gt;- Chatbots just showed scientists how to make social media less toxic.&lt;br&gt;- Giskard's open-source framework evaluates AI models before they're pushed into production.&lt;br&gt;- A New Research Paper Introduces a Machine-Learning Tool that can Easily Spot when Chemistry Papers are Written Using the Chatbot ChatGPT.&lt;br&gt;- Can Synthetic Clinical Text Generation Revolutionize Clinical NLP Tasks? Meet ClinGen: An AI Model that Involves Clinical Knowledge Extraction and Context-Informed LLM Prompting.&lt;br&gt;- Can Transformer Blocks Be Simplified Without Compromising Efficiency? This AI Paper from ETH Zurich Explores the Balance Between Design Complexity and Performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Meet the typical HENRY: Urban 32-year-olds with no kids who make a six-figure income and have a college degree.&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage Interest Rates Today, November 14, 2023 | Rates Inch up but Remain Below Recent Highs.&lt;br&gt;- Recession will hit the US in 2024 – so get ready for massive interest-rate cuts, UBS says.&lt;br&gt;- Children working as riders for food delivery apps – BBC investigation.&lt;br&gt;- Boeing wins orders worth $52 billion from Emirates at the Dubai Air Show.&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's company slashed its stake in BYD. Here's why that's surprising – and 5 possible explanations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Chatbots just showed scientists how to make social media less toxic.&lt;br&gt;- Giskard's open-source framework evaluates AI models before they're pushed into production.&lt;br&gt;- A New Research Paper Introduces a Machine-Learning Tool that can Easily Spot when Chemistry Papers are Written Using the Chatbot ChatGPT.&lt;br&gt;- Can Synthetic Clinical Text Generation Revolutionize Clinical NLP Tasks? Meet ClinGen: An AI Model that Involves Clinical Knowledge Extraction and Context-Informed LLM Prompting.&lt;br&gt;- Can Transformer Blocks Be Simplified Without Compromising Efficiency? This AI Paper from ETH Zurich Explores the Balance Between Design Complexity and Performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The partnership between Wiley Edge and Cisco Networking Academy highlights the importance of training job seekers in tech skills to meet industry demands.&lt;br&gt;- The use of intelligent LC/MS tools in quantitation and characterization of substances can revolutionize scientific research and analysis.&lt;br&gt;- The DIY approach to getting pregnant through Facebook reflects the changing dynamics of seeking reproductive assistance.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of climate change, as shown in the latest US climate assessment, emphasizes the urgent need for action to mitigate its effects.&lt;br&gt;- The potential recession in 2024 and the predicted interest-rate cuts by UBS indicate potential challenges and opportunities for the economy.&lt;br&gt;- The EU Parliament's decision to protect private messages from being scanned raises questions about privacy and surveillance.&lt;br&gt;- The investigation into children working as riders for food delivery apps sheds light on the exploitation of young workers in the gig economy.&lt;br&gt;- The use of AI-powered language models, such as GPT, has the potential to revolutionize various industries, including healthcare and chemistry research.&lt;br&gt;- The accidental limitation of the Linux kernel to a maximum of 8 cores highlights the importance of thorough testing and development in software engineering.&lt;br&gt;- The adoption of Rust as a programming language for front-end development in 2024 raises discussions about efficiency and codebase rewriting.&lt;br&gt;- Marques Brownlee's success as a tech reviewer on YouTube showcases the influence of online platforms in shaping consumer preferences.&lt;br&gt;- The importance of ethical considerations in designing AI wearables is highlighted to avoid potential negative consequences.&lt;br&gt;- The survey findings on American workers seeking therapy to cope with toxic bosses shed light on the impact of toxic work environments on mental health.&lt;br&gt;- The unexpected reduction in Warren Buffett's company's stake in BYD raises speculation about the reasons behind the decision.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The report highlights various topics in the fields of tech, business, and AI. It emphasizes the importance of training job seekers in tech skills, the potential of intelligent LC/MS tools, the impact of climate change, the challenges and opportunities in the economy, the ethical considerations in AI development, and the influence of online platforms. It also discusses the exploitation of young workers, the potential of AI language models, the limitations in software engineering, and the implications of stake reductions in companies. Overall, the report provides insights into current trends and developments in these areas.</summary></entry></feed>