<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-18T04:01:15Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 18 Aug 2023 04:01:15</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-18T04:01:15Z</published><updated>2023-08-18T04:01:15Z</updated><id>4638f777-80c4-49e4-a9b1-01210a8cce8d</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Top 10 new online resources from McMaster University Library - McMaster Daily News&lt;br&gt;- Highlights the top 10 new online resources available from McMaster University Library.&lt;br&gt;- Provides information on the resources and how they can benefit users.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: The availability of online resources from universities is expanding, providing users with more access to valuable information.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Show HN: Shadeform – Single Platform and API for Provisioning GPUs&lt;br&gt;- Introduces Shadeform, a platform and API for provisioning GPUs.&lt;br&gt;- Explains how Shadeform simplifies the process of accessing and utilizing GPUs.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: Shadeform aims to make GPU provisioning more accessible and user-friendly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. China's economic model is 'washed up on the beach' and it's not going to bounce back, veteran investor says&lt;br&gt;- Discusses the current state of China's economic model and predicts that it will not recover.&lt;br&gt;- Provides insights from a veteran investor on the challenges faced by China's economy.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: The future of China's economic model is uncertain and may require significant changes to bounce back.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Walmart vs Target: When it comes to groceries it's not really a competition&lt;br&gt;- Compares the grocery offerings of Walmart and Target.&lt;br&gt;- Highlights the strengths and weaknesses of each retailer in the grocery sector.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: Walmart has a significant advantage over Target in the grocery market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. Job seekers are scrambling to add new AI skills to their LinkedIn profiles as postings mentioning ChatGPT surge&lt;br&gt;- Discusses the increasing demand for AI skills among job seekers.&lt;br&gt;- Highlights the surge in job postings mentioning ChatGPT, an AI language model.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: The demand for AI skills is rapidly growing, and job seekers are adapting to meet this demand.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. 6 fintech investors sound off on AI, down rounds and what’s ahead&lt;br&gt;- Features insights from six fintech investors on the role of AI in the industry.&lt;br&gt;- Discusses the impact of down rounds and predictions for the future.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: AI is playing a significant role in the fintech industry and is expected to continue shaping its future.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The availability of online resources from universities is expanding, providing users with more access to valuable information.&lt;br&gt;- Shadeform aims to make GPU provisioning more accessible and user-friendly.&lt;br&gt;- The future of China's economic model is uncertain and may require significant changes to bounce back.&lt;br&gt;- Walmart has a significant advantage over Target in the grocery market.&lt;br&gt;- The demand for AI skills is rapidly growing, and job seekers are adapting to meet this demand.&lt;br&gt;- AI is playing a significant role in the fintech industry and is expected to continue shaping its future.</summary></entry></feed>