<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-09T17:44:56Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 09 Aug 2023 17:44:56</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-09T17:44:56Z</published><updated>2023-08-09T17:44:56Z</updated><id>e7197893-2595-48f1-b6ff-c3b0ea6b0a21</id><summary type="html">SEC chairman warns AI could be at the heart of future financial crises&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The chairman of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has issued a warning about the potential risks of artificial intelligence (AI) in the financial industry.&lt;br&gt;- He expressed concerns that AI algorithms could amplify market volatility and contribute to future financial crises.&lt;br&gt;- The SEC is currently working on regulations to address the risks associated with AI in the financial sector.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mega Millions drawing tonight&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- There is a Mega Millions lottery drawing scheduled for tonight.&lt;br&gt;- Participants have a chance to win a large cash prize.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protein Loss Linked to Growth Defects in Mice, Humans - Mirage News&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A study has found a link between protein loss and growth defects in both mice and humans.&lt;br&gt;- The research suggests that protein loss may play a role in stunted growth and developmental abnormalities.&lt;br&gt;- Further studies are needed to understand the underlying mechanisms and potential therapeutic interventions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Student-loan payments and steeper interest rates will pave way for a severe consumer-led recession, top economist David Rosenberg says&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Prominent economist David Rosenberg predicts that the combination of student loan payments and higher interest rates will lead to a severe recession driven by consumer spending.&lt;br&gt;- He warns that the burden of student debt and rising borrowing costs will significantly impact consumer finances and ultimately the overall economy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Zuckerberg, wife Priscilla's relationship timeline, from dating to marriage&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A timeline of the relationship between Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg and his wife Priscilla is provided.&lt;br&gt;- It highlights key milestones from their dating years to their marriage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quote Post Maker&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- There is a tool called Quote Post Maker that allows users to create visually appealing quote posts.&lt;br&gt;- This tool can be used to enhance social media posts or other forms of content.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lofi &amp; Jazz Hip Hop Producing Handbook&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The Lofi &amp; Jazz Hip Hop Producing Handbook is a resource for music producers interested in creating lofi and jazz-inspired hip hop beats.&lt;br&gt;- It provides tips, techniques, and insights into the production process.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minimalist eCommerce&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The concept of minimalist eCommerce is discussed.&lt;br&gt;- It refers to a streamlined and simplified approach to online retail, focusing on essential elements and removing unnecessary clutter.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Review My Design&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A request is made for a design review.&lt;br&gt;- The specific design or project is not specified, but the person is seeking feedback and critique.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Backendless&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Backendless is mentioned, but no further information is provided about its context or purpose.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reflecting on My Failure to Build a Billion-Dollar Company (2019)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The author reflects on their failure to build a billion-dollar company in 2019.&lt;br&gt;- They share their insights and lessons learned from the experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon has more than half of all Arm server CPUs in the world&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Amazon is reported to have the majority share of Arm server CPUs globally.&lt;br&gt;- This indicates their dominance in the market for these types of processors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Llama from Scratch (or how to implement a paper without crying)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The content discusses the process of implementing a research paper from scratch, using the example of a paper about llamas.&lt;br&gt;- It emphasizes the challenges and frustrations that may arise during the implementation process.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preserving endangered species' genes for the future: National Institute for Environmental Studies seeks funding for "time capsule"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The National Institute for Environmental Studies is seeking funding through crowdfunding for a "time capsule" project.&lt;br&gt;- The project aims to preserve the genes of endangered species for future generations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Completing tedious operations in one sentence: 8 Windows command-line tools you can try&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The content highlights eight Windows command-line tools that can simplify and streamline various operations.&lt;br&gt;- It suggests using these tools to accomplish tasks more efficiently.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAS AI BECOME TOO HUMAN? Researchers At Google AI Find LLMs Can Now Use ML Models And APIs With Just Tool Documentation!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Researchers at Google AI have discovered that large language models (LLMs) can now utilize machine learning models and APIs with just tool documentation.&lt;br&gt;- This suggests that AI has become more human-like in its ability to understand and utilize tools.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pretiosum Ventures hits first close on its second fund to back infrastructure startups&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Pretiosum Ventures has achieved its first close on its second fund, which aims to support infrastructure startups.&lt;br&gt;- The fund will provide financial backing and resources to help these startups grow and succeed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to get more suggestions from GitHub Copilot&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The content provides tips and strategies for obtaining more suggestions from GitHub Copilot, an AI-powered coding assistant.&lt;br&gt;- It suggests techniques such as providing more context and using specific prompts to improve the quality and relevance of suggestions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cloud Providers Showdown: AWS vs. Azure vs. Google Cloud&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A comparison is made between the top cloud providers, Amazon Web Services (AWS), Microsoft Azure, and Google Cloud.&lt;br&gt;- The content discusses their respective features, capabilities, and strengths, helping readers make informed decisions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weekly web development resources #161&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A compilation of web development resources is provided, specifically for the 161st week.&lt;br&gt;- It includes articles, tutorials, tools, and other useful content for web developers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Introduction to CSS: Customizing with index.css and Classes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The content serves as an introduction to CSS, focusing on customizing web pages using index.css and classes.&lt;br&gt;- It provides basic information and examples to help beginners understand and apply CSS styling.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone was wrong about antipsychotics&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The content challenges the conventional understanding and use of antipsychotic medications.&lt;br&gt;- It suggests that the prevailing beliefs about their effectiveness and safety may be incorrect.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;People-centered startups: making employees happy is a key ingredient to success&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The content highlights the importance of prioritizing employee happiness in startups.&lt;br&gt;- It argues that creating a people-centered culture is a crucial factor in achieving success.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kangmei Pharmaceutical: Company operations are normal, rumors of "two-month company vacation" are false&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Kangmei Pharmaceutical reassures that its operations are normal and dismisses rumors of a "two-month company vacation" as false.&lt;br&gt;- The company aims to clarify any misinformation and maintain transparency.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tianli Lithium Energy: Signs strategic cooperation framework agreement with Penghui Energy&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tianli Lithium Energy has signed a strategic cooperation framework agreement with Penghui Energy.&lt;br&gt;- The agreement outlines their collaboration in the lithium energy sector.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian Broadcasting Corporation withdraws from X, citing increasing prevalence of "harmful interactions" on the platform&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The Australian Broadcasting Corporation has decided to withdraw from X, citing the growing prevalence of "harmful interactions" on the platform.&lt;br&gt;- The decision reflects concerns about the negative impact of such interactions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another UK property developer announces layoffs due to high interest rates suppressing new home demand&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Another property developer in the UK has announced layoffs, attributing them to the impact of high interest rates on new home demand.&lt;br&gt;- The company is facing challenges in the housing market due to the financial constraints imposed by higher borrowing costs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;China Unicom: Net profit of 5.44 billion yuan in the first half of the year, a year-on-year increase of 13.7%&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- China Unicom reports a net profit of 5.44 billion yuan in the first half of the year, representing a 13.7% year-on-year increase.&lt;br&gt;- The company's financial performance indicates growth and positive momentum.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street financial institutions collectively fined over $2.5 billion for using unofficial communication software for business purposes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Wall Street financial institutions have been collectively fined over $2.5 billion for using unofficial communication software for business purposes.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the regulatory scrutiny and penalties imposed on firms for non-compliance with official communication channels.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hang Seng Index rises 0.32%, Hang Seng Tech Index falls 0.01%&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The Hang Seng Index has increased by 0.32%, while the Hang Seng Tech Index has fallen by 0.01%.&lt;br&gt;- The performance of these indices reflects the overall market trends and investor sentiment.</summary></entry></feed>