<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-25T20:02:34Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 25 Aug 2023 20:02:34</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-25T20:02:34Z</published><updated>2023-08-25T20:02:34Z</updated><id>72780132-3c22-4fe5-9908-599b18935da5</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Explore the Dragon Realm: Build a C++ adventure game with a little help from AI&lt;br&gt;- Deci Introduces DeciCoder: An Open-Source 1B-Parameter Large Language Model For Code Generation&lt;br&gt;- Stephen King doesn't mind his work being used to train AI systems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech section of the report highlights the advancements in AI and its applications in the gaming industry. It also showcases the development of open-source language models for code generation. Additionally, it mentions the acceptance of renowned author Stephen King towards the use of his work in training AI systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- 7481 Shares in John Wiley &amp; Sons, Inc. (NYSE:WLY) Acquired by ... - MarketBeat&lt;br&gt;- As a financial planner, I give my clients 4 tips to make their money last a lifetime&lt;br&gt;- Better.com CEO Who Fired 900 People On Zoom Is Struggling To Keep His Company Afloat&lt;br&gt;- 7 Fast Tracks you need to sign up for during Fast Company’s Innovation Festival&lt;br&gt;- These are the 6 best big cities in the U.S. to launch a startup&lt;br&gt;- Many Of 2021’s IPOs Have Flopped. What Does That Mean For 2023’s Hopefuls?&lt;br&gt;- 'Mind-blowing' US debt binge amid high interest rates is threatening financial stability, Larry McDonald says&lt;br&gt;- Top economist Steve Hanke says stocks look expensive – and a recession is 'right around the corner'&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business section covers various topics such as stock acquisitions, financial planning tips, challenges faced by CEOs, startup opportunities in big cities, IPO performance, and concerns about the US debt binge and stock market. It provides insights into the current state of the business landscape and the potential risks and opportunities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Donald Trump's mugshot post single-handedly shows X is still the place that moves the internet&lt;br&gt;- Routine screening of abnormal vaginal flora during pregnancy ... - Nature.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The AI section includes a mention of Donald Trump's mugshot post, which showcases the influence and impact of social media platforms. It also highlights the use of AI in healthcare for routine screenings, indicating the advancements in AI technology for medical purposes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Billionaire investor Ray Dalio says India's moon landing demonstrates its economic 'ascendance'&lt;br&gt;- Former Treasury Secretary Larry Summers faces backlash from Jim Bianco, Paul Krugman for inflation 'chart crime'&lt;br&gt;- Deloitte's human-sustainability chief wants to help employees beat burnout. She says the best solutions go beyond vacation and office yoga — and involve undoing 100 years of routine.&lt;br&gt;- Russia may 'suddenly break' under pressure from Ukraine's counteroffensive, former US general Petraeus says&lt;br&gt;- Around 10,000 penguin chicks died when the Antarctic ice they lived on melted — they were still too young to survive in the icy water&lt;br&gt;- Meet the Prigozhins: What to know about the Wagner boss and the relatives who help run his business empire&lt;br&gt;- New Video Shows India’s Moon Rover Is Alive—Will It Survive The Night?&lt;br&gt;- How Weather Startups Are Holding Up In A Dryer Funding Climate&lt;br&gt;- What is Portal from Facebook? A guide to Facebook's Alexa-enabled video-chatting devices and their features&lt;br&gt;- HIMARS changed the game in Ukraine, but a former US artillery officer says what they need now is a firepower boost with M26 cluster rockets&lt;br&gt;- Today's Mortgage and Refinance Rates: August 25, 2023 | Are Rates Topping Out?&lt;br&gt;- Video shows the moment a California bear opens the door to a man's home: 'I nearly fell off the couch'&lt;br&gt;- Donald Trump has finally broken his silence on X, posting a picture of his mugshot and a defiant message about never surrendering&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The other section covers a wide range of topics including global economic trends, environmental concerns, technology advancements, geopolitical tensions, and lifestyle incidents. It provides a diverse perspective on various aspects of the world and its current events.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;The report highlights the advancements in AI technology and its applications in various industries. It also sheds light on the challenges faced by businesses, the impact of social media, and the global economic landscape. Additionally, it addresses environmental concerns and lifestyle incidents. Overall, the report provides a comprehensive overview of the current events and trends shaping the world.</summary></entry></feed>