<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-16T20:01:59Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 16 Sep 2023 20:01:59</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-16T20:01:59Z</published><updated>2023-09-16T20:01:59Z</updated><id>efd0fd33-b44a-4ded-8125-a91ed2d2da1a</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- iPhone Charging: The new USB-C port on the iPhone can deliver a significant amount of power.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk: His biographer describes him as a jerk but shares similarities with Jeff Bezos and Bill Gates.&lt;br&gt;- TikTok: Fined $368 million in Europe for failing to protect children's privacy.&lt;br&gt;- F-150: The new F-150 and other cool things were showcased at the Detroit auto show.&lt;br&gt;- Starlink: Falling short of projections on revenue and users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- David's Bridal: CEO discusses the company's future after its second bankruptcy.&lt;br&gt;- Bosses' Challenge: Balancing the needs of rigid 9-to-5ers and employees seeking a flexible schedule.&lt;br&gt;- Student Loans: Some borrowers facing debt and shady payment plans with minimal legal protection.&lt;br&gt;- Dow Chemical: Warren Buffett's investment during the financial crisis helped the manufacturing titan.&lt;br&gt;- Healthcare: An American in Paris shares why they won't return due to the healthcare system.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's Social Cues: He learned from books due to a lack of friends as a child.&lt;br&gt;- Streaming Pirated Movies: People are sharing short clips of pirated movies on TikTok.&lt;br&gt;- Wayve's Lingo-1: Bringing human-like reasoning to self-driving cars.&lt;br&gt;- Outsourcing Wedding Vows: A couple is using AI, like ChatGPT, to write their wedding vows.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Others:&lt;br&gt;- Russia-Ukraine Conflict: UK intel suggests Russia is increasing its cruise missile stockpile to target Ukraine's energy infrastructure.&lt;br&gt;- Hybrid Dog-Fox: The first known hybrid between a dog and a fox was discovered in Brazil.&lt;br&gt;- Sea Drone: An experimental sea drone was allegedly used to damage a Russian missile ship.&lt;br&gt;- Austrian Minister: A former minister who danced with Putin at her wedding reportedly flew to Russia with her ponies on a military plane.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The USB-C port on the iPhone provides a significant power delivery capability.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's personality traits are compared to other tech moguls.&lt;br&gt;- TikTok faces a substantial fine for privacy violations.&lt;br&gt;- The F-150 and other innovations were showcased at the Detroit auto show.&lt;br&gt;- Starlink is not meeting expectations in terms of revenue and user numbers.&lt;br&gt;- David's Bridal plans to move forward after its second bankruptcy.&lt;br&gt;- Balancing the needs of employees with different schedule preferences is a challenge for bosses.&lt;br&gt;- Student loan borrowers are facing debt and questionable payment plans.&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's investment in Dow Chemical was successful.&lt;br&gt;- The American healthcare system is a factor in someone's decision to stay in Paris.&lt;br&gt;- AI is being used for various purposes, including writing wedding vows.&lt;br&gt;- The Russia-Ukraine conflict continues to escalate.&lt;br&gt;- A hybrid dog-fox was discovered in Brazil.&lt;br&gt;- An experimental sea drone allegedly damaged a Russian missile ship.&lt;br&gt;- An Austrian minister's actions with Putin and her transportation of ponies raise questions.</summary></entry></feed>