<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-19T04:01:12Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 19 Aug 2023 04:01:12</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-19T04:01:12Z</published><updated>2023-08-19T04:01:12Z</updated><id>8e9469aa-ce27-4f8d-9ed1-da939f82ee1d</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- LLM comparison: GPT-4, Claude 2 and Llama 2 - which is hallucinating, which is hedging?&lt;br&gt;- Google Pixel Watch vs. Fitbit Sense 2: The Pixel Watch has the smarts but the Sense 2 is the better fitness tracker&lt;br&gt;- Lamborghini’s Lanzador EV concept has over one megawatt of peak power&lt;br&gt;- SpaceX’s new Bandwagon program is a big threat to small launch providers&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft Deletes Bizarre AI-Generated Travel Guide That Recommended Visiting Food Bank With an "Empty Stomach"&lt;br&gt;- Let's Understand and Create Cool Animations with GSAP - GreenSock and Angular&lt;br&gt;- Build Your IDP at Light Speed with a Platform Reference Architecture&lt;br&gt;- The New AI Jobs, Smaller Firms Shaping Remote Work And How United Is Luring Tech Workers&lt;br&gt;- A beginner's guide to YouTube TV, a live TV app with over 100 channels and unlimited DVR&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Here's why the surge in bankruptcy filings this year isn't as scary as it sounds&lt;br&gt;- Jack Dorsey quit Instagram and entered the Musk-Zuckerberg fight, posting on X (formerly Twitter) that he's going 'Meta free'&lt;br&gt;- Hong Kong's benchmark stock index just closed in a bear market as China's economy wavers&lt;br&gt;- A Democratic lawmaker who voted to block Biden's broad student-loan forgiveness doubled down on his opposition and said borrowers can 'pay back their loans just like working class people'&lt;br&gt;- Trump is skipping the first GOP presidential debate for a Tucker Carlson interview: NYT&lt;br&gt;- Wharton professor Jeremy Siegel says the US won't spiral into a new bout of inflation even as economy stays hot&lt;br&gt;- The Week’s 10 Biggest Funding Rounds: Biotech Startup Abcuro Takes Top Spot&lt;br&gt;- Wiley Consumer Protection Download (August 7, 2023) - Dodd ... - Mondaq News Alerts&lt;br&gt;- Robert Kennedy Jr. and his wife Cheryl Hines are worth an estimated $15 million, according to Forbes&lt;br&gt;- Yellowknife wildfires: The Facebook news ban in Canada has been complicating evacuations&lt;br&gt;- Restorative justice can be cheaper and more effective than jail time at preventing reoffences. An innovative Philadelphia program for youth has a 100% success rate.&lt;br&gt;- An AI weapons race may create a world where everyone stays inside out of fear of being 'chased down by swarms of slaughterbots,' warns founding Skype engineer&lt;br&gt;- I'm entering my last year of college. Here's what I wish I knew as an incoming freshman.&lt;br&gt;- Here are all of the Republican elected officials backing Trump's 2024 campaign&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- LLM comparison: GPT-4, Claude 2 and Llama 2 - which is hallucinating, which is hedging?&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft Deletes Bizarre AI-Generated Travel Guide That Recommended Visiting Food Bank With an "Empty Stomach"&lt;br&gt;- The New AI Jobs, Smaller Firms Shaping Remote Work And How United Is Luring Tech Workers&lt;br&gt;- An AI weapons race may create a world where everyone stays inside out of fear of being 'chased down by swarms of slaughterbots,' warns founding Skype engineer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Others:&lt;br&gt;- A 15-year-old medieval girl was buried face down with her ankles possibly tied together to stop her from returning from the dead, researchers say&lt;br&gt;- Police Are Getting DNA Data from People Who Think They Opted Out&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine is closer to having F-16s, but don't expect them to suddenly start 'taking down' Russia's formidable air defenses, top US general says&lt;br&gt;- Graphic video shows orcas hunting and eating dolphins near San Diego. Orca scientist says they just like playing with their food.&lt;br&gt;- A 77-year-old talks to an AI-companion robot called ElliQ over a dozen times daily to combat her loneliness: 'It really is like having somebody else in here'&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The surge in bankruptcy filings may not be as alarming as it seems, as there are factors that mitigate the impact.&lt;br&gt;- Jack Dorsey's involvement in the Musk-Zuckerberg fight highlights the competitive nature of the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- The bear market in Hong Kong's benchmark stock index reflects the uncertainty in China's economy.&lt;br&gt;- The debate over student loan forgiveness continues, with some lawmakers opposing broad forgiveness.&lt;br&gt;- Trump's decision to skip the GOP presidential debate in favor of a Tucker Carlson interview shows his media strategy.&lt;br&gt;- The US economy is expected to avoid spiraling into a new bout of inflation, according to a Wharton professor.&lt;br&gt;- Restorative justice programs, such as the one in Philadelphia, have shown success in preventing reoffenses.&lt;br&gt;- The potential AI weapons race raises concerns about the impact on society and individuals' fear of autonomous weapons.&lt;br&gt;- The use of AI-generated content can lead to controversial and inappropriate recommendations, as seen with Microsoft's travel guide.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of AI on jobs and remote work is shaping the future of work, with smaller firms playing a significant role.&lt;br&gt;- The Facebook news ban in Canada has complicated evacuation efforts during the Yellowknife wildfires.&lt;br&gt;- The use of AI-companion robots, like ElliQ, can help combat loneliness among the elderly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The report covers various topics including tech, business, AI, and others. Key insights include the mitigated impact of bankruptcy filings, the competitive nature of the tech industry, the uncertainty in China's economy, the ongoing debate over student loan forgiveness, and the avoidance of a new bout of inflation in the US. Additionally, the report highlights the success of restorative justice programs, the concerns surrounding an AI weapons race, the potential for controversial AI-generated content, and the impact of AI on jobs and remote work. The report also discusses the complications caused by the Facebook news ban during wildfires and the use of AI-companion robots to combat loneliness.</summary></entry></feed>