<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-16T20:02:07Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 16 Oct 2023 20:02:07</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-16T20:02:07Z</published><updated>2023-10-16T20:02:07Z</updated><id>a5ba9a32-73ab-44e2-b6ad-d1ae7deb1f0a</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's DALL-E 3 generates images in ChatGPT following specific rules.&lt;br&gt;- AI models can now analyze millions of words at a time, thanks to a breakthrough by a Google researcher.&lt;br&gt;- NASA's Psyche mission is testing a space laser for communications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Israel's richest man and his wife stepped down from a Harvard board due to their dissatisfaction with the school's response to the Hamas attacks.&lt;br&gt;- General Catalyst and European early stage fund La Famiglia are partnering to invest in European startups.&lt;br&gt;- A leaked T.J. Maxx document reveals the extreme lengths customers will go to get viral products like Rae Dunn mugs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- The SEC head predicts that AI will cause a financial crash within a decade.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from Princeton and the University of Chicago introduce SWE-bench, an evaluation framework for testing machine learning models on real issues from GitHub.&lt;br&gt;- Can language models replace programmers? This question is explored by researchers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The use of AI in generating images and analyzing large amounts of data continues to advance.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of AI on the economy and financial markets is a growing concern.&lt;br&gt;- The intersection of AI and programming raises questions about the future role of programmers.&lt;br&gt;- The business world is experiencing shifts and challenges, with some leaders expressing dissatisfaction with certain institutions.&lt;br&gt;- Startups and investment in European markets are gaining momentum.&lt;br&gt;- Consumer behavior and demand for viral products can drive extreme actions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report highlights the ongoing developments in AI technology, the potential risks it poses to the economy, and the evolving landscape of business and investment. It also sheds light on the intersection of AI and programming, as well as the impact of consumer behavior on the market.</summary></entry></feed>