<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2023-12-18T20:02:12Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:02:12</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-18T20:02:12Z</published><updated>2023-12-18T20:02:12Z</updated><id>870e0d72-8b17-4c5a-aba6-8e74bcec055c</id><summary type="html">In the world, there have been various events and developments across different sectors. In sports, the Birmingham vs Leicester match is anticipated, with predictions suggesting that the Leicester team will seize the opportunity and both teams will score. In the tech industry, AlgorithmWatch reports that Microsoft is "unable or unwilling" to fix misinformation issues in Bing Chat. On the scientific front, John Wiley announces the upcoming development of Smart 6D Nanoscopy in 2023. In the culinary world, a London restaurant has removed spaghetti carbonara from its menu due to complaints from diners about the lack of cream and requests to add chicken. In international relations, a new deal grants the US military "unimpeded access" to Sweden's bases, including a crucial outpost in northern Europe. In a different context, an escort and stripper catering to Wall Street clients reveals earning $34,000 per week during the holiday season. In politics, the Florida GOP reduces Christian Ziegler's salary to $1 and strips him of power following a rape allegation. Additionally, three women who drive for Uber and Lyft share their strategies for making up to $1,400 a week and receiving customer tips. Deloitte's Kwasi Mitchell discusses the importance of alleviating college students' concerns about the future of work. In the manufacturing sector, the creation of a new high-entropy alloy opens up possibilities for applications such as 3D printing and paste-like inks. The European Union initiates a formal investigation into X under the Digital Services Act (DSA) in the aftermath of the Israel-Hamas conflict. Meltwater, a media monitoring startup, secures a $65 million investment from Verdane. IBM announces its acquisition of StreamSets and WebMethods from Software AG for $2.3 billion. DoorDash shares insights into their privacy engineering efforts, specifically in geomasking and data protection. Troubleshooting tips for fixing errors in RSS feeds are provided. The potential of chemical recycling in achieving a more sustainable future is explored. Twitch reverses its policy on "artistic nudity" after facing backlash. The question of whether generative AI should prioritize caution or boldness in providing personalized mental health advice is raised. A Norwegian battery maker plans to move to the US to take advantage of federal incentives. The concept of sharing office space with an orchestra is introduced as a possibility in the future. Estée Lauder's chief sustainability officer discusses the greening of the beauty industry. The limited accessibility of body camera footage, originally intended for police reform, is highlighted. John Wiley announces the publication of a study on mass spectrometric protein analysis in clinical laboratories in 2023. Wiley Rein, a law firm, recognizes 64 of its attorneys in the 2024 edition of The Best Lawyers in America. A comparison between Alo Yoga and Lululemon is made to determine which brand is superior. An individual shares their decision to quit their job at UCLA due to the requirement of returning to in-person work and expresses reluctance to ever return to an office setting. Elon Musk contemplates taking inspiration from Ferrari's playbook for Tesla's Cybertruck. Readers are invited to share their experiences with using AI, such as ChatGPT, in their professional lives. The best and worst cities for expats are identified. May Mobility successfully achieves full driverless operations while avoiding the challenges faced by robotaxis.</summary></entry></feed>