<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-21T20:01:49Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 21 Jan 2024 20:01:49</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-21T20:01:49Z</published><updated>2024-01-21T20:01:49Z</updated><id>0580d97e-64a4-471f-b8bd-f13876a493f8</id><summary type="html">In recent news, OpenAI has made the decision to ban the Dean Phillips chatbot, while still allowing users to engage in conversations with a chatbot modeled after Donald Trump in OpenAI's GPT store. Meanwhile, a Gen Xer who relocated from Kansas to Phoenix expresses that although he is facing higher housing costs and enduring harsh summers, he finds that there are numerous activities to enjoy in his new city. Additionally, individuals are resorting to cash transfers, such as basic income, to cover their rent expenses, highlighting the urgent need for a solution to the ongoing housing crisis. In a surprising turn of events, a Colorado pastor has been charged with a cryptocurrency scam that he claims was carried out under God's command. The future of China, which is rapidly diminishing, is predicted to have a significant impact on the world for many years to come. Congress is expressing concerns about China potentially surpassing the United States in reaching the moon. Furthermore, there have been discussions about utilizing generative AI as a lie detector, including attempts to expose the popular "Two Truths and a Lie" game through ChatGPT. Africa's wealthiest individual has recently inaugurated a massive $19 billion oil refinery aimed at reducing Nigeria's fuel imports. Lastly, the ocean's landscape is being transformed by the creation of artificial reefs using sunken ships, voting machines, and oil rigs.</summary></entry></feed>