<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-20T00:00:58Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:58</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-20T00:00:58Z</published><updated>2023-08-20T00:00:58Z</updated><id>8e77638b-d44c-4513-a450-15b5f3e74cba</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- MacBooks are better for gaming than expected, comparing them to PC gaming laptops.&lt;br&gt;- Visual Studio 2022 17.7 released with .NET and C++ development features, performance improvements, and more.&lt;br&gt;- Rivet, an open-source game server management platform using Nomad and Rust, is introduced.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from Alibaba propose INSTAG, an open-set fine-grained tagger leveraging modern chatbots' instruction following ability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech section highlights the advancements in gaming capabilities on MacBooks, the release of Visual Studio 2022 with improved features, the introduction of Rivet as a game server management platform, and the proposal of INSTAG for fine-grained tagging. These developments showcase the continuous progress in the tech industry and the integration of AI in chatbot systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Rupert Murdoch urges Virginia Gov. Glenn Youngkin to join the Republican presidential race.&lt;br&gt;- TikTokers criticize the McDonald's clothing collaboration with skate brand Palace.&lt;br&gt;- A Taylor Swift fan expresses embarrassment over paying $5,500 for resale tickets.&lt;br&gt;- The Rolling Stones' success as the highest-grossing act in rock history is discussed.&lt;br&gt;- JPMorgan predicts a potential fall in stocks due to consumers exhausting their excess savings from the pandemic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business section covers a range of topics, including political endorsements, brand collaborations, fan experiences, and market predictions. It highlights the influence of prominent figures like Rupert Murdoch, the impact of consumer sentiment on brand partnerships, and the financial implications of pandemic-related savings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Amazon enhances reviews with AI, while Snap's AI goes rogue.&lt;br&gt;- Development in nano-arrays using deep learning is explored as a new AI method for designing specific structural colors.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers propose INSTAG, an open-set fine-grained tagger leveraging modern chatbots' instruction following ability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The AI section focuses on the application of AI in different domains. It discusses the use of AI in improving review systems, the potential of deep learning in nano-array development, and the integration of AI in chatbot systems. These advancements demonstrate the versatility and potential of AI technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;The report highlights the continuous advancements in technology, with MacBooks proving to be capable gaming devices and the release of Visual Studio 2022 with enhanced features. It also showcases the influence of key figures in the business world, such as Rupert Murdoch, and the impact of consumer behavior on markets. Additionally, the report emphasizes the growing role of AI in various fields, including review systems, nano-array design, and chatbot development. Overall, the insights gathered from the broader topics illustrate the dynamic nature of the tech, business, and AI industries.</summary></entry></feed>