<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-15T20:02:17Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 15 Nov 2023 20:02:17</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-15T20:02:17Z</published><updated>2023-11-15T20:02:17Z</updated><id>3d3b4624-9db3-47ab-b1c8-b682a1b0f09e</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Development and characterisation of highly specific monoclonal antibodies&lt;br&gt;- Surface analysis insight note: An example of a cluster analysis&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Academic Partnerships buys Wiley's online business for $150M&lt;br&gt;- Billionaire hedge fund boss Ken Griffin says remote working makes it easier for companies to fire people&lt;br&gt;- The CEO of Pret was promoted 10 times from store manager to CEO — here are 3 his tips to get the promotion&lt;br&gt;- It's increasingly unlikely Amazon will ever catch up to Walmart in online groceries&lt;br&gt;- JPMorgan boss Jamie Dimon warns it's too early for a Fed victory lap, as inflation 'may not go away that quickly'&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway reveals it sold a bunch of long-held stocks - and made at least one secret bet&lt;br&gt;- How Cleobella scaled from an LA farmer’s market stand to fashion powerhouse&lt;br&gt;- Meet the Seattle punk rocker who wants your boss to take action on the climate&lt;br&gt;- Insurance Executives Refused to Pay for the Cancer Treatment That Could Have Saved Him. This Is How They Did It.&lt;br&gt;- College Volleyball: Wiley ends season in GCAC quarterfinals&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Meet Your Future Co-workers: The Rise of AI Agents in the Office&lt;br&gt;- New megacomputer will perform 2 quintillion operations in a quarter of the time it took you to read this headline&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Black Friday Meta Quest 3 and Oculus Quest 2 deals and bundles 2023&lt;br&gt;- Retailers and delivery apps must act on e-bike safety, NY officials say, after 3 people died in a house fire linked with a scooter battery&lt;br&gt;- Tenants and a top prosecutor have accused major landlords and a popular apartment-pricing site of colluding to inflate rents. A legal expert says it shows algorithmic collusion is no longer 'science fiction.'&lt;br&gt;- Sorry New York and San Francisco, these 4 red-state cities could be the future of America&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage Interest Rates Today, November 15, 2023 | Slowing Inflation is Great News for Mortgage Rates&lt;br&gt;- Gut epithelial barrier damage caused by dishwasher detergents and rinse aids&lt;br&gt;- KubeCon NA 2023: Kubernetes Storage Platform to Run Real-Time Analytic Databases&lt;br&gt;- The Biggest Questions: Is it possible to really understand someone else’s mind?&lt;br&gt;- How managers can use these tools from the ‘Ten Percent Happier’ podcast to become better leaders&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Remote working is seen as a way for companies to easily fire employees.&lt;br&gt;- Amazon is unlikely to surpass Walmart in the online grocery market.&lt;br&gt;- Inflation may not disappear quickly, according to JPMorgan boss Jamie Dimon.&lt;br&gt;- The rise of AI agents in the office is changing the future of work.&lt;br&gt;- Algorithmic collusion is a real concern in the rental market.&lt;br&gt;- The future of America may lie in red-state cities.&lt;br&gt;- The use of AI in the workplace is increasing, leading to potential changes in job roles.&lt;br&gt;- Understanding someone else's mind is a complex and challenging task.&lt;br&gt;- Managers can benefit from using tools from the 'Ten Percent Happier' podcast to improve their leadership skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The report covers a range of topics including tech, business, AI, and others. Key insights include the impact of remote working on employment, the competition between Amazon and Walmart in the online grocery market, the challenges of inflation, the rise of AI agents in the workplace, concerns about algorithmic collusion in the rental market, the potential future of America in red-state cities, the use of AI in various industries, the complexities of understanding others' minds, and the benefits of using tools for leadership development.</summary></entry></feed>