<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-11T18:01:32Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 11 Aug 2023 18:01:32</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-11T18:01:32Z</published><updated>2023-08-11T18:01:32Z</updated><id>a6b822b8-a218-4839-a2b7-d6138c53265e</id><summary type="html">Report: Multilingual Insights on Various Topics&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from ByteDance and CMU Introduce AvatarVerse: A Novel AI Pipeline for Generating High-Quality 3D Avatars Controlled by both Text Descriptions and Pose Guidance.&lt;br&gt;- Meet the new Core Web Vital: Interaction to Next Paint (INP) 🎨.&lt;br&gt;- Meet AgentBench: A Multidimensional Benchmark Which Has Been Developed To Assess Large Language Models-As-Agents In A Variety Of Settings.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from Stanford and Google have made an entire AI village. The 25 bots that live there gossip, work, and plan Valentine's Day parties.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech industry is constantly evolving, with advancements in AI and web development. The introduction of AvatarVerse and AgentBench showcases the progress in generating high-quality avatars and assessing language models. The creation of an AI village demonstrates the potential for AI to mimic human behavior and social interactions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Business:&lt;br&gt;- My company runs on a 4-day workweek. Our days can be intense but revenue has increased and we're never going back.&lt;br&gt;- Saudi Arabia is about to send more oil to China, even though it's slashed crude supply levels.&lt;br&gt;- Chinese online retailer Pinduoduo has a 'hyper-aggressive' culture with hours surpassing a '996' schedule, analysts write.&lt;br&gt;- Overstock’s rebrand as Bed Bath &amp; Beyond may go down as the best in marketing history.&lt;br&gt;- Apple has spent $1.5 billion on affordable housing. Here’s where the money went.&lt;br&gt;- Investors are now eyeing Country Garden chairperson's huge $5.3 billion fortune for help with the struggling property developer's dues.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business landscape is diverse, with companies adopting innovative strategies like the 4-day workweek and successful rebranding efforts. The oil industry continues to adapt to changing market demands, and the aggressive culture in Chinese companies raises concerns about work-life balance. Apple's investment in affordable housing highlights corporate social responsibility, while investors seek solutions for struggling property developers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. AI:&lt;br&gt;- ChatGPT and GPT-4 skew the most liberal &amp;mdash; and Meta's LLaMA is the most conservative AI model, a new study says.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from ByteDance and CMU Introduce AvatarVerse: A Novel AI Pipeline for Generating High-Quality 3D Avatars Controlled by both Text Descriptions and Pose Guidance.&lt;br&gt;- Meet AgentBench: A Multidimensional Benchmark Which Has Been Developed To Assess Large Language Models-As-Agents In A Variety Of Settings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The study on AI models reveals their political biases, with ChatGPT and GPT-4 leaning liberal and Meta's LLaMA being more conservative. The development of AvatarVerse and AgentBench showcases advancements in AI capabilities, particularly in generating high-quality avatars and assessing language models.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Miscellaneous:&lt;br&gt;- The remote work revolution is crashing into a cold reality: Research is finding workers are less productive at home.&lt;br&gt;- The US economy seems to be getting a boost from Hollywood - but Hollywood is missing out.&lt;br&gt;- Jeff Bezos has added a $68 million waterfront mansion on Florida's 'billionaire bunker' to his real-estate collection: report.&lt;br&gt;- Storm snaps up new crime thriller series by Kate Wiley - The Bookseller.&lt;br&gt;- The reason why adults appreciate Van Gogh’s art lies in their infancy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The shift towards remote work has its challenges, with research suggesting decreased productivity. The US economy benefits from the entertainment industry, but Hollywood may be missing out on potential opportunities. Jeff Bezos's real estate acquisitions reflect his wealth, and the release of a new crime thriller series generates excitement. The appreciation of Van Gogh's art is linked to individuals' early experiences and nostalgia.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry continues to push boundaries with advancements in AI, web development, and avatar generation.&lt;br&gt;- Business strategies vary, with companies exploring alternative work schedules, rebranding efforts, and corporate social responsibility.&lt;br&gt;- AI models exhibit political biases, highlighting the need for ethical considerations in their development and deployment.&lt;br&gt;- Miscellaneous topics touch on the challenges of remote work, the impact of the entertainment industry on the economy, and individual preferences in art.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In conclusion, this report provides insights into various topics, showcasing the diversity and advancements in tech, business, AI, and other areas. It highlights the challenges and opportunities faced by different industries and offers valuable perspectives on societal and cultural aspects.</summary></entry></feed>