<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-20T14:01:10Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 20 Aug 2023 14:01:10</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-20T14:01:10Z</published><updated>2023-08-20T14:01:10Z</updated><id>f25e90da-3c11-42e4-9e13-1ba5f6bff9b5</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Zelenskyy begins talks with Sweden about receiving Gripen jets, which some experts think could give Ukraine a better chance at taking on Russia's air defenses.&lt;br&gt;- Large Language Models: Compilers for the 4th Gen of Programming Languages? [pdf]&lt;br&gt;- Grindr has a reputation for its hookup culture, but the company says a quarter of its users are there to network. The CEO says he even hired people through the app.&lt;br&gt;- AMD's 7900 XTX achieves better value for Stable Diffusion than Nvidia RTX 4080&lt;br&gt;- Part 2 - Building a Full Stack Contact Form: Node.js Backend 2023&lt;br&gt;- Part 1 - Full Stack Contact Form: Getting Started &amp; React Frontend 2023&lt;br&gt;- Self-driving car company Cruise agreed to reduce its driverless fleet by 50% after a spate of recent crashes. San Francisco officials previously pushed for a slower rollout of robotaxis.&lt;br&gt;- Mousetrap.jl: a GUI library for Julia and C++ that fully wrap GTK4&lt;br&gt;- Unlocking the Power of Context with Google AI: A Showdown Between prefixLM and causalLM in In-Context Learning&lt;br&gt;- Oil companies are approaching influencers and enlisting PR firms to reach younger generations on social media&lt;br&gt;- Apple devices spoofed, Musk eggs on Zuckerberg and Better.com goes public&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: &lt;br&gt;- Zelenskyy's talks with Sweden regarding Gripen jets highlight Ukraine's efforts to strengthen its air defenses against Russia. This move could potentially shift the power dynamics in the region.&lt;br&gt;- The development of large language models as compilers for the 4th generation of programming languages presents new possibilities for software development and automation.&lt;br&gt;- Grindr's revelation that a quarter of its users are there to network showcases the evolving nature of social networking platforms and their potential for professional connections.&lt;br&gt;- The comparison between AMD's 7900 XTX and Nvidia RTX 4080 highlights the competition in the graphics card market and the pursuit of better performance and value.&lt;br&gt;- The reduction of Cruise's driverless fleet after recent crashes raises concerns about the safety and regulation of autonomous vehicles.&lt;br&gt;- Mousetrap.jl's GUI library for Julia and C++ demonstrates the continuous development of tools and frameworks to enhance programming capabilities.&lt;br&gt;- Google AI's exploration of in-context learning and the comparison between prefixLM and causalLM showcases the advancements in natural language processing and contextual understanding.&lt;br&gt;- The collaboration between oil companies, influencers, and PR firms reflects the industry's adaptation to reach younger audiences through social media marketing.&lt;br&gt;- The spoofing of Apple devices, Musk's interaction with Zuckerberg, and Better.com's public listing highlight notable events in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Zelenskyy says Ukraine is working with Sweden to produce 'cool vehicles' like CV90s: 'Just what is needed at the front'&lt;br&gt;- Grindr has a reputation for its hookup culture, but the company says a quarter of its users are there to network. The CEO says he even hired people through the app.&lt;br&gt;- Self-driving car company Cruise agreed to reduce its driverless fleet by 50% after a spate of recent crashes. San Francisco officials previously pushed for a slower rollout of robotaxis.&lt;br&gt;- Cellebrite asks cops to keep its phone hacking tech ‘hush hush’&lt;br&gt;- Oil companies are approaching influencers and enlisting PR firms to reach younger generations on social media&lt;br&gt;- Apple devices spoofed, Musk eggs on Zuckerberg and Better.com goes public&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Zelenskyy's statement about Ukraine working with Sweden to produce vehicles like CV90s highlights the country's efforts to enhance its military capabilities and strengthen its defense industry.&lt;br&gt;- Grindr's recognition of its users' networking intentions showcases the platform's potential for professional connections and expands its scope beyond its hookup reputation.&lt;br&gt;- Cruise's decision to reduce its driverless fleet after recent crashes raises concerns about the safety and public acceptance of autonomous vehicles.&lt;br&gt;- Cellebrite's request for confidentiality regarding its phone hacking technology suggests the sensitive nature of its services and the potential implications for law enforcement practices.&lt;br&gt;- The collaboration between oil companies, influencers, and PR firms reflects the industry's adaptation to reach younger audiences through social media marketing.&lt;br&gt;- The spoofing of Apple devices, Musk's interaction with Zuckerberg, and Better.com's public listing highlight notable events in the business and technology sectors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Large Language Models: Compilers for the 4th Gen of Programming Languages? [pdf]&lt;br&gt;- Unlocking the Power of Context with Google AI: A Showdown Between prefixLM and causalLM in In-Context Learning&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The exploration of large language models as compilers for the 4th generation of programming languages presents new possibilities for AI-driven software development and automation.&lt;br&gt;- Google AI's research on in-context learning and the comparison between prefixLM and causalLM highlight the advancements in natural language processing and contextual understanding, contributing to the development of more sophisticated AI systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- A national security historian explains why you won’t probably find aliens at Area 51&lt;br&gt;- W. H. Auden’s 1954 review of The Fellowship of the Ring&lt;br&gt;- Sleep ALL NIGHT to Heavy Rain | Black screen, 10 hrs, No ads&lt;br&gt;- Today’s Wordle #792 Hints, Clues And Answer For Sunday, August 20th&lt;br&gt;- The Rimac Nevera Has Broken the Production EV Nurburgring Lap Record&lt;br&gt;- A new way to identify chiral molecules with light could vastly improve detection&lt;br&gt;- How to watch UFC 292: live streams for Sterling vs. O'Malley, Weili vs. Lemos title fights&lt;br&gt;- Stormzy at All Points East review: after a slow start the rapper gave fans a fast and furious thrill ride - Yahoo Canada Sports&lt;br&gt;- Little Rock Nine members slam restrictions on AP African American Studies course in Arkansas&lt;br&gt;- North Korea's new ICBM looks and works an awful lot like a Russian ICBM, experts say&lt;br&gt;- How to watch Messi and Inter Miami vs. Nashville live stream in Leagues Cup final&lt;br&gt;- A judge dismissed a Wisconsin politician's defamation suit against a newspaper, but the legal fees may still shutter the paper.&lt;br&gt;- Stormzy at All Points East review: after a slow start the rapper gave fans a fast and furious thrill ride - Yahoo Eurosport UK&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The explanation by a national security historian regarding the unlikelihood of finding aliens at Area 51 provides insights into the popular culture and speculation surrounding the secretive military facility.&lt;br&gt;- W. H. Auden's review of The Fellowship of the Ring in 1954 offers a historical perspective on the reception and impact of J.R.R. Tolkien's work.&lt;br&gt;- The mention of the Rimac Nevera breaking the production EV Nurburgring lap record highlights advancements in electric vehicle technology and performance.&lt;br&gt;- The development of a new method to identify chiral molecules with light showcases potential advancements in detection techniques with various applications.&lt;br&gt;- The coverage of UFC 292 and the review of Stormzy's performance at All Points East offer insights into the entertainment and sports industries.&lt;br&gt;- The criticism by Little Rock Nine members regarding restrictions on an AP African American Studies course sheds light on ongoing debates about curriculum and education.&lt;br&gt;- The comparison between North Korea's new ICBM and a Russian ICBM raises questions about international relations and potential collaborations or influences.&lt;br&gt;- The coverage of a defamation suit against a newspaper and its potential impact on the publication highlights the challenges faced by media organizations in the face of legal battles.</summary></entry></feed>