<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-12T20:02:16Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 12 Oct 2023 20:02:16</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-12T20:02:16Z</published><updated>2023-10-12T20:02:16Z</updated><id>558cf3d9-c443-4d92-955c-8f0b9919ec19</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway has gained a 93% increase in Nubank stock, making it the best performer.&lt;br&gt;- A truck drove around Harvard displaying names and photos of students involved in a letter blaming Israel for Hamas' attacks.&lt;br&gt;- Former Harvard president Larry Summers criticizes Bill Ackman's request for student names as reminiscent of Joe McCarthy.&lt;br&gt;- Slack's Google Drive App can share private Docs and Drive files.&lt;br&gt;- Trezor releases a new hardware wallet and metal private key backup.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Phoenix's Mayor Kate Gallego is leveraging the semiconductor revolution to establish the city as a global hub.&lt;br&gt;- IRS claims Microsoft may owe over $29B in back taxes, but Microsoft disagrees.&lt;br&gt;- Thousands of workers walk out of Ford's biggest plant as the auto workers' strike expands.&lt;br&gt;- Columbia University faces revelations about its failure to stop a predator for decades.&lt;br&gt;- Companies should be able to challenge old rules with new injuries, according to Bloomberg Law.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Implementing Spring Security 6 with Spring Boot 3: A Guide to OAuth and JWT with Nimbus for Authentication.&lt;br&gt;- Google VP teases Gemini's multimodal future and mentions seeing amazing things.&lt;br&gt;- Linda Yaccarino responds to the EU regarding content related to the Israel-Hamas war.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Free daycare for teachers' kids could help fix the crisis for all parents.&lt;br&gt;- Moving to Portugal has become more expensive.&lt;br&gt;- Downsizing to a tiny house in the countryside increased the cost of living instead of saving money.&lt;br&gt;- Bond yields will stay high, and Harvard economist Ken Rogoff believes the Fed's war on inflation isn't over yet.&lt;br&gt;- Hybrid workers spend an average of $51 a day when they go into the office.&lt;br&gt;- Taco Bell debuts "premium" nuggets, throwing shade at McDonald's.&lt;br&gt;- The executive sales coach lead at Google identifies four habits that successful leaders practice.&lt;br&gt;- Boost your productivity in VS Code with the best themes: A developer's guide.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's investment in Nubank has been highly successful, showcasing the potential of crypto-friendly banks.&lt;br&gt;- The controversy surrounding student involvement in blaming Israel for Hamas' attacks highlights the sensitive nature of political discussions on campuses.&lt;br&gt;- The use of technology, such as Slack's Google Drive App, raises concerns about privacy and data sharing.&lt;br&gt;- The strike at Ford's plant reflects ongoing labor disputes in the auto industry.&lt;br&gt;- The failure of institutions like Columbia University to address predatory behavior raises questions about accountability and student safety.&lt;br&gt;- The ability for companies to challenge old rules with new injuries can foster innovation and adaptability in business.&lt;br&gt;- The development of AI technologies, such as Spring Security and Gemini, continues to shape various industries.&lt;br&gt;- The rising cost of living and the impact of inflation affect individuals' financial decisions and lifestyle choices.&lt;br&gt;- The hybrid work model has financial implications for both employees and employers.&lt;br&gt;- Fast food chains engage in competitive marketing strategies to attract customers.&lt;br&gt;- Successful leaders exhibit specific habits that contribute to their effectiveness.&lt;br&gt;- Developers can enhance their productivity by utilizing themes in VS Code.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report highlights the diverse range of topics in the tech, business, AI, and other sectors. It showcases the impact of investments, controversies, technological advancements, labor issues, institutional failures, legal considerations, and consumer trends. The insights gathered emphasize the importance of innovation, privacy, accountability, financial decision-making, and effective leadership in today's dynamic landscape.</summary></entry></feed>