<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-19T06:01:05Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 19 Aug 2023 06:01:05</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-19T06:01:05Z</published><updated>2023-08-19T06:01:05Z</updated><id>15bfc3ab-4959-42f0-94a9-cffc1b981dcd</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Cisco CEO says AI is already becoming a huge new market after it 'missed' the initial cloud computing boom.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: AI is emerging as a significant market opportunity for Cisco.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: Cisco acknowledges the importance of AI and aims to capitalize on its potential.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Meta's updated RTO mandate is as strict as Amazon's, with a few unique rules. Here are all the key details.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: Meta's RTO mandate is comparable to Amazon's in terms of strictness.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: Meta is taking steps to ensure user safety and privacy, similar to Amazon's approach.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. WD refused to answer our questions about its self-wiping SanDisk SSDs.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: WD declined to provide information regarding its self-wiping SSDs.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: WD's refusal raises questions about the transparency and reliability of their products.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. California is letting a lot more people get a digital ID.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: California is expanding access to digital identification.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: This move aims to enhance convenience and efficiency in various sectors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. The Women's World Cup broke even after years of financial losses.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: The Women's World Cup achieved financial stability after a period of losses.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: This success highlights the growing popularity and commercial viability of women's sports.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. California Blue Shield Deal Exposes Amazon’s And Mark Cuban’s Pharmacy Limitations.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: The California Blue Shield deal reveals limitations in Amazon's and Mark Cuban's pharmacy services.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: This exposes potential challenges faced by major players in the pharmacy industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. ListenAI: Elevate Your Health Journey with Our Caring AI Chatbot Companion.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: ListenAI offers an AI chatbot companion for personalized health support.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: AI-powered chatbots can enhance healthcare experiences and provide tailored assistance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Imposter Syndrome and the Final Phase of a Coding Bootcamp: Inevitable Perhaps, but Possible to Overcome?&lt;br&gt;- Key point: Imposter syndrome can affect coding bootcamp participants during the final phase.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: Overcoming imposter syndrome is crucial for success in coding bootcamps.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Beyond the Pen: AI’s Artistry in Handwritten Text Generation from Visual Archetypes.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: AI can generate handwritten text based on visual archetypes.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: AI's ability to mimic human handwriting opens up new possibilities in various industries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The AI market is rapidly expanding, with Cisco recognizing its potential.&lt;br&gt;- Meta and Amazon have similar strict mandates regarding user safety.&lt;br&gt;- California is embracing digital identification for increased convenience.&lt;br&gt;- The Women's World Cup's financial success showcases the viability of women's sports.&lt;br&gt;- Challenges and limitations exist in the pharmacy industry, as seen in the California Blue Shield deal.&lt;br&gt;- AI chatbots can revolutionize healthcare support and personalization.&lt;br&gt;- Overcoming imposter syndrome is crucial for success in coding bootcamps.&lt;br&gt;- AI's ability to generate handwritten text has diverse applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report highlights the growing influence of AI, developments in technology and business sectors, and the impact of various events and decisions on industries and society.</summary></entry></feed>