<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-12T00:01:16Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:01:16</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-12T00:01:16Z</published><updated>2023-08-12T00:01:16Z</updated><id>859780e8-a5da-438f-8fad-080e5f122f4c</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Ukrainian pilots taking English classes to fly US-made jets&lt;br&gt;- OpenTerraform, an MPL fork of Terraform after HashiCorp's license change&lt;br&gt;- Apple's discounted 14-inch MacBook Pro with M2 Pro&lt;br&gt;- Bose's upcoming flagship headphones with premium flair&lt;br&gt;- Comparing machine learning methods: traditional vs. cost-saving alternatives&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's Twitter updates, including layoffs and verification&lt;br&gt;- Italy's unexpected win in the Musk-Zuckerberg fight saga&lt;br&gt;- Crafting a memorable developer portfolio guide&lt;br&gt;- GPT grocery bot generating poison recipes as an example of AI pitfalls&lt;br&gt;- Biden launches AI competition to tackle cybersecurity challenges&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- The 5 most pressing questions about the bullish 'resilience' thesis of the stock market and the economy&lt;br&gt;- Ex-Goldman CEO Lloyd Blankfein's complaint and offer to rejoin the firm after a stock hit&lt;br&gt;- Publishers in Canada urging regulator to prevent Meta from restricting news access&lt;br&gt;- The brewing backlash against DEI in corporate America and a venture capital fund getting sued for racial bias&lt;br&gt;- How data pros can create the future of customer experience insights&lt;br&gt;- The U.S. government's aim to control online speech to protect kids&lt;br&gt;- K-12 textbook market sales estimation and Europe's capture of 47%&lt;br&gt;- US stocks drop after wholesale inflation exceeds expectations&lt;br&gt;- Only a couple dozen student-loan borrowers have had their debt wiped out in court since Biden announced changes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Brewing backlash against DEI in corporate America and a venture capital fund getting sued for racial bias&lt;br&gt;- GPT grocery bot generating poison recipes as an example of AI pitfalls&lt;br&gt;- Biden launches AI competition to tackle cybersecurity challenges&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Tech: The tech section highlights various developments such as Ukrainian pilots preparing to fly US-made jets, the launch of OpenTerraform, discounted Apple products, and Bose's upcoming flagship headphones. It also discusses the comparison of machine learning methods and the impact of Elon Musk's Twitter updates.&lt;br&gt;- Business: The business section covers topics such as the stock market and economy, complaints and offers in the corporate world, publisher concerns regarding news access, the backlash against DEI, and the future of customer experience insights.&lt;br&gt;- AI: The AI section focuses on the brewing backlash against DEI in corporate America and the pitfalls of AI, exemplified by the GPT grocery bot generating poison recipes. It also mentions Biden's AI competition to address cybersecurity challenges.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report highlights the latest developments in the tech industry, discusses various business-related issues, and explores the challenges and controversies surrounding AI.</summary></entry></feed>