<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-09T08:03:46Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 09 Nov 2023 08:03:46</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-09T08:03:46Z</published><updated>2023-11-09T08:03:46Z</updated><id>cd1ba473-ff4a-42da-b4a3-228a294d0178</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Instacart confirms that most of its retailers charge higher prices through its app compared to in-store prices.&lt;br&gt;- Exclusive leak reveals details about Humane's AI Pin, which integrates with OpenAI and costs $699.&lt;br&gt;- Rocket Lab's Electron launch vehicle is fully booked for next year and will resume flights in November.&lt;br&gt;- Adobe is selling AI-generated images of the Israel-Hamas war, some of which are being used without proper labeling.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- BMO Alto Accounts: What to know before opening a BMO Alto Savings Account or CD.&lt;br&gt;- Alliant Credit Union review: Easy membership process with high interest rates on savings and checking.&lt;br&gt;- Mogul Club raises $3.6M to make real estate investing more accessible.&lt;br&gt;- Walmart Black Friday deals 2023 include early sales on AirPods, PS5 bundles, air fryers, vacuums, and more.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Supercharge Your Testing Workflow: Creating Unit and E2E Tests 10x Faster with ChatGPT-3 Inside NestJS.&lt;br&gt;- It's time to define levels of autonomy for digital workers and AI agents similar to self-driving vehicles.&lt;br&gt;- AI research introduces PERF, a panoramic NeRF that transforms single images into explorable 3D scenes.&lt;br&gt;- Grimes expresses disagreement with AI philosophy at an AI event, then DJs the party.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine's successful ATACMS strike shows Russia's willingness to "take it on the chin" when Kyiv gets new weapons.&lt;br&gt;- A rapid clean-energy transition could save 181 million years of healthy human life annually by 2050.&lt;br&gt;- FDA approval of Eli Lilly's Zepbound is a win for patients as Ozempic competitors boom.&lt;br&gt;- Mississippi sheriff known for torturing Black people and calling his deputies the "Goon Squad" wins reelection.&lt;br&gt;- Voters in Ohio express anger over the reversal of Roe v. Wade.&lt;br&gt;- A new interim CEO is hired for the Topeka Zoo.&lt;br&gt;- Wiley Analytical Science Award 2024: Award Ceremony - 2023.&lt;br&gt;- Aliens are back in Mexico's congress chambers as a presenter claims to have found a new species.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Instacart's confirmation of higher prices on its app highlights the challenges faced by gig workers and shoppers.&lt;br&gt;- The leaked details about Humane's AI Pin showcase the integration of AI technology into consumer products.&lt;br&gt;- Rocket Lab's fully booked launch schedule indicates a growing demand for satellite launches.&lt;br&gt;- The sale of AI-generated images by Adobe raises concerns about the authenticity of media content.&lt;br&gt;- The success of Ukraine's ATACMS strike suggests Russia's vulnerability to new weapons.&lt;br&gt;- The potential health benefits of a rapid clean-energy transition emphasize the importance of sustainable practices.&lt;br&gt;- Eli Lilly's FDA approval and the booming market for Ozempic competitors indicate advancements in diabetes treatment.&lt;br&gt;- The reelection of a Mississippi sheriff known for misconduct raises questions about accountability in law enforcement.&lt;br&gt;- Voter anger over the reversal of Roe v. Wade in Ohio highlights the ongoing debate on reproductive rights.&lt;br&gt;- The hiring of a new interim CEO for the Topeka Zoo signifies a period of transition and leadership change.&lt;br&gt;- The Wiley Analytical Science Award recognizes excellence in the field of analytical science.&lt;br&gt;- The claim of finding a new species by a presenter in Mexico's congress chambers sparks curiosity and interest.</summary></entry></feed>