<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-31T20:02:46Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 31 Aug 2023 20:02:46</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-31T20:02:46Z</published><updated>2023-08-31T20:02:46Z</updated><id>e190a8d5-9f91-4628-8017-ed939c303f10</id><summary type="html">Low Upgrade Rates, Strong Cable Performance Highlight US Q2 2023 Wireless Landscape (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- The US wireless industry saw low upgrade rates in the second quarter of 2023.&lt;br&gt;- Despite this, cable performance remained strong, indicating a stable wireless landscape.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Runway ML's new motion slider makes AI video animation more flexible (AI)&lt;br&gt;- Runway ML has introduced a new motion slider that enhances the flexibility of AI video animation.&lt;br&gt;- This innovation allows for more dynamic and customizable animations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;X-ray free electron laser observation of ultrafast lattice behaviour ... - Nature.com (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- A recent study published in Nature.com utilized X-ray free electron laser observation to study the ultrafast lattice behavior.&lt;br&gt;- This research provides valuable insights into the dynamics of lattice structures.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to log into Facebook on all your devices, even if you don't know your password (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- A guide on how to log into Facebook on multiple devices without knowing the password has been shared.&lt;br&gt;- This can be helpful for users who have forgotten their passwords or want to access their accounts from different devices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video shows a Ukrainian soldier celebrating after his first-person-view drone slams into a Russian military truck from behind (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- A video has surfaced showing a Ukrainian soldier celebrating after his drone crashes into a Russian military truck.&lt;br&gt;- This incident highlights the use of drones in military operations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companies like Goldman Sachs may want workers back in the office full-time, but most US execs think hybrid working is here to stay, study finds (Business)&lt;br&gt;- A study reveals that while companies like Goldman Sachs prefer full-time office work, most US executives believe hybrid working is the future.&lt;br&gt;- This indicates a shift in work culture and the acceptance of remote and flexible work arrangements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you work remotely, your bosses are probably using software to track you. Here's how they'll catch you slacking off. (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Remote workers are likely being monitored by their employers using tracking software.&lt;br&gt;- This article discusses how employers can catch employees slacking off and maintain productivity in remote work settings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The best tips and advice for selling items on Facebook Marketplace (Business)&lt;br&gt;- A comprehensive guide provides tips and advice for effectively selling items on Facebook Marketplace.&lt;br&gt;- This can be useful for individuals looking to maximize their sales on the platform.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pret a Manger was fined $1 million after an employee was trapped in a freezer for more than 2 hours and thought she was going to die (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Pret a Manger faced a $1 million fine after an employee was trapped in a freezer for an extended period.&lt;br&gt;- This incident highlights the importance of workplace safety and the consequences of negligence.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I moved to Norway nine years ago. Being stereotyped as an American helped me get ahead at work, but it's tough making friends and the weather isn't for everyone. (Personal)&lt;br&gt;- A personal account shares the experience of moving to Norway and the advantages and challenges faced as an American.&lt;br&gt;- This provides insights into cultural differences and the impact of stereotypes on professional life.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Gen Zer living in a microstudio in Dubai says it's changed how she shops, cleans, budgets, and socializes (Personal)&lt;br&gt;- A Gen Z individual living in a microstudio in Dubai shares how this lifestyle has influenced various aspects of their life.&lt;br&gt;- This offers insights into the impact of living in small spaces and adapting to a different environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Hawaii mourns its dead, 'disaster vultures' are swooping in to make a quick buck (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Amidst the mourning in Hawaii, opportunistic individuals are taking advantage of the situation for financial gain.&lt;br&gt;- This sheds light on the unethical practices that can arise during times of tragedy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warren Buffett dumps stock, regulators open probes as claims of abuse and fraud mount against a top Globe Life agency (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's decision to sell stock and the opening of regulatory probes are linked to allegations of abuse and fraud against a prominent Globe Life agency.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the potential consequences of unethical practices in the financial industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk's X wants to collect users' biometric data and education history, an upcoming privacy policy update shows (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- An upcoming privacy policy update reveals that Elon Musk's company, X, plans to collect users' biometric data and education history.&lt;br&gt;- This raises concerns about privacy and the ethical implications of data collection.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I regret moving to Boulder, Colorado. I thought I'd fit right in, but it was the loneliest two years of my life. (Personal)&lt;br&gt;- A personal reflection expresses regret over moving to Boulder, Colorado, due to feelings of loneliness.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the emotional impact of relocating and the importance of social connections.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese property market may look like it's imploding. But one expert doesn't think it'll cause a financial crisis &amp;mdash; and there may even be a bright spot. (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Despite the apparent decline of the Chinese property market, an expert believes it will not lead to a financial crisis.&lt;br&gt;- This offers a contrasting perspective and suggests potential positive outcomes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cybertruck photos in the wild reveal the truck's quirks ahead of Elon Musk's most important launch yet (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Photos of the Cybertruck in real-world settings showcase its unique features and characteristics.&lt;br&gt;- This generates excitement and anticipation for Elon Musk's upcoming launch.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Managed to death: How Canada turned its forests into a carbon bomb (Business)&lt;br&gt;- An investigation explores how Canada's forest management practices have contributed to a significant carbon footprint.&lt;br&gt;- This sheds light on the environmental impact of certain industries and the need for sustainable practices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not just you – no one is posting on social media anymore (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- A trend of decreased social media posting is observed, indicating a shift in user behavior.&lt;br&gt;- This suggests changing attitudes towards social media and potential implications for the industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Eve Play brings AirPlay 2 audio to your Hi-Fi gear this November (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- The Eve Play is set to launch in November, offering AirPlay 2 audio compatibility for Hi-Fi gear.&lt;br&gt;- This introduces a new product that enhances audio streaming capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft is unbundling Teams from Office in Europe to address regulator concerns (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft is separating Teams from Office in Europe to address regulatory concerns.&lt;br&gt;- This demonstrates the company's responsiveness to regional regulations and market demands.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;iPhone camera app Obscura releases a new version with iPad support (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- The iPhone camera app, Obscura, has released an updated version that includes support for iPads.&lt;br&gt;- This expands the app's compatibility and functionality across Apple devices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK gov't urged against delay in setting AI rulebook as MPs warn policymakers aren’t keeping up with tech (AI)&lt;br&gt;- UK government officials are advised against delaying the establishment of an AI rulebook.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the need for policymakers to stay informed and proactive in regulating emerging technologies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OpenAI-backed language learning app Speak raises $16M to expand to the U.S. (AI)&lt;br&gt;- Speak, a language learning app backed by OpenAI, has raised $16 million to expand its services to the US market.&lt;br&gt;- This indicates the growing demand for AI-powered language learning tools.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google Researchers Introduce 𝗦𝘆𝗻𝘁𝗵𝗜𝗗: A Digital Tool to Watermark and Identify AI-Generated Images (AI)&lt;br&gt;- Google researchers have developed a digital tool called 𝗦𝘆𝗻𝘁𝗵𝗜𝗗, which can watermark and identify AI-generated images.&lt;br&gt;- This addresses the challenge of distinguishing between AI-generated and human-created images.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;JCPenney is spending $1 billion on store and online upgrades in the latest bid to revive its business (Business)&lt;br&gt;- JCPenney has allocated $1 billion for store and online upgrades as part of its efforts to revitalize its business.&lt;br&gt;- This demonstrates the company's commitment to adapting to changing consumer preferences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Report says close associates of India's Adani Group secretly purchased large numbers of shares (Business)&lt;br&gt;- A report reveals that close associates of India's Adani Group have covertly acquired significant amounts of shares.&lt;br&gt;- This raises concerns about transparency and potential market manipulation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Idalia caused millions of dollars in damage in Florida and Georgia (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Hurricane Idalia resulted in extensive damage and financial losses in Florida and Georgia.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the destructive impact of natural disasters on communities and economies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Feds are looking into whether Tesla funds were used to build a secret glass house for Elon Musk (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Federal authorities are investigating whether Tesla funds were utilized to construct a hidden glass house for Elon Musk.&lt;br&gt;- This investigation raises questions about financial practices and potential misuse of company resources.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Introducing Hoppscotch Enterprise Edition and a plethora of features - The Hoppscotch August 2023 Release You Can't Miss! (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Hoppscotch has introduced the Hoppscotch Enterprise Edition, along with various new features in their August 2023 release.&lt;br&gt;- This showcases the company's product updates and advancements in API development tools.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The US wireless industry experienced low upgrade rates in Q2 2023, indicating a potential shift in consumer behavior.&lt;br&gt;- AI video animation becomes more flexible with Runway ML's new motion slider, allowing for dynamic and customizable animations.&lt;br&gt;- X-ray free electron laser observation provides valuable insights into ultrafast lattice behavior.&lt;br&gt;- Remote workers are being monitored by employers using tracking software, highlighting the importance of maintaining productivity.&lt;br&gt;- The Chinese property market's decline may not lead to a financial crisis, according to an expert's perspective.&lt;br&gt;- Decreased social media posting suggests changing attitudes towards the platform.&lt;br&gt;- The need for sustainable forest management practices in Canada is emphasized to mitigate the carbon footprint.&lt;br&gt;- Speak, a language learning app backed by OpenAI, raises funding to expand its services to the US market.&lt;br&gt;- Google researchers introduce a digital tool to watermark and identify AI-generated images, addressing the challenge of distinguishing between AI and human-created content.&lt;br&gt;- JCPenney's investment in store and online upgrades reflects its commitment to adapting to changing consumer preferences.&lt;br&gt;- Federal authorities are investigating the potential misuse of Tesla funds in the construction of a glass house for Elon Musk.</summary></entry></feed>