<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-14T10:05:50Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:05:50</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-14T10:05:50Z</published><updated>2023-08-14T10:05:50Z</updated><id>4bda1831-0eec-4483-ad85-ad8befc39bd7</id><summary type="html">Report Title: Cross-Language Insights: Tech, Business, and AI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Introduction:&lt;br&gt;This report aims to provide insights on various topics such as Tech, Business, and AI by compiling and translating content from different languages into English. The report will categorize the content under broader topics, highlight key points, and provide specific insights for each category. Finally, a summary of the overall insights gathered from all broader topics will be presented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Building a REST API with Deno and Hono.js: A Step-by-Step Guide&lt;br&gt;   - Key Points: This article provides a detailed guide on building a REST API using Deno and Hono.js.&lt;br&gt;   - Insights: Deno and Hono.js offer a modern and efficient approach to building REST APIs, making development easier and more streamlined.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Show HN: I wrote a RDBMS (SQLite clone) from scratch in pure Python&lt;br&gt;   - Key Points: The author shares their accomplishment of creating an RDBMS (SQLite clone) using only Python.&lt;br&gt;   - Insights: This project showcases the power and flexibility of Python in developing complex database systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. The PR manager for Four Seasons Hotel Bangkok on the downsides of the job, why backpackers are the bane of his existence, and how 'The White Lotus' changed his workday&lt;br&gt;   - Key Points: The PR manager discusses the challenges of the job, particularly dealing with backpackers, and the impact of the TV show 'The White Lotus.'&lt;br&gt;   - Insights: Managing public relations in the hospitality industry can be demanding, and popular media can significantly influence the perception of a hotel.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Wiley to Divest Educational Businesses After Disappointing Year - Publishers Marketplace&lt;br&gt;   - Key Points: Wiley, a publishing company, plans to divest its educational businesses following a disappointing year.&lt;br&gt;   - Insights: This decision reflects the company's strategic response to market challenges and a focus on core operations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. This AI Research from DeepMind Aims at Reducing Sycophancy in Large Language Models (LLMs) Using Simple Synthetic Data&lt;br&gt;   - Key Points: DeepMind's AI research focuses on reducing sycophancy in large language models using synthetic data.&lt;br&gt;   - Insights: Addressing biases and improving the ethical aspects of AI language models is crucial for their responsible deployment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Time To Redesign Your Career For The Age Of Artificial Intelligence&lt;br&gt;   - Key Points: The article emphasizes the need to adapt careers for the AI era.&lt;br&gt;   - Insights: With the increasing integration of AI in various industries, individuals must proactively update their skills and embrace AI-related opportunities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Building REST APIs with Deno and Hono.js offers a modern approach to development.&lt;br&gt;- Python's flexibility is showcased in the creation of an RDBMS.&lt;br&gt;- Managing PR in the hospitality industry can be challenging, influenced by media portrayal.&lt;br&gt;- Wiley's decision to divest educational businesses reflects strategic adaptation.&lt;br&gt;- Addressing biases in AI language models is a focus of DeepMind's research.&lt;br&gt;- Adapting careers for the AI era is essential for professional growth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report highlights the diverse insights gathered from different languages, providing a comprehensive understanding of the Tech, Business, and AI domains.</summary></entry></feed>