<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-30T08:03:46Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 30 Oct 2023 08:03:46</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-30T08:03:46Z</published><updated>2023-10-30T08:03:46Z</updated><id>33630fdf-2ae0-4e31-95be-52130f870d5e</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- EPA's Mandatory PFAS Reporting Rule Under TSCA Includes ... - Wiley Rein&lt;br&gt;- We migrated our back end from Vercel to Fly.io and the challenges we faced&lt;br&gt;- ChatGPT Plus members can upload and analyze files in the latest beta&lt;br&gt;- What is white hydrogen? Scientists say the clean-energy gas could save the world.&lt;br&gt;- What is a Stun Server: The Complete Guide to NAT Traversal&lt;br&gt;- Console #181 - Story of LocalSend, a cross-platform alternative to AirDrop&lt;br&gt;- AI and elections: An introduction to the special issue - John Wiley&lt;br&gt;- Dear SaaStr: What does a US-Based SaaS company Need to Know Before Expanding into Europe?&lt;br&gt;- 🔒 Authenticate with Session-Based Auth in Django, Bootstrap, React &amp; Vite&lt;br&gt;- Hacktoberfest 2023: Celebrating the Last Days- My Rewards and Your Opportunity to Shine&lt;br&gt;- Sieve (YC W22), the video/audio AI cloud, is hiring AI engineers&lt;br&gt;- Apple Watch violates patents held by Orange Co. tech company, ITC finds&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: &lt;br&gt;- The EPA has implemented a mandatory PFAS reporting rule under TSCA, which has implications for environmental regulation.&lt;br&gt;- The migration of a back end from Vercel to Fly.io posed challenges for the company.&lt;br&gt;- ChatGPT Plus members now have the ability to upload and analyze files in the latest beta version.&lt;br&gt;- White hydrogen is being touted as a clean-energy gas with potential to save the world.&lt;br&gt;- Understanding Stun Servers and NAT Traversal is important for network communication.&lt;br&gt;- LocalSend is a cross-platform alternative to AirDrop, providing file sharing capabilities.&lt;br&gt;- AI's role in elections is explored in a special issue by John Wiley.&lt;br&gt;- US-based SaaS companies should consider important factors before expanding into Europe.&lt;br&gt;- Session-based authentication in Django, Bootstrap, React, and Vite is discussed.&lt;br&gt;- Hacktoberfest 2023 is celebrated, offering rewards and opportunities for developers.&lt;br&gt;- Sieve, a video/audio AI cloud platform, is hiring AI engineers.&lt;br&gt;- Apple Watch has been found to violate patents held by an Orange Co. tech company.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Layoffs at VW’s Cariad further delay software launch in Porsche, Audi models&lt;br&gt;- Korean Investment Partners is the latest Korean VC firm to launch a Southeast Asia fund&lt;br&gt;- Laid-off masses have a message for Zuckerberg, Benioff: We'll never come back&lt;br&gt;- Panera Bread founder says he thought it would be easier to be 'hit by a truck' during the chain's stressful 2015 overhaul&lt;br&gt;- Mike Johnson is the first Republican House speaker from the South since Newt Gingrich, putting the region back in the driver's seat of GOP politics&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk Says X Users Spreading Lies Won’t Get Paid For Those Tweets&lt;br&gt;- Free Mexico F1 live stream: Where to watch Formula 1 GP online from anywhere&lt;br&gt;- Dear SaaStr: What does a US-Based SaaS company Need to Know Before Expanding into Europe?&lt;br&gt;- Hacktoberfest 2023: Celebrating the Last Days- My Rewards and Your Opportunity to Shine&lt;br&gt;- Apple Watch violates patents held by Orange Co. tech company, ITC finds&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Layoffs at VW's Cariad have caused further delays in software launch for Porsche and Audi models.&lt;br&gt;- Korean Investment Partners has joined other Korean VC firms in launching a Southeast Asia fund.&lt;br&gt;- The laid-off masses express their dissatisfaction with Zuckerberg and Benioff, stating they will not return.&lt;br&gt;- The founder of Panera Bread reflects on the challenges faced during the chain's overhaul in 2015.&lt;br&gt;- Mike Johnson's appointment as the first Republican House speaker from the South since Newt Gingrich signifies the region's influence in GOP politics.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk warns that users spreading lies on X will not be paid for their tweets.&lt;br&gt;- Formula 1 fans can watch the Mexico GP live stream online from anywhere.&lt;br&gt;- US-based SaaS companies should consider important factors before expanding into Europe.&lt;br&gt;- Hacktoberfest 2023 offers rewards and opportunities for developers.&lt;br&gt;- Apple Watch has been found to violate patents held by an Orange Co. tech company.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- ChatGPT Plus members can upload and analyze files in the latest beta&lt;br&gt;- AI and elections: An introduction to the special issue - John Wiley&lt;br&gt;- Sieve (YC W22), the video/audio AI cloud, is hiring AI engineers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- ChatGPT Plus members now have the ability to upload and analyze files in the latest beta version.&lt;br&gt;- The special issue by John Wiley explores the role of AI in elections.&lt;br&gt;- Sieve, a video/audio AI cloud platform, is actively hiring AI engineers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The EPA's mandatory PFAS reporting rule under TSCA highlights the importance of environmental regulation.&lt;br&gt;- Technology advancements, such as the migration of back ends and the introduction of new features, present challenges and opportunities.&lt;br&gt;- Business news showcases layoffs, investments, and the impact of key figures in various industries.&lt;br&gt;- AI continues to play a significant role in various sectors, including elections and video/audio processing.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report highlights the dynamic nature of technology, business, and AI, with insights that range from environmental concerns to market trends and technological advancements.</summary></entry></feed>