<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-02T20:01:59Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 02 Dec 2023 20:01:59</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-02T20:01:59Z</published><updated>2023-12-02T20:01:59Z</updated><id>0359b358-2231-45c9-82a2-b73683f1bcbb</id><summary type="html">In the world, there have been various developments and events. The effects of low-level laser therapy on severe acute respiratory conditions have been studied, providing potential insights into new treatment options. Meanwhile, artist William T. Wiley's work has been discussed, with the conclusion that nothing more can be done for him. In the realm of technology, an AI tool called Goblin.tools has been utilized to enhance the professionalism of emails. Additionally, Tesla is offering great deals on their vehicles, making them more accessible to those who cannot afford a Cybertruck. In Florida, a Gen Xer who previously made a living as an Uber and Lyft driver has shared his struggles and alternative methods of boosting his income. Millennials have also faced challenges in the housing market, becoming their own worst enemy in some cases. The transformation of retail stores Banana Republic and J. Crew has been observed, with one of them providing a more enjoyable shopping experience. In the realm of entertainment, Aretha Franklin's sons have been awarded valuable property after her handwritten will, signed with a smiley face, was discovered hidden in a couch. Finance workers in London are facing the threat of AI, which should serve as a warning to Wall Street. Airbnb hosts have mixed feelings about Christmas, as they try to maximize their earnings during the winter months. Sadly, the world's 'saddest' elephant has passed away after spending over 40 years alone in a concrete pen at Manila Zoo. On the technological front, Google DeepMind's AI has generated 380,000 new materials, presenting the challenge of bringing them to life. A startup linked to Neuralink is working on technology that would allow individuals to work while they dream. Apple has released an urgent update for its MacOS Sonoma 14.1.2, highlighting its importance for all MacBook users. The importance of diversity in the talent pool has been discussed, debunking the fallacy of a small talent pool. Fannie Mae predicts that U.S. home prices will remain stable in 2024, even in the event of a mild recession. The 50th anniversary of hip-hop has shed light on the influence and struggles of women in the industry. Yondr, a phone-free technology, is gaining popularity in schools, concerts, and potentially even living rooms. Under Armour's new CEO acknowledges the brand's bro-centric image and aims to make changes. Google Maps has undergone a redesign, resembling Apple Maps, which has received mixed reviews. The issue of SIM swapping and port-out attacks has been raised, prompting discussions on which wireless carriers provide protection against such threats. The fight against HIV continues, with the understanding that anything less than victory creates future problems. Efforts to end preventable deaths among children, including those caused by AIDS, serve as inspiration for broader goals. Lastly, magnetic force field distributions in microfluidic devices have been measured, potentially leading to advancements in various fields.</summary></entry></feed>