<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-16T22:01:23Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 16 Aug 2023 22:01:23</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-16T22:01:23Z</published><updated>2023-08-16T22:01:23Z</updated><id>49a0c5c4-4c01-40e3-b515-73ff7a97c645</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- A Vietnamese electric carmaker is now worth $85 billion, which is almost as much as Ford and General Motors combined.&lt;br&gt;- There's an oversupply of electric vehicles (EVs) versus gas cars at dealerships, solving two of the biggest problems with car shopping.&lt;br&gt;- Amazon Pharmacy automates discounts to help insulin patients get pledged prices.&lt;br&gt;- Meet JEN-1, a universal AI framework that combines bi-directional and uni-directional modes to generate high-quality music conditioned on either text or music representations.&lt;br&gt;- Meet Marqo, an open-source vector search engine for AI applications.&lt;br&gt;- ASP.NET Core in .NET 8 Preview 7 introduces features like Blazor, Native AOT, Antiforgery, and more.&lt;br&gt;- Build an expandable/collapsible data table with 2 shadcn/ui components.&lt;br&gt;- Demystifying "No 'Access-Control-Allow-Origin' Header" in JavaScript and Postman: A comprehensive exploration.&lt;br&gt;- The Best Serverless Framework in 2023: A data-driven showdown for AWS projects.&lt;br&gt;- The Download: Tech's ethical congregation and the Inflation Reduction Act's anniversary.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- The owner of a luxury retailer in San Francisco says that rising crime and homelessness could make this year its last after 162 years of business.&lt;br&gt;- Police in Ireland had to guard ATMs after a glitch at the country's biggest bank allowed some people to withdraw over $1,000 of cash they didn't have.&lt;br&gt;- SEC amps up breach disclosure requirements, focusing on how to support the board of directors.&lt;br&gt;- The White House's efforts to combat climate change have sparked a tech arms race with the EU.&lt;br&gt;- Target sales fell for the first time in 6 years, but the retailer's stock is surging.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Tesla's 'ultra hardcore' work culture, as told by its employees.&lt;br&gt;- Meet JEN-1, a universal AI framework that combines bi-directional and uni-directional modes to generate high-quality music conditioned on either text or music representations.&lt;br&gt;- Meet Marqo, an open-source vector search engine for AI applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine is angered by a NATO official's suggestion that it could 'give up territory' to Russia and get NATO membership in return.&lt;br&gt;- The S&amp;P 500 is massively overvalued and likely to plunge like it did last year, according to top economist David Rosenberg.&lt;br&gt;- The captain of a Boeing 787 Dreamliner died mid-air after becoming unwell, according to reports.&lt;br&gt;- How do we save water? Stop growing alfalfa in Imperial County.&lt;br&gt;- Netflix's 'Scott Pilgrim Takes Off' anime debuts teaser trailer and premiere date.&lt;br&gt;- Baldur's Gate 3's Steam Cloud Save Syncing is killing internet connections.&lt;br&gt;- 12 games you really need to play if you love 'Baldur's Gate 3'.&lt;br&gt;- Cybersecurity as a strategic investment: How ROI optimization can lead to a more secure future.&lt;br&gt;- Lithium Iron Phosphate is set to be the next big thing in EV batteries.&lt;br&gt;- From vulnerability to resilience: A guide to cybersecurity in the manufacturing sector.&lt;br&gt;- Honey Pepper Pimento Chicken: How to get Chick-fil-A's first new sandwich in years.&lt;br&gt;- In a tipster's note, a view of science publishing's Achilles heel.</summary></entry></feed>