<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-26T20:01:56Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 26 Nov 2023 20:01:56</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-26T20:01:56Z</published><updated>2023-11-26T20:01:56Z</updated><id>ddedf875-0137-48ca-abe3-17e1284f7573</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Humanoid robots could be the next big thing to come from the AI boom. Take a look at 8 of the most advanced ones around.&lt;br&gt;- Boom Supersonic says it will conduct the first test flight of its ultra-speedy 'baby boom' prototype aircraft later this year.&lt;br&gt;- Meet PhysGaussian: An Artificial Intelligence Technique that Produces High-Quality Novel Motion Synthesis by Integrating Physically Grounded Newtonian Dynamics into 3D Gaussians.&lt;br&gt;- About That Mysterious AI Breakthrough Known As Q* By OpenAI That Allegedly Attains True AI Or Is On The Path Toward Artificial General Intelligence (AGI).&lt;br&gt;- How to turn your iPad into an HDMI-capable TV or monitor.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- I'm a Ukrainian CEO who's expanded my bridal business despite the war. Here's how I did it.&lt;br&gt;- This legendary market forecaster has warned of a stock-market crash and a recession for years. Here are Gary Shilling's 14 best X posts since the pandemic.&lt;br&gt;- Meet the typical student-loan borrower: a millennial woman with a $35,000 balance who wants debt relief.&lt;br&gt;- TJ Maxx and other discount retailers could be the big winners in an otherwise bleak holiday shopping season.&lt;br&gt;- I moved to Germany from the US for free education and almost got deported. It's one of the best things that ever happened to me.&lt;br&gt;- Panera founder says the idea of 'swashbuckling' entrepreneurs finding success from taking big risks is 'a myth'.&lt;br&gt;- Some business leaders like Jeff Bezos hate the phrase 'work-life balance.' Here's what they prefer instead.&lt;br&gt;- He wanted to be a trombone player. Instead, he ended up as CEO of one of the world's biggest airlines.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Humanoid robots could be the next big thing to come from the AI boom. Take a look at 8 of the most advanced ones around.&lt;br&gt;- Meet PhysGaussian: An Artificial Intelligence Technique that Produces High-Quality Novel Motion Synthesis by Integrating Physically Grounded Newtonian Dynamics into 3D Gaussians.&lt;br&gt;- About That Mysterious AI Breakthrough Known As Q* By OpenAI That Allegedly Attains True AI Or Is On The Path Toward Artificial General Intelligence (AGI).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The advancement of humanoid robots in the AI field shows potential for significant technological developments.&lt;br&gt;- The market forecaster's warnings about a stock-market crash and recession have been consistent since the pandemic.&lt;br&gt;- The struggles of millennial women with student loan debt highlight the need for debt relief solutions.&lt;br&gt;- Discount retailers like TJ Maxx may see success during a challenging holiday shopping season.&lt;br&gt;- The experience of moving to Germany for free education showcases the positive impact it had on an individual's life.&lt;br&gt;- The Panera founder challenges the notion that success comes from taking big risks.&lt;br&gt;- Business leaders prefer alternative phrases to "work-life balance" to emphasize a different perspective.&lt;br&gt;- Unexpected career paths can lead individuals to become successful CEOs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The report covers various topics including tech, business, and AI. It highlights the potential of humanoid robots in the AI field and the advancements in motion synthesis. It also discusses market forecasts, student loan debt, holiday shopping trends, and personal experiences of individuals in different industries. The report provides insights into the potential impact of these topics and concludes that there is a wide range of opportunities and challenges in these fields.</summary></entry></feed>