<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-12T02:01:24Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 12 Aug 2023 02:01:24</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-12T02:01:24Z</published><updated>2023-08-12T02:01:24Z</updated><id>a04287eb-7308-4908-8f35-ac8a3adaab36</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Zoom rewrites its policies to make clear that your videos aren't used to train AI tools&lt;br&gt;- I'm an AI prompt engineer. Here are 3 ways I use ChatGPT to get the best results.&lt;br&gt;- Authorization and Amazon Verified Permissions - A New Way to Manage Permissions Part IX: Hierarchies and ABAC&lt;br&gt;- This Stanford social network could be the next Facebook on college campuses—but it has a Gen-Z twist&lt;br&gt;- There's a brewing backlash against DEI in corporate America &amp;mdash; and a venture capital fund getting sued for racial bias is now caught in the middle&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- The US housing market hits a record value of $47 trillion as the inventory shortage fuels a price boom&lt;br&gt;- From 'lazy girl jobs' to 'loud quitting,' here are the biggest workplace buzzwords of 2023 &amp;mdash; and what they mean&lt;br&gt;- The Fed can take the rest of the year off as inflation is crumbling and there's no recession in sight, market vet Ed Yardeni says&lt;br&gt;- Zoom Wants Workers Back, Cotopaxi’s People Chief On Remote Work And WeWork’s Warning&lt;br&gt;- Buy tech stocks now as solid 2nd-quarter earnings will power a 15% rally into year-end, Wedbush says&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- I'm an AI prompt engineer. Here are 3 ways I use ChatGPT to get the best results.&lt;br&gt;- Zoom rewrites its policies to make clear that your videos aren't used to train AI tools&lt;br&gt;- There's a brewing backlash against DEI in corporate America &amp;mdash; and a venture capital fund getting sued for racial bias is now caught in the middle&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Trump was warned by a judge about making even 'ambiguous statements' that could intimidate witnesses or influence jurors in the Jan. 6 case&lt;br&gt;- Kentucky's largest school district had to cancel class for two days so it could overhaul a 'disastrous' new bus system that left kids on buses until 10 p.m.&lt;br&gt;- Lyft riders look at their app about 9 times per ride. Now they'll see ads when they check it.&lt;br&gt;- Leesa's Summer Daze mattress sale is back with up to $700 off our expert's top sleeper pick&lt;br&gt;- Apple TV's MLS Season Pass subscriptions doubled since Messi's arrival in US&lt;br&gt;- The Verge Launches “Installer,” a Newsletter About the Next Big Things to Download, Watch, and Explore&lt;br&gt;- Vampire Survivors: our collective obsession with the quirky, genre-defining indie game&lt;br&gt;- TechCrunch+ Roundup: Creator economy VC survey, B2C fintech growth strategy, web3 demo day&lt;br&gt;- The MOVEit mass hacks hold a valuable lesson for the software industry&lt;br&gt;- Top 10 Flutter Side Projects that can end up becoming your next big startup project or SAAS 🚀&lt;br&gt;- These airports have the best and worst wait times, according to actual passenger ratings&lt;br&gt;- The Week’s 10 Biggest Funding Rounds: Neuralink Connects With $270M, Biotech Goes Big Again&lt;br&gt;- Back to School sales: cheap laptops, dorm room essentials, headphones, and more&lt;br&gt;- These are the 5 most pressing questions about the bullish 'resilience' thesis of the stock market and the economy&lt;br&gt;- A Democratic House candidate said he was dropping out of the race because of a 'lack of joy.' Eight hours later, he said it was a mistake and is still in the race&lt;br&gt;- Ukrainian pilots have been taking English classes in between their missions to prepare to fly US-made jets&lt;br&gt;- There's a brewing backlash against DEI in corporate America &amp;mdash; and a venture capital fund getting sued for racial bias is now caught in the middle&lt;br&gt;- I'm one of only 26 Black women astrophysicists in America. Acting helped me overcome the stereotypes I felt as a woman of color in STEM.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The US housing market is experiencing a record value due to an inventory shortage, leading to a price boom.&lt;br&gt;- The Fed believes there is no recession in sight and can take the rest of the year off as inflation is crumbling.&lt;br&gt;- Zoom is making policy changes to ensure user videos are not used to train AI tools.&lt;br&gt;- There is a growing backlash against diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) efforts in corporate America, with a venture capital fund facing a lawsuit for racial bias caught in the middle.&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is seeing advancements in AI technology, with AI prompt engineers utilizing tools like ChatGPT for optimal results.&lt;br&gt;- The stock market is expected to rally into year-end based on solid 2nd-quarter earnings, particularly in the tech sector.&lt;br&gt;- Various industries, such as transportation and mattress sales, are experiencing changes and promotions.&lt;br&gt;- The education sector faces challenges, such as a problematic bus system and job market difficulties for recent college graduates.&lt;br&gt;- Cultural and social topics, such as indie games and the representation of underrepresented groups in STEM fields, are also discussed.</summary></entry></feed>