<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-18T08:03:50Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 18 Nov 2023 08:03:50</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-18T08:03:50Z</published><updated>2023-11-18T08:03:50Z</updated><id>d17d4002-52f1-4396-9418-80bbf01723f4</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI ousts CEO Sam Altman - CTO Mira Murati appointed interim CEO&lt;br&gt;- Just to be clear, we have no idea why Sam Altman is out at OpenAI&lt;br&gt;- The tech world reacts in shock to Sam Altman's departure from OpenAI&lt;br&gt;- Meet Sam Altman, the ex-OpenAI CEO who learned to code at 8 and is a doomsday prepper with a stash of guns and gold&lt;br&gt;- Sam Altman is no longer CEO of OpenAI after losing the confidence of the board&lt;br&gt;- Sam Altman out at OpenAI, CTO Mira Murati to take over&lt;br&gt;- 6 things to know about Mira Murati, OpenAI’s new interim CEO&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- This week in 5 numbers: Wiley sells its OPM business - Higher Ed Dive&lt;br&gt;- State school board weighs increased funding requests ahead of ... - Southwest Regional Publishing&lt;br&gt;- Comings &amp; Goings: McCord Gallery Holiday Shoppe opens tonight - Southwest Regional Publishing&lt;br&gt;- Ransomware Attacker Files SEC Complaint to Increase Pressure on ... - Wiley Rein&lt;br&gt;- Blueberry Hill Cafe continues breakfast, lunch tradition in Oak Lawn - Southwest Regional Publishing&lt;br&gt;- Ransomware Attacker Files SEC Complaint to Increase Pressure on ... - Wiley Rein&lt;br&gt;- How chefs feed 100,000 Michigan fans at America's biggest football stadium&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI ousts CEO Sam Altman - CTO Mira Murati appointed interim CEO&lt;br&gt;- Just to be clear, we have no idea why Sam Altman is out at OpenAI&lt;br&gt;- The tech world reacts in shock to Sam Altman's departure from OpenAI&lt;br&gt;- Meet Sam Altman, the ex-OpenAI CEO who learned to code at 8 and is a doomsday prepper with a stash of guns and gold&lt;br&gt;- Sam Altman is no longer CEO of OpenAI after losing the confidence of the board&lt;br&gt;- Sam Altman out at OpenAI, CTO Mira Murati to take over&lt;br&gt;- 6 things to know about Mira Murati, OpenAI’s new interim CEO&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Jury deliberating in first-degree murder trial; Barnard says Wiley ... - Muddy River News&lt;br&gt;- Arretta Wiley Obituary - Daniels &amp; Hutchison Funeral Home ... - Legacy.com&lt;br&gt;- Kenneth Price Obituary - O. W. Wiley Mortuary - Houston - 2023 - Legacy.com&lt;br&gt;- Samuel Blile Obituary - Wiley Funeral Home - Granbury - 2023 - Legacy.com&lt;br&gt;- Frogs Odds: TCU Football vs. Baylor Bears - Frogs O' War&lt;br&gt;- Eastern Michigan football tops Akron in 2OT; Western Michigan shut ... - Detroit Free Press&lt;br&gt;- Satellite photos of crowds trying to flee Gaza shows the unimaginable scale of the crisis&lt;br&gt;- US stocks edge higher and notch 3rd consecutive week of gains&lt;br&gt;- How chefs feed 100,000 Michigan fans at America's biggest football stadium&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The departure of Sam Altman as CEO of OpenAI has caused shock and speculation in the tech world.&lt;br&gt;- Mira Murati has been appointed as the interim CEO of OpenAI.&lt;br&gt;- Wiley has sold its OPM business, and there are increased funding requests being weighed by the state school board.&lt;br&gt;- Ransomware attacks and SEC complaints are putting pressure on companies like Wiley Rein.&lt;br&gt;- There is a mix of news articles, obituaries, and sports updates in the provided content.&lt;br&gt;- The scale of the crisis in Gaza is evident through satellite photos.&lt;br&gt;- US stocks have seen consecutive weeks of gains.&lt;br&gt;- Chefs are able to feed a large number of fans at America's biggest football stadium.</summary></entry></feed>