<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-02T08:03:25Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 02 Sep 2023 08:03:25</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-02T08:03:25Z</published><updated>2023-09-02T08:03:25Z</updated><id>f503ed55-3ca4-429c-9e40-39fb84ca9e50</id><summary type="html">Report: Tech and Business News&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Supreme's Creative Director Resigns Citing 'Systemic Racism'&lt;br&gt;- The creative director of Supreme, a popular streetwear brand, abruptly resigned, claiming 'systemic racism' within the company.&lt;br&gt;- Supreme denied the allegations and stated that they have a diverse and inclusive work environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: This highlights the ongoing issue of racism within the fashion industry and the need for companies to address and combat systemic racism.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Parental Policy on Smartphones for Children&lt;br&gt;- A user on Ask HN asked about the community's policy regarding smartphones for children.&lt;br&gt;- Various responses were given, with some advocating for limited usage and others promoting educational apps and parental controls.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: The discussion reflects the concerns and considerations parents have regarding their children's smartphone usage and the need for responsible guidelines.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Rise of the Trackers: A Fireflies Trilogy Game&lt;br&gt;- Leader N U has developed a game called "Rise of the Trackers" as part of the Fireflies Trilogy.&lt;br&gt;- The game combines augmented reality and real-world exploration, allowing players to track and capture virtual creatures.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: This game demonstrates the growing popularity of augmented reality and its integration into gaming experiences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Google Raises Nest Aware Subscription Prices&lt;br&gt;- Google has increased the prices of its Nest Aware subscription plans, with the highest tier now costing up to $30 per year.&lt;br&gt;- Nest Aware offers advanced features and storage for Nest security cameras and smart home devices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: The price increase may impact consumers' decisions to subscribe to Nest Aware and raises questions about the affordability of smart home security services.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. Gizmodo's Owner Shuts Down Spanish Language Site&lt;br&gt;- Gizmodo's owner has decided to shut down its Spanish language site and focus on AI translations instead.&lt;br&gt;- The move aims to streamline operations and reach a broader audience through automated translations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: This decision reflects the increasing reliance on AI technology for content translation and the potential impact on traditional media outlets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. Company Receives $2.6 Million to Relinquish Oil Lease on Sacred Native American Land&lt;br&gt;- A company has received $2.6 million to give up its oil lease on land in Montana that is considered sacred to Native Americans.&lt;br&gt;- The decision is seen as a victory for indigenous communities and their efforts to protect their cultural and environmental heritage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: This case highlights the ongoing conflicts between resource extraction and indigenous rights, emphasizing the importance of respecting sacred lands.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. Former Harrods Owner Mohamed Al Fayed Passes Away&lt;br&gt;- Mohamed Al Fayed, the former owner of Harrods and father of Dodi Al Fayed, who died in a car crash with Princess Diana, has died at the age of 94.&lt;br&gt;- Al Fayed was a prominent figure in the business and luxury retail industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: The passing of Mohamed Al Fayed marks the end of an era and reflects the legacy he leaves behind in the world of business and retail.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. Cable Dispute Leaves Millions of Subscribers in the Dark&lt;br&gt;- A dispute between Disney and cable providers has left millions of subscribers without access to sports events and other programming.&lt;br&gt;- The disagreement over contract terms has resulted in a blackout for cable subscribers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: This situation highlights the challenges and frustrations faced by consumers when disputes between media companies affect their access to content.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The fashion industry continues to grapple with issues of systemic racism, emphasizing the need for companies to address diversity and inclusion.&lt;br&gt;- Parental concerns regarding smartphone usage for children reflect the importance of responsible guidelines and education.&lt;br&gt;- Augmented reality gaming experiences are gaining popularity, merging virtual and real-world elements.&lt;br&gt;- The affordability of smart home security services may be impacted by price increases.&lt;br&gt;- AI translations are becoming more prevalent, potentially impacting traditional media outlets.&lt;br&gt;- Indigenous rights and the protection of sacred lands remain important issues in resource extraction.&lt;br&gt;- The passing of prominent figures in business and retail marks the end of eras and leaves behind legacies.&lt;br&gt;- Disputes between media companies can disrupt access to content for cable subscribers.</summary></entry></feed>