<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-20T20:01:04Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 20 Aug 2023 20:01:04</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-20T20:01:04Z</published><updated>2023-08-20T20:01:04Z</updated><id>bba1a2cb-69f7-4e3d-8d7a-2cceb2a4a8b9</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- US court denies AI image copyright, but this ruling means little&lt;br&gt;- Lamborghini's first electric car is a badass 4-seater with over 1,000 horsepower&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk admits X 'may fail, as so many have predicted'&lt;br&gt;- Researchers at Stanford Crack The Code of Natural Vision As New Model Reveals How Eyes Decode Visual Scene&lt;br&gt;- Seamlessly Integrating AWS S3 Static Web Hosting with CloudFront and DNS Configuration: An In-Depth Guide&lt;br&gt;- Denon PerL Pro Earbuds With Customized Hearing And Exceptional Spatial Audio&lt;br&gt;- An artist used AI to put Barbie in the internet's weirdest memes and moments &amp;mdash; check out the darkly subversive images&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI Just Bought a Game Studio Working on a "Minecraft" Clone&lt;br&gt;- Apple Vision Pro’s hand tracking: a big mistake, or the future of gaming?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- A $49,000 monthly student-loan bill and incomplete debt relief: Borrowers are facing confusion as repayment looms&lt;br&gt;- Gov. Ron DeSantis angers Trump supporters suggesting they are 'listless vessels' &amp;ndash; echoes Clinton's 'deplorables' jab, they say&lt;br&gt;- The dedollarization drive is facing a confidence crisis as the yuan, ruble and Argentine peso simultaneously plummet, an analyst says&lt;br&gt;- 'Slum' landlord stuffed 40 tenants into a 4-bed house, making $450,000&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Russia's attempt to land on the moon for the first time in almost half a century ended in disaster&lt;br&gt;- Oz eyes UK online bill in fight with tech over encryption &amp; child safety&lt;br&gt;- This AI Paper Aims to Transfer the Hand Motion Semantics Amongst Avatars Based on Each of their Hand Models&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Remote workers are falling behind in one major way: They're forgetting how to hang out with people&lt;br&gt;- The biggest threat to the dollar is the US itself, top economist Benn Steil warns&lt;br&gt;- The best time to send an email is Sunday at 3:00 p.m, a survey found, but experts warn this could be a form of 'techno-invasion'&lt;br&gt;- 30 years on, Debian is at the heart of the most successful Linux distros&lt;br&gt;- This new immersive exhibit honors 50 years of hip hop with a ‘visual mixtape’&lt;br&gt;- A simple playbook for new managers (or anyone who wants to improve their leadership)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The report covers various topics in the tech, business, and AI sectors. Key points include the denial of AI image copyright by a US court, the introduction of Lamborghini's first electric car, and Elon Musk's admission of potential failure. Insights highlight the challenges faced by remote workers in social interactions and the threat to the dollar. Additionally, the report explores the best time to send emails and the success of Debian in the Linux distro market. The report concludes with an immersive exhibit honoring hip hop and a playbook for new managers.</summary></entry></feed>