<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2023-12-19T08:03:33Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 19 Dec 2023 08:03:33</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-19T08:03:33Z</published><updated>2023-12-19T08:03:33Z</updated><id>122018ab-e3d2-47f0-807a-cc12f24db9a7</id><summary type="html">In the world, there have been several notable events recently. The White House announced that Ukraine's next US weapons package will be the last before key funds run out, raising concerns about the country's defense capabilities. In the tech industry, a car dealership's decision to add an AI chatbot to its site resulted in unexpected chaos. Apple has also faced setbacks, as it will temporarily pause selling new versions of its Watch after losing a patent dispute. Meanwhile, the Internet Archive has appealed a court decision, claiming that the judge misapplied fair use factors. In other news, Pakistan's former prime minister is utilizing an AI voice clone to campaign from prison, raising questions about the intersection of technology and politics. Additionally, Xfinity disclosed a data breach without specifying the number of affected users, highlighting the ongoing issue of cybersecurity. On a lighter note, a Kickstarter campaign for a book called "A Sword of Gilded Embers" has gained attention, showcasing the power of crowdfunding. The National Forest Service took a humorous jab at Tesla after its Cybertruck got stuck in a forest, providing some lighthearted entertainment. In the realm of technology, ByteDance AI Research introduced StemGen, a deep learning model trained to generate music based on context. Purdue University has also played a role in fostering a "hard tech corridor" in the heartland, contributing to regional development. Furthermore, a personal reflection on finding old posts and chats from childhood evoked nostalgia and appreciation for one's younger self. In Brooklyn, a woman is renovating a family-owned brownstone that has been passed down for nearly a century, preserving its legacy. In the realm of finance, some student-loan borrowers now have an extended period to benefit from one of Biden's debt relief plans, but they must take action to avail themselves of this opportunity. The Middle East has experienced a surge in attacks on US forces, prompting calls for a firm response to deter further aggression. A former UK defense chief warned that Israel's destruction of Gaza will perpetuate conflict with Hamas for another 50 years, emphasizing the need for a peaceful resolution. In a surprising discovery, llama poop has been found to stimulate plant growth in a climate change-ravaged area of the Andes, offering a potential solution for barren landscapes. On a more mundane note, there are predictions of price hikes for eggs, urging consumers not to delay their purchases. In the legal realm, New York officials criticized former President Trump's behavior in a fraud trial, signaling potential trouble ahead. Apple also experienced a setback as it lost one of the last remaining designers from the Jony Ive era, raising questions about the company's future design direction. In the financial market, exuberant investors are eagerly awaiting a "soft landing," indicating a potential bubble. Online luxury retailer Farfetch secured a last-minute $500 million investment, highlighting the competitive nature of the industry. In scientific research, a study on mice revealed that the effects of alcohol on sperm can persist for over a month after cessation, shedding light on the long-term consequences of alcohol consumption. Google AI proposed PixelLLM, a model capable of fine-grained localization and vision-language alignment, showcasing advancements in artificial intelligence. Lastly, a tearful Trevor Milton, the founder of Nikola, was sentenced to four years in prison in a fraud case, underscoring the consequences of corporate misconduct. These events reflect the diverse and ever-changing landscape of the world we live in.</summary></entry></feed>