<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2023-12-12T20:02:45Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 12 Dec 2023 20:02:45</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-12T20:02:45Z</published><updated>2023-12-12T20:02:45Z</updated><id>4b9626b1-7074-402c-b257-02f73d7c08a0</id><summary type="html">In the world today, there are various news stories making headlines. One concerning topic is the fear of humans losing control of artificial intelligence (AI), as expressed by a chip-company boss. The potential consequences of this scenario keep him up at night. On a different note, a millennial with a disability had hoped that becoming a Lyft driver would provide her with financial freedom. However, after seven years, she is struggling to make ends meet. In the entertainment industry, celebrities Amy Poehler and Michael B. Jordan have shared career advice specifically targeted towards Generation Z. They aim to guide and inspire the younger generation in their professional journeys. As the concept of hybrid work gains popularity, experts suggest that the ideal balance could be spending two days in the office and the rest working from home. This arrangement aims to maximize productivity and flexibility. Unfortunately, giant food companies have been quietly altering beloved snacks, hoping consumers won't notice. This revelation raises concerns about the quality and authenticity of these products. In a recent incident, a California restaurant owner claimed that a group of diners left fake $100 bills and left before their server could verify the money. This highlights the issue of fraudulent activities in the hospitality industry. Moving on to personal experiences, an individual shares their contrasting educational experiences in the United States and Japan. While Japan provided a strong sense of community, the US taught them the importance of having independent opinions. Shifting focus to the corporate world, the author discusses their internships at HRT and SIG, shedding light on the qualities top quant trading firms seek in potential employees. In China, the rapid rise of PDD prompts billionaire Richard Liu to call for change at JD.com, emphasizing the need for adaptation and innovation. In the entertainment industry, AI is expected to have a transformative impact, revolutionizing Hollywood in a positive way. However, it is important to note that this transformation will not resemble a horror story. In the healthcare sector, representatives propose a ban on insurers charging doctors a fee for electronic payments, aiming to streamline the payment process and reduce financial burdens on medical professionals. Unfortunately, a researcher who warned against unnecessary and risky vascular procedures faced severe backlash, including being labeled a "Nazi" and accused of "fratricide." This incident highlights the challenges faced by those who advocate for patient safety. Furthermore, it is revealed that thousands of patients may be undergoing vascular procedures prematurely or unnecessarily, raising concerns about the appropriateness of medical interventions. In the field of cancer research, a study explores the effect of chemotherapy on urinary volatile biomarkers for lung cancer. The findings provide valuable insights into potential diagnostic methods. Shifting gears to the business sector, John Wiley &amp; Sons releases its earnings guidance for FY 2024, providing investors with important financial information. Additionally, an individual reflects on their experience of benefiting from "pretty privilege" in corporate America, questioning whether the advantages outweigh the potential drawbacks. Another individual shares their journey of earning $200K a year without a college degree, having tested out 28 different jobs. They provide valuable lessons learned from their job-hopping experiences. In the realm of office attendance tracking, bosses employ various methods, such as under-desk sensors and badge swipes, to monitor employees' presence in the workplace. The use of technology raises questions about privacy and surveillance. Comparing AI models, the author asks ChatGPT and Google's Gemini to answer 10 questions. While Gemini demonstrates an edge in current events, it is not without its flaws. Geopolitical concerns and the actions of bad actors are identified as the stock market's top fear as we enter 2024. The potential impact of global events on financial markets is a significant concern. Former Yahoo CEO Marissa Mayer expresses her desire to embrace the AI race and associated risks in a responsible manner. She emphasizes the importance of ethical considerations in the development and implementation of AI technologies. In a peculiar incident, a 3D-printed home builder demolishes a house before its completion, raising questions about the reasons behind this unexpected action. On a different note, a fantasy computer called BF-SYS utilizes Brainfuck as its instruction set, showcasing unique technological advancements. Amazon introduces ElastiCache Serverless, a new option for instantly scaling cache capacity, providing users with increased flexibility and efficiency. Meta AI announces Purple Llama, a tool designed to assist the community in building ethical and generative AI models. This initiative aims to promote responsible AI development. Additionally, NexusRaven-V2, a 13B LLM, outperforms GPT-4 in zero-shot function calling and possesses the capability to convert natural language instructions into executable code. This advancement showcases the potential of AI in understanding and executing complex tasks. In the field of communication, a two-way free-space optics-based interface between fiber and 5G communication is being explored, utilizing polarization-orthogonal modulation. This innovation has the potential to enhance communication capabilities. Apple releases iOS 17.2, providing iPhone users with 12 new reasons to update their devices. The update introduces various features and improvements to enhance user experience. Lastly, in the educational AI race, Merlyn Mind focuses on classrooms rather than individual students, aiming to revolutionize the learning experience for students in educational settings.</summary></entry></feed>