<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2023-12-14T08:03:32Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 14 Dec 2023 08:03:32</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-14T08:03:32Z</published><updated>2023-12-14T08:03:32Z</updated><id>679dafd1-7b6d-4629-835c-5c0c9648ec59</id><summary type="html">In the world, there have been several significant events. Firstly, a resolution declaring that the presidents of Harvard and MIT should resign after recent antisemitism testimony was voted against by 125 Democrats. This decision has sparked controversy and debate. Additionally, President Biden has stated that the US will support Ukraine for as long as possible, marking a change in policy from "as long as it takes." On the political front, every single Republican voted to formalize an impeachment inquiry into President Joe Biden, including one who had previously been against it. In other news, the trial of Young Thug was paused due to a stabbing incident, adding another twist to the already complex case. Furthermore, the judge presiding over Trump's fraud trial was evacuated from the Manhattan courthouse soon after testimony ended, raising concerns for their safety. In the business world, the CEO of Wayfair informed employees that the company is profitable once again but warned them to expect long hours and a blending of work and personal life. A San Francisco tech founder is facing serious accusations of forcing his assistant into a "slave contract" and trafficking her for sex around the world. On a lighter note, the popular children's show "Cocomelon" has garnered immense viewership on Netflix, with kids watching over 600 million hours. In technology news, Microsoft PowerPoint for the web now has the capability to add videos with closed captions, enhancing accessibility. The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) has closed major loopholes used by businesses and scammers to send unwanted calls and texts, providing relief to consumers. Looking ahead, Amazon's CTO, Dr. Werner Vogels, has shared tech predictions for 2024 and beyond. In science-related developments, low-frequency sound has been found to be a potential indicator of an approaching tornado, while scientists are preparing to activate a computer designed to simulate the entire human brain. Lastly, Google researchers have unveiled a novel approach for auditing differentially private machine learning systems. These events highlight the diverse range of happenings in the world, spanning politics, technology, business, entertainment, and science.</summary></entry></feed>