<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-18T22:01:05Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 18 Aug 2023 22:01:05</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-18T22:01:05Z</published><updated>2023-08-18T22:01:05Z</updated><id>47ecac39-d34b-4c39-a987-c8e736e9512a</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Nvidia's H100 GPU is selling well with high profit margins.&lt;br&gt;- Luma AI has developed an iPhone app that turns videos into 3D flythroughs resembling professional drone footage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- The US Courseware Market is projected to grow to USD 1061.45 million.&lt;br&gt;- Michael Burry, known for his bet against the stock market in "The Big Short," is being criticized by a veteran analyst as a "one-trick pony."&lt;br&gt;- Disney heiress criticizes CEO Bob Iger for prioritizing money and power.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Google AI introduces STUDY, a socially aware-temporally causal recommender system for audiobooks in an educational setting.&lt;br&gt;- Unbabel unveils an AI project that aims to enable communication using thought alone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Financial planners warn about saving too much for retirement.&lt;br&gt;- Ukrainian soldiers defend their counteroffensive strategy.&lt;br&gt;- Vlad the Impaler, the inspiration behind Dracula, may have cried tears of blood.&lt;br&gt;- Amazon's low payment rate for influencers promoting its new shopping feed is being mocked on social media.&lt;br&gt;- Rudy Giuliani complains about being prosecuted using the RICO laws he pioneered.&lt;br&gt;- Firefox 117 Beta 8 is compared to Google Chrome 116 in terms of Linux browser performance.&lt;br&gt;- Facebook is fined $100,000 per day in Norway for violating privacy rights.&lt;br&gt;- Climate tech startups are benefiting from the IRA.&lt;br&gt;- Background processing in Android with WorkManager is discussed.&lt;br&gt;- Node.js scheduled queue jobs processing with BullMQ and Redis on Heroku is explained.&lt;br&gt;- DPGA improves its online presence with a website revamp and on-demand CI/CD pipeline.&lt;br&gt;- Hurricane Hilary and the busy Atlantic Basin are highlighted as things to watch.&lt;br&gt;- The shortage of AI engineers is discussed.&lt;br&gt;- LG unveils the new 'Magnit' Micro LED Screen with Bang &amp; Olufsen speakers.&lt;br&gt;- Smart manufacturing focuses on work instructions, metrics, and error-proofing.&lt;br&gt;- Bitcoin's price drop is attributed to SpaceX and Elon Musk.&lt;br&gt;- Americans are depleting their excess savings, according to a Fed study.&lt;br&gt;- A live stream of the Women's World Cup Final between England and Spain is available.&lt;br&gt;- A driverless car in San Francisco gets stuck in wet concrete after mistaking it for a regular road.&lt;br&gt;- VinFast's shares plummet after its market debut.&lt;br&gt;- A rare Ferrari 250 GTO is expected to be auctioned for $60 million.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;- Nvidia's H100 GPU and Luma AI's iPhone app are successful in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- The US Courseware Market shows potential for growth.&lt;br&gt;- Michael Burry's bet against the stock market is criticized.&lt;br&gt;- Financial planners warn about saving too much for retirement.&lt;br&gt;- Disney heiress criticizes CEO Bob Iger.&lt;br&gt;- Various topics related to AI are discussed, including Google AI's STUDY and Unbabel's thought communication project.&lt;br&gt;- Insights are provided on a range of topics, from Ukrainian soldiers' counteroffensive strategy to the value of Bitcoin dropping.&lt;br&gt;- The report concludes with a summary of the overall insights gathered.</summary></entry></feed>