<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-18T16:01:16Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 18 Aug 2023 16:01:16</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-18T16:01:16Z</published><updated>2023-08-18T16:01:16Z</updated><id>eb9ee27a-1acc-428b-bd42-972a0573ba3c</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. "Saccharopolyspora oryzae sp. nov., isolated from rhizosphere soil of ..." - Nature.com: This article discusses the discovery of a new species of bacteria found in the soil. Key points include the isolation of the bacteria from the rhizosphere soil and its classification as a new species.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "ESP32 Standard Library Embedded Rust: Analog Temperature Sensing using the ADC": This article explains how to use the ESP32 microcontroller's standard library in the Rust programming language to sense analog temperature using the ADC. Key points include the steps involved in implementing the temperature sensing and the benefits of using Rust for embedded development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. "The Kremlin's top brass are trying to pass the buck over the ruble's collapse. This rare public infighting shows just how precarious Russia's wartime economy is.": This article discusses the economic challenges faced by Russia and the infighting within the Kremlin regarding the collapse of the ruble. Key points include the precarious state of Russia's wartime economy and the political implications of the infighting.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "Unlocking Success: The Top 5 Benefits of Engaging a Dedicated Development Team for Your Upcoming Project": This article highlights the advantages of hiring a dedicated development team for project success. Key points include improved efficiency, expertise, cost-effectiveness, flexibility, and reduced time to market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. "Alex Graves’s Team Latest Work, Bayesian Flow Networks Address Discrete Data Generation Issues": This article showcases the latest work by Alex Graves's team on Bayesian flow networks and their application in addressing discrete data generation issues. Key points include the use of Bayesian methods, the challenges in generating discrete data, and the potential impact of this research on AI development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "Sparse Models, The Math, And A New Theory For Ground-Breaking AI": This article explores the concept of sparse models in AI and their mathematical foundations. Key points include the advantages of sparse models, the mathematical principles behind them, and the potential for groundbreaking advancements in AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section focuses on scientific discoveries and advancements in technology, highlighting the importance of research and development in various fields.&lt;br&gt;- The business section delves into economic challenges and the benefits of strategic decision-making for companies.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section showcases the latest research and theories in artificial intelligence, emphasizing the potential for groundbreaking advancements in the field.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report highlights the interconnectedness of different disciplines and the importance of innovation and collaboration in driving progress.</summary></entry></feed>