<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-23T08:03:31Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 23 Jan 2024 08:03:31</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-23T08:03:31Z</published><updated>2024-01-23T08:03:31Z</updated><id>24a128a5-f2ca-41c0-8208-7dbc430c0a13</id><summary type="html">In the world today, LG has introduced a new 32-inch 4K smart monitor that comes with built-in features like Netflix and Google Calendar. This innovative device aims to enhance the user experience by providing easy access to popular apps and scheduling tools. On another note, Apple's Vision Pro has only seen the development of 150 specific apps so far, highlighting the need for further expansion in this area. In the field of chemistry, a machine learning toolkit called PythiaCHEM has been designed to create data-driven predictive models, revolutionizing the way we approach chemical research. Additionally, a popular word game called 'Wordle' has released hints and clues for its 948th edition, challenging players to solve the puzzle. Unfortunately, we also mourn the loss of Dexter Scott King, who passed away from prostate cancer, shedding light on one of the most common forms of cancer. While a recent MIT study suggests that AI may not take over our jobs, it still leaves some uncertainty about the future impact of artificial intelligence. Furthermore, the size of a backlog is found to be inversely proportional to the frequency of customer interaction, emphasizing the importance of regular communication in managing tasks efficiently. In the entertainment industry, the sudden departure of the head of Netflix's movie studio raises questions about the reasons behind this significant change. Lastly, Sam Altman, a prominent figure in the tech industry, warns about the excessive energy consumption of AI and the need for a breakthrough energy source to sustain its growth.</summary></entry></feed>