<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-24T20:02:01Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 24 Nov 2023 20:02:01</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-24T20:02:01Z</published><updated>2023-11-24T20:02:01Z</updated><id>4d979c63-df90-40df-87ff-659d1054dcb0</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. OpenAI Saga: UNO Game and What it All Means For AI&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's UNO game showcases advancements in AI technology and its ability to learn and adapt in complex environments.&lt;br&gt;- The game demonstrates the potential for AI to improve decision-making and problem-solving capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Deepmind founder says his latest LLM Inflection-2 is the second best in the world&lt;br&gt;- Deepmind's LLM Inflection-2 is ranked as the second-best AI model globally.&lt;br&gt;- The model's performance highlights the progress made in natural language processing and understanding.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. I tried Microsoft's AI-powered assistant, Copilot. The tool helpfully attends meetings and summarizes emails, but it's best to treat it as a rookie intern.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's AI-powered assistant, Copilot, assists with meeting attendance and email summarization.&lt;br&gt;- While helpful, it is advised to consider Copilot as a beginner-level assistant.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. AIM WINNERS &amp; LOSERS: RUA Life Science slides after strong week - Morningstar&lt;br&gt;- RUA Life Science experiences a decline in performance after a strong week.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the volatility of the stock market and the importance of monitoring market trends.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Gavin Newsom's career in politics: How the multimillionaire restaurateur became the Democrats' candidate-in-waiting for the presidency&lt;br&gt;- Gavin Newsom's political career trajectory, from a successful restaurateur to a potential Democratic presidential candidate.&lt;br&gt;- This showcases the influence of personal background and achievements in political aspirations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Terry Gou, the founder of iPhone maker Foxconn, drops out of Taiwan's presidential election race&lt;br&gt;- Terry Gou, founder of Foxconn, withdraws from the Taiwan presidential election race.&lt;br&gt;- This decision has implications for the political landscape in Taiwan and the future leadership of the country.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. OpenAI Saga: UNO Game and What it All Means For AI&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's UNO game demonstrates the capabilities of AI in learning and adapting in complex environments.&lt;br&gt;- This showcases the potential for AI to enhance decision-making and problem-solving abilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Deepmind founder says his latest LLM Inflection-2 is the second best in the world&lt;br&gt;- Deepmind's LLM Inflection-2 ranks as the second-best AI model globally.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the advancements in natural language processing and understanding.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. 'Chessmaster' Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella was the true winner from the OpenAI fiasco, Wedbush analyst says&lt;br&gt;- Satya Nadella, Microsoft CEO, emerges as a winner in the OpenAI controversy.&lt;br&gt;- This suggests the strategic advantage gained by Microsoft in the AI industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The advancements in AI technology, as demonstrated by OpenAI and Deepmind, showcase the potential for AI to enhance decision-making and problem-solving capabilities.&lt;br&gt;- The volatility of the stock market, as seen in RUA Life Science's performance, emphasizes the importance of monitoring market trends.&lt;br&gt;- The career trajectories of Gavin Newsom and Terry Gou highlight the influence of personal background and achievements in political aspirations.&lt;br&gt;- Satya Nadella's strategic advantage in the AI industry signifies the importance of leadership in driving innovation and success.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report highlights the progress and impact of AI technology, the dynamics of the stock market, and the role of personal background in political careers.</summary></entry></feed>