<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-17T04:01:04Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 17 Aug 2023 04:01:04</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-17T04:01:04Z</published><updated>2023-08-17T04:01:04Z</updated><id>ce951d5e-a048-4567-80c5-3aa7c241bd9b</id><summary type="html">Report: Multilingual Insights on Tech, Business, and AI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Introduction:&lt;br&gt;This report compiles translated content from various languages, focusing on topics related to Tech, Business, and AI. The aim is to provide insights and key points within each category, followed by specific insights for each broader topic. The report concludes with a summary of the overall insights gathered.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Windows feature causing havoc: A Windows feature that resets system clocks based on random data is causing disruptions.&lt;br&gt;2. Skich app for mobile games: Skich, a discovery app, now allows users to launch and manage game downloads.&lt;br&gt;3. Migrating from WordPress to a headless CMS: A guide on migrating from WordPress to a headless CMS in three easy steps.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights on Tech: The tech industry faces challenges with system disruptions, but also offers solutions such as mobile game discovery apps and simplified content management systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Corporate capture of open-access publishing: The Chronicle of Higher Education highlights the issue of corporate influence in open-access publishing.&lt;br&gt;2. Commercial real estate lending decline: Commercial real estate lending has plunged by 53% due to a sector logjam.&lt;br&gt;3. Private equity groups and rising rents: Tenants warn of private equity groups raising rent and neglecting maintenance issues.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights on Business: The corporate capture of open-access publishing raises concerns about academic freedom. The decline in commercial real estate lending and rising rents pose challenges for the real estate sector.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. Generative AI spending in entertainment companies: 96% of entertainment companies are increasing their spending on generative AI.&lt;br&gt;2. Google's training data advantage: Google's vast training data could give Gemini an edge in the AI arms race.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights on AI: The entertainment industry is heavily investing in generative AI, while Google's training data gives it a competitive advantage in the AI field.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;1. Tech: The tech industry faces challenges with system disruptions but offers solutions for mobile game discovery and simplified content management.&lt;br&gt;2. Business: Concerns arise regarding corporate influence in open-access publishing, declining commercial real estate lending, and rising rents.&lt;br&gt;3. AI: The entertainment industry is investing in generative AI, and Google's training data gives it an advantage in the AI arms race.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report highlights the diverse insights gathered from various languages, providing a comprehensive overview of the current trends and challenges in the fields of Tech, Business, and AI.</summary></entry></feed>