<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-12T14:01:19Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 12 Aug 2023 14:01:19</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-12T14:01:19Z</published><updated>2023-08-12T14:01:19Z</updated><id>89ccf90e-b74d-42ae-825a-5748fbf3617f</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Imaging inside highly scattering media using hybrid deep learning&lt;br&gt;- Feel Risky to Train Your Language Model on Restricted Data? Meet SILO: A New Language Model that Manages Risk-Performance Tradeoffs During Inference&lt;br&gt;- If it can be designed on a computer, it can be built by robots&lt;br&gt;- Show HN: Open-source proxy server for Llama2, GPT-4, Claude2 with Logging, Cache&lt;br&gt;- Samsung Remote Test Lab: Run Emulated Samsung Phones from the Browser&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Hybrid deep learning techniques are being used to image inside highly scattering media, which can have applications in medical imaging and remote sensing.&lt;br&gt;- SILO is a new language model that aims to balance the tradeoff between risk and performance when training on restricted data.&lt;br&gt;- The open-source proxy server allows for testing and logging of various language models.&lt;br&gt;- Samsung's Remote Test Lab enables users to run emulated Samsung phones directly from their browser for testing purposes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Hybrid deep learning techniques have the potential to revolutionize imaging in challenging environments.&lt;br&gt;- SILO addresses the ethical concerns surrounding training language models on restricted data.&lt;br&gt;- Open-source tools like the proxy server and Remote Test Lab make it easier for developers to test and optimize their applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Zelenskyy fires recruitment officials for accepting $10,000 bribes to help Ukrainian men dodge the draft: 'bribery during war is treason'&lt;br&gt;- A former executive says he was fired by Salesforce after raising concerns about software said to process and organize customer data in milliseconds: 'It was all a lie.'&lt;br&gt;- Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez and House Democrats push Attorney General Merrick Garland to investigate Clarence Thomas' lavish gifts from billionaires&lt;br&gt;- The Biden Administration Will Spend $1.2 Billion On Two Projects That Remove CO2 From The Air&lt;br&gt;- Humans have pumped so much groundwater from the Earth that it's actually caused the planet's axis to shift, a new study found&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Corruption in recruitment processes can have severe consequences during times of war.&lt;br&gt;- The former executive alleges that Salesforce misrepresented the capabilities of their software, leading to his termination.&lt;br&gt;- Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez and House Democrats are calling for an investigation into Clarence Thomas' acceptance of gifts from billionaires.&lt;br&gt;- The Biden Administration is investing in projects aimed at removing CO2 from the air to combat climate change.&lt;br&gt;- Excessive groundwater extraction has had an unexpected impact on the Earth's axis.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Corruption in recruitment processes undermines the integrity of military operations.&lt;br&gt;- The allegations against Salesforce highlight the importance of transparency and accountability in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- The investigation into Clarence Thomas' gifts raises questions about potential conflicts of interest among public officials.&lt;br&gt;- The Biden Administration's investment in CO2 removal projects demonstrates a commitment to addressing climate change.&lt;br&gt;- The study on groundwater extraction highlights the unintended consequences of human activities on the Earth's systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Feel Risky to Train Your Language Model on Restricted Data? Meet SILO: A New Language Model that Manages Risk-Performance Tradeoffs During Inference&lt;br&gt;- If it can be designed on a computer, it can be built by robots&lt;br&gt;- Show HN: Open-source proxy server for Llama2, GPT-4, Claude2 with Logging, Cache&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- SILO is a language model that aims to manage the tradeoff between risk and performance when training on restricted data.&lt;br&gt;- The development of robots capable of building computer-designed structures is advancing.&lt;br&gt;- The open-source proxy server allows for testing and logging of various language models.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- SILO addresses the ethical concerns surrounding training language models on restricted data.&lt;br&gt;- The advancement of robotics in construction has the potential to revolutionize the industry.&lt;br&gt;- Open-source tools like the proxy server make it easier for developers to test and optimize language models.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of insights:&lt;br&gt;- Hybrid deep learning techniques have the potential to revolutionize imaging in challenging environments.&lt;br&gt;- SILO addresses the ethical concerns surrounding training language models on restricted data.&lt;br&gt;- Corruption in recruitment processes undermines the integrity of military operations.&lt;br&gt;- The allegations against Salesforce highlight the importance of transparency and accountability in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- The investigation into Clarence Thomas' gifts raises questions about potential conflicts of interest among public officials.&lt;br&gt;- The Biden Administration's investment in CO2 removal projects demonstrates a commitment to addressing climate change.&lt;br&gt;- The study on groundwater extraction highlights the unintended consequences of human activities on the Earth's systems.&lt;br&gt;- The advancement of robotics in construction has the potential to revolutionize the industry.&lt;br&gt;- Open-source tools like the proxy server make it easier for developers to test and optimize language models.</summary></entry></feed>