<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-11T20:03:18Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 11 Dec 2023 20:03:18</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-11T20:03:18Z</published><updated>2023-12-11T20:03:18Z</updated><id>6ee08016-47b9-4cb0-9d27-7d1b98544244</id><summary type="html">In recent news, there have been several significant events happening around the world. One notable development is the advancement in commingled human remains analysis between 2014 and 2023, as reported by John Wiley. Additionally, John Wiley &amp; Sons released their fiscal Q2 earnings snapshot, providing insights into their financial performance. On a more concerning note, it appears that Russia has initiated a massive missile barrage on Ukraine, which they had been saving up for. This escalation of tensions is a cause for global concern. In the tech world, Apple has shut down an app that allowed Android users to send blue-bubble texts to iPhones. Furthermore, an embarrassing incident occurred during a livestream involving Vivek Ramaswamy, Elon Musk, Alex Jones, and thousands of others, as Ramaswamy forgot to mute himself while using the restroom. On a different note, a Gen Xer making a substantial income has shared their secret of working three jobs to retire early, along with two strategies for getting away with it. The impact of the ongoing conflict in Ukraine is also affecting plane safety incidents in Russia, as airlines struggle to obtain spare parts due to sanctions. In the realm of technology, Android Studio Hedgehog has upgraded to IntelliJ 2023.1, enhancing the developer experience. Additionally, there are six open-source libraries recommended for achieving AI mastery before 2024. Moving on, Owen introduces a cool open-source low-code tool that his team has been developing for the past two years. In the world of programming, there is a discussion on the differences between "require" and "import" in JavaScript and how it can enhance code for the future. Shifting gears, the prevention of the deadliest gynecological cancer is highlighted, emphasizing the importance of removing multiple organs. The EU AI Act is also a topic of discussion, as its agreement was challenging to reach. In the realm of design, the construction of a massive ship called Charybdis, designed to transport wind turbines to the ocean, is explored. Apple's commitment to clean energy is also highlighted, as they have convinced over 300 suppliers in 28 countries to adopt sustainable practices. On a more concerning note, a notorious gun shop linked to hundreds of guns in Chicago is investigated. In personal stories, a Gen Zer shares their decision to leave Texas in search of acceptance and peace of mind, citing the need for the state to address its issues before encouraging others to live there. Argentina's president, Javier Milei, warns the country to prepare for a painful economic shock due to the reliance on the dollar. In the tech industry, Elon Musk expresses his desire for Ilya Sutskever from OpenAI to join him at xAI. The founder of Panera suggests that employees today are not motivated solely by making money for shareholders, highlighting a shift in priorities. In the programming world, the number of lines of code required to execute a simple addition in Python is discussed. Power Apps provides guidance on uploading images for barcode, MRZ, and document detection. The impact of team design on business efficiency is explored, along with strategies to address the five dysfunctions of a team. Additionally, the interaction between Scala and Kotlin in building user-friendly DSLs is examined. Government agencies are encouraged to accelerate their digital journey to empower citizens. Lastly, a guide for successful client assessments and discoveries is provided, focusing on the importance of understanding people. These are just a few of the many events happening around the world, showcasing the diverse range of topics and issues that are shaping our global landscape.</summary></entry></feed>