<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-24T08:03:34Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 24 Sep 2023 08:03:34</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-24T08:03:34Z</published><updated>2023-09-24T08:03:34Z</updated><id>4f691bcd-50c4-44f6-b8d9-a33f086b7973</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- California governor vetoes a bill requiring humans in autonomous big rigs&lt;br&gt;- Mastering Asynchronous Programming in JavaScript: Unraveling the Magic of async/await, Promises, and More&lt;br&gt;- Viral Photo Of Sen. Rand Paul Wearing Bathrobe Actually AI Fake&lt;br&gt;- These are the Must-Have New Camera Features of the New Google Pixel 8&lt;br&gt;- Here is How the AI Features in the New Edge Browser Can Help You Do Better&lt;br&gt;- How to Setup Tailwind CSS in React JS with VS Code&lt;br&gt;- Project Gutenberg has implemented one of the worst AI fears of striking actors&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk threatens to charge for X, OpenAI launches DALL-E 3 and Cisco acquires Splunk&lt;br&gt;- Building a Workout Tracker Web App with React and Docker Part 1&lt;br&gt;- AndShare CMS: A new age of content curation, development, and syndication&lt;br&gt;- The Google Pixel 8’s latest leak shows off big AI camera updates&lt;br&gt;- I tried the new Coke flavor made with AI. I was surprised by the taste.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Bob Menendez is rejecting the wave of calls for him to resign after his federal indictment, arguing that 'some are rushing to judge a Latino and push him out of his seat'&lt;br&gt;- Fetterman becomes first Democratic senator to demand Bob Menendez resign over corruption charges&lt;br&gt;- Bob Menendez' political future is in serious peril after he gets a major primary challenger in Rep. Andy Kim after his indictment on bribery charges&lt;br&gt;- A class-action lawsuit aims to force United Airlines to reimburse the baggage fees for the luggage they lose&lt;br&gt;- The housing market is about to take a hit as student loan payments restart&lt;br&gt;- SHAREHOLDER ALERT: Pomerantz Law Firm Investigates Claims ... - PR Newswire&lt;br&gt;- Lachlan Murdoch backs Fox board role for former Australian PM who called climate change science 'absolute crap'&lt;br&gt;- Feds open investigation into major American chicken companies over use of child labor&lt;br&gt;- The era of America’s subminimum wage for tipped restaurant workers may be ending&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Viral Photo Of Sen. Rand Paul Wearing Bathrobe Actually AI Fake&lt;br&gt;- Project Gutenberg has implemented one of the worst AI fears of striking actors&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk threatens to charge for X, OpenAI launches DALL-E 3 and Cisco acquires Splunk&lt;br&gt;- The Google Pixel 8’s latest leak shows off big AI camera updates&lt;br&gt;- I tried the new Coke flavor made with AI. I was surprised by the taste.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The California governor vetoing a bill requiring humans in autonomous big rigs highlights the ongoing debate and challenges surrounding the adoption of autonomous vehicles in the transportation industry.&lt;br&gt;- The advancements in asynchronous programming in JavaScript, as well as the integration of AI features in various technologies, demonstrate the continuous evolution and innovation in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- The controversies surrounding political figures, such as Bob Menendez, and the legal actions against major companies, like United Airlines and American chicken companies, shed light on the importance of accountability and ethical practices in the business world.&lt;br&gt;- The potential impact of student loan payments restarting on the housing market suggests a need for careful consideration and support for individuals facing financial challenges.&lt;br&gt;- The implementation of AI in various fields, including content curation, development, and syndication, raises concerns and fears about the potential consequences and implications of relying heavily on AI technologies.&lt;br&gt;- The interest and excitement surrounding new AI camera features and products, such as the Google Pixel 8 and the AI-made Coke flavor, indicate the growing fascination and integration of AI in everyday life.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report highlights the intersection of technology, business, and AI, showcasing both the advancements and challenges in these areas. It emphasizes the importance of responsible and ethical practices, as well as the need for continuous innovation and adaptation in a rapidly evolving world.</summary></entry></feed>