<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-22T08:03:37Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 22 Sep 2023 08:03:37</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-22T08:03:37Z</published><updated>2023-09-22T08:03:37Z</updated><id>b5347048-8e15-41e6-bca2-55ef585585e3</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- You Are Holding It Wrong 2: Apple Confirms Finger Smudge Marks on Titanium iPhone 15 Pro Only Temporary&lt;br&gt;   - Key point: Apple confirms that finger smudge marks on the Titanium iPhone 15 Pro are only temporary.&lt;br&gt;   - Insight: This reassures users that the smudge marks are not permanent and can be easily wiped off.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Elevate Your Typography: Adding Custom Fonts in Next.js 13 with Tailwind CSS&lt;br&gt;   - Key point: Next.js 13 now allows users to add custom fonts to their typography with Tailwind CSS.&lt;br&gt;   - Insight: This feature enhances the design options for developers and improves the overall user experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Katie Haun believes now is a good time to invest in crypto&lt;br&gt;   - Key point: Katie Haun, a prominent figure in the crypto industry, believes that now is a favorable time to invest in cryptocurrencies.&lt;br&gt;   - Insight: This endorsement from a respected individual in the industry may influence more people to consider investing in crypto.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- And the winner of Startup Battlefield at Disrupt 2023 is… BioticsAI&lt;br&gt;   - Key point: BioticsAI emerges as the winner of the Startup Battlefield competition at Disrupt 2023.&lt;br&gt;   - Insight: This recognition highlights the potential and innovation of BioticsAI, positioning them as a promising startup in the industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Factors Assessing Science’s Self-Presentation model and their effect on conservatives’ and liberals’ support for funding science&lt;br&gt;   - Key point: A study examines the factors that influence conservatives' and liberals' support for funding science based on Science's Self-Presentation model.&lt;br&gt;   - Insight: Understanding these factors can help bridge the gap between different political ideologies and promote bipartisan support for scientific research.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- An inference model gives insights into innate immune adaptation and repertoire diversity&lt;br&gt;   - Key point: An inference model provides insights into the innate immune system's adaptation and diversity.&lt;br&gt;   - Insight: This research contributes to a better understanding of the immune system and its potential applications in healthcare and disease prevention.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The temporary nature of finger smudge marks on the Titanium iPhone 15 Pro reassures users about the device's durability and aesthetics.&lt;br&gt;- The addition of custom fonts in Next.js 13 with Tailwind CSS enhances design options for developers and improves user experience.&lt;br&gt;- Katie Haun's endorsement of investing in crypto may encourage more individuals to enter the cryptocurrency market.&lt;br&gt;- BioticsAI's victory in the Startup Battlefield competition highlights their potential as an innovative startup.&lt;br&gt;- Understanding the factors that influence support for funding science can help bridge political divides and promote scientific research.&lt;br&gt;- The inference model for innate immune adaptation contributes to a better understanding of the immune system's diversity and potential applications.&lt;br&gt;</summary></entry></feed>