<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-13T20:02:13Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 13 Oct 2023 20:02:13</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-13T20:02:13Z</published><updated>2023-10-13T20:02:13Z</updated><id>79e2fa7b-29a7-448b-ad26-94bb4deb5e5b</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- The MCRA platform for EU regulatory actions: governance, user ... - EFSA news&lt;br&gt;- Wiley in India Introduces Online Mock Tests in Hindi for UPSC's ... - Press Trust of India&lt;br&gt;- Hackers infiltrated Israeli smart billboards to post pro-Hamas messages, reports say&lt;br&gt;- Retailers are using a simple mind trick on you to make their discounts seem bigger than they are&lt;br&gt;- Presentation: The Commoditization of the Software Stack: How Application-first Cloud Services are Changing the Game&lt;br&gt;- Durable Execution for Control Planes: Sergey Bykov at QCon San Francisco&lt;br&gt;- The cult of Obsidian: Why people are obsessed with the note-taking app&lt;br&gt;- While Amazon is under fire, its doorbell brand is offering $1 million for proof of aliens&lt;br&gt;- Meta made its Llama 2 AI model open-source because 'Zuck has balls,' a former top Facebook engineer says&lt;br&gt;- Google tests adding a Discover Feed to its valuable desktop homepage&lt;br&gt;- Tradeshift co-founder accused of sexual assault by company, allegations he denies&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- I did 4 things to pay for college as a first-generation, low-income student&lt;br&gt;- McDonald's is donating thousands of free meals to the Israel Defence Forces and citizens after Hamas attacks&lt;br&gt;- CEOs condemn Hamas attacks and express support for Israel in messages to employees&lt;br&gt;- How US tax dollars have supported Israel and its military for 75 years &amp;mdash; and what's next for American aid&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage Interest Rates Today, October 13, 2023 | Rates Are Cooling, but Will it Last?&lt;br&gt;- There's now a 50% chance of world war as the Israel-Hamas conflict threatens to spread, hedge fund legend Ray Dalio says&lt;br&gt;- Israeli startup founders go to war: 'We're fighting for our home.'&lt;br&gt;- China still can't beat deflation as its economy continues to flounder&lt;br&gt;- Some Walmart employees say customers are getting hostile at self-checkout &amp;mdash; and they blame anti-theft tech&lt;br&gt;- Legislation to Support Stillbirth Prevention Heads to House After Unanimous Senate Approval&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Jeremy Grantham and Bill Gross have warned stocks are overvalued. Wharton professor Jeremy Siegel disagrees: "They are underpriced"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Over half of pet owners don’t want vaccines for their dogs&lt;br&gt;- Who is Sam Wrench, director of Taylor Swift’s Eras tour movie?&lt;br&gt;- How Local Projects translated the horrors of the Holocaust into a kid-friendly museum experience&lt;br&gt;- Go in the Devil's Name: When Isobel Gowdie Confessed to Being a Witch&lt;br&gt;- Cricket-mad India is hosting the World Cup &amp;ndash; and tickets are reselling at astronomical prices&lt;br&gt;- I'll never regret living in Europe after giving birth. I got way better maternity leave and my American friends envied me.&lt;br&gt;- Vomit fees are being added to some restaurant brunch bills. Be careful with those bottomless mimosas!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section covers a range of topics including cybersecurity, software development, and AI. It highlights the advancements and challenges in these areas.&lt;br&gt;- The business section focuses on financial matters, international conflicts, and the impact of policies on various industries.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section presents contrasting opinions on the stock market, showcasing the diversity of perspectives in the field.&lt;br&gt;- The other section includes diverse topics such as pet care, entertainment, historical events, and cultural experiences.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report provides a snapshot of current news and trends across different sectors, highlighting the interconnectedness of technology, business, and society.</summary></entry></feed>