<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-29T20:02:06Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 29 Aug 2023 20:02:06</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-29T20:02:06Z</published><updated>2023-08-29T20:02:06Z</updated><id>62a20854-0a8f-4b6c-85fd-9b9f9ccb6cde</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Inside Citadel's $19,000-a-month summer internship, where interns are taught how to schmooze and are judged on the length of their emails&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's Tesla almost ran a red light during a FSD demo, video shows&lt;br&gt;- 4 ways to show customers they can trust your generative AI enterprise tool&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from UCL and Google Propose AudioSlots: A Slot-Centric Generative Model For Audio Domain Blind Source Separation&lt;br&gt;- Google Launches Three New Cloud Storage Options: Cloud Storage FUSE, Parallelstore, NetApp Volumes&lt;br&gt;- What's new in LiveG OS V0.2.0: multiplatform support and plenty more&lt;br&gt;- How to get ChatGPT to write you a killer cover letter that doesn't sound like it was AI-generated: step-by-step guide with exact prompts&lt;br&gt;- Tech stocks will start rallying again soon thanks to the AI 'tidal wave', Wedbush says&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Audiobooks for Kids Market 2023: Comprehensive Study by Top Key ... - The Knox Student&lt;br&gt;- Children's Picture Book Market to Witness Growth Acceleration ... - The Knox Student&lt;br&gt;- There could be even tougher times ahead for China's economy, as forecasters slash their growth predictions&lt;br&gt;- The wild life of billionaire Twitter co-founder Jack Dorsey, who is known for eccentricities like eating one meal a day, and taking ice baths&lt;br&gt;- 2 millennials who have bought a combined 22 properties with friends and family explain how they got into real estate without waiting on a spouse&lt;br&gt;- The hype around Vinfast made it the third-most valuable carmaker in the world&lt;br&gt;- These are 4 of the most common work mistakes. Here’s how to use them to your advantage&lt;br&gt;- Caraway wooed us with beautiful pans. Now it’s coming for the rest of the kitchen&lt;br&gt;- The 45-year history of The Cheesecake Factory: How a family bakery turned into global restaurant chain with an enormous menu&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- 4 ways to show customers they can trust your generative AI enterprise tool&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from UCL and Google Propose AudioSlots: A Slot-Centric Generative Model For Audio Domain Blind Source Separation&lt;br&gt;- Tech stocks will start rallying again soon thanks to the AI 'tidal wave', Wedbush says&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is constantly evolving, with new developments in AI, cloud storage, and generative models. Trust and reliability are key factors in gaining customer confidence.&lt;br&gt;- The business landscape is diverse, with markets for audiobooks, children's picture books, real estate, and carmakers experiencing growth and challenges. The personal lives of influential figures like Jack Dorsey also attract attention.&lt;br&gt;- China's economy and its efforts to incentivize marriage and childbirth are areas of concern. Forecasters predict tougher times ahead for the country's economy.&lt;br&gt;- The Cheesecake Factory's success story highlights the transformation of a family bakery into a global restaurant chain.</summary></entry></feed>