<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-13T08:03:52Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 13 Oct 2023 08:03:52</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-13T08:03:52Z</published><updated>2023-10-13T08:03:52Z</updated><id>4116452c-70a9-4f51-a3fb-2e3408dcb4d2</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Ukraine's 'free-spirited use' of anti-tank missiles is wrecking Russian armor, but it doesn't mean the tank's days are over:&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine's unconventional use of anti-tank missiles is proving effective against Russian armor.&lt;br&gt;- However, this does not imply that tanks are becoming obsolete in warfare.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Elon Musk has custody of son X despite mother Grimes' objections, court doc says:&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk has been granted custody of his son X, despite objections from the child's mother, Grimes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. What is a forbearance? How mortgage forbearance can help you keep your home:&lt;br&gt;- Explains the concept of forbearance and how it can assist homeowners in retaining their properties.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Aside from the fraud, Donald Trump was a very well-behaved borrower, Deutsche Bank testimony shows:&lt;br&gt;- Deutsche Bank's testimony reveals that Donald Trump was a responsible borrower, aside from the fraud allegations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Why Microsoft’s $29 billion tax bill could be the knockout punch in a decade-long fight with the IRS:&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's substantial tax bill may mark the end of a lengthy battle with the IRS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Ford’s joint EV battery venture increases wages at planned factories amid UAW strike:&lt;br&gt;- Ford's collaboration in the electric vehicle battery sector leads to wage increases at upcoming factories, amidst a strike by the UAW.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. No Fakes Act wants to protect actors and singers from unauthorized AI replicas:&lt;br&gt;- The No Fakes Act aims to safeguard performers from unauthorized AI replicas.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Google promises to take the legal heat in users’ AI copyright lawsuits:&lt;br&gt;- Google assures users that it will handle the legal repercussions in copyright lawsuits involving AI-generated content.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. No Fakes Act wants to protect actors and singers from unauthorized AI replicas:&lt;br&gt;- The No Fakes Act seeks to shield actors and singers from unauthorized AI replicas.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The use of anti-tank missiles by Ukraine showcases the evolving nature of warfare, but tanks still hold significance.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's custody battle highlights personal disputes amidst high-profile individuals.&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage forbearance can be a helpful tool for homeowners facing financial difficulties.&lt;br&gt;- Despite allegations of fraud, Donald Trump maintained a responsible borrowing record.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's substantial tax bill may have significant implications for their ongoing dispute with the IRS.&lt;br&gt;- Ford's joint venture in the EV battery sector contributes to resolving labor disputes through wage increases.&lt;br&gt;- The No Fakes Act reflects the need to protect performers from unauthorized AI replicas.&lt;br&gt;- Google's commitment to handling AI copyright lawsuits demonstrates their responsibility as a platform.&lt;br&gt;- The report emphasizes the importance of safeguarding actors and singers from unauthorized AI replicas.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The report covers various topics such as the use of anti-tank missiles in warfare, Elon Musk's custody battle, mortgage forbearance, Donald Trump's borrowing behavior, Microsoft's tax bill, Ford's EV battery venture, the No Fakes Act, and Google's commitment to handling AI copyright lawsuits. These insights highlight the evolving nature of warfare, personal disputes among high-profile individuals, financial assistance for homeowners, responsible borrowing practices, legal disputes, labor negotiations, and the importance of protecting performers from unauthorized AI replicas.</summary></entry></feed>