<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-18T12:01:27Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 18 Aug 2023 12:01:27</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-18T12:01:27Z</published><updated>2023-08-18T12:01:27Z</updated><id>e8191d96-9283-4ec6-89a0-89b9fe107cc2</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- How to implement a disk cache plugin for Elixir's Req HTTP client?&lt;br&gt;- Razer’s new BlackWidow V4 75 could be a great starter mechanical keyboard&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Lyft threatens to leave Minneapolis if the city raises the minimum wage for drivers&lt;br&gt;- China Evergrande, the world's most heavily indebted property developer, just filed for Chapter 15 bankruptcy protection&lt;br&gt;- New book considers the impact of electronic logging devices on drivers&lt;br&gt;- Amazon’s New Fee on Third-Party Sellers: A Strategic Move or Coercive Tactic?&lt;br&gt;- Parmigiano-Reggiano makers are putting edible microchips the size of a grain of sand into their 90-pound cheese wheels to combat counterfeiters&lt;br&gt;- US Courseware Market: Unlocking a USD 1061.45 Million Growth&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- The modern sea spider had started to diversify by the Jurassic, study finds&lt;br&gt;- New type of star gives clues to mysterious origin of magnetars&lt;br&gt;- Threads gets retweets — sorry, reposts — in the reverse-chronological feed&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- The generation that lived during/participated in the war and the ... - BMC Psychiatry&lt;br&gt;- Rudy Giuliani helped Purdue Pharma keep selling OxyContin. Here's the real story behind what's depicted in 'Painkiller.'&lt;br&gt;- Some former mobsters who were prosecuted by Rudy Giuliani are thrilled that the ex-Trump attorney got hit with RICO charges, mob lawyers say: report&lt;br&gt;- Today’s Wordle #790 Hints, Clues And Answer For Friday, August 18th&lt;br&gt;- This archive broadened access during the pandemic. Then ... - Fronteras: The Changing America Desk&lt;br&gt;- Why is RFK Jr.'s voice raspy? He has a neurological disorder called spasmodic dysphonia&lt;br&gt;- Cruise Robotaxi Drives Into Wet Concrete; Waymo Shows Off Same Route&lt;br&gt;- Blue Light Glasses May Not Help With Eye Strain Or Improve Sleep Quality, Study Says&lt;br&gt;- Some people say they're angry that UPS workers could make $170,000 including benefits. Members of Congress make more than that for working a lot less.&lt;br&gt;- The US is quietly warning its Middle East partners about the cost of stocking up on Chinese-made weapons&lt;br&gt;- When To See Saturn At Its Biggest, Brightest And Best This Week&lt;br&gt;- When To See Saturn At Its Biggest, Brightest And Best This Week&lt;br&gt;- An underwater landslide knocked out two critical submarine cables serving Africa&lt;br&gt;- One surviving Reddit app plans to charge based on how much you use it&lt;br&gt;- South Africa to ban fishing around African penguin colonies for 10 years&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section covers topics related to technology and software development, including implementing a disk cache plugin and a new mechanical keyboard.&lt;br&gt;- The business section discusses Lyft's potential departure from Minneapolis, China Evergrande's bankruptcy protection filing, the impact of electronic logging devices on drivers, Amazon's new fee on third-party sellers, and the use of microchips in cheese wheels to combat counterfeiting.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section explores studies on the diversification of sea spiders, the discovery of a new type of star, and the use of threads in reverse-chronological feeds.&lt;br&gt;- The other section includes various topics such as the impact of war on mental health, Rudy Giuliani's involvement with Purdue Pharma, the excitement of former mobsters regarding Giuliani's charges, word puzzles, archives during the pandemic, RFK Jr.'s neurological disorder, autonomous vehicles, blue light glasses, income disparities, warnings about Chinese-made weapons, Saturn observation, submarine cable damage, Reddit app pricing, and fishing bans in South Africa.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report covers a wide range of topics, providing insights into technology, business, AI, and other areas of interest.</summary></entry></feed>