<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-05T20:01:49Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 05 Nov 2023 20:01:49</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-05T20:01:49Z</published><updated>2023-11-05T20:01:49Z</updated><id>8a5efbe3-845f-4f94-a2b6-83dfca7c359c</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- This $13,000 microcar is outselling Teslas in Japan. Drivers love its affordability and compact size.&lt;br&gt;- Brian Cox says AI replacing actors is a "human rights issue." Raises concerns about the impact on human creativity and job displacement.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk unveils X chatbot "Grok," which answers "spicy" questions others won't. Aims to provide more interactive and personalized AI experiences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- An Airbnb host whose SF duplex was flooded by a guest says she only got enough compensation to 'make a difference' after posting on X. Highlights the challenges of dealing with insurance and seeking fair compensation.&lt;br&gt;- Skims, a clothing brand, has had a successful week with partnerships and product launches. Shows the brand's growth and expansion in the market.&lt;br&gt;- Adidas is selling Bugatti collab boots with digital twins. Explores the use of virtual representations to enhance the shopping experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- How Beatles producer Giles Martin used AI to reunite the band for 'Now and Then.' Demonstrates the application of AI in music production and collaboration.&lt;br&gt;- Inspired by Seinfeld, Google unveils new AI model for image generation. Discusses the development of AI models for creative purposes.&lt;br&gt;- Meet FANToM: A benchmark for stress-testing machine theory of mind in interactions. Introduces a new benchmark for evaluating AI's understanding of human behavior and intentions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Gen Z is pushing for workplace changes that should have been implemented earlier. Reflects the growing demand for inclusivity and equality in the workplace.&lt;br&gt;- Israeli defense minister suggests a controversial approach to ending the war in Gaza. Raises ethical concerns and highlights the complexities of the conflict.&lt;br&gt;- Moving back to New York before the COVID lockdown led to personal growth and reflection. Emphasizes the importance of living in the present moment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;- The report covers various topics including tech, business, and AI.&lt;br&gt;- It highlights key points within each section and provides insights on the broader topics.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report showcases the impact of technology, societal changes, and global events on different aspects of life.</summary></entry></feed>