<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-19T10:03:05Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 19 Aug 2023 10:03:05</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-19T10:03:05Z</published><updated>2023-08-19T10:03:05Z</updated><id>b59447e1-d869-41e3-9c03-6a563e21b61b</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Meet CipherChat: An AI Framework to Systematically Examine the Generalizability of Safety Alignment to Non-Natural Languages-Specifically Ciphers&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Introducing CipherChat, an AI framework for analyzing safety alignment in non-natural languages like ciphers.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This framework can help researchers and developers assess the safety and generalizability of AI systems in various non-natural language contexts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Implementing CI/CD pipeline with GitHub Actions, and GitHub Pages in a React app.&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Guide on setting up a CI/CD pipeline using GitHub Actions and GitHub Pages for a React app.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This approach streamlines the development and deployment process, ensuring continuous integration and delivery of the React app.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Express is laying off 150 workers. Here's the full list of major retailers making cuts, from Gap to Walmart.&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Express is laying off 150 employees, and other major retailers like Gap and Walmart are also making cuts.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: The retail industry is facing challenges, leading to job cuts in various companies. This trend may indicate broader economic impacts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Analysis: Health care CEOs hauled in $4B last year as inflation pinched workers&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Health care CEOs earned $4 billion last year, while workers faced inflation-related challenges.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This highlights the growing income disparity between CEOs and workers in the health care industry, raising concerns about fair compensation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. Xbox’s new “8 strikes” mod rollout judges hate speech 3x worse than cheating&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Xbox's new mod rollout penalizes hate speech more severely than cheating.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This demonstrates a proactive approach by Xbox to address hate speech and promote a safer gaming environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Cisco CEO says AI is already becoming a huge new market after it 'missed' the initial cloud computing boom&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Cisco's CEO believes that AI is emerging as a significant market after the initial boom of cloud computing.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: The growing adoption and advancements in AI technologies present new opportunities for businesses and investors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;1. On Maui, a perfect storm of climate, colonialism, and failed emergency systems made the deadliest US wildfire in over a century&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The deadliest US wildfire in over a century on Maui was influenced by climate conditions, colonialism, and failed emergency systems.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This highlights the complex factors contributing to devastating wildfires and the need for improved emergency response and climate resilience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Ecuador could make history by banning oil drilling in the Amazon&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Ecuador is considering a historic ban on oil drilling in the Amazon region.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This potential ban reflects the growing recognition of the environmental importance of the Amazon and the need to protect it from further degradation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is exploring AI frameworks for analyzing safety alignment in non-natural languages.&lt;br&gt;- CI/CD pipelines using GitHub Actions and GitHub Pages streamline app development and deployment.&lt;br&gt;- The retail industry is experiencing job cuts, indicating potential economic challenges.&lt;br&gt;- Income disparity between health care CEOs and workers raises concerns about fair compensation.&lt;br&gt;- Xbox's mod rollout prioritizes penalizing hate speech to create a safer gaming environment.&lt;br&gt;- AI is emerging as a significant market, presenting new opportunities for businesses.&lt;br&gt;- Wildfires are influenced by climate, colonialism, and emergency system failures, emphasizing the need for improved response and resilience.&lt;br&gt;- Ecuador's potential ban on oil drilling in the Amazon reflects growing environmental awareness.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report highlights various developments and challenges in the tech, business, and environmental sectors.</summary></entry></feed>