<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-17T20:02:27Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 17 Jan 2024 20:02:27</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-17T20:02:27Z</published><updated>2024-01-17T20:02:27Z</updated><id>50d1b9fc-8071-4274-a873-52164fe48c53</id><summary type="html">In today's news, there are several notable events happening around the world. Tax prep companies are engaged in a showdown, while Drizly, a popular alcohol delivery service, has closed shop. Additionally, the proposed merger between JetBlue and Spirit has been axed. On a different note, a browser extension has been developed to help restore our brain's response and alleviate stress while working. In the realm of creativity, an astronaut, Molly Baz, and even your mom can teach valuable lessons. Build a Rocket Boy, a game studio founded by a former Grand Theft Auto developer, has successfully raised $110 million. The topic of AI is also making waves, with many people discussing it, even if they don't fully understand it. In other news, a Yemeni influencer known as 'Timhouthi Chalamet' disappeared from TikTok after posting a tour of a captured cargo ship. Former Twitter employees have acquired hashtag signs and artwork auctioned off by Elon Musk to decorate their homes. Unfortunately, an intoxicated passenger on a flight from Japan to Seattle bit an attendant, leading to the plane turning around. On a more positive note, Ukraine is receiving a new cache of Storm Shadow missiles from its allies. In the tech world, TikTok owner ByteDance has quietly launched four generative AI apps powered by OpenAI's GPT. Lastly, technology is being utilized to combat the threat of fungal disease in food, and a congressional watchdog will launch an inquiry into the FDA's oversight of medical device recalls.</summary></entry></feed>