<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-04T20:02:05Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 04 Dec 2023 20:02:05</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-04T20:02:05Z</published><updated>2023-12-04T20:02:05Z</updated><id>0871f5e6-80de-4b05-8c5b-9d5c06067bcf</id><summary type="html">In recent news, the White House has implemented new rules aimed at preventing China from entering the US electric vehicle market. The regulations are part of ongoing efforts to protect domestic industries and maintain national security. Meanwhile, a millennial reflects on her decision to rush into a managerial role in her 20s, expressing regret and emphasizing that it is perfectly acceptable to not aspire to be a boss at all. UBS, a Swiss bank, has come under scrutiny for selling a private jet that was used by its former chairman to violate COVID-19 travel restrictions by attending events such as Wimbledon and the Euros, as well as taking a family vacation in the Maldives. Frontline workers who are unable to work remotely are advocating for more control over their schedules, highlighting the challenges they face in balancing work and personal life. Additionally, a former burglar shares insights into her past criminal activities, revealing the flaws in alarm systems and shedding light on her targeting strategies. Artificial intelligence is found to be increasing productivity in unexpected ways. In a personal success story, an individual shares how they transitioned from a law career to a tech job, quadrupling their salary in the process. The potential of the Julia programming language for high energy physics computing is explored, showcasing its relevance in scientific research. Doubtnut, a company previously offered a $150 million deal by Byju's, has been sold for $10 million. A comprehensive guide to integrating the Upsales API is provided, offering insights into streamlining sales and marketing operations. Users of a Chinese food delivery app are taking matters into their own hands to ensure justice is served. The Pentagon's drones are revealed to be incredibly expensive, costing their weight in gold. Designers who uplift the next generation of Black creative talent are celebrated for their contributions. The new podium used by President Biden is seen as a metaphor for his presidency, symbolizing change and progress. Homeowners are advised on how to determine if their drinking water contains lead. The top 10 housing markets that homebuyers are moving to in 2024 are identified. Tribes in Maine have faced significant challenges in their fight to rebury ancestral remains, with Harvard resisting their efforts. Wiley College has announced its transformation into Wiley University, along with the introduction of new graduate programs. Spotify's CEO has sent a memo to employees announcing a 17% reduction in staff, citing the necessity of being lean in the current market. In the tech industry, Spotify is not alone in implementing job cuts, as other companies have also been forced to downsize. A roundup of hot topics in the workplace, SharePoint, and the power platform is provided. A comprehensive guide to enhancing Next.js apps with the Image Component is offered. Researchers from the University of Texas have showcased the use of machine learning in predicting complications in implant-based reconstruction procedures. Meta AI introduces Seamless, a publicly available AI system that enables real-time cross-lingual communication. Lastly, the different colors of hydrogen and their significance are explored.</summary></entry></feed>