<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-03T20:02:09Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 03 Nov 2023 20:02:09</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-03T20:02:09Z</published><updated>2023-11-03T20:02:09Z</updated><id>9f9a265d-deb0-4e1d-a7f3-7f667dbe6115</id><summary type="html">Report: Tech&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Warren Buffett's favorite stocks gauge is flashing red, markets guru John Hussman says&lt;br&gt;- Key points: John Hussman warns that Warren Buffett's favorite stocks gauge, the Buffett Indicator, is signaling an overvalued market.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This suggests that investors should exercise caution and be prepared for a potential market correction.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Turning a tiny fraction of America's dead strip malls into housing could create 700,000 new apartments&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Converting abandoned strip malls into housing could help alleviate the housing shortage in the US.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This presents an opportunity for urban revitalization and addressing the affordable housing crisis.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Visual Studio 2022 17.8 Preview 3: Structured Diagnostics, SQL Server Data Tools Upgrade and More&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The latest preview of Visual Studio 2022 introduces new features such as structured diagnostics and upgraded SQL Server data tools.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: These updates enhance the development experience for software developers using Visual Studio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Forget the baby books: ParentGPT uses AI to give advice to new parents&lt;br&gt;- Key points: ParentGPT is an AI-powered platform that provides personalized advice and guidance to new parents.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This technology can support and supplement traditional parenting resources, offering tailored recommendations based on individual circumstances.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Report: Business&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. 3 passengers sued Alaska Airlines for emotional distress over off-duty pilot accused of trying to turn off the engines mid-flight&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Three passengers have filed a lawsuit against Alaska Airlines, claiming emotional distress caused by an off-duty pilot's alleged attempt to turn off the engines during a flight.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This incident highlights the importance of ensuring the mental well-being and stability of airline personnel.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Savings Rates and CD Rates Today | New 5 Month CD at 5.60% APY&lt;br&gt;- Key points: This article provides information on current savings rates and CD rates, highlighting a new 5-month CD with a high APY.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: Savers can take advantage of competitive rates to maximize their returns on savings and investments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Design giant Ideo cuts a third of staff and closes offices as the era of design thinking ends&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Ideo, a prominent design firm, has downsized its workforce and closed offices, signaling a shift in the design industry away from traditional design thinking.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This reflects the evolving landscape of design and the need for new approaches to problem-solving and innovation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Publishers outline AI practices in attempt to balance efficiency and... - The Bookseller&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Publishers are adopting AI practices to streamline operations and improve efficiency while maintaining a balance with human creativity and editorial judgment.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: AI can enhance various aspects of the publishing industry, but it should be used in conjunction with human expertise to ensure quality and authenticity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Report: AI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. AI did not generate The Beatles's last song. The Beatles did&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Contrary to some claims, AI did not generate The Beatles' last song. The song was created by the band itself.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This highlights the distinction between human creativity and AI-generated content, emphasizing the unique abilities of human artists.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. GPT In Business: A Powerful Tool, But Not A Silver Bullet&lt;br&gt;- Key points: GPT (Generative Pre-trained Transformer) is a powerful tool in business applications, but it is not a one-size-fits-all solution.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: While GPT can automate certain tasks and generate content, it should be used judiciously and in conjunction with human expertise to ensure accuracy and relevance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Google AI Introduces Spectron: The First Spoken Language AI Model that is Trained End-to-End to Directly Process Spectrograms as Both Input and Output&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Google AI has developed Spectron, an AI model trained to process spectrograms as both input and output, enabling more advanced speech recognition and synthesis.&lt;br&gt;- Insights: This advancement in spoken language AI has the potential to improve various applications, such as voice assistants and transcription services.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights from all broader topics:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The market may be overvalued, signaling a potential correction.&lt;br&gt;- Converting abandoned strip malls into housing can address the housing shortage.&lt;br&gt;- Visual Studio 2022 updates enhance the development experience.&lt;br&gt;- AI can provide personalized advice to new parents.&lt;br&gt;- Ensuring the mental well-being of airline personnel is crucial.&lt;br&gt;- Savers can take advantage of competitive rates for higher returns.&lt;br&gt;- The design industry is undergoing a transformation away from traditional design thinking.&lt;br&gt;- AI can streamline publishing processes while maintaining human creativity.&lt;br&gt;- Human creativity remains distinct from AI-generated content.&lt;br&gt;- GPT is a powerful tool in business but should be used alongside human expertise.&lt;br&gt;- Spectron advances spoken language AI for improved speech recognition and synthesis.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report highlights the intersection of technology, business, and AI, showcasing key developments, challenges, and opportunities in these fields. It emphasizes the importance of balancing technological advancements with human expertise and creativity.</summary></entry></feed>