<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-09T14:01:08Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 09 Aug 2023 14:01:08</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-09T14:01:08Z</published><updated>2023-08-09T14:01:08Z</updated><id>94487c56-fe8e-4911-b8c8-d5242913cb68</id><summary type="html">What Time is the Mega Millions drawing&lt;br&gt;Selena Gomez&lt;br&gt;America vs Nashville&lt;br&gt;Alabama brawl&lt;br&gt;黄发布最强AIGC chip! Memory capacity increased by nearly 50%, can run any large model, "the iPhone moment of generative AI has come"&lt;br&gt;Wang Xiaochuan updates larger models: 53 billion parameters but closed source, on-site questioning about room temperature superconductivity-related issues&lt;br&gt;How to optimize ChatGLM-6B? Just one line of code | The most "in" large model&lt;br&gt;Jia Jiaya team proposes LISA large model: understanding human language "segmenting everything", playable online&lt;br&gt;The latest schedule has been announced! | August 25-26, gather at the first International Conference on Artificial Intelligence Generated Content in Shanghai!&lt;br&gt;Tesla's meritorious CFO suddenly resigns! After 13 years of joining, he was once regarded as Musk's successor along with Zhu Xiaotong&lt;br&gt;Huawei's genius teenager starts a business with large models! Former rank 20, now focusing on AI document writing&lt;br&gt;Xiaomi's smart glasses: developed in 48 hours, designed for the visually impaired&lt;br&gt;OpenAI: ChatGPT will comply with web crawling protocols, websites can refuse freeloaders&lt;br&gt;Tesla CFO resigns suddenly, future whereabouts are a mystery, has already sold $6 million worth of stocks before leaving&lt;br&gt;G9.js: Automatically Interactive Graphics&lt;br&gt;Google AI Research Proposes VidLNs: An Annotation Procedure that Obtains Rich Video Descriptions that are Semantically Correct and Densely Grounded with Accurate Spatio-Temporal Localizations&lt;br&gt;ETH Zurich Researchers Introduce the Biomimetic Tendon-Driven Faive Hand: A 3D Printable High-DoF Design with Dexterous In-Hand Rotation Skills&lt;br&gt;Made Renovation promises "tech-enabled" remodels; customers describe "absolute nightmare"&lt;br&gt;A Guide to Python&lt;br&gt;Building an intelligent WhatsApp bot for PDF Question-Answering using Langchain, Twilio, Python and ChatGPT&lt;br&gt;Data element concept stocks weaken in the afternoon, People's Daily Online falls more than 5%&lt;br&gt;Cathay Pacific Airways: First half-year profit of HKD 4.268 billion, turning losses around year-on-year&lt;br&gt;Financial technology stocks active again, Anshuo Information rises more than 13%&lt;br&gt;Busy Snacks strategically invests tens of millions of yuan in Cha Huozi&lt;br&gt;Photovoltaic sector fluctuates and declines, leading the way in perovskite battery direction&lt;br&gt;Jibang Consulting: Original factory expansion, estimated 105% annual growth rate of HBM supply in 2024&lt;br&gt;XGimi falls from grace: market value shrinks by 80%, relying on high-priced repairs to cut leeks? | Krypton · Hard Technology&lt;br&gt;Anhong Capital partners with luxury fashion brand ZIMMERMANN&lt;br&gt;Two departments: Organize the application pilot project of "5G+Smart Tourism"&lt;br&gt;Zhou Hongyi releases 360 strategic product "360 Security Cloud"</summary></entry></feed>