<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-06T20:02:13Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 06 Oct 2023 20:02:13</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-06T20:02:13Z</published><updated>2023-10-06T20:02:13Z</updated><id>1a5e1b1a-2bf4-45af-a100-f9b9fc852cae</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI is exploring making its own chips as AI companies scramble to overcome the global processor shortage, report says&lt;br&gt;- Google’s Magnifier accessibility app is ready for download to Pixel phones&lt;br&gt;- Mistral AI Open-Sources Mistral 7B: A Small Yet Powerful Language Model Adaptable to Many Use-Cases&lt;br&gt;- Show HN: A tool to Convert JSON schemas into TypeScript Deno classes&lt;br&gt;- Upgrade Your Laptop With The Fast And Affordable Lexar 790 NVMe SSD&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- An Airbnb guest who has overstayed for 542 days was kicked out of another rental just 2 months earlier&lt;br&gt;- A pair of Bahamian private jets said to be funded by a 'handshake deal' with Sam Bankman-Fried are set to be confiscated by the US government&lt;br&gt;- Santa Clara's Levi's Stadium generated $2 billion for the local economy in 10 years, thanks to non-NFL events&lt;br&gt;- John Wiley &amp; Sons Inc. - (WLY) Declares $0.35 Dividend - Nasdaq&lt;br&gt;- Grimes is asking for physical custody of her and Elon Musk's 3 kids in parental rights lawsuit&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI is exploring making its own chips as AI companies scramble to overcome the global processor shortage, report says&lt;br&gt;- Mistral AI Open-Sources Mistral 7B: A Small Yet Powerful Language Model Adaptable to Many Use-Cases&lt;br&gt;- mRNA vaccines just won a Nobel Prize. Now they’re ready for the next act.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Points:&lt;br&gt;- An Airbnb guest overstayed for 542 days, highlighting potential issues with rental policies and guest monitoring.&lt;br&gt;- Earth's inner core is more like a ball of butter than a solid metal sphere, according to a new study.&lt;br&gt;- Jeremy Grantham warns of a potential crash in the S&amp;P, emphasizing the need for caution in the market.&lt;br&gt;- The upcoming Prime Day in 2023 is expected to offer great deals on headphones.&lt;br&gt;- The global processor shortage is pushing AI companies like OpenAI to explore making their own chips.&lt;br&gt;- Personal loan and mortgage interest rates are experiencing fluctuations, with the latter reaching the highest rates since 2000.&lt;br&gt;- ESG ETFs are found to have unremarkable returns in a new study.&lt;br&gt;- Hacktoberfest 2023 provides beginners with an opportunity to embark on their open-source adventure.&lt;br&gt;- Tips and tricks for efficient coding in VS Code can help increase productivity.&lt;br&gt;- The US government's failure to publish reports of criminal activity on cruise ships raises concerns about transparency.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The global processor shortage is impacting various industries, including AI, leading companies to seek alternative solutions.&lt;br&gt;- The fluctuating interest rates in personal loans and mortgages indicate a dynamic economic environment.&lt;br&gt;- The success of non-NFL events in generating revenue for local economies highlights the importance of diversifying event offerings.&lt;br&gt;- The potential crash in the S&amp;P and the unremarkable returns of ESG ETFs suggest the need for careful investment strategies.&lt;br&gt;- The lack of transparency in reporting criminal activity on cruise ships raises questions about the safety and accountability of the industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The report covers a range of topics including tech, business, and AI. It highlights key points such as the potential issues with long-term Airbnb guests, the unique nature of Earth's inner core, and the warning of a potential market crash by Jeremy Grantham. The report also provides insights into the impact of the global processor shortage on AI companies, the fluctuating interest rates in personal loans and mortgages, and the importance of diversifying event offerings for local economies. Overall, the report emphasizes the need for caution in the market, efficient coding practices, and transparency in various industries.</summary></entry></feed>