<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-15T18:01:24Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 15 Aug 2023 18:01:24</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-15T18:01:24Z</published><updated>2023-08-15T18:01:24Z</updated><id>57125b3c-dc96-4218-b01c-f2787859b2e5</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- The New York Times is taking measures to prevent AI companies from using its content as training data.&lt;br&gt;- The original source code of the vi text editor, taken from System V, has been made available.&lt;br&gt;- Revolute Robotics has developed a hybrid mobility robot that can function as both a rover and a drone.&lt;br&gt;- Aqara has released a new Zigbee light strip that supports HomeKit Adaptive Lighting and Matter.&lt;br&gt;- DeepMind researchers have introduced AlphaStar Unplugged, a breakthrough in large-scale offline reinforcement learning using the game StarCraft II.&lt;br&gt;- Amazon has introduced AWS HealthImaging, a platform for storing and analyzing medical imaging data.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech industry is constantly evolving, with companies taking steps to protect their content and develop innovative products. The availability of the vi text editor's source code allows for further exploration and development. The development of hybrid mobility robots and advanced lighting solutions showcases the potential for advancements in robotics and smart home technology. DeepMind's AlphaStar Unplugged demonstrates the progress in reinforcement learning, which has implications for various industries. The introduction of AWS HealthImaging highlights the growing importance of data analysis in the healthcare sector.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Multiple brides and grooms are facing uncertainty and potential financial loss after a formal wear chain abruptly closed.&lt;br&gt;- Biden's climate bill has had a significant impact on the economy, creating jobs and driving economic growth.&lt;br&gt;- China's disappointing July report card follows a significant interest rate cut, indicating challenges in the country's economy.&lt;br&gt;- WhoFundsWho is a platform that allows users to see the funding sources of organizations they are reading about.&lt;br&gt;- Sam Bankman-Fried, a prominent figure in the cryptocurrency industry, is currently in jail.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The closure of the formal wear chain highlights the challenges faced by businesses and the potential impact on customers. Biden's climate bill has shown positive effects on the economy, with job creation and economic changes. China's economic performance and interest rate cuts indicate ongoing challenges in the country's economy. The availability of platforms like WhoFundsWho provides transparency in funding sources, allowing users to make informed decisions. The incarceration of Sam Bankman-Fried raises questions about the implications for the cryptocurrency industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Continuous batch processing has significantly improved throughput and latency in LLM inference.&lt;br&gt;- The scam targeting kids through popular games like Roblox and Fortnite has been widespread.&lt;br&gt;- The development of large language models and their downsizing is seen as the future of generative AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: Continuous batch processing has shown promising results in improving AI performance, with significant improvements in throughput and latency. The prevalence of scams targeting children through popular games raises concerns about online safety and security measures. The downsizing of large language models represents a shift towards more efficient and practical applications of generative AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is focused on protecting content, developing innovative products, and advancing AI capabilities.&lt;br&gt;- Business news highlights challenges faced by companies, the impact of policy changes, and the importance of transparency.&lt;br&gt;- AI advancements include improved processing techniques, addressing online scams, and the future of generative AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, the report showcases the diverse range of topics and insights gathered from different languages, providing a comprehensive overview of the current trends and developments in the tech, business, and AI sectors.</summary></entry></feed>