<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-17T08:03:56Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 17 Sep 2023 08:03:56</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-17T08:03:56Z</published><updated>2023-09-17T08:03:56Z</updated><id>9652b7b4-3474-4126-95ad-ca7ca34dcf17</id><summary type="html">Satya Nadella: "I want to use this tactically vs. GOOG/AAPL" (2022)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech: Satya Nadella, the CEO of Microsoft, expresses his intention to use a certain strategy tactically against Google and Apple.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In wealthy Colorado ski towns, teens are building tiny homes for teachers who can't afford a place to live&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Social Impact: Teenagers in affluent ski towns in Colorado are constructing small homes for teachers who are unable to afford housing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lantern (YC W24) – Hiring Engineers to Build PostgreSQL Vector Database for AI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech: Lantern, a startup from Y Combinator's Winter 2024 batch, is recruiting engineers to develop a PostgreSQL Vector Database specifically for artificial intelligence applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Linux on a MacBook Pro (M1 Pro): How Good Is Asahi Now?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech: An evaluation of the performance and functionality of the Asahi Linux project, which enables Linux to run on Apple's M1 Pro MacBook Pro.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lodash just declared issue bankruptcy and closed every issue and open PR&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech: Lodash, a popular JavaScript utility library, has announced the closure of all open issues and pull requests, declaring "issue bankruptcy."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Show HN: Every Breath You Take – Heart Rate Variability Training&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech: A showcase of a project called "Every Breath You Take," which focuses on heart rate variability training.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Samsung Galaxy S24 Shows Up on Certification Site, Confirms Feature Upgrade&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech: The Samsung Galaxy S24 smartphone has appeared on a certification site, confirming the inclusion of upgraded features.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former GOP Sen. Bob Corker says he's not surprised Mitt Romney isn't running for re-election because politics are 'not as conducive' to problem-solving as they once were&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Politics: Former Republican Senator Bob Corker comments on Mitt Romney's decision not to seek re-election, attributing it to the current political climate being less conducive to problem-solving.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cache line alignment in C++ – How it makes your program faster&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech: An explanation of cache line alignment in C++ programming and how it can improve program performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The iPhone 15 gets USB-C, a redesigned Cybertruck surfaces, and California considers banning AV trucks&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech: Updates on the iPhone 15, which will feature USB-C connectivity, the emergence of a redesigned Cybertruck, and the potential ban of autonomous vehicle trucks in California.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's how General Motors' CEO Mary Barra justifies her $29 million salary&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Business: General Motors CEO Mary Barra's rationale for her $29 million salary is discussed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dark money donations to Virginia Republicans outpace Democrats 6 to 1 in the fight for control of the state legislature&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Politics: A report on the significant disparity in dark money donations between Virginia Republicans and Democrats in their battle for control of the state legislature.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New camera offers ultrafast imaging at a fraction of the normal cost&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech: An introduction to a new camera that provides high-speed imaging capabilities at a reduced cost compared to traditional options.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have A Heart! We All Do, Actually…And AI Might Improve Cardio Care&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech/Healthcare: The potential of artificial intelligence to enhance cardiovascular care is explored.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite Critics Calling it Ugly and Stillborn, Tesla Cybertruck Appears to Top 2 Million Reservations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech/Automotive: Despite criticism, Tesla's Cybertruck has reportedly received over 2 million reservations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Lauren Boebert is divorcing her husband of nearly 20 years. Here's a timeline of their relationship.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Politics/Personal: An overview of the relationship timeline between Representative Lauren Boebert and her husband, as they announce their divorce after almost 20 years of marriage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is this fraud? And if so, to what extent am I responsible?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Legal: A question is raised regarding potential fraud and the level of responsibility an individual may have in such a situation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Higgs: I wouldn't be productive enough for today's academic system (2013)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Education: Physicist Peter Higgs expresses his belief that he would not be productive enough to succeed in the contemporary academic system.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go 1.21 Toolchain is Now Reproducible to Help Safeguard from Supply-Chain Attacks&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech: The Go 1.21 toolchain has been made reproducible to enhance security against supply-chain attacks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is Delta Air Lines tarnishing its brand by ousting some Sky Club customers?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Business/Travel: The potential impact on Delta Air Lines' brand reputation due to the removal of certain Sky Club customers is discussed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Science Policy and Diplomacy Meet, One Week One Lab program concludes at CSIR-NIScPR on September 16, 2023 - India Education Diary&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Education/Science: The One Week One Lab program, which focuses on science policy and diplomacy, concludes at CSIR-NIScPR in India.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden leads Trump and DeSantis in Michigan, a battleground state key to his 2024 reelection calculus, poll says&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Politics: A poll indicates that President Joe Biden is leading former President Donald Trump and Florida Governor Ron DeSantis in Michigan, a crucial state for Biden's potential re-election in 2024.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump lawyer and co-defendant Jenna Ellis says she won't support him due to his 'malignant narcissistic' tendencies&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Politics: Jenna Ellis, a former lawyer for Donald Trump and co-defendant, states that she will not support him due to his "malignant narcissistic" traits.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A high school band director was tased by cops at a football game after he refused orders to stop his musicians from playing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Social Issues: A high school band director was tased by police officers during a football game after he refused to comply with orders to stop his musicians from playing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia is making a 'very costly' tactical mistake that means its second line of defense will be easier to penetrate, analysts say&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Politics/Security: Analysts suggest that Russia is making a costly tactical error, which could make its second line of defense more vulnerable to penetration.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bear rescued from theme park 'didn't understand trees,' relocated to sanctuary&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Environment/Animal Welfare: A bear that was rescued from a theme park is relocated to a sanctuary after it is observed that the bear did not understand trees.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Threat from Climate Change to Some of India's Sacred Sites Is Reshaping Beliefs&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Environment/Culture: The impact of climate change on sacred sites in India is discussed, highlighting how it is reshaping beliefs and practices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OnePlus' next tablet is a budget model called the OnePlus Pad Go&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech: OnePlus is set to release a budget tablet called the OnePlus Pad Go.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Nintendo Switch OLED and jet-black Xbox Series S are both on sale right now&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech/Gaming: The Nintendo Switch OLED and jet-black Xbox Series S consoles are currently available for purchase.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elevate Your Flutter App with Advanced Animations: A Deep Dive into AnimationController and Tween 🚀&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech: A comprehensive guide on utilizing AnimationController and Tween to enhance animations in Flutter applications.</summary></entry></feed>