<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-08T08:03:40Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 08 Oct 2023 08:03:40</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-08T08:03:40Z</published><updated>2023-10-08T08:03:40Z</updated><id>35254392-8dd3-48a9-a0f2-04aa1176a4c5</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Dockerized local and offline backing up of PostgreSQL with rotation, compression&lt;br&gt;- HVM updates: simplifications, finally runs on GPUs, 80x speedup on RTX 4090&lt;br&gt;- Overcoming Hallucinations in AI: How Factually Augmented RLHF Optimizes Vision-Language Alignment in Large Multimodal Models&lt;br&gt;- Toyota Will Adopt Tesla-Style Cast Bodies That Might Be Impossible to Fix&lt;br&gt;- How to customize colors in dark and light modes in Material UI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- USA paying more interest on its $33T debt than on defense – who holds the IOUs&lt;br&gt;- Permission Slip: Consumer Reports app to take back control of your data&lt;br&gt;- MGM didn’t pay up after hackers broke into its system and stole customer data&lt;br&gt;- Sam Altman backs teens’ startup, Google unveils the Pixel 8 and TikTok tests an ad-free tier&lt;br&gt;- The leading Democratic challenger to Lauren Boebert raised $3.4 million in the third quarter, a mega haul that comes as the GOP congresswoman has faced widespread criticism over her public conduct&lt;br&gt;- Dear SaaStr: How Long Should It Take to Negotiate a VC Term Sheet?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Overcoming Hallucinations in AI: How Factually Augmented RLHF Optimizes Vision-Language Alignment in Large Multimodal Models&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Others:&lt;br&gt;- 1400 year old gold foil figures found in Norwegian pagan temple&lt;br&gt;- Where to watch WWE Fastlane live streams: See John Cena, LA Knight, and more&lt;br&gt;- User data stolen from genetic testing giant 23andMe is now for sale on the dark web&lt;br&gt;- Show HN: Display all stories and comments for a specific Hacker News user&lt;br&gt;- FTX "insurance fund" calculated by multiplying trading volume by random number&lt;br&gt;- Show HN: Timbre – An app that finds the best sounds for your sleep&lt;br&gt;- FTC: Stop falling for social media scams, you've given crooks $650M+ this year&lt;br&gt;- Doctors Without Borders says healthcare facilities 'cannot become targets' after Israeli forces struck a hospital and ambulance in Gaza&lt;br&gt;- Jewish institutions in the US are on guard following Hamas' attack on Israel&lt;br&gt;- Israeli officials are calling on armed civilians to stand guard following Hamas attacks&lt;br&gt;- Republican Rep. Tim Burchett says he 'slept like a baby' after voting to remove Kevin McCarthy as speaker&lt;br&gt;- An EasyJet flight was forced to make an emergency landing due to a disruptive passenger who attacked a man with a carrier bag&lt;br&gt;- Free Ireland vs. Scotland live stream: Where to watch Rugby World Cup online from anywhere&lt;br&gt;- Israel's war with Hamas could increase competition for the US artillery shells needed by Ukraine&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The USA's debt and interest payments are a significant concern, potentially impacting defense spending.&lt;br&gt;- Data breaches and hacking incidents continue to pose a threat to businesses, with MGM being a recent victim.&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is constantly evolving, with advancements in areas such as Dockerization, AI, and material UI customization.&lt;br&gt;- Political and international conflicts, such as the situation between Israel and Hamas, have implications beyond their immediate regions.&lt;br&gt;- Consumer protection and awareness regarding scams and data privacy remain important issues.&lt;br&gt;- Fundraising and investment activities in the business sector continue to shape the startup landscape.</summary></entry></feed>