<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-11T20:02:21Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 11 Oct 2023 20:02:21</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-11T20:02:21Z</published><updated>2023-10-11T20:02:21Z</updated><id>53dbaa21-3c7c-47f8-9875-7e62338f2864</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Elon Musk to spend well over $1 billion on Tesla AI supercomputer&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk plans to invest more than $1 billion in building a supercomputer for Tesla's artificial intelligence (AI) projects.&lt;br&gt;- This move highlights the importance of AI in the development of autonomous vehicles and other technologies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. AI won't replace creative jobs just as the invention of the camera didn't make paintings obsolete, Adobe exec says&lt;br&gt;- An executive from Adobe believes that AI will not replace creative jobs, drawing a parallel to how the invention of the camera did not make paintings obsolete.&lt;br&gt;- This insight suggests that AI can enhance creativity and collaboration rather than replace human creativity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. An advanced humanoid robot says it can simulate dreams to help it learn about the world&lt;br&gt;- An advanced humanoid robot claims to be able to simulate dreams as a means of learning about the world.&lt;br&gt;- This development showcases the potential for robots to mimic human cognitive processes and improve their understanding of the environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Big bank chains may be more convenient, but I'll never give up the personal help I can get from my credit union&lt;br&gt;- Despite the convenience offered by big bank chains, the author expresses loyalty to their credit union due to the personalized assistance they receive.&lt;br&gt;- This perspective highlights the value of personalized customer service in the banking industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Personal Loan Interest Rates Today, October 11, 2023 | Today's Top Personal Loan Rates&lt;br&gt;- This content provides information on current personal loan interest rates.&lt;br&gt;- It serves as a resource for individuals seeking personal loans and helps them make informed financial decisions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. I'm a financial dominatrix. People send me $1,500 a month to be humiliated and 'owned' – here's how it works.&lt;br&gt;- The author shares their experience as a financial dominatrix, where individuals pay them $1,500 per month for humiliation and ownership.&lt;br&gt;- This unique business model sheds light on unconventional forms of income generation and explores the dynamics of power and control in financial relationships.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. Why it matters if ChatGPT wrote an apology for "The Lord of the Rings: Gollum" game disaster&lt;br&gt;- The article discusses the significance of an AI language model, ChatGPT, issuing an apology for its involvement in the development of a video game.&lt;br&gt;- This event raises questions about the accountability and responsibility of AI systems in creative industries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. AI won't replace creative jobs just as the invention of the camera didn't make paintings obsolete, Adobe exec says&lt;br&gt;- This content, categorized under both 'Tech' and 'AI', emphasizes that AI will not replace creative jobs.&lt;br&gt;- The comparison to the invention of the camera highlights the potential for AI to enhance creative processes rather than replace human creativity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Unraveling Gene Regulation with Deep Learning: A New AI Approach to Understanding Alternative Splicing&lt;br&gt;- This article explores the application of deep learning and AI in understanding gene regulation, specifically alternative splicing.&lt;br&gt;- It showcases the potential of AI in advancing scientific research and gaining insights into complex biological processes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The investment in Tesla's AI supercomputer demonstrates the growing importance of AI in the automotive industry and autonomous vehicles.&lt;br&gt;- AI is seen as a tool to enhance creativity and collaboration rather than replace human creativity in various fields.&lt;br&gt;- The development of advanced humanoid robots that can simulate dreams highlights the potential for robots to learn and understand the world in a more human-like manner.&lt;br&gt;- Personalized customer service remains a valuable aspect of the banking industry, even in the face of convenience offered by big bank chains.&lt;br&gt;- The unconventional business model of a financial dominatrix sheds light on alternative forms of income generation and power dynamics in financial relationships.&lt;br&gt;- The accountability and responsibility of AI systems in creative industries, such as video game development, are subjects of discussion and scrutiny.&lt;br&gt;- AI has the potential to revolutionize scientific research, as seen in its application in understanding gene regulation and alternative splicing.</summary></entry></feed>