<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-26T20:02:12Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 26 Sep 2023 20:02:12</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-26T20:02:12Z</published><updated>2023-09-26T20:02:12Z</updated><id>bfcdfde3-ec56-44a3-9067-329f3634ab0e</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Journal Production Guidance for Software and Data Citations - Nature.com provides guidance on how to cite software and data in academic journals.&lt;br&gt;- 'A Catastrophic Mistake': Upheaval at Philosophy Journal Points to... - The Chronicle of Higher Education discusses the upheaval at a philosophy journal and its implications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech section highlights the importance of proper citation of software and data in academic journals and the challenges faced by philosophy journals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- JPMorgan's Jamie Dimon warns of the risk of 7% interest rates: "Are you prepared?" - Jamie Dimon, CEO of JPMorgan, warns about the potential risk of high interest rates.&lt;br&gt;- 3 reasons I keep all my money at the same bank after years of chasing high rates - An individual shares their reasons for keeping all their money at the same bank despite the pursuit of high rates.&lt;br&gt;- Australia's new submarines are still 2 decades away from delivery, but the Aussies are already looking out for spies - Australia's new submarines face delays, and concerns about espionage arise.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business section highlights the potential risks of high interest rates, the personal preferences of individuals in managing their money, and the challenges faced in the delivery of Australia's new submarines.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Spotify is launching an eerie new AI-led feature that mimics podcasters' voices and translates them into different languages - Spotify introduces an AI-led feature that can mimic podcasters' voices and translate them into different languages.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The AI section showcases the advancements in AI technology, specifically in voice mimicry and translation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- The Taliban-controlled afghani has thrashed the US dollar this quarter, becoming the world's best-performing currency - The Afghan afghani outperforms the US dollar as the best-performing currency.&lt;br&gt;- Childcare is getting even more expensive as providers battle landlords and zoning regulations at a time when federal funding is running out - Childcare costs increase due to conflicts with landlords and zoning regulations, compounded by a lack of federal funding.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The other section highlights the economic shifts in currency performance and the challenges faced in the childcare industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Proper citation of software and data is crucial in academic journals.&lt;br&gt;- Philosophy journals face upheaval and challenges.&lt;br&gt;- High interest rates pose risks.&lt;br&gt;- Personal preferences influence financial decisions.&lt;br&gt;- Delays and espionage concerns arise in the delivery of Australia's new submarines.&lt;br&gt;- AI technology advances in voice mimicry and translation.&lt;br&gt;- Currency performance fluctuates.&lt;br&gt;- Childcare costs rise amid conflicts and limited funding.</summary></entry></feed>