<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-11T20:01:51Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 11 Nov 2023 20:01:51</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-11T20:01:51Z</published><updated>2023-11-11T20:01:51Z</updated><id>d7b06dd6-a171-48e1-817e-67c5f031a708</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Bill Gates predicts that AI agents will have a significant impact on the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- Google's AI chatbot, Bard, expresses fear of Elon Musk's rival chatbot, Grok.&lt;br&gt;- Warner Bros shelves a film called Coyote vs. Acme as a tax write-off.&lt;br&gt;- Google is considering investing hundreds of millions of dollars into AI chatbot startup Character.AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- An online banking platform releases three new offers with interest rates above 5% APY.&lt;br&gt;- Airbnb's business model has shifted from cheap accommodations to attracting Wall Street investors.&lt;br&gt;- News Corp. seeks AI licensing deals to keep generative AI up-to-date with its content.&lt;br&gt;- Stability AI experiences a tenfold revenue increase and gains support from Intel.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Google's AI chatbot, Bard, expresses fear of Elon Musk's rival chatbot, Grok.&lt;br&gt;- A new AI paper introduces JudgeLM, a novel approach for evaluating large language models.&lt;br&gt;- The creator of "Shrek" believes that AI will replace human jobs in animation.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's Neuralink has thousands of people lined up for a brain chip implant.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Fort Worth's 1936 Frontier Centennial event is criticized for ignoring Black history.&lt;br&gt;- The winner of an upcoming major election must address chronic hyperinflation and a recession.&lt;br&gt;- A Florida resident plans to move back to California due to better weather and lifestyle.&lt;br&gt;- A professor warns that solar activity could disrupt the internet.&lt;br&gt;- Parasitic worms manipulate their hosts' behavior, and scientists have made progress in understanding how.&lt;br&gt;- The limited-edition Kendrick Lamar 'dumb' phone is sold out, but a similar model is available for $299.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- AI is a prominent topic, with discussions on its impact on the tech industry, job displacement, and evaluation methods.&lt;br&gt;- The business sector is experiencing changes, such as online banking offers and the shift in Airbnb's business model.&lt;br&gt;- Social issues, such as the neglect of Black history and the manipulation of hosts by parasites, are also addressed.&lt;br&gt;- The upcoming major election and the potential disruption of the internet by solar activity are significant concerns.&lt;br&gt;- Consumer trends, like the popularity of limited-edition products, are also mentioned.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, the report highlights the intersection of technology, business, and societal issues, with AI being a central theme. It emphasizes the potential impact of AI on various industries, the changing landscape of businesses, and the importance of addressing social and environmental challenges.</summary></entry></feed>