<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-12T08:03:39Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 12 Nov 2023 08:03:39</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-12T08:03:39Z</published><updated>2023-11-12T08:03:39Z</updated><id>f633b1db-90c2-4fc7-9f8c-d3266976c864</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Prompt Engineering plus AlphaZero: Microsoft's XOT improves LLM's ability to generalize&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's XOT (Cross-Objective Training) enhances the generalization ability of LLM (Language Model) by incorporating prompts and reinforcement learning techniques.&lt;br&gt;- XOT enables LLM to perform better on various tasks and domains, demonstrating improved flexibility and adaptability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. A Rusty CHERI – The path to hardware capabilities in Rust [video]&lt;br&gt;- This video discusses the development of hardware capabilities in the Rust programming language.&lt;br&gt;- Rust's unique features and memory safety make it a promising choice for building secure and efficient hardware systems.&lt;br&gt;- The video explores the challenges and progress in implementing hardware capabilities in Rust.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. SpaceX will launch the X-37B on a Falcon Heavy rocket Dec. 7&lt;br&gt;- SpaceX is scheduled to launch the X-37B spaceplane on December 7 using its Falcon Heavy rocket.&lt;br&gt;- The X-37B is an unmanned spacecraft used for various classified missions by the U.S. Air Force.&lt;br&gt;- This launch demonstrates SpaceX's capabilities in delivering payloads to space.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Creators are complaining that the TikTok Shop is turning the app into an ad-filled wasteland&lt;br&gt;- TikTok creators express concerns about the increasing number of ads on the platform's TikTok Shop feature.&lt;br&gt;- The influx of ads is seen as negatively impacting the user experience and the organic content creators' ability to reach their audience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Wiley College to hold annual 2023 Fall Preview Day - Marshall News Messenger&lt;br&gt;- Wiley College announces its annual Fall Preview Day, providing prospective students with an opportunity to explore the college's programs and campus.&lt;br&gt;- The event aims to attract and engage potential students for the upcoming academic year.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Apple agrees to $25M settlement with US over hiring of immigrants&lt;br&gt;- Apple reaches a settlement with the U.S. government, agreeing to pay $25 million over allegations of discriminatory hiring practices against immigrants.&lt;br&gt;- The settlement resolves claims that Apple favored hiring non-immigrant visa holders over qualified U.S. citizens and permanent residents.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. Researchers from China Propose iTransformer: Rethinking Transformer Architecture for Enhanced Time Series Forecasting&lt;br&gt;- Chinese researchers propose iTransformer, a novel architecture for time series forecasting based on the Transformer model.&lt;br&gt;- iTransformer incorporates attention mechanisms and self-supervised learning techniques to improve the accuracy and efficiency of time series predictions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Are You Doing Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) for Biomedicine? Meet MedCPT: A Contrastive Pre-trained Transformer Model for Zero-Shot Biomedical Information Retrieval&lt;br&gt;- Introducing MedCPT, a pre-trained Transformer model designed for zero-shot biomedical information retrieval using the Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) framework.&lt;br&gt;- MedCPT demonstrates promising results in retrieving relevant biomedical information and can assist in various medical research tasks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's XOT shows the potential for improving language models' generalization abilities, making them more versatile in various tasks and domains.&lt;br&gt;- Rust's development in hardware capabilities opens up new possibilities for building secure and efficient hardware systems.&lt;br&gt;- SpaceX's upcoming launch of the X-37B highlights its capabilities in delivering payloads to space.&lt;br&gt;- Concerns arise among TikTok creators regarding the increasing number of ads on the platform's TikTok Shop.&lt;br&gt;- Wiley College's Fall Preview Day aims to attract prospective students for the upcoming academic year.&lt;br&gt;- Apple's settlement over hiring practices sheds light on the issue of discrimination against immigrants.&lt;br&gt;- iTransformer and MedCPT showcase advancements in AI models for time series forecasting and biomedical information retrieval, respectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report highlights advancements and developments in technology, business, and AI, showcasing the potential for innovation and addressing challenges in various fields.</summary></entry></feed>