<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-26T20:01:40Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 26 Jan 2024 20:01:40</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-26T20:01:40Z</published><updated>2024-01-26T20:01:40Z</updated><id>6e3030f3-ff13-42ff-b67d-4e1f9ccef057</id><summary type="html">In Europe, there is a focus on economic security, with the need for a plan that encompasses both defensive and offensive strategies. Meanwhile, the estate of late comedian George Carlin has filed a lawsuit against the creators of an AI-generated special featuring his likeness. In the UK, an antitrust probe has been launched into the proposed $19 billion merger between Vodafone and Three. In a surprising move, Elon Musk's SpaceX has acquired a Boeing 737 with a mysterious livery, leaving many puzzled about the purpose behind this purchase. Salesforce, a prominent tech company, has reportedly laid off 700 employees, joining the trend of job cuts in the industry. A relatively unknown electric vehicle company has managed to surpass Tesla's popularity in the US market. Royal Caribbean has pushed the boundaries of cruise ship design, fitting an absurd number of amenities, including 7 pools, 6 waterslides, and an ice skating rink, onto their latest vessel. A sci-fi device has been developed that can accurately predict the shelf life of an avocado. The stunning apartment of renowned art director George Lois is up for sale for $6 million, offering a glimpse into his creative world. Microsoft's Xbox mobile apps will soon introduce touch controls for remote play. Action bots are expected to play a significant role in the next evolution of enterprise AI. In a tragic incident, Kenneth Smith endured a 22-minute struggle for life during an Alabama execution involving nitrogen gas. Genetic testing company 23andMe recently discovered that hackers had stolen customer data from their accounts, a breach that took them five months to detect.</summary></entry></feed>