<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-14T20:02:18Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 14 Sep 2023 20:02:18</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-14T20:02:18Z</published><updated>2023-09-14T20:02:18Z</updated><id>a75fb222-0930-4e05-ba48-b86c827058e9</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- All eyes are on ARM as the chipmaker prepares for its IPO, testing confidence in the AI boom.&lt;br&gt;- Electric Hydrogen receives its first firm order for its unique 100MW electrolyser.&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI plans to open its first EU office as it prepares for regulatory hurdles.&lt;br&gt;- The role of generative AI in the next phase of middleware.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- ProShare Advisors LLC sells 61054 shares of John Wiley &amp; Sons.&lt;br&gt;- US commercial-property crisis deepens with office vacancy rate hitting a new record.&lt;br&gt;- Calif. passes strongest right-to-repair bill yet, requiring 7 years of parts.&lt;br&gt;- Binance's CEO sees signing up another 100 million crypto users as a big challenge.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- All eyes are on ARM as the chipmaker prepares for its IPO, testing confidence in the AI boom.&lt;br&gt;- The role of generative AI in the next phase of middleware.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Personal loan interest rates remain steady at 4.60%.&lt;br&gt;- I stopped saving much for retirement and found 3 more important things to spend money on.&lt;br&gt;- Earth's mysterious core may be encased by an ancient ocean floor with mountains 5 times taller than Everest.&lt;br&gt;- Apple's new iPhone 15 disappoints fans.&lt;br&gt;- Video shows Lauren Boebert giving the middle finger after being kicked out of a performance.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk and his siblings put tiny firecrackers in a boyfriend's cigarettes, book says.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk had to take random drug tests after smoking weed on a podcast.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk refuses to answer if he is responsible for dead Ukrainians.&lt;br&gt;- What it's like to be a ski patroller in an expensive mountain town.&lt;br&gt;- What the Luddites can teach us about the next tech rebellion.&lt;br&gt;- Israel's startup funding drops as its cyber sector takes a hit.&lt;br&gt;- Arm shares set to start trading in biggest IPO in almost 2 years.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk rebuked by Taiwan after appearing to defend the one-China policy.&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway sells $158 million of HP stock in 3 days.&lt;br&gt;- The stock market bull run is in its twilight, says Fidelity's global macro head.&lt;br&gt;- Mortgage interest rates inch up, but they should fall as inflation slows.&lt;br&gt;- An American in Sweden is shocked to see a baby alone in a stroller.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The IPO of ARM is a significant event for the AI industry and will test investor confidence.&lt;br&gt;- Generative AI is playing a crucial role in the development of middleware.&lt;br&gt;- The commercial-property crisis in the US is deepening, with office vacancy rates reaching new highs.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's actions and statements continue to generate controversy and speculation.&lt;br&gt;- The right-to-repair movement gains momentum with California passing a strong bill.&lt;br&gt;- The tech rebellion and the impact of automation on jobs are topics of interest.&lt;br&gt;- The global macro head at Fidelity believes the stock market bull run is nearing its end.&lt;br&gt;- Interest rates for personal loans and mortgages are fluctuating.&lt;br&gt;- Cultural differences and observations can be surprising when moving to a new country.</summary></entry></feed>