<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2023-12-17T20:01:54Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 17 Dec 2023 20:01:54</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-17T20:01:54Z</published><updated>2023-12-17T20:01:54Z</updated><id>5429cfa9-1770-4662-8b0d-af385939e5a6</id><summary type="html">In recent news, a TikTok user shared their experience of getting paid to let other users decide how they spent their money for a month. The choices made by the TikTok community surprised them. Meanwhile, Tucker Carlson and Elon Musk have shown support for an American 'red pill' dating coach who has turned into a Russian propagandist and is currently detained in Ukraine. In a lighter story, someone attended IKEA's all-you-can-eat annual Swedish Christmas feast, known as 'Julbord,' in New York City after purchasing a $20 ticket. They shared their experience of the event. In Colorado, two planes narrowly avoided colliding on a runway thanks to a pilot's quick-thinking maneuver. The top 5 ads of 2023 were also revealed, with Apple receiving criticism for having the worst one. In the tech world, Upstage unveiled a new language model called Solar-10.7B, which aims to enhance single-turn conversations. Additionally, a paper survey discussed the role of large language models in medicine. Tragically, the billionaire founder of China's AI giant SenseTime passed away at the age of 55 due to an unknown illness. On a lighter note, a study involving mice wearing VR goggles provided insights into the workings of our brains. The CEO of Epic Games expressed concerns about Google potentially stifling Play Store competitors. AWS made improvements to Kubernetes monitoring and introduced a free tier API to help developers avoid unexpected bills. Kinara introduced the Ara-2 Processor, which aims to revolutionize on-device AI processing for enhanced performance. In politics, Democrat Wiley Nickel announced his departure from Congress after redistricting, setting up a potential Senate run in 2026. Miranda Watson from Benjamin Wiley Charter School received the Golden Apple Award. In a different story, a sleuth discovered a paper mill through fishy email addresses. A former Amazon engineer pleaded guilty to stealing $12.3 million of cryptocurrency in the first-ever hacking case involving smart contracts. NTU researchers unveiled Upscale-A-Video, a text-guided latent diffusion technique for enhanced video super-resolution. Another AI paper introduced Perseus, a framework for reducing energy consumption in large-scale machine learning and AI model training. Americans have been experiencing delays in receiving instant payments, and the reasons behind this were explored. A new super-simple to-do app called NowDo was shared with the community. Tesla's recall of its Autosteer technology could potentially strengthen lawsuits claiming the feature is dangerous. Climate change is threatening the future of Senegalese herders who have been raising livestock for centuries. The potential of APIs was discussed in-depth, with a focus on POSTMAN API 101. The AWS community team expressed gratitude for another year in the community. In the gaming world, 'Homeworld 3' showcased its stunning visuals in a new mini-documentary. The US Congress has postponed the decision on warrantless wiretapping until April next year. Lastly, the Wordle puzzle for December 17th was shared, along with the obituary of Raymond Beard and the achievement of Grambling women's basketball team in passing the century mark on Education Day.</summary></entry></feed>