<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-24T08:03:32Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 24 Jan 2024 08:03:32</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-24T08:03:32Z</published><updated>2024-01-24T08:03:32Z</updated><id>4f613e66-d608-4457-82cf-a3b0b14170b0</id><summary type="html">In recent news, Google has decided to cancel its contract with an AI data firm that has been instrumental in training Bard, an artificial intelligence system. This move by Google showcases the company's commitment to reassessing its partnerships and ensuring ethical practices in AI development. In another development, Netflix has taken a dig at Amazon's Prime Video, emphasizing that they do not "force" viewers to watch advertisements. This statement highlights Netflix's dedication to providing an ad-free streaming experience for its subscribers. However, controversy has arisen as members of the black community and scientists express their objections to a plan that involves burying skulls from a Philadelphia museum. This plan has sparked a debate regarding the ethical treatment of historical artifacts. On a positive note, Netflix's Q4 earnings report reveals that their password crackdown initiative has been successful, resulting in a surge of subscribers and record-breaking numbers. Additionally, a new word puzzle game called 'Wordle' has provided hints and clues for its Wednesday edition, engaging puzzle enthusiasts. In the tech world, a new codemod library called Codemodder has been introduced for Java and Python, offering developers a valuable tool for code modification. Shifting gears, a fashion article suggests considering alternative luxury handbags for the year 2024, highlighting the desire for uniqueness rather than following popular trends. Lastly, individuals seeking guidance on handling CORS issues when deploying a NodeJS Express app on Vercel can find helpful information in a tech-related discussion. Furthermore, there is growing evidence indicating that ADT is preparing to launch a new smart home security system, indicating advancements in the field of home security technology.</summary></entry></feed>