<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-14T18:01:28Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 14 Aug 2023 18:01:28</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-14T18:01:28Z</published><updated>2023-08-14T18:01:28Z</updated><id>27c4e5c3-73c6-42ef-ab04-e97ea09166b8</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Firefox's Android app is getting proper support for extensions once again.&lt;br&gt;- Momentum, a DIY 12-voice virtual analogue polyphonic synthesizer based on TSynth.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers at Boston University release the Platypus Family of Fine-Tuned LLMs for cheap, fast, and powerful refinement of base LLMs.&lt;br&gt;- AI startup Anthropic raises $100M from Korean telco giant SK Telecom.&lt;br&gt;- IBM Researchers introduce an Analog AI Chip for deep learning inference, showcasing critical building blocks of a scalable mixed-signal architecture.&lt;br&gt;- Unlocking the Power of Ethereum Tokens: A Guide to Raising Funds for Your Business.&lt;br&gt;- Elevate Your Python Skills: Machine Learning Packages That Transformed My Journey as an ML Engineer.&lt;br&gt;- To navigate the age of AI, the world needs a new Turing test.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The support for extensions in Firefox's Android app is a positive development for users who rely on these extensions for enhanced browsing experiences.&lt;br&gt;- Momentum's DIY synthesizer offers music enthusiasts the opportunity to create their own polyphonic synthesizer.&lt;br&gt;- The Platypus Family of Fine-Tuned LLMs from Boston University provides a cost-effective solution for refining base LLMs.&lt;br&gt;- Anthropic's $100M investment from SK Telecom highlights the growing interest in AI startups.&lt;br&gt;- IBM's Analog AI Chip showcases advancements in deep learning inference and mixed-signal architecture.&lt;br&gt;- The guide on raising funds for businesses through Ethereum tokens provides valuable insights for entrepreneurs.&lt;br&gt;- The article on Python machine learning packages offers practical advice for ML engineers.&lt;br&gt;- The need for a new Turing test reflects the evolving landscape of AI and the challenges it presents.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- How to become a UPS driver, which now pays $170,000 a year when including benefits.&lt;br&gt;- Aritzia's mirrorless dressing rooms cause outrage online but seem to be a brilliant sales tactic.&lt;br&gt;- Downtowns are in decline, leading to the rise of 'donut cities'.&lt;br&gt;- Gartner says less than 10% of HR functions are achieving functional excellence.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The high salary and benefits offered to UPS drivers make it an attractive career option.&lt;br&gt;- Aritzia's mirrorless dressing rooms generate controversy but also drive sales through innovative customer experiences.&lt;br&gt;- The decline of downtown areas and the emergence of 'donut cities' reflect changing urban dynamics.&lt;br&gt;- Gartner's findings highlight the need for improvement in HR functions to achieve functional excellence.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers at Boston University release the Platypus Family of Fine-Tuned LLMs for cheap, fast, and powerful refinement of base LLMs.&lt;br&gt;- AI startup Anthropic raises $100M from Korean telco giant SK Telecom.&lt;br&gt;- To navigate the age of AI, the world needs a new Turing test.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The Platypus Family of Fine-Tuned LLMs offers a valuable tool for refining base LLMs in the field of AI.&lt;br&gt;- Anthropic's significant investment from SK Telecom demonstrates the growing interest and potential in AI startups.&lt;br&gt;- The need for a new Turing test reflects the challenges and ethical considerations surrounding AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry continues to witness advancements in various areas, including browser extensions, synthesizers, AI chips, and machine learning packages.&lt;br&gt;- The business sector explores topics such as career opportunities, innovative sales tactics, urban dynamics, and HR functional excellence.&lt;br&gt;- AI remains a prominent field, with developments in fine-tuning LLMs, AI startup investments, and the need for ethical considerations.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report highlights the ongoing progress and challenges in the tech, business, and AI sectors.</summary></entry></feed>