<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-30T08:03:42Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 30 Nov 2023 08:03:42</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-30T08:03:42Z</published><updated>2023-11-30T08:03:42Z</updated><id>45a619ec-21cb-4aca-9c72-2af4ef9f6042</id><summary type="html">In the world, there have been various news stories making headlines. One topic of discussion is the debate over what matters more when recruiting, wages or benefits. This has been a point of contention for many employers and job seekers. In another news story, a man accused of attempted murder testified that he did not intend to kill or harm an Upper Merion police officer during a shooting at a mall. The case has been closely followed by the public. Marcellus Wiley, a prominent figure, has responded to sexual assault allegations, dismissing them as "BS." On the financial front, Hotchkis &amp; Wiley has capitalized on Discover Financial Services in the third quarter, making significant gains. In a technological breakthrough, it has been discovered that some electric vehicles can charge while they drive, thanks to special coils installed under a street in Detroit. This development could revolutionize the electric vehicle industry. Moving on to politics, JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon has expressed his belief that the term "ultra-MAGA" is insulting to a large group of people. In international news, Ukraine has captured a radar during a daring oil platform assault, which it is now using to track Russian warships. This development highlights the ongoing tensions between the two nations. Shifting gears, a millennial mom has broken down the Gen Z trends she refuses to adopt, from "chunky" dad shoes to laminated eyebrows. In the business world, it has been revealed that Disney's Bob Iger was merely testing the waters when he floated the idea of selling ABC. Meanwhile, Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang has made a bold prediction, stating that artificial general intelligence will be achieved in the next five years. In a bizarre incident, an American Airlines passenger is facing charges after a chaotic meltdown before takeoff, as detailed in a wild police report. The world of finance also saw Deutsche Bank praising Donald Trump as a lucrative "whale" in internal documents, despite the ongoing fraud trial involving the former president. Tragedy struck as a high-ranking Russian general was killed by a landmine in Ukraine, with reports suggesting that his own military may have placed it. In the tech industry, Amazon has unveiled Graviton4, a powerful ARM CPU with impressive memory bandwidth. Jerry, a startup from Y Combinator, is currently hiring for various roles, including VP Product, engineers, and product managers. The CEOs of Meta, X, TikTok, Snap, and Discord are set to testify before the US Senate on child safety, highlighting the growing concerns surrounding online platforms. In other news, Evernote is set to limit its plan for free users, potentially impacting its user base. Windows 11 is testing an energy saver mode for both laptops and desktop PCs, aiming to improve energy efficiency. Google's Nest cameras now have the ability to notify users when their garage door is left open, enhancing home security. However, there has been controversy as a streaming service has been telling friends and family what users are watching, leaving many horrified. On a lighter note, TikTok users have embraced a new trend of creating Christmas wish list PowerPoint decks from their kids. In a legal update, a Philadelphia man has been convicted of the attempted murder of an Upper Merion police officer during a shooting at a mall. The verdict brings closure to a highly publicized case. The National Telecommunications and Information Administration (NTIA) is seeking input and meetings on the implementation plan for a national initiative, seeking to gather valuable insights. In another incident involving law enforcement, a man from Southwest Philly who shot at a cop outside the King of Prussia Mall has been arrested. The Office of Management and Budget (OMB) has issued updated guidance on implementing the Build America, Buy America policy, aiming to promote domestic manufacturing. O'Reilly has launched digital badges for expert-led learning, providing a new way for individuals to showcase their skills. In a surprising move, a ransomware attacker has filed an SEC complaint to increase pressure on their victims. Spotify Wrapped, a popular feature, now includes the ability to see which city shares your taste in music, adding a fun element to the annual tradition. In the automotive industry, Tesla is reportedly losing ground in the electric vehicle market, with its future heavily reliant on the success of the Cybertruck. Lastly, Nvidia CEO has revealed that he wakes up every morning worried that his company might fail, highlighting the pressures faced by industry leaders. These news stories provide a glimpse into the diverse events happening around the world.</summary></entry></feed>