<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-19T02:01:12Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 19 Aug 2023 02:01:12</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-19T02:01:12Z</published><updated>2023-08-19T02:01:12Z</updated><id>3c10ef50-1c31-4601-9a98-bb5795788af5</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- A beginner's guide to YouTube TV, a live TV app with over 100 channels and unlimited DVR&lt;br&gt;- An AI weapons race may create a world where everyone stays inside out of fear of being 'chased down by swarms of slaughterbots,' warns founding Skype engineer&lt;br&gt;- Here’s how Bambu will fix its 3D printers that began printing by themselves&lt;br&gt;- TechCrunch+ Roundup: Reaching $1M ARR, tech job market rundown, women-led VC firms&lt;br&gt;- Google's Apparently Building an AI That Tells You How to Live Your Life&lt;br&gt;- AI No Longer A Techie’s Playground: Now, Everyone Needs To Take Charge&lt;br&gt;- Unveiling The Dark Side Of Artificial Intelligence In The Job Market&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech section highlights the growing influence and impact of artificial intelligence in various aspects of life, including entertainment, warfare, and personal decision-making. It also emphasizes the need for individuals to understand and take charge of AI technologies. The section raises concerns about the potential negative consequences of AI, such as privacy invasion and job market disruption.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Robert Kennedy Jr. and his wife Cheryl Hines are worth an estimated $15 million, according to Forbes&lt;br&gt;- Restorative justice can be cheaper and more effective than jail time at preventing reoffences. An innovative Philadelphia program for youth has a 100% success rate.&lt;br&gt;- Rupert Murdoch's new girlfriend always had a touch of glamour even as a research scientist in the 2000s, former colleague says&lt;br&gt;- As net retention plummets, AI could be the savior software companies need&lt;br&gt;- Amazon tries to boost its TikTok-like shopping feed by asking influencers to submit videos — for $25 each&lt;br&gt;- A $40,000 Nvidia chip has become the world's most sought-after hardware&lt;br&gt;- Advice from LinkedIn's COO on how to hold on to great employees&lt;br&gt;- Could Trump Be Forced To Shut Down Truth Social If Convicted Or Elected?&lt;br&gt;- How Women Benefited From The Inflation Reduction Act – Year One&lt;br&gt;- Kentucky Retirement Systems Sells 1188 Shares of Walmart Inc ... - MarketBeat&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business section covers a range of topics, including wealth and celebrity profiles, criminal justice alternatives, AI in business, influencer marketing, and economic policies. It highlights the importance of restorative justice and the potential benefits of AI in the software industry. The section also touches on political and social issues related to the Trump administration and gender equality in the workforce.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- An AI weapons race may create a world where everyone stays inside out of fear of being 'chased down by swarms of slaughterbots,' warns founding Skype engineer&lt;br&gt;- AI No Longer A Techie’s Playground: Now, Everyone Needs To Take Charge&lt;br&gt;- Unveiling The Dark Side Of Artificial Intelligence In The Job Market&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The AI section focuses on the potential dangers and ethical implications of AI technology. It raises concerns about the militarization of AI and the need for individuals to understand and take responsibility for AI systems. The section also highlights the negative impact of AI on job markets and the potential for bias and discrimination.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;The report highlights the increasing influence and impact of artificial intelligence in various aspects of life, including entertainment, warfare, business, and job markets. It emphasizes the need for individuals to understand and take charge of AI technologies to mitigate potential negative consequences. The report also touches on topics such as wealth and celebrity profiles, criminal justice alternatives, political issues, and gender equality in the workforce. Overall, it provides a comprehensive overview of current trends and concerns in the tech, business, and AI sectors.</summary></entry></feed>