<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-27T08:03:35Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 27 Nov 2023 08:03:35</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-27T08:03:35Z</published><updated>2023-11-27T08:03:35Z</updated><id>0e8aa801-6068-4026-a847-fa2ebaa7a503</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- The 30 best Apple Cyber Monday 2023 deals on MacBooks, AirPods, Apple Watches, and iPads&lt;br&gt;- Cisco aids Ukraine defense with modified switches to counter Russian attacks&lt;br&gt;- Redefining Transformers: How Simple Feed-Forward Neural Networks Can Mimic Attention Mechanisms for Efficient Sequence-to-Sequence Tasks&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech section highlights the latest deals on Apple products, the use of technology in defense against cyber attacks, and advancements in neural networks for efficient tasks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Wiley reflects on Arizona's past struggles after Territorial Cup win - 247Sports&lt;br&gt;- Meta 'misled' the public through a campaign that downplayed the amount harmful content on Instagram and Facebook, court documents show&lt;br&gt;- India’s EMotorad rides high with $20M investment for global e-bike push&lt;br&gt;- An editor resigned in protest. Now, Wiley is firing him four months ... - Retraction Watch&lt;br&gt;- A retiring Democratic congressman laments the 'absolute chaos' of the current session that he says contributed to his decision to forgo reelection&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business section covers various topics such as sports, social media controversies, investments in e-bikes, and internal conflicts within organizations. It also highlights the challenges faced by politicians in the current political climate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Redefining Transformers: How Simple Feed-Forward Neural Networks Can Mimic Attention Mechanisms for Efficient Sequence-to-Sequence Tasks&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The AI section focuses on the advancements in neural networks and their potential to mimic attention mechanisms for more efficient tasks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Museum of Fine Arts Houston exhibition melds classical, contemporary - Beaumont Enterprise&lt;br&gt;- Queer allyship figures prominently in Streisand memoir - Los Angeles Blade&lt;br&gt;- A holiday book for Christmas lovers and haters alike - Los Angeles Blade&lt;br&gt;- Take a look inside Singapore's public housing estates, where 80% of the resident population resides&lt;br&gt;- IDF 'rejuvenation complex' near Gaza has concerts, massage chairs, buffet, and more &amp;mdash; a stark contrast to the horrors of the conflict zone&lt;br&gt;- A group of Black voters recently sounded off on Biden, Trump, and their feelings about Democrats. One voter said the party 'has forgot about the Black male.'&lt;br&gt;- Los Angeles is defined by its deep-rooted car culture. Could the recent I-10 freeway fire make Angelenos rethink that relationship?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The other section covers a wide range of topics including art exhibitions, memoirs, holiday books, public housing, conflicts in war zones, political opinions, and the impact of recent events on car culture. It provides a diverse perspective on various aspects of society.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The report highlights key news articles from different categories such as tech, business, AI, and others. It covers a range of topics including technology deals, defense against cyber attacks, advancements in neural networks, sports, social media controversies, investments, internal conflicts, art exhibitions, memoirs, public housing, conflicts in war zones, political opinions, and the impact of recent events on car culture. The insights gathered from these articles showcase the current trends, challenges, and developments in various fields.</summary></entry></feed>