<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2023-12-13T20:02:09Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 13 Dec 2023 20:02:09</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-13T20:02:09Z</published><updated>2023-12-13T20:02:09Z</updated><id>9cbc2b38-f632-4c31-b5b8-9b9b1e68e394</id><summary type="html">In recent news, there has been a significant trend of Gen Zers and millennials leaving California and moving to states like Texas and Arizona. These individuals, who typically earn around $53,500 a year, are seeking new opportunities and a lower cost of living. Meanwhile, in New York City, the largest-ever office building is being transformed into homes, providing a glimpse into the changing real estate landscape. On a different note, a global president at Mars Snacking shares insights into their daily routine, starting at 5:30 a.m., and describes their headquarters as resembling 'Charlie and the Chocolate Factory.' In a surprising turn of events, a fantasy author admits to creating eight fake Goodreads accounts to sabotage her competitors after being dropped by her publisher. Additionally, an OpenAI investor warns that people should be more concerned about China than the potential threat of a sentient AI. In the retail industry, a former employee of Louis Vuitton reveals how they dealt with customers attempting to return fake bags. Furthermore, a Stanford professor cautions that fully remote workers are at the highest risk of being replaced by AI. Tesla's first Cybertrucks are priced at $120,000, indicating that more affordable options may still be a while away. Germany is selling its Airbus A340 'Merkel One' aircraft due to mechanical failures, while an open-source alternative to Jira called Plane reaches the number one spot on GitHub. The COP28 Climate Summit marks the beginning of the end for the fossil fuel era, signaling a shift towards cleaner energy sources. In the tech world, discussions range from adding distributed tracing using Jaeger and OpenTelemetry to Golang applications, to the impact of cloud zombies on the environment. Additionally, a Gartner survey reveals that 45% of organizations have experienced business interruptions due to third-party-related issues. AI research focuses on large language models (LLMs) and their applications on graphs, while Together AI introduces StripedHyena-7B, an alternative artificial intelligence model. Lastly, a modular apartment complex in Pittsburgh aims to revolutionize housing construction, and Midjourney launches an alpha version for AI image generation on the web. These diverse developments highlight the ever-changing landscape of our world.</summary></entry></feed>