<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-15T16:01:28Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 15 Aug 2023 16:01:28</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-15T16:01:28Z</published><updated>2023-08-15T16:01:28Z</updated><id>7e16c3d9-1269-4350-ad4d-f8790281779a</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Aqara's new Zigbee light strip supports HomeKit Adaptive Lighting and Matter.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: Aqara has released a new Zigbee light strip that is compatible with HomeKit Adaptive Lighting and Matter.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: This new product allows users to control their lighting with greater flexibility and integration with other smart home devices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Amazon introduces AWS HealthImaging to store and analyze medical imaging data.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: Amazon has launched AWS HealthImaging, a service that enables the storage and analysis of medical imaging data.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: This service provides healthcare professionals with a secure and scalable solution for managing and leveraging medical imaging data for diagnosis and treatment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Why downsizing large language models is the future of generative AI.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: Downsizing large language models is seen as the future of generative AI.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: By reducing the size and computational requirements of language models, they can be deployed more efficiently and effectively in various applications, leading to advancements in natural language processing and generation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Trump would have to serve 5 years in prison before he can be pardoned in Georgia criminal case, expert says.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: According to an expert, Trump would need to serve 5 years in prison before being eligible for a pardon in his Georgia criminal case.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: This highlights the potential legal consequences and limitations of presidential pardons, even after leaving office.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Georgia prosecutors are using 12 tweets of Trump's as part of its RICO charge against Trump and associates.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: Georgia prosecutors are utilizing 12 tweets from Trump as evidence in their RICO charge against him and his associates.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: This demonstrates the increasing use of social media content as evidence in legal cases, particularly in cases involving influential figures.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. DeepMind researchers introduce AlphaStar Unplugged: A leap forward in large-scale offline reinforcement learning by mastering the real-time strategy game StarCraft II.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: DeepMind researchers have made significant progress in offline reinforcement learning by developing AlphaStar Unplugged, which has mastered the complex game of StarCraft II.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: This advancement showcases the potential of AI in mastering complex tasks and games, paving the way for further developments in reinforcement learning algorithms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. What coal and Jevons' paradox tell us about AI and data.&lt;br&gt;- Key point: The relationship between coal consumption and Jevons' paradox can provide insights into the implications of AI and data usage.&lt;br&gt;- Insight: Just as increased efficiency in coal consumption led to increased overall consumption, the efficient use of AI and data may also lead to increased demand and usage, highlighting the need for responsible and ethical AI practices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section highlights advancements in smart home devices and medical imaging data management, showcasing the ongoing development and integration of technology in various industries.&lt;br&gt;- The business section sheds light on the potential legal consequences for influential figures and the use of social media content as evidence in legal cases.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section showcases the progress made in reinforcement learning and the implications of AI and data usage, emphasizing the need for responsible and ethical practices.</summary></entry></feed>