<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-31T08:03:13Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 31 Aug 2023 08:03:13</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-31T08:03:13Z</published><updated>2023-08-31T08:03:13Z</updated><id>18c4bbba-4eb8-4ceb-994c-bfca9e1e37f0</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Sennheiser has released a new soundbar that is smaller and cheaper than previous models.&lt;br&gt;- Apple has launched a new event page for the release of the iPhone 15.&lt;br&gt;- Tesla is under investigation by the DOJ and SEC for its secretive "Project 42".&lt;br&gt;- The US Copyright Office is working on new rules for generative AI.&lt;br&gt;- Mux, a video infrastructure company, is hiring a Senior Platform Engineer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- The Global Professional Development Market is projected to grow by USD 21,958.09 million during 2022-2027, with a CAGR of 7.83%.&lt;br&gt;- The Global Test Preparation Market is expected to grow by USD 46,860.24 million during 2022-2027, with a CAGR of 6.88%.&lt;br&gt;- Poland is making significant purchases of tanks and helicopters, possibly inspired by the US Army.&lt;br&gt;- A Memphis plant that uses potentially hazardous chemicals will be closing.&lt;br&gt;- A Texas judge has ruled a law limiting the power of Democrat-led cities as unconstitutional.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- The US Copyright Office is working on new rules for generative AI.&lt;br&gt;- AI21 Labs, a generative AI startup, has raised $155 million at a valuation of $1.4 billion.&lt;br&gt;- DenseDiffusion, a training-free AI technique, aims to address dense captions and layout manipulation in text-to-image generation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- An elite team of Ukrainian snipers, known as "Devils and Angels," is targeting top Russian commanders to demoralize troops.&lt;br&gt;- A passenger went overboard from Royal Caribbean's Wonder of the Seas, the largest operating cruise ship in the world.&lt;br&gt;- Interstellar debris falling to the sea floor is met with skepticism.&lt;br&gt;- The Pacific metal discovered is believed to be beyond extraterrestrial.&lt;br&gt;- The best ways to earn credit card points on rent and mortgage payments are discussed.&lt;br&gt;- Pot stocks have surged as a federal agency reportedly seeks to downgrade cannabis from the hard-drug category.&lt;br&gt;- An indicator of Americans' willingness to gamble suggests resilience in the US economy.</summary></entry></feed>