<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-25T08:03:27Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 25 Nov 2023 08:03:27</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-25T08:03:27Z</published><updated>2023-11-25T08:03:27Z</updated><id>9b6875a4-376d-49b5-b17f-8ebd3688ed7c</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Show HN: IP Guide – info on IP addresses, Networks, and ASNs&lt;br&gt;- Asus Intros GeForce RTX 4060 Ti Video Card with Integrated M.2 SSD Slot&lt;br&gt;- How to get notified of newly connected devices on your OpenWRT router&lt;br&gt;- Show HN: Perfect Pitch Puzzle – a musical Wordle daily ear training game&lt;br&gt;- Android Circuit: Galaxy Unpacked Dates, Redmagic 9 Pro Launch, Pixel 8 Pro Problems&lt;br&gt;- Fire TV now also displays full-screen video ads on its homescreen&lt;br&gt;- Lean Startup y MVPs: Soluciones Ágiles para el Desarrollo de Software&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- IP Guide provides information on IP addresses, networks, and ASNs.&lt;br&gt;- Asus has introduced a new video card with an integrated M.2 SSD slot.&lt;br&gt;- OpenWRT router users can learn how to receive notifications for newly connected devices.&lt;br&gt;- Perfect Pitch Puzzle is a musical Wordle game for daily ear training.&lt;br&gt;- Android Circuit highlights Galaxy Unpacked dates, Redmagic 9 Pro launch, and Pixel 8 Pro problems.&lt;br&gt;- Fire TV now displays full-screen video ads on its homescreen.&lt;br&gt;- Lean Startup and MVPs offer agile solutions for software development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section covers a range of topics, including networking, hardware, software, and mobile devices.&lt;br&gt;- The introduction of new products and features in the tech industry is ongoing.&lt;br&gt;- The integration of different technologies, such as video cards and SSDs, is becoming more common.&lt;br&gt;- User experience and advertising are important considerations in tech products and services.&lt;br&gt;- Agile development methodologies like Lean Startup and MVPs are gaining popularity in software development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Why ServiceNow Shares Have Rallied 27% Since The Recent Earnings Report&lt;br&gt;- RMWD General Manager Wiley appointed to SDCWA Board - Fallbrook / Bonsall Villlage News&lt;br&gt;- Former NFL Star Marcellus Wiley Faces Rape Allegations - Black Enterprise&lt;br&gt;- 2024 NFL Draft: Trade Scenarios and Best Prospect Fits for League's Worst Teams - Bleacher Report&lt;br&gt;- RHOBH Newbie Annemarie Wiley's Husband Marcellus Wiley Accused of Raping Fellow Columbia Student in 1994 - Yahoo Entertainment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- ServiceNow shares have experienced a 27% rally following a recent earnings report.&lt;br&gt;- RMWD General Manager Wiley has been appointed to the SDCWA Board.&lt;br&gt;- Former NFL star Marcellus Wiley is facing rape allegations.&lt;br&gt;- The 2024 NFL Draft trade scenarios and best prospect fits are discussed.&lt;br&gt;- Marcellus Wiley, husband of RHOBH newbie Annemarie Wiley, is accused of raping a fellow Columbia student in 1994.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The business section covers a range of topics, including stock market performance, board appointments, and legal issues.&lt;br&gt;- The performance of a company's shares can be influenced by earnings reports.&lt;br&gt;- Individuals in prominent positions may face allegations and legal challenges.&lt;br&gt;- Sports-related events, such as the NFL Draft, generate significant interest and speculation.&lt;br&gt;- Personal and legal issues involving public figures can attract media attention.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Show HN: Perfect Pitch Puzzle – a musical Wordle daily ear training game&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Perfect Pitch Puzzle is an AI-powered game that helps with daily ear training.&lt;br&gt;- The game utilizes AI algorithms to generate musical puzzles for users to solve.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- AI technology is being used in various applications, including gaming and music.&lt;br&gt;- AI algorithms can enhance user experiences and provide personalized challenges.&lt;br&gt;- Daily practice and training can improve skills in specific areas, such as music.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section highlights advancements in networking, hardware, software, and mobile devices.&lt;br&gt;- The business section covers stock market performance, board appointments, and legal issues.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section focuses on an AI-powered game for musical ear training.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report showcases the ongoing developments and challenges in the tech, business, and AI sectors.</summary></entry></feed>