<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-06T08:03:44Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:03:44</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-06T08:03:44Z</published><updated>2023-12-06T08:03:44Z</updated><id>c0dda1e1-6702-49df-a634-4cdc554fbe9a</id><summary type="html">In the world news, there have been several developments across different fields. Dallas County Commissioner John Wiley Price has accused a retiring elections administrator of lying during a presentation. Meanwhile, Brendan Wiley has taken up the position of director at Cameron Park Zoo in Waco. In the field of archaeology, Sudanese textile dyes have confirmed local practices, as reported by John Wiley. Additionally, John Wiley has published research on the separation, identification, and structural characterization of sucrose ester isomers from tobacco, as well as artificial intelligence for surface-enhanced Raman spectroscopy. The winners of the Wiley Analytical Science Award 2024 have also been announced. Moving on to other news, UWorld has acquired Wiley's Efficient Learning Test Prep Portfolio, expanding its offerings in finance and accounting. In the tech world, Meta's top AI scientist has reportedly warned Mark Zuckerberg about the potential extinction of Facebook and Instagram if they don't catch up with ChatGPT. The recent conflict between Israel and Hamas has highlighted the limitations of tank upgrades. In entertainment news, Playstation is removing 1,318 seasons of Discovery shows from customer libraries. The Governor of Amazonas is seeking to charge Amazon royalties for the use of its brand. Other news includes a bug on Reddit that allows slurs to be added to its links, DNA analysis of polar bear snowprints, and the nomination of the "How to Fix the Internet" podcast for an Anthem Award. CVS has announced changes in the way its pharmacies are paid. In the field of science, a study published by John Wiley explores the effect of adventitious contamination on Pt photoemission peak intensities. On a somber note, the obituary of Dorothy Wiley has been published. Artist Kehinde Wiley has released new limited-edition prints to fund his Dakar artist residency. The CEO of Young's Jersey Dairy has received a major award from the Ohio Restaurant Association. The city has honored Wiley Hughey of OIDC, and Rep. Wiley Nickel has discussed congressional news on Washington Journal. Former NFL star Marcellus Wiley has been accused of rape in a lawsuit and has denied the allegations. In sports, Wiley Killham's hot start led West Plains to victory over Plainview. Lastly, John Wiley &amp; Sons has had a strong week in the stock market, although it doesn't alleviate the pain of a five-year loss. The prosecution has rested its case in the Wiley murder trial, with a medical witness testifying that abuse head trauma caused the infant's death.</summary></entry></feed>