<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-13T06:01:14Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 13 Aug 2023 06:01:14</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-13T06:01:14Z</published><updated>2023-08-13T06:01:14Z</updated><id>88156aca-dfd3-48d1-ac09-930c7dbf1973</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Freshpaint (YC S19) Is Hiring Engineers to Build a HIPAA Compliant Data Platform&lt;br&gt;- Researchers jailbreak a Tesla, the FCC fines robocallers and WeWork finds itself in trouble (again)&lt;br&gt;- Moderation on a popular AI image generator can be easily circumvented to create images that drive conspiracy theories, new report finds&lt;br&gt;- 'The most stunning demo I've ever seen in my life': ChatGPT impressed Bill Gates by acing AP Bio exam&lt;br&gt;- Tracing the roots of the 8086 instruction set to the Datapoint 2200 minicomputer&lt;br&gt;- Paper investigating police chief prior to the raids on his office and home&lt;br&gt;- A core plank of the SaaS economic model is under extreme pressure&lt;br&gt;- Dissecting the UN Cybercrime Convention’s Threat to Coders’ Rights at DEFCON&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Freshpaint is looking to hire engineers to develop a HIPAA compliant data platform.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers have successfully jailbroken a Tesla, highlighting potential security vulnerabilities.&lt;br&gt;- WeWork is facing more troubles, indicating ongoing challenges for the company.&lt;br&gt;- The moderation system of an AI image generator can be easily bypassed, leading to the creation of conspiracy-driven images.&lt;br&gt;- ChatGPT impressed Bill Gates with its performance on an AP Bio exam.&lt;br&gt;- The 8086 instruction set can be traced back to the Datapoint 2200 minicomputer.&lt;br&gt;- A paper is being investigated regarding a police chief prior to raids on his office and home.&lt;br&gt;- The SaaS economic model is facing significant pressure.&lt;br&gt;- The UN Cybercrime Convention may pose threats to coders' rights.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry continues to face challenges in terms of security vulnerabilities and ethical considerations.&lt;br&gt;- AI technologies require robust moderation systems to prevent the spread of misinformation and conspiracy theories.&lt;br&gt;- The SaaS economic model may need to adapt to changing market conditions.&lt;br&gt;- The UN Cybercrime Convention should be carefully evaluated to ensure it does not infringe on coders' rights.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Georgia Gov. Brian Kemp needles Trump over his refusal to sign a loyalty pledge committing to back the eventual GOP presidential nominee and says the 2024 race is 'too important for political games'&lt;br&gt;- James Carville dismisses concerns that Democrats don't have a strong presidential bench for 2028: 'So many people, it's breathtaking'&lt;br&gt;- The once-mighty Iowa Democratic Party is struggling as the GOP dominates the onetime swing state: 'I can't even describe to you how bad it is'&lt;br&gt;- Congressmen call on Biden to stop Greg Abbott from transporting migrants to Democratic-led cities after a 3-year-old child died on a bus headed from Texas to Chicago&lt;br&gt;- An Uber Eats rider and YouTuber says he's stopped picking up from McDonald's as it treats delivery staff badly and its drinks keep spilling&lt;br&gt;- Saving Our Rainforests - The Business Case For Acting On Nature&lt;br&gt;- Soccer fans caught burning or ripping money in Argentina face up to 30 days in prison as the country cracks down on those mocking its high inflation&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Georgia Gov. Brian Kemp criticizes Trump for not signing a loyalty pledge and emphasizes the importance of the 2024 race.&lt;br&gt;- James Carville dismisses concerns about the Democratic Party's presidential bench for 2028, highlighting the number of potential candidates.&lt;br&gt;- The Iowa Democratic Party is struggling as the GOP gains dominance in the state.&lt;br&gt;- Congressmen are urging Biden to intervene in the transportation of migrants to Democratic-led cities after a child's death.&lt;br&gt;- An Uber Eats rider boycotts McDonald's due to mistreatment of delivery staff and spillage issues.&lt;br&gt;- The business case for protecting rainforests is discussed.&lt;br&gt;- Argentina is cracking down on soccer fans who mock the country's high inflation by burning or ripping money.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Political dynamics and party struggles continue to shape the landscape of US politics.&lt;br&gt;- Ethical concerns and treatment of workers in the gig economy are gaining attention.&lt;br&gt;- Environmental sustainability is becoming a more prominent consideration in business decisions.&lt;br&gt;- Governments are taking action to address economic and social issues, such as high inflation.</summary></entry></feed>