<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-18T08:03:53Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 18 Oct 2023 08:03:53</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-18T08:03:53Z</published><updated>2023-10-18T08:03:53Z</updated><id>6f79f497-7529-4b47-b113-e333a0d95546</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- iPhone 15 Pro deals: The best trade-in prices at Verizon, AT&amp;T, and more&lt;br&gt;- Apple’s latest iOS update could have a big impact on podcast downloads&lt;br&gt;- Dead Space is coming to Xbox Game Pass just in time for Halloween&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella says empathy isn't a soft skill — it's actually 'the hardest skill we learn'&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's CEO on one of the biggest philosophical questions about AI and whether it's manipulating us&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech section highlights updates and developments in the tech industry. It includes information about new iPhone deals, the impact of Apple's iOS update on podcast downloads, the addition of Dead Space to Xbox Game Pass, and insights from Microsoft's CEO on empathy and AI manipulation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Big money donors are slamming Ivy League universities and pulling funding over their response to the Israel-Palestine war&lt;br&gt;- Trump and NY AG Letitia James are fighting hard over one short but incriminating quote from his NY fraud trial&lt;br&gt;- Can Tupperware’s second female CEO in its 77-year history revive the house party?&lt;br&gt;- Chick-fil-A to shell out $4.4 million in cash and gift cards after customers accused it of inflating delivery prices, report says&lt;br&gt;- Markets are misreading Fed officials' comments, and the central bank could still raise rates, analyst warns&lt;br&gt;- Billionaire Ronald Lauder threatens to stop Penn donations unless the school takes a stronger stance against antisemitism&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business section covers a range of topics including the impact of political conflicts on university funding, legal battles involving Trump and the NY AG, Tupperware's new CEO, Chick-fil-A's response to delivery price accusations, market misinterpretations of Fed officials' comments, and a billionaire's threat to stop donations to a university.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella says empathy isn't a soft skill — it's actually 'the hardest skill we learn'&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's CEO on one of the biggest philosophical questions about AI and whether it's manipulating us&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The AI section focuses on insights from Microsoft's CEO regarding the importance of empathy as a skill and the ethical implications of AI manipulation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Moore, Wiley Pace Women's Golf at Lady Red Wolves Classic - MSU Eagles&lt;br&gt;- Warrant issued man found guilty shooting at family driving in Lubbock - LubbockOnline.com&lt;br&gt;- "Stop the self-destruction": Local leaders create 90-day plan to end youth gang violence in North Columbia - WACH.com&lt;br&gt;- Recie Wiley Sr. | Obituaries | baycitytribune.com - Bay City Daily Tribune&lt;br&gt;- Wiley: 'If the Jets are anywhere near contention, Rodgers will be ... - TSN&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine's top general posts first video of Kyiv's forces firing US-made ATACMS at the Russians&lt;br&gt;- Netanyahu deleted a post on X about a struggle against 'children of darkness' around the time of a tragic hospital explosion in Gaza&lt;br&gt;- Detroit: magic wand makes dirty air look clean and lets polluters off the hook&lt;br&gt;- Israel looks to roll out SpaceX Starlink internet amid war with Hamas&lt;br&gt;- Human Rights Watch Executive Director Tirana Hassan takes our career questionnaire&lt;br&gt;- Global profiling of protein lactylation in Caenorhabditis elegans - John Wiley &amp; Sons&lt;br&gt;- Biggest surprises and disappointments for Arizona Wildcats football so far this season - Arizona Desert Swarm&lt;br&gt;- Judge Wiley E. Manuel Lecture and CREJ Visiting Scholar ... - UC Law San Francisco&lt;br&gt;- Acute effects of angler's groundbaits: nutrient flux to water column ... - Nature.com&lt;br&gt;- Photos show the chaos of Jim Jordan's first attempt at becoming speaker of the House&lt;br&gt;- A Russian dissident journalist who is recovering from a suspected poisoning attack explains why Russia must lose in Ukraine&lt;br&gt;- Marc Andreessen is getting raked over the coals for calling social responsibility the 'enemy'&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The other section covers a wide range of topics including sports events, crime news, local initiatives to combat violence, obituaries, political statements, environmental issues, internet infrastructure, human rights, scientific research, sports analysis, lectures, and political controversies. These topics provide a diverse perspective on various current events.</summary></entry></feed>