<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-09T18:01:19Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 09 Aug 2023 18:01:19</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-09T18:01:19Z</published><updated>2023-08-09T18:01:19Z</updated><id>7d9936b2-acc7-4329-af24-5e705fc02aab</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- SEC chairman warns AI could be at the heart of future financial crises: The chairman of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has expressed concerns about the potential risks posed by artificial intelligence (AI) in the financial industry. He warns that AI algorithms could amplify market volatility and lead to financial crises if not properly regulated and monitored.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Amazon has more than half of all Arm server CPUs in the world: Amazon, the e-commerce giant, currently holds over 50% of the global market share for Arm-based server CPUs. This dominance in the market highlights Amazon's growing influence in the cloud computing industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- HAS AI BECOME TOO HUMAN? Researchers At Google AI Find LLMs Can Now Use ML Models And APIs With Just Tool Documentation!: Researchers at Google AI have made significant advancements in language models, enabling them to use machine learning models and application programming interfaces (APIs) with just tool documentation. This development blurs the line between human and AI capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Student-loan payments and steeper interest rates will pave the way for a severe consumer-led recession, top economist David Rosenberg says: Economist David Rosenberg predicts that the combination of high student loan payments and increasing interest rates will lead to a consumer-led recession. He warns that these factors could have a significant impact on the overall economy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Pretiosum Ventures hits first close on its second fund to back infrastructure startups: Pretiosum Ventures, a venture capital firm, has successfully raised the initial funding for its second fund. The firm aims to support infrastructure startups and contribute to their growth and development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- People-centered startups: making employees happy is a key ingredient to success: This article emphasizes the importance of prioritizing employee happiness in startups. It suggests that creating a positive work environment and focusing on employee well-being can lead to greater success and productivity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- SEC chairman warns AI could be at the heart of future financial crises: The chairman of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has expressed concerns about the potential risks posed by artificial intelligence (AI) in the financial industry. He warns that AI algorithms could amplify market volatility and lead to financial crises if not properly regulated and monitored.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- HAS AI BECOME TOO HUMAN? Researchers At Google AI Find LLMs Can Now Use ML Models And APIs With Just Tool Documentation!: Researchers at Google AI have made significant advancements in language models, enabling them to use machine learning models and application programming interfaces (APIs) with just tool documentation. This development blurs the line between human and AI capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- How to get more suggestions from GitHub Copilot: This article provides tips and techniques for maximizing the benefits of GitHub Copilot, an AI-powered code completion tool. It offers insights on how developers can leverage the tool to improve their coding efficiency and productivity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The potential risks of AI in the financial industry: The SEC chairman's warning highlights the need for proper regulation and monitoring of AI algorithms in the financial sector. It emphasizes the importance of ensuring that AI is used responsibly to avoid potential market volatility and financial crises.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The growing dominance of Amazon in the cloud computing industry: Amazon's significant market share in Arm-based server CPUs demonstrates its increasing influence in the cloud computing market. This dominance raises questions about competition and market dynamics in the industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The blurring line between human and AI capabilities: The advancements made by Google AI researchers in language models showcase the increasing capabilities of AI. This development raises ethical and societal questions about the potential impact of AI on various industries and human interactions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall insights:&lt;br&gt;- AI has the potential to revolutionize various industries, but it also poses risks that need to be carefully managed and regulated.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The dominance of tech giants like Amazon in certain sectors raises concerns about competition and market dynamics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Prioritizing employee happiness and well-being can contribute to the success and productivity of startups.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The advancements in AI language models blur the line between human and AI capabilities, raising ethical and societal questions.</summary></entry></feed>