<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-20T08:03:27Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 20 Jan 2024 08:03:27</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-20T08:03:27Z</published><updated>2024-01-20T08:03:27Z</updated><id>320c2ca7-3d3b-4bf9-ba68-ac42563ac692</id><summary type="html">In recent news, hackers managed to breach Microsoft's security systems with the intention of uncovering information about themselves. Meanwhile, Microsoft AI Research has unveiled a new technology called DeepSpeed-FastGen, which aims to enhance the efficiency of LLM serving through an innovative dynamic SplitFuse technique. Additionally, a paper from Google's AI division delves into the intricacies of self-correction in language models, exploring logical errors and the effectiveness of backtracking. On a different note, the S&amp;P 500 has reached a record high after two years, driven by significant investments in artificial intelligence. Despite allegations of a romantic relationship between DA Fani Willis and a prosecutor, experts believe it is unlikely to impact Trump's case. However, it does raise concerns about optics. The No AI Fraud Act has garnered attention, but critics argue that it creates more problems than it solves. Amid backlash, the founder of Selkie defends the use of AI in their new dress collection. In the tech world, Apple Loop highlights leaks about the design of the iPhone 16 Pro, App Store issues, and missing apps in Vision Pro. Meanwhile, Android Circuit covers the unveiling of Galaxy 24, a review of ROG Phone 8, and special offers for Pixel 8 Pro. Returning to the earlier news, hackers targeted Microsoft once again to discover what the company knows about them. Additionally, a Python tutorial explains how to mass import YouTube videos into a Reddit subreddit. Lastly, a Florida GOP leader has been cleared of rape allegations, but he may still face charges related to the illegal recording of the sexual encounter. Apple AI Research has also introduced AIM, a collection of vision models pre-trained with an autoregressive objective.</summary></entry></feed>