<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-15T08:03:42Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 15 Nov 2023 08:03:42</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-15T08:03:42Z</published><updated>2023-11-15T08:03:42Z</updated><id>bfeee4aa-f8e9-4164-ad54-d2fb3a72503c</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- eToro Review 2023: 25 Million Users Worldwide, but is eToro Trustworthy?&lt;br&gt;- Upgraded Tesla Cyberquad for Kids back on sale after safety recall&lt;br&gt;- What OpenAI's latest batch of chips says about the future of AI&lt;br&gt;- Web5 Meets Generative AI: Reimagining the Future of Digital Identity with Netonomy&lt;br&gt;- Artificial Intelligence, the False Claims Act, and the Public Disclosure ... - Wiley Rein&lt;br&gt;- Wiley Edge &amp; Cisco Tech Training – The Global Recruiter - The Global Recruiter&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- eToro has 25 million users worldwide, but its trustworthiness is questioned.&lt;br&gt;- Tesla's Cyberquad for Kids is back on sale after a safety recall.&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's latest batch of chips indicates the future of AI.&lt;br&gt;- Web5 and Netonomy are reimagining the future of digital identity with generative AI.&lt;br&gt;- The False Claims Act and public disclosure are discussed in relation to artificial intelligence.&lt;br&gt;- Wiley Edge and Cisco Tech Training partnership is highlighted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is rapidly evolving with advancements in AI and digital identity.&lt;br&gt;- Trust and safety are important considerations for users of tech platforms.&lt;br&gt;- Partnerships and collaborations are driving innovation in the tech sector.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Academic Partnerships to buy Wiley's OPM business for base price ... - Higher Ed Dive&lt;br&gt;- Margin loans allows you to borrow against securities you already own to make additional investments&lt;br&gt;- Corporations Whimper That They Won't Be Able to Make So Much Money If They Aren't Allowed to Pollute&lt;br&gt;- The 5 worst things you can do with your inheritance, according to a financial planner&lt;br&gt;- Jeff Bezos' yacht reportedly cost $500 million and is the largest sailing yacht in the world. Here's what we know.&lt;br&gt;- Stock market winners and losers are already emerging from the next extreme weather cycle&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Academic Partnerships is acquiring Wiley's OPM business.&lt;br&gt;- Margin loans enable borrowing against owned securities for additional investments.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of environmental regulations on corporate profitability is discussed.&lt;br&gt;- A financial planner shares the worst things to do with an inheritance.&lt;br&gt;- Details about Jeff Bezos' $500 million yacht, the largest sailing yacht in the world, are provided.&lt;br&gt;- The stock market is already showing winners and losers due to extreme weather conditions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Mergers and acquisitions are common in the business world, as seen with Academic Partnerships and Wiley.&lt;br&gt;- Financial planning and responsible inheritance management are important considerations.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of environmental regulations on corporate profits is a topic of discussion.&lt;br&gt;- Extreme weather events can have significant effects on the stock market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- What OpenAI's latest batch of chips says about the future of AI&lt;br&gt;- Artificial Intelligence, the False Claims Act, and the Public Disclosure ... - Wiley Rein&lt;br&gt;- Climate resilience gets a boost with Deepmind's AI-based GraphCast weather forecasts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's latest chips provide insights into the future of AI.&lt;br&gt;- The False Claims Act and public disclosure are discussed in relation to artificial intelligence.&lt;br&gt;- Deepmind's AI-based GraphCast weather forecasts contribute to climate resilience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's advancements in chip technology indicate the direction of AI development.&lt;br&gt;- Legal considerations and public disclosure play a role in the AI industry.&lt;br&gt;- AI-based weather forecasts contribute to climate resilience efforts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is rapidly evolving, with AI and digital identity being key areas of focus.&lt;br&gt;- Trust and safety are important considerations for users of tech platforms.&lt;br&gt;- Partnerships and collaborations are driving innovation in the tech sector.&lt;br&gt;- Mergers and acquisitions are common in the business world, with a focus on profitability and environmental impact.&lt;br&gt;- Responsible financial planning and inheritance management are crucial.&lt;br&gt;- Extreme weather events can have significant effects on the stock market.&lt;br&gt;- AI advancements have implications for various industries, including legal and climate resilience.</summary></entry></feed>