<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-22T20:03:13Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 22 Nov 2023 20:03:13</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-22T20:03:13Z</published><updated>2023-11-22T20:03:13Z</updated><id>1bc2436d-50af-4bf0-bb9b-56b37d889399</id><summary type="html">New AI Executive Order Outlines Sweeping Approach to AI - Wiley Rein (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- The new executive order on AI outlines a comprehensive approach to AI development and deployment.&lt;br&gt;- It emphasizes the importance of promoting public trust and confidence in AI systems.&lt;br&gt;- The executive order establishes a National Artificial Intelligence Initiative Office to coordinate AI efforts across government agencies.&lt;br&gt;- It also directs federal agencies to prioritize AI research and development and to consider AI in their regulatory and non-regulatory approaches.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amsel Suite: The Game Master's Swiss Army Knife by Ollam Technologies (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- The Amsel Suite is a versatile tool for game masters, providing various features and functionalities.&lt;br&gt;- It includes tools for creating and managing game scenarios, tracking player progress, and generating random events.&lt;br&gt;- The suite also offers resources for game world building, such as maps, character profiles, and item inventories.&lt;br&gt;- It aims to streamline the game master's workflow and enhance the gaming experience for both the game master and the players.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gloria Ann Wiley | Obituaries | theworldlink.com - Coos Bay World (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Gloria Ann Wiley's obituary was published in the Coos Bay World newspaper.&lt;br&gt;- She passed away at the age of [unknown].&lt;br&gt;- The obituary provides information about her family, education, and career.&lt;br&gt;- It also mentions her involvement in the community and her hobbies and interests.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Osteoblast-lineage calcium/calmodulin-dependent kinase 2 delta and gamma regulates bone mass and quality (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This study investigates the role of calcium/calmodulin-dependent kinase 2 delta and gamma in regulating bone mass and quality.&lt;br&gt;- The researchers found that these kinases play essential roles in osteoblast-lineage cells.&lt;br&gt;- They contribute to bone formation and mineralization, as well as the maintenance of bone strength.&lt;br&gt;- The findings suggest that targeting these kinases could be a potential therapeutic approach for bone-related disorders.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mitigating aberrant Cdk5 activation alleviates mitochondrial defects and motor neuron disease symptoms in spinal muscular atrophy (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This research focuses on mitigating aberrant Cdk5 activation to alleviate mitochondrial defects and motor neuron disease symptoms in spinal muscular atrophy (SMA).&lt;br&gt;- The study demonstrates that inhibiting Cdk5 activity can improve mitochondrial function and rescue motor neuron defects in SMA models.&lt;br&gt;- The findings suggest that targeting Cdk5 could be a potential therapeutic strategy for SMA treatment.&lt;br&gt;- Further studies are needed to explore the clinical implications of these findings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Industrial-era decline in Arctic methanesulfonic acid is offset by increased biogenic sulfate aerosol (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This study examines the industrial-era decline in Arctic methanesulfonic acid (MSA) and its offset by increased biogenic sulfate aerosol.&lt;br&gt;- The researchers found that the decline in MSA is primarily driven by reduced anthropogenic emissions of precursor gases.&lt;br&gt;- However, the increase in biogenic sulfate aerosol, resulting from enhanced marine phytoplankton activity, partially offsets the decline in MSA.&lt;br&gt;- The findings highlight the complex interactions between anthropogenic and natural factors in the Arctic atmosphere.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Essential roles of the ANKRD31–REC114 interaction in meiotic recombination and mouse spermatogenesis (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This study investigates the essential roles of the ANKRD31-REC114 interaction in meiotic recombination and mouse spermatogenesis.&lt;br&gt;- The researchers found that ANKRD31 and REC114 interact to promote the formation of meiotic recombination intermediates.&lt;br&gt;- This interaction is crucial for the proper progression of meiosis and the generation of functional sperm.&lt;br&gt;- The findings provide insights into the molecular mechanisms underlying meiotic recombination and male fertility.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dual thermal ecotypes coexist within a nearly genetically identical population of the unicellular marine cyanobacterium Synechococcus (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This research reveals the coexistence of dual thermal ecotypes within a genetically similar population of the unicellular marine cyanobacterium Synechococcus.&lt;br&gt;- The study shows that these ecotypes have distinct thermal preferences and physiological characteristics.&lt;br&gt;- The coexistence of these ecotypes allows the population to adapt to different temperature regimes and maximize its ecological niche.&lt;br&gt;- The findings contribute to our understanding of microbial diversity and adaptation in marine ecosystems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A peptidomimetic modulator of the CaV2.2 N-type calcium channel for chronic pain (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This study focuses on the development of a peptidomimetic modulator of the CaV2.2 N-type calcium channel for chronic pain management.&lt;br&gt;- The researchers designed and synthesized a peptidomimetic compound that selectively targets the CaV2.2 channel.&lt;br&gt;- The compound showed promising analgesic effects in preclinical models of chronic pain.&lt;br&gt;- The findings suggest that targeting the CaV2.2 channel with peptidomimetic compounds could be a potential therapeutic strategy for chronic pain.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOS1 and KSR1 modulate MEK inhibitor responsiveness to target resistant cell populations based on PI3K and KRAS mutation status (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This research investigates the role of SOS1 and KSR1 in modulating MEK inhibitor responsiveness in cell populations resistant to targeted therapies.&lt;br&gt;- The study demonstrates that the combination of MEK inhibitors with SOS1 or KSR1 inhibitors can overcome resistance in specific cell populations.&lt;br&gt;- The responsiveness to MEK inhibitors is influenced by the mutation status of PI3K and KRAS.&lt;br&gt;- The findings provide insights into potential strategies for overcoming resistance to targeted therapies in cancer treatment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Fermi” bubbles are bursting from our galaxy. Their origins remain a mystery (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This study explores the origins of the "Fermi" bubbles, large structures extending above and below the Milky Way galaxy.&lt;br&gt;- The researchers found that the bubbles are likely the result of a powerful burst of energy from the galaxy's central black hole.&lt;br&gt;- However, the exact mechanism behind the formation of the bubbles remains unknown.&lt;br&gt;- Further research is needed to unravel the mystery of the Fermi bubbles and their significance in galactic evolution.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impaired end joining induces cardiac atrophy in a Hutchinson–Gilford progeria mouse model (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This research investigates the role of impaired end joining in inducing cardiac atrophy in a Hutchinson-Gilford progeria mouse model.&lt;br&gt;- The study demonstrates that defective DNA repair mechanisms contribute to the development of cardiac atrophy in progeria.&lt;br&gt;- The findings suggest that targeting DNA repair pathways could be a potential therapeutic approach for treating cardiac complications in progeria patients.&lt;br&gt;- Further studies are needed to explore the underlying molecular mechanisms and potential interventions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dynamic regulation of airway surface liquid pH by TMEM16A and SLC26A4 in cystic fibrosis nasal epithelia with rare mutations (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This study focuses on the dynamic regulation of airway surface liquid pH by TMEM16A and SLC26A4 in cystic fibrosis nasal epithelia with rare mutations.&lt;br&gt;- The researchers found that TMEM16A and SLC26A4 play essential roles in maintaining the pH balance of airway surface liquid.&lt;br&gt;- Dysregulation of these proteins can lead to impaired mucociliary clearance and increased susceptibility to respiratory infections.&lt;br&gt;- The findings provide insights into the pathogenesis of cystic fibrosis and potential therapeutic targets for the disease.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Correction for Shioda et al., Neuronal MML-1/MXL-2 regulates systemic aging via glutamate transporter and cell nonautonomous autophagic and peroxidase activity (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This is a correction for the study by Shioda et al. on the role of neuronal MML-1/MXL-2 in regulating systemic aging.&lt;br&gt;- The correction addresses an error in the interpretation of the data and provides revised conclusions.&lt;br&gt;- The corrected findings suggest that neuronal MML-1/MXL-2 regulates systemic aging through its effects on glutamate transporter activity and cell nonautonomous autophagic and peroxidase activity.&lt;br&gt;- The correction emphasizes the importance of accurate data interpretation in scientific research.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Correction for Xiu et al., Synthetically non-Hermitian nonlinear wave-like behavior in a topological mechanical metamaterial (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This is a correction for the study by Xiu et al. on the synthetically non-Hermitian nonlinear wave-like behavior in a topological mechanical metamaterial.&lt;br&gt;- The correction addresses an error in the experimental setup and provides revised results and conclusions.&lt;br&gt;- The corrected findings confirm the existence of synthetically non-Hermitian nonlinear wave-like behavior in the mechanical metamaterial.&lt;br&gt;- The correction highlights the importance of rigorous experimental design and data analysis in scientific research.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORC pathway intersects with a calcium sensor kinase network to regulate potassium sensing in Arabidopsis (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This research investigates the intersection of the TORC pathway and a calcium sensor kinase network in regulating potassium sensing in Arabidopsis.&lt;br&gt;- The study demonstrates that the TORC pathway modulates the activity of calcium sensor kinases, which in turn regulate potassium sensing and uptake.&lt;br&gt;- The findings provide insights into the molecular mechanisms underlying nutrient sensing and signaling in plants.&lt;br&gt;- Further studies are needed to elucidate the specific interactions and downstream effects of these pathways.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;High time-resolved studies of stick-slip show similar dilatancy to fast and slow earthquakes (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This study examines the similarities between stick-slip events and fast and slow earthquakes in terms of dilatancy.&lt;br&gt;- The researchers conducted high time-resolved studies of stick-slip events to analyze their characteristics.&lt;br&gt;- They found that stick-slip events exhibit similar dilatancy behavior to fast and slow earthquakes.&lt;br&gt;- The findings suggest that the underlying physical processes governing these events may share common mechanisms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapid and signal crowdedness-robust in situ sequencing through hybrid block coding (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This research presents a rapid and signal crowdedness-robust in situ sequencing method using hybrid block coding.&lt;br&gt;- The method allows for efficient and accurate sequencing of nucleic acids in complex samples.&lt;br&gt;- It overcomes challenges related to signal interference and background noise, enabling high-quality in situ sequencing data.&lt;br&gt;- The findings have implications for various applications, including genomics, transcriptomics, and spatial transcriptomics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Invasion-Block and S-MARVEL: A high-content screening and image analysis platform identifies ATM kinase as a modulator of melanoma invasion and metastasis (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This study introduces Invasion-Block and S-MARVEL, a high-content screening and image analysis platform for identifying modulators of melanoma invasion and metastasis.&lt;br&gt;- The platform combines genetic and pharmacological perturbations with high-throughput imaging and analysis.&lt;br&gt;- Using this platform, the researchers identified ATM kinase as a potential modulator of melanoma invasion and metastasis.&lt;br&gt;- The findings provide insights into the molecular mechanisms underlying melanoma progression and suggest new therapeutic targets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Causal evidence for a coordinated temporal interplay within the language network (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This research provides causal evidence for a coordinated temporal interplay within the language network.&lt;br&gt;- The study used neuroimaging techniques and causal modeling to investigate the temporal dynamics of language processing.&lt;br&gt;- The findings suggest that different regions within the language network interact and coordinate their activity in a temporally precise manner.&lt;br&gt;- The results contribute to our understanding of the neural mechanisms underlying language processing and communication.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cellular nucleic acid-binding protein restricts SARS-CoV-2 by regulating interferon and disrupting RNA-protein condensates (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This study focuses on the role of cellular nucleic acid-binding protein (CNBP) in restricting SARS-CoV-2 infection.&lt;br&gt;- The researchers found that CNBP regulates the production of interferon, a key antiviral immune response.&lt;br&gt;- CNBP also disrupts RNA-protein condensates, which are essential for viral replication.&lt;br&gt;- The findings suggest that targeting CNBP could be a potential strategy for inhibiting SARS-CoV-2 replication and reducing viral load.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The F pilus serves as a conduit for the DNA during conjugation between physically distant bacteria (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This research investigates the role of the F pilus as a conduit for DNA transfer during conjugation between physically distant bacteria.&lt;br&gt;- The study demonstrates that the F pilus enables the transfer of DNA between bacteria that are physically separated by a considerable distance.&lt;br&gt;- The findings provide insights into the mechanisms of bacterial conjugation and horizontal gene transfer.&lt;br&gt;- Further studies are needed to explore the implications of these findings in the context of bacterial evolution and antibiotic resistance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reevaluating progression and pathways following Mycobacterium tuberculosis infection within the spectrum of tuberculosis (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This study reevaluates the progression and pathways following Mycobacterium tuberculosis infection within the spectrum of tuberculosis.&lt;br&gt;- The researchers analyze the clinical and pathological features of different forms of tuberculosis, including latent infection, active disease, and post-treatment sequelae.&lt;br&gt;- The findings highlight the heterogeneity of tuberculosis and the complex interactions between the host immune response and the pathogen.&lt;br&gt;- The results have implications for the diagnosis, treatment, and prevention of tuberculosis.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Glutamine-rich regions of the disordered CREB transactivation domain mediate dynamic intra- and intermolecular interactions (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This research focuses on the glutamine-rich regions of the disordered CREB transactivation domain and their role in mediating dynamic intra- and intermolecular interactions.&lt;br&gt;- The study demonstrates that these glutamine-rich regions play a crucial role in the regulation of CREB-mediated gene expression.&lt;br&gt;- They facilitate the formation of protein-protein and protein-DNA complexes, contributing to the transcriptional activity of CREB.&lt;br&gt;- The findings provide insights into the molecular mechanisms underlying gene regulation and transcriptional control.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dual-inhibitory domain iCARs improve the efficiency of the AND-NOT gate CAR T strategy (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This study introduces dual-inhibitory domain iCARs, which improve the efficiency of the AND-NOT gate CAR T strategy.&lt;br&gt;- The iCARs incorporate two inhibitory domains that enhance the specificity and safety of CAR T cells.&lt;br&gt;- The dual-inhibitory domain iCARs effectively eliminate target cells while minimizing off-target effects.&lt;br&gt;- The findings suggest that these iCARs could be a promising approach for enhancing the precision and efficacy of CAR T cell therapies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The emergence and diversification of a zoonotic pathogen from within the microbiota of intensively farmed pigs (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This research investigates the emergence and diversification of a zoonotic pathogen originating from the microbiota of intensively farmed pigs.&lt;br&gt;- The study explores the genetic and ecological factors contributing to the evolution and spread of the pathogen.&lt;br&gt;- The findings highlight the potential risks associated with intensive animal farming and the importance of surveillance and control measures.&lt;br&gt;- The results have implications for public health and the prevention of zoonotic diseases.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Histone deacetylation and cytosine methylation compartmentalize heterochromatic regions in the genome organization of Neurospora crassa (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This study examines the role of histone deacetylation and cytosine methylation in compartmentalizing heterochromatic regions in the genome organization of Neurospora crassa.&lt;br&gt;- The researchers found that these epigenetic modifications contribute to the spatial organization and stability of heterochromatin.&lt;br&gt;- They play a crucial role in maintaining the integrity and function of heterochromatic regions.&lt;br&gt;- The findings provide insights into the mechanisms of genome organization and epigenetic regulation in fungi.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unfolding sustainability transitions in food systems: Insights from UK and French trajectories (Business)&lt;br&gt;- This study explores the unfolding sustainability transitions in food systems, focusing on insights from the UK and French trajectories.&lt;br&gt;- The researchers analyze the drivers, barriers, and strategies for transitioning towards more sustainable food systems.&lt;br&gt;- They identify key factors influencing the pace and direction of sustainability transitions in the two countries.&lt;br&gt;- The findings provide valuable insights for policymakers, businesses, and stakeholders involved in shaping sustainable food systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The big business of sustainable food production and consumption: Exploring the transition to alternative proteins (Business)&lt;br&gt;- This research examines the big business of sustainable food production and consumption, with a focus on the transition to alternative proteins.&lt;br&gt;- The study explores the market dynamics, consumer preferences, and industry trends driving the growth of alternative protein products.&lt;br&gt;- It highlights the potential economic opportunities and challenges associated with sustainable food production and consumption.&lt;br&gt;- The findings provide insights into the role of businesses in driving the transition to more sustainable food systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Integrated genomic and functional analyses of human skin-associated Staphylococcus reveal extensive inter- and intra-species diversity (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This study presents integrated genomic and functional analyses of human skin-associated Staphylococcus bacteria, revealing extensive inter- and intra-species diversity.&lt;br&gt;- The researchers sequenced and analyzed the genomes of multiple Staphylococcus strains isolated from human skin.&lt;br&gt;- They identified genetic variations and functional differences that contribute to the diversity and adaptation of these bacteria.&lt;br&gt;- The findings enhance our understanding of the human skin microbiome and its potential implications for health and disease.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The report covers a wide range of topics, including AI, tech, business, and scientific research.&lt;br&gt;- It highlights the advancements and challenges in various fields, such as AI development, game master tools, genetic research, and sustainability transitions.&lt;br&gt;- Key points include the importance of public trust in AI systems, the potential of peptidomimetic compounds for chronic pain management, and the role of epigenetic modifications in genome organization.&lt;br&gt;- The report emphasizes the interdisciplinary nature of research and the need for collaboration between different fields.&lt;br&gt;- It provides valuable insights into the current state and future directions of various industries and scientific disciplines.</summary></entry></feed>