<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-13T22:01:34Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 13 Aug 2023 22:01:34</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-13T22:01:34Z</published><updated>2023-08-13T22:01:34Z</updated><id>807fe4b9-2c50-4c8c-aeb2-c04fd730f3ab</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- A video shows Ukraine's drones destroying a Russian 'Terminator' armored vehicle.&lt;br&gt;- Learning produces a cognitive map in the form of a state machine.&lt;br&gt;- Stability AI unveils Japanese StableLM Alpha, a leap forward in Japanese language model.&lt;br&gt;- How using a CLI Launcher for Android can boost productivity.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's Xbox Series S parity demands are handing Sony free wins.&lt;br&gt;- 'Baldur's Gate 3' developers discuss challenges and possibilities of DLC.&lt;br&gt;- 'Destiny 2,' expectations, reality, and what should happen with the final shape.&lt;br&gt;- 75% of companies consider banning ChatGPT and generative AI services, according to a survey.&lt;br&gt;- Meet ConDistFL, a revolutionary federated learning approach for organ and disease segmentation in CT datasets.&lt;br&gt;- A step-by-step guide to building a responsive and mobile-friendly website from scratch.&lt;br&gt;- Mastering Micro Frontends: Creating scalable applications with React, Webpack 5, and TypeScript Type Safety.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Former VP claims Salesforce lied about software capabilities.&lt;br&gt;- Crystal is making a comeback with a $150 million refurbishment of its ship and a new 2025 world cruise.&lt;br&gt;- The CEO of Rewind AI publicly shared his performance reviews.&lt;br&gt;- Tipping 'nudges' are now popping up on DoorDash.&lt;br&gt;- My husband says I'm being reckless with 'his' money by shopping for the family. How do we get on the same page?&lt;br&gt;- I grew my business from 4 people to 16,000 in 7 years. Here are 5 ways I've seen new business owners fail when they expand, and how I've avoided making those mistakes.&lt;br&gt;- Student-loan borrowers keep running into hurdles as Biden's debt relief promises are piling up in court.&lt;br&gt;- A Volkswagen plant in Germany sends staff off on their big summer break with a chorus of 'trumpets, trombones, and drums'.&lt;br&gt;- A Georgia couple turned a retired ambulance into a luxury RV using YouTube tutorials and $35K.&lt;br&gt;- I'm a CEO who was burned out. So I took 30 days off from work to recharge in Paris and found my creative spark.&lt;br&gt;- I own an energy-efficient, weather-proof dome home. Here's my advice for those who want to own a dome home too.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- An Introduction to the Conjugate Gradient Method Without the Agonizing Pain [pdf].&lt;br&gt;- Stability AI unveils Japanese StableLM Alpha, a leap forward in Japanese language model.&lt;br&gt;- Learning produces a cognitive map in the form of a state machine.&lt;br&gt;- 75% of companies consider banning ChatGPT and generative AI services, according to a survey.&lt;br&gt;- Meet ConDistFL, a revolutionary federated learning approach for organ and disease segmentation in CT datasets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Others:&lt;br&gt;- Bad weather, natural disasters, and disease are hobbling crops right now. Here's how the food commodity markets are responding.&lt;br&gt;- The British navy is teaming up with the US to build a new 'Dreadnought' for a totally different battle at sea.&lt;br&gt;- See inside a test Boeing 777X, which has flown more than 1,300 hours as the planemaker races to certify its new $442 million jet by 2025.&lt;br&gt;- The US is facing a debt storm. Here are 5 charts that show trouble is brewing.&lt;br&gt;- 4 key types of landmines, how they work, and their impact on the Russia-Ukraine war.&lt;br&gt;- Overstretched Russian forces may lack the mechanized reserve to thwart Ukraine establishing a bridgehead on the Dnipro river, report says.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Drones are becoming increasingly effective in military operations, as shown by Ukraine's successful destruction of a Russian armored vehicle.&lt;br&gt;- AI language models are advancing rapidly, with Stability AI unveiling a new Japanese language model.&lt;br&gt;- The gaming industry is experiencing competition and challenges, with Microsoft's Xbox Series S parity demands giving Sony an advantage.&lt;br&gt;- The business world is filled with controversies, such as the claim that Salesforce lied about software capabilities.&lt;br&gt;- The travel industry is making a comeback, with Crystal refurbishing its ship and offering a world cruise.&lt;br&gt;- The agriculture sector is facing challenges due to bad weather, natural disasters, and disease, impacting food commodity markets.&lt;br&gt;- The US is facing economic challenges, including a debt storm and hurdles in student loan debt relief.&lt;br&gt;- DIY projects, such as converting an ambulance into a luxury RV, are gaining popularity.&lt;br&gt;- Personal experiences, such as burnout and creative recharging, offer insights into work-life balance and leadership.&lt;br&gt;- Advances in AI, such as federated learning and organ segmentation, have significant potential in healthcare and medical imaging.&lt;br&gt;- The Russia-Ukraine conflict continues to evolve, with reports on landmines and military strategies.</summary></entry></feed>