<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-17T08:03:38Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 17 Oct 2023 08:03:38</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-17T08:03:38Z</published><updated>2023-10-17T08:03:38Z</updated><id>f23fab4b-bb05-4307-99da-abfa93367204</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- LinkedIn employees discovered a mysterious list of around 500 names over the weekend. On Monday, workers said those on the list were laid off.&lt;br&gt;- Tech leaders are pulling out of a CEO's conference over remarks he made about Israel.&lt;br&gt;- Pixel 6 owners who use multiple profiles run into problems with Android 14.&lt;br&gt;- Web Summit derailed by founder’s public fight with those supporting Israel in Hamas war.&lt;br&gt;- Archer Aviation to launch air taxis in Abu Dhabi in 2026.&lt;br&gt;- Soon You Can Play Blurry N64 Games In 4K On The Mysterious Analogue 3D.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- McDonald's caught up in Israel-Hamas war as franchisees in the Middle East pledge aid to different sides.&lt;br&gt;- Former tech CEO being sued for defrauding JPMorgan has hit back with dramatic allegations.&lt;br&gt;- The House Republican Conference has been built for chaos since the 1990s. It only took one slim majority for that to blow up on them.&lt;br&gt;- Billionaire founder of Victoria's Secret pulls funding from Harvard, accusing the school of 'dismal failure' to take a stand for Israel.&lt;br&gt;- Werner Herzog on beer, yoga, and what he would ask God.&lt;br&gt;- Trump fraud judge cracks 'what's sauce for the goose...' joke in response to complaint about Michael Cohen's anti-Trump tweets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Prosecutors say Sam Bankman-Fried got shady doctor to prescribe Adderall as judge denies greater access to pills during trial.&lt;br&gt;- The sound of a human voice is more scary to animals in the Savanna than lions, dogs, or guns, a study found.&lt;br&gt;- Low serotonin levels might explain some Long Covid symptoms, study proposes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Congressional candidate Wiley holds meet and greet in Corsicana - Corsicana Daily Sun.&lt;br&gt;- 2025 WR CJ Wiley holds early Georgia offer, talks recent visit to Athens - 247Sports.&lt;br&gt;- Analysis of silver nanoparticles by flame atomic absorption... - John Wiley &amp; Sons.&lt;br&gt;- ALJ Declines to Rubber Stamp EB Position on License Revocation - Wiley Rein.&lt;br&gt;- Long-time Family Court judge honored with plaque dedication in Mercer County - WVVA.&lt;br&gt;- Candidate Profile: Brian Wiley, Guilford Board of Assessment Appeals - Patch.&lt;br&gt;- Where to watch Cowboys vs. Chargers live streams for Monday Night Football.&lt;br&gt;- Halley’s Comet, Last Seen In 1986, Will Unleash ‘Shooting Stars This Weekend—How To Watch.&lt;br&gt;- Gong CEO Amit Bendov On Netanyahu And The Israel-Hamas War’s Impact.&lt;br&gt;- Laurel Lord will bless Israel | Letters to the Editor | leader-call.com - leader-call.com.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The conflict between Israel and Hamas has had repercussions in various industries, including tech and business.&lt;br&gt;- LinkedIn faced internal issues with layoffs, while tech leaders boycotted a conference due to controversial remarks about Israel.&lt;br&gt;- The Pixel 6 faced compatibility issues with Android 14, and the Web Summit faced disruptions due to the founder's public fight.&lt;br&gt;- McDonald's franchisees in the Middle East pledged aid to different sides of the Israel-Hamas conflict.&lt;br&gt;- Legal battles and allegations involving CEOs and fraud have emerged.&lt;br&gt;- The House Republican Conference faced chaos, and a billionaire founder pulled funding from Harvard.&lt;br&gt;- AI-related news included a case involving prescription drugs and a study on the impact of human voices on animals.&lt;br&gt;- Other topics ranged from sports events to celestial phenomena and personal opinions on Israel.</summary></entry></feed>