<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-09T18:01:15Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 09 Aug 2023 18:01:15</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-09T18:01:15Z</published><updated>2023-08-09T18:01:15Z</updated><id>9ce5a352-dcfb-41b3-a0c3-3ed8d2a65858</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- SEC chairman warns AI could be at the heart of future financial crises: The chairman of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has expressed concerns about the potential risks posed by artificial intelligence (AI) in the financial industry. He warns that AI algorithms could amplify market volatility and lead to financial crises if not properly regulated and monitored.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Amazon has more than half of all Arm server CPUs in the world: Amazon, the e-commerce giant, currently holds the majority share of Arm server CPUs globally. This dominance in the market highlights Amazon's significant presence and influence in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- HAS AI BECOME TOO HUMAN? Researchers At Google AI Find LLMs Can Now Use ML Models And APIs With Just Tool Documentation!: Researchers at Google AI have made significant advancements in language models, enabling them to use machine learning models and application programming interfaces (APIs) with minimal documentation. This development showcases the progress made in AI technology and its potential to streamline processes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Student-loan payments and steeper interest rates will pave the way for a severe consumer-led recession, top economist David Rosenberg says: Economist David Rosenberg predicts that the combination of high student loan payments and increasing interest rates will lead to a consumer-led recession. This highlights the potential economic impact of student loan debt and the importance of managing interest rates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Pretiosum Ventures hits first close on its second fund to back infrastructure startups: Pretiosum Ventures, a venture capital firm, has successfully raised funds for its second fund, which aims to support infrastructure startups. This demonstrates the continued interest and investment in the infrastructure sector.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- People-centered startups: making employees happy is a key ingredient to success: The success of startups is increasingly linked to prioritizing employee happiness and well-being. This shift in focus highlights the recognition of the importance of a positive work environment and its impact on overall business success.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- SEC chairman warns AI could be at the heart of future financial crises: The chairman of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has expressed concerns about the potential risks posed by artificial intelligence (AI) in the financial industry. He warns that AI algorithms could amplify market volatility and lead to financial crises if not properly regulated and monitored.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- HAS AI BECOME TOO HUMAN? Researchers At Google AI Find LLMs Can Now Use ML Models And APIs With Just Tool Documentation!: Researchers at Google AI have made significant advancements in language models, enabling them to use machine learning models and application programming interfaces (APIs) with minimal documentation. This development showcases the progress made in AI technology and its potential to streamline processes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- How to get more suggestions from GitHub Copilot: GitHub Copilot, an AI-powered code suggestion tool, can provide developers with more suggestions by utilizing specific techniques and approaches. This highlights the continuous improvement and optimization of AI tools in the programming field.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The potential risks of AI in the financial industry and the need for proper regulation and monitoring.&lt;br&gt;- Amazon's dominant position in the Arm server CPU market, indicating its significant influence in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- Advancements in AI language models, enabling them to use machine learning models and APIs with minimal documentation.&lt;br&gt;- The potential economic impact of student loan debt and increasing interest rates on consumer-led recessions.&lt;br&gt;- The importance of prioritizing employee happiness and well-being for the success of startups.&lt;br&gt;- The continuous improvement and optimization of AI tools, such as GitHub Copilot, in the programming field.</summary></entry></feed>