<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-17T22:01:13Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:01:13</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-17T22:01:13Z</published><updated>2023-08-17T22:01:13Z</updated><id>372b5253-1ac9-40e3-82a4-ea4e2e2a1556</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI could potentially face a plagiarism lawsuit from The New York Times as negotiations become tense.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft will soon allow users to uninstall more built-in apps in Windows 11 to reduce bloat.&lt;br&gt;- UpCodes is hiring fullstack engineers to assist in making buildings more affordable.&lt;br&gt;- A guide on how to instruction tune code LLMs without GPT4 data using OctoPack, a set of AI models.&lt;br&gt;- CISA warns of hackers exploiting a new file transfer bug in Citrix ShareFile.&lt;br&gt;- Hackers discovered three separate ways to break into US Air Force satellites, earning up to $50K for their efforts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech industry is facing legal challenges and security threats. OpenAI's potential plagiarism lawsuit highlights the importance of intellectual property rights. Microsoft's decision to allow users to uninstall built-in apps shows a commitment to user customization. The need for cybersecurity measures is evident with the exploitation of the Citrix ShareFile bug and the successful hacking of US Air Force satellites.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Redfin's CEO claims that the housing market is at rock bottom due to high rates and prices.&lt;br&gt;- Hedge fund Vantage Point is reducing exposure to US stocks and seeking value in China.&lt;br&gt;- Aldi is expanding its presence in the US by acquiring 400 grocery stores in Florida and the southeast.&lt;br&gt;- Ken Griffin's Citadel is experiencing a successful year as its flagship fund surges 9%.&lt;br&gt;- Rudy Giuliani is facing a lawsuit alleging that he pocketed $300,000 from farmers for an anti-Biden documentary that was never made.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The housing market's current state reflects the challenges of high rates and prices. Hedge funds are shifting their focus to China for potential value. Aldi's expansion signifies its growth in the US market. Citadel's success highlights the positive performance of certain investment funds. The lawsuit against Rudy Giuliani raises questions about financial misconduct.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- OctoPack offers AI models for instruction tuning code in large language models.&lt;br&gt;- Italian mayors hope for an Elon Musk vs. Mark Zuckerberg fight to boost their towns' profiles.&lt;br&gt;- Italian mayors are still hopeful despite Musk's apparent disinterest in engaging in such a fight.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: AI continues to advance with OctoPack's AI models for code tuning. The interest of Italian mayors in a high-profile tech battle demonstrates the potential impact of such events on local economies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;This report covers various topics in the tech, business, and AI sectors. It highlights legal challenges faced by OpenAI and Rudy Giuliani, cybersecurity threats, the housing market's state, investment trends, and AI advancements. Overall, it showcases the dynamic nature of these industries and the impact they have on society.</summary></entry></feed>