<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-15T08:03:53Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 15 Oct 2023 08:03:53</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-15T08:03:53Z</published><updated>2023-10-15T08:03:53Z</updated><id>cd78618d-fc6f-46cf-8f05-ea89ab3eccaa</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Anti-Anti-Adblocker uBlock filter to get rid of the annoying YouTube message&lt;br&gt;- Unleashing the Power of Flask: A Guide to Building Web Applications with Python&lt;br&gt;- Skio (YC S20) – Subscriptions for Shopify, ReCharge Migrations Is Hiring&lt;br&gt;- Show HN: Firefox add-on to open YouTube videos in alternative front ends&lt;br&gt;- Is Multilingual AI Truly Safe? Exposing the Vulnerabilities of Large Language Models in Low-Resource Languages&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech section of the report highlights various developments and discussions in the tech industry. It covers topics such as adblockers, web application development, subscription services, alternative front ends for YouTube, and the vulnerabilities of large language models in low-resource languages. These insights showcase the ongoing advancements and challenges in the tech field.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Late Goal Sends Wabash Home With 2-1 Loss At Wooster - Wabash College&lt;br&gt;- 2025 WR CJ Wiley holds early Georgia offer, talks recent visit to Athens - 247Sports&lt;br&gt;- Is Kehinde Wiley's Dakar Residency a Bridge or an Oasis? | News - Ocula Magazine&lt;br&gt;- Wiley Kitchings Obituary (1936 - 2023) - Augusta, GA - The Augusta ... - Legacy.com&lt;br&gt;- A temporary pay bump for federal firefighters is slated to end in November, raising fears that up to 50% of the workforce could quit as the country faces more extreme wildfires&lt;br&gt;- A pro-DeSantis super PAC stopped its door-knocking operation in California after the state's GOP engineered changes to award its presidential delegates to the candidate who wins a majority of the vote&lt;br&gt;- John Wiley &amp; Sons Inc. - (WLY) Declares $0.35 Dividend - Nasdaq&lt;br&gt;- Derek Avery Hopes to Take Over for John Wiley Price in Dallas ... - Dallas Observer&lt;br&gt;- What Contractors Need to Know About a Government Shutdown - Wiley Rein&lt;br&gt;- Kari Lake, previously a fire-breathing, hard-charging, far-right candidate for Arizona governor, may attempt to pivot to normie for her Senate bid&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business section of the report covers a range of topics, including sports, offers, obituaries, federal firefighters, political changes, dividends, potential leadership changes, government shutdowns, and political strategies. These insights reflect the diverse aspects of the business world and the impact of various events on different sectors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Is Multilingual AI Truly Safe? Exposing the Vulnerabilities of Large Language Models in Low-Resource Languages&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The AI section focuses on the safety and vulnerabilities of multilingual AI models, particularly in low-resource languages. This insight sheds light on the potential risks and challenges associated with AI language models and emphasizes the need for further research and development in this area.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The report provides insights into various topics, including tech, business, and AI. It highlights key points within each section, offering a glimpse into the latest developments, discussions, and challenges in these fields. The report concludes that the tech industry is constantly evolving, the business world is influenced by various events and strategies, and AI poses both opportunities and risks. Overall, the report emphasizes the importance of staying updated and informed in these rapidly changing domains.</summary></entry></feed>