<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-27T08:03:33Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 27 Jan 2024 08:03:33</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-27T08:03:33Z</published><updated>2024-01-27T08:03:33Z</updated><id>ce84a3ee-4f84-4e36-a6c1-29edc0c8834c</id><summary type="html">In recent news, the White House has called for legislation to combat the rise of AI-generated fakes featuring popular singer Taylor Swift. Concerns have been raised about the potential misuse of this technology and its impact on public figures. Meanwhile, iPad users may face limitations as they will no longer have access to third-party app stores and browser engines. This decision could affect the user experience and customization options for iPad owners. Additionally, Domino's pizza has become the latest American product to face backlash in Asia due to the ongoing turmoil in the Middle East. An executive from the company acknowledges the challenges they are currently facing in the region. In the tech industry, Spotify has strongly criticized Apple's DMA compliance plan, labeling it as "extortion" and a "complete and total farce." This highlights the ongoing tensions between the two companies. On a different note, recycled plastics have been found to contain dangerous chemicals, rendering them unsafe for use. This discovery raises concerns about the potential health risks associated with the use of such materials. Lastly, in the Trump defamation trial, the judge has advised jurors to never disclose their participation in the trial, emphasizing the need for confidentiality. In a separate matter, an entrepreneur working at a non-profit organization seeks advice on dealing with ineffective volunteers. This situation poses challenges for the entrepreneur who is managing the organization alone.</summary></entry></feed>