<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-25T20:02:18Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 25 Oct 2023 20:02:18</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-25T20:02:18Z</published><updated>2023-10-25T20:02:18Z</updated><id>e8d36ba6-182c-4109-936e-f8cef7dbfa07</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft jumps while Google owner Alphabet slips as Wall Street zeroes in on the tech giants' AI efforts&lt;br&gt;- FTX is considering 3 bids to restart the crypto exchange, report says&lt;br&gt;- 'Spider-Man 2' reveals Peter Parker's mortgage rate, so I asked brokers if he got a good deal in the new PS5 game&lt;br&gt;- Here's what reportedly led to Cruise robotaxis getting banned in San Francisco&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft Announces Radius: a New Open Application Platform for the Cloud&lt;br&gt;- Node.js 21 Release Updates V8 Engine, WebSteams Module and Test Runner&lt;br&gt;- Node.js Worker Threads Vs. Child Processes: Which one should you use?&lt;br&gt;- How to Build and Deploy an API-Driven Streamlit/Python Microservice on AWS&lt;br&gt;- Google DeepMind Proposes An Artificial Intelligence Framework for Social and Ethical AI Risk Assessment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Bragar Eagel &amp; Squire, P.C. Is Investigating Wiley, and R1 RCM and ... - StreetInsider.com&lt;br&gt;- Californians are fleeing amid sky-high housing costs. Here are the top 10 states they're flocking to.&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett is set to indirectly bet on a tiny nation that's the world's fastest-growing economy and an emerging oil superpower&lt;br&gt;- The Cost Of Manual Sales Order Management Workflows And The Benefits Of Automation&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft jumps while Google owner Alphabet slips as Wall Street zeroes in on the tech giants' AI efforts&lt;br&gt;- Google DeepMind Proposes An Artificial Intelligence Framework for Social and Ethical AI Risk Assessment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech giants, Microsoft and Google, are both making moves in the AI space, with Microsoft gaining traction and Google facing challenges.&lt;br&gt;- The crypto exchange FTX is considering bids to restart its operations, indicating continued interest and investment in the cryptocurrency market.&lt;br&gt;- The banning of Cruise robotaxis in San Francisco highlights the regulatory challenges faced by autonomous vehicle companies.&lt;br&gt;- The announcement of Microsoft's Radius platform showcases the company's commitment to cloud computing and application development.&lt;br&gt;- The updates to Node.js and the comparison between worker threads and child processes provide insights into the development and optimization of JavaScript applications.&lt;br&gt;- Google DeepMind's proposal for an AI risk assessment framework demonstrates the growing importance of ethical considerations in AI development.&lt;br&gt;- The migration of Californians to other states due to high housing costs reflects the impact of affordability on population movements.&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's indirect bet on a fast-growing economy and emerging oil superpower suggests his confidence in long-term economic growth.&lt;br&gt;- The benefits of automation in sales order management workflows highlight the potential for increased efficiency and cost savings in business operations.</summary></entry></feed>