<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-14T20:01:45Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 14 Oct 2023 20:01:45</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-14T20:01:45Z</published><updated>2023-10-14T20:01:45Z</updated><id>57d1615c-f605-4777-a3e9-903e3b9da47d</id><summary type="html">Report Title: Weekend Reads: Insights on Biotech, Publishing, Housing, Personal Loans, and More&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Tech&lt;br&gt;- AMD pulls driver after anti-lag feature causes CS2 bans&lt;br&gt;- PostgresJs: The fastest full-featured PostgreSQL client for Node.js and Deno&lt;br&gt;- Google improves Cloud Spanner with more compute and storage without price increase&lt;br&gt;- "Laravel: Real-time Application Data Issue Export Directly To A Slack Channel"&lt;br&gt;- Google offers legal shield to AI-generated content users amid copyright concerns&lt;br&gt;- Tech workers turning to buzzy peptide treatments for longevity&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech industry continues to evolve with advancements in hardware and software. However, concerns about copyright and legal issues surrounding AI-generated content persist. Additionally, tech workers are exploring unconventional treatments to enhance their well-being and longevity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Business&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's deputy, Todd Combs, shares insights on risk-taking and investing&lt;br&gt;- Efforts to form a new union surge since Biden became president&lt;br&gt;- Housing affordability reaches an all-time low, according to Goldman Sachs&lt;br&gt;- A tennis center owner capitalizes on the pickleball surge, doubling revenue&lt;br&gt;- The UAW strike poses a threat to new pickup truck production&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: Business leaders like Todd Combs provide valuable insights into risk management and investment strategies. The formation of new unions has seen a significant increase under the Biden administration. Housing affordability remains a pressing issue, while entrepreneurs find opportunities in emerging trends like pickleball. The UAW strike impacts the automotive industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. AI&lt;br&gt;- Israel's military faces challenges in countering Hamas' new drone arsenal&lt;br&gt;- Astrophysicist explains the visibility of Voyager probes from a distance&lt;br&gt;- Fake airline reps involved in rebooking scams&lt;br&gt;- Self-driving cars still have limitations, according to an autonomous vehicle boss&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The use of drones in conflicts poses challenges for military forces. The visibility of space probes like Voyager from vast distances showcases the remarkable capabilities of scientific exploration. Scams involving fake airline representatives highlight the need for vigilance. Despite advancements, self-driving cars still have limitations that need to be addressed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;This report covers a range of topics, including biotech, publishing, housing, personal loans, and more. Key insights include the evolving tech industry, challenges in the business sector, and the impact of AI on various domains. It also highlights the importance of risk management, housing affordability, and emerging trends. Overall, the report provides a comprehensive overview of current events and trends in these areas.</summary></entry></feed>