<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-09T08:03:35Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 09 Oct 2023 08:03:35</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-09T08:03:35Z</published><updated>2023-10-09T08:03:35Z</updated><id>09ea97e6-24d6-45be-b092-405e18f3acec</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Rooster Teeth, a popular entertainment company, has removed its shows, including Red vs. Blue, from YouTube.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft is rumored to be considering buying Activision Blizzard, which would have implications for the popular game franchise, "Call of Duty."&lt;br&gt;- Apple is reportedly working on an exciting upgrade for the iPhone 16 Pro.&lt;br&gt;- A journey of compiling Rust binaries for older Windows versions, such as Windows 98 SE, is documented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Uber and UnitedHealth's Optum have partnered to provide app payment for seniors' ancillary benefits.&lt;br&gt;- Matt Gaetz, a GOP congressman, believes it will be worth losing his congressional seat if it means removing Kevin McCarthy as speaker.&lt;br&gt;- A GOP congressman warns that conservative hardliners could potentially cause the party to lose its House majority in 2024.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from ITU Denmark have introduced Neural Developmental Programs, which aim to bridge the gap between biological growth and artificial neural networks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Rooster Teeth's decision to remove its shows from YouTube may indicate a shift in their distribution strategy or a desire for more control over their content.&lt;br&gt;- The potential acquisition of Activision Blizzard by Microsoft could have significant implications for the gaming industry.&lt;br&gt;- Apple's rumored upgrade for the iPhone 16 Pro suggests continued innovation in the smartphone market.&lt;br&gt;- The development of Neural Developmental Programs highlights ongoing efforts to improve artificial intelligence and its applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conclusion:&lt;br&gt;This report covers a range of topics in the tech, business, and AI sectors. It highlights significant developments, partnerships, and potential impacts on various industries. Overall, it showcases the dynamic nature of these fields and the continuous pursuit of innovation.</summary></entry></feed>