<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-12T12:01:06Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 12 Aug 2023 12:01:06</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-12T12:01:06Z</published><updated>2023-08-12T12:01:06Z</updated><id>aceadc7b-b654-41d0-9333-ddb996a30011</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Ukrainian troops face delays in learning to pilot F-16 jets&lt;br&gt;- Former executive claims Salesforce fired him after raising concerns about software&lt;br&gt;- Open-source proxy server for Llama2, GPT-4, Claude2 with Logging, Cache&lt;br&gt;- Samsung Remote Test Lab allows running emulated Samsung phones from the browser&lt;br&gt;- AI causes real harm, focus should be on that rather than end-of-humanity hype&lt;br&gt;- Only a few hours left to save on passes to TechCrunch Disrupt 2023&lt;br&gt;- A look back at the secrets to going big, going multi-product, and going public with Amplitude CEO Spenser Skates&lt;br&gt;- Publishers and Internet Archive agree to streamline digital book-lending&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- A former executive says he was fired by Salesforce after raising concerns about software&lt;br&gt;- Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez and House Democrats push Attorney General Merrick Garland to investigate Clarence Thomas' lavish gifts from billionaires&lt;br&gt;- The Biden Administration will spend $1.2 billion on two projects that remove CO2 from the air&lt;br&gt;- The U.S. is investing $1.2 billion to fight climate change with vacuums that suck carbon from the sky&lt;br&gt;- John Wiley &amp; Sons, Inc. announces resignation of Laurie A. Leshin&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- If it can be designed on a computer, it can be built by robots&lt;br&gt;- AI causes real harm, focus should be on that rather than end-of-humanity hype&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Depression and anxiety won't raise your risk of cancer, study finds&lt;br&gt;- For over 20 years, archaeologists in Germany thought a 35,000-year-old figurine they found was a horse. Now, they aren't sure whether or not it's a cave lion or cave bear.&lt;br&gt;- What is 'phubbing'? Study shows how it can hurt your relationships&lt;br&gt;- Today's Wordle #783 hints, clues, and answer for Friday, August 11th&lt;br&gt;- Unleash your focus: The ultimate ADHD Pomodoro method for enhanced productivity&lt;br&gt;- A psychologist tells us which 'love type' is the key to a lasting marriage&lt;br&gt;- Perseids 2023: Your last-minute guide to the year's best meteor shower&lt;br&gt;- New shows and movies to stream this weekend on Netflix, Hulu, HBO Max, Disney+&lt;br&gt;- Perseids 2023: Your last-minute guide to the year's best meteor shower&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Tech: The advancements in technology, such as open-source proxy servers and remote testing labs, are enabling more efficient and accessible development and testing processes.&lt;br&gt;- Business: The Biden Administration's investment in projects to remove CO2 from the air highlights the growing focus on combating climate change and the role of technology in achieving environmental goals.&lt;br&gt;- AI: While AI has the potential to revolutionize various industries, there is a need to address the real harm it can cause and prioritize ethical considerations.&lt;br&gt;- Other: The topics covered in this category range from mental health and relationships to astronomy and entertainment, showcasing the diverse interests and concerns of individuals.</summary></entry></feed>