<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-13T20:01:21Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 13 Aug 2023 20:01:21</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-13T20:01:21Z</published><updated>2023-08-13T20:01:21Z</updated><id>88bc16e4-1901-4631-9174-a5ded4023103</id><summary type="html">Report: Tech and AI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. "The Last Artist": Pika Labs' AI video platform has generated a sci-fi short film called "The Last Artist."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The film showcases the capabilities of Pika Labs' AI video platform in creating visually stunning and engaging content.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Solar storm threat to power grids and satellites:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Scientists are concerned about a once-in-a-century solar storm that could potentially cause severe damage to power grids and satellite systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Radious: Rent your home as a coworking space:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Radious is a platform that allows homeowners to rent their properties to businesses as coworking spaces, combining the concepts of Airbnb and WeWork.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Sony and music labels sue Internet Archive:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Sony and other music labels have filed a lawsuit against the Internet Archive for digitizing old records without permission.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. PlayHT introduces AI model with emotions for voice AI:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Key points: PlayHT has developed an AI model that incorporates the concept of emotions, allowing users to control and direct the generation of speech with specific emotions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The advancements in AI technology are enabling the creation of visually stunning content and enhancing the capabilities of video platforms.&lt;br&gt;- The potential threat of solar storms highlights the need for robust infrastructure and preparedness to protect power grids and satellite systems.&lt;br&gt;- The emergence of platforms like Radious demonstrates the growing demand for flexible and shared workspace solutions.&lt;br&gt;- The legal battle between Sony and the Internet Archive raises questions about copyright and digital preservation.&lt;br&gt;- The integration of emotions in AI models opens up new possibilities for personalized and expressive voice AI applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Report: Business&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Near miss between private jet and Southwest flight sparks investigations:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Key points: A near miss incident between a private jet and a Southwest flight has triggered investigations into the safety protocols and potential risks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Zelenskyy fires recruitment officials for accepting bribes:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Key points: Ukrainian President Zelenskyy has dismissed recruitment officials for accepting bribes, highlighting the ongoing issue of corruption in the country.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Mortgage and Refinance Rates:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The current mortgage and refinance rates are discussed, suggesting that rates may have peaked.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Starter homes becoming more expensive:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Key points: The cost of starter homes has increased significantly, making it more challenging for first-time buyers to enter the housing market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. Feud between Arizona workers and chipmaker:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Key points: A dispute has arisen between Arizona workers and a leading chipmaker over claims that the US lacks the necessary skills to build a new factory.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Safety incidents in the aviation industry raise concerns about the effectiveness of safety protocols and the need for thorough investigations.&lt;br&gt;- The dismissal of recruitment officials for accepting bribes highlights the pervasive issue of corruption in Ukraine and the need for stronger anti-corruption measures.&lt;br&gt;- The fluctuating mortgage and refinance rates indicate the dynamic nature of the housing market and the potential impact on homeowners and buyers.&lt;br&gt;- The rising cost of starter homes poses challenges for individuals looking to enter the housing market, potentially exacerbating the issue of housing affordability.&lt;br&gt;- The feud between Arizona workers and the chipmaker underscores the ongoing debate surrounding domestic manufacturing capabilities and the reliance on foreign supply chains.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall Insights:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The integration of AI technology in various industries is driving innovation and transforming traditional processes.&lt;br&gt;- Corruption remains a significant challenge in many countries, requiring continuous efforts to combat and eradicate it.&lt;br&gt;- The housing market is experiencing fluctuations and challenges, impacting both buyers and homeowners.&lt;br&gt;- The debate surrounding domestic manufacturing capabilities and supply chain reliance highlights the need for strategic planning and investment in workforce development.&lt;br&gt;- The intersection of technology and society raises ethical and legal considerations that need to be addressed.</summary></entry></feed>