<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-30T20:02:11Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 30 Oct 2023 20:02:11</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-30T20:02:11Z</published><updated>2023-10-30T20:02:11Z</updated><id>57e3d6d0-77df-4f11-8d29-998ad478bc19</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's chief scientist admits that they didn't think ChatGPT was very good when it was released.&lt;br&gt;- Expensify shuts down its glitzy lounge where employees could pay $9 a month for coffee and cocktails, just 6 months after its launch.&lt;br&gt;- Internal slides reveal the work of Google's "Ads Quality" team.&lt;br&gt;- A wild AI tool is developed that can improve any website.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Ford, Bank of America, and Morgan Stanley are among the 120 S&amp;P 500 stocks that have experienced a significant drop of over 20% since the end of July.&lt;br&gt;- Walmart managers resort to extreme measures to get customers to complete the retailer's checkout survey, causing confusion among shoppers and workers.&lt;br&gt;- A stay-at-home mom becomes a professional cuddler, earning $150 an hour.&lt;br&gt;- Dizzee Rascal and Wiley seemingly end their feud after appearing together.&lt;br&gt;- Zendy announces a new global subscription plan at Frankfurt Book Fair.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Understanding the Difference Between GPT and LLM: Deciphering AI Language Models.&lt;br&gt;- This AI Paper Introduces POYO-1: An Artificial Intelligence Framework Deciphering Neural Activity across Large-Scale Recordings with Deep Learning.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- German-Israeli Shani Louk is confirmed dead, three weeks after being captured by Hamas and paraded through Gaza in her underwear.&lt;br&gt;- People with autism are found to be less likely to succumb to the bystander effect, according to research.&lt;br&gt;- 15,000 scientists warn that society could collapse by 2100 due to climate change.&lt;br&gt;- Extreme heat-related cardiovascular deaths are projected to double by midcentury at the current emission pace.&lt;br&gt;- Delta's chief sustainability officer is determined to use less fuel.&lt;br&gt;- In 2018, an abusive cop that was previously reported on is sentenced to a year in prison.&lt;br&gt;- Scientists create the largest map of the brain, potentially revolutionizing disease treatment.&lt;br&gt;- What DoorDash drivers really think about customers may surprise you.&lt;br&gt;- The chief engineer at Google shares the four mistakes he has seen even the best candidates make during interviews.&lt;br&gt;- An etiquette coach highlights the common mistakes made by Gen Zers and provides advice on how to fix them.&lt;br&gt;- A journalist drives the electric BMW i4 and finds it to be a more luxurious and familiar alternative to a Tesla.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's admission about ChatGPT's initial quality raises questions about the development and testing process of AI models.&lt;br&gt;- The closure of Expensify's lounge raises concerns about the sustainability and effectiveness of employee perks.&lt;br&gt;- Walmart's aggressive approach to customer surveys may negatively impact the shopping experience and confuse both customers and employees.&lt;br&gt;- The feud between Dizzee Rascal and Wiley coming to an end suggests a potential reconciliation and collaboration in the music industry.&lt;br&gt;- The introduction of a new global subscription plan by Zendy indicates the company's expansion and efforts to reach a wider audience.&lt;br&gt;- The research on autism and the bystander effect provides valuable insights into the behavior and social dynamics of individuals with autism.&lt;br&gt;- The warning from scientists about the potential collapse of society due to climate change emphasizes the urgency of addressing environmental issues.&lt;br&gt;- The projection of increased heat-related cardiovascular deaths highlights the need for immediate action to mitigate the effects of climate change.&lt;br&gt;- Delta's commitment to reducing fuel usage aligns with the growing focus on sustainability in the transportation industry.&lt;br&gt;- The sentencing of an abusive cop demonstrates the importance of holding law enforcement accountable for their actions.&lt;br&gt;- The development of a comprehensive brain map opens up possibilities for advancing research and treatment of neurological conditions.&lt;br&gt;- The AI tool that improves websites showcases the potential of AI in enhancing user experiences and optimizing online platforms.&lt;br&gt;- The insights from the Google engineering executive and etiquette coach provide valuable advice for job seekers and individuals navigating social situations.&lt;br&gt;- The positive review of the electric BMW i4 suggests a competitive alternative to Tesla in the electric vehicle market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report highlights various developments in the tech, business, and AI sectors, as well as significant social and environmental issues. It emphasizes the importance of continuous improvement in AI models, the challenges of sustaining employee perks, the impact of aggressive customer survey tactics, the potential for reconciliation in the music industry, and the need for urgent action on climate change. Additionally, it showcases advancements in brain mapping, AI technology, and electric vehicles.</summary></entry></feed>