<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-23T20:02:25Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 23 Aug 2023 20:02:25</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-23T20:02:25Z</published><updated>2023-08-23T20:02:25Z</updated><id>f2d27570-4d6c-4df7-97ac-e15ad906c15d</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Nvidia plans to triple production of its $40,000 chips to meet demand from AI companies.&lt;br&gt;- AI2 unveils Dolma, a 3 trillion token corpus pioneering transparency in language model research.&lt;br&gt;- Elevenlabs unveils its latest multilingual AI speech technology with enhanced authenticity.&lt;br&gt;- TSMC's Arizona plant is delayed due to poor management, not a shortage of skilled labor.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- US Feature Phone Market stages a comeback as Gen Z and Millennials advocate digital detox.&lt;br&gt;- Trump's Atlanta booking on RICO charges highlights the need for perp-walkable cities.&lt;br&gt;- As Better.com prepares for its public debut, CEO Vishal Garg emphasizes leadership training.&lt;br&gt;- Maria Shriver's MOSH secures $3M for retail expansion.&lt;br&gt;- QIA invests $1 billion in Ambani's Reliance Retail at a $100 billion valuation.&lt;br&gt;- Startup world watches as Arm and Instacart test the IPO market.&lt;br&gt;- Apple Business Connect transforms how companies showcase themselves.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- AI2 unveils Dolma, a 3 trillion token corpus pioneering transparency in language model research.&lt;br&gt;- Making smart use of emerging prompt-pattern catalogs for generative AI.&lt;br&gt;- The evolving role of CIOs and CTOs in the AI economy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The US Feature Phone Market is experiencing a resurgence as younger generations seek digital detox.&lt;br&gt;- The demand for AI chips is skyrocketing, leading Nvidia to triple production.&lt;br&gt;- Transparency in language model research is being prioritized with the unveiling of Dolma.&lt;br&gt;- The role of CIOs and CTOs is evolving in the AI economy.&lt;br&gt;- The IPO market is being closely watched by the startup world.&lt;br&gt;- Apple Business Connect is transforming how companies showcase themselves.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The tech industry is experiencing significant developments in AI, with Nvidia increasing chip production and AI2 unveiling Dolma for transparency in language model research. The business sector sees the resurgence of the US Feature Phone Market and the investment of QIA in Reliance Retail. The evolving role of CIOs and CTOs in the AI economy is also highlighted. Overall, there is a growing demand for AI technologies and a shift in the way businesses operate and showcase themselves.</summary></entry></feed>