<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-31T08:03:38Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:03:38</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-31T08:03:38Z</published><updated>2023-10-31T08:03:38Z</updated><id>4396e6fd-75e0-459c-9e02-8efb687540b6</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- After watching Russia's and Ukraine's electronic warriors battle it out, the US military wants to 'dial up' up its own 'jamming power'&lt;br&gt;- NASA's James Webb Space Telescope imaged a stunning supernova remnant and revealed details Hubble couldn't capture&lt;br&gt;- Google Brain founder says big tech is lying about AI danger&lt;br&gt;- AI Startups Fear That Biden’s AI Executive Order Could Stifle Innovation&lt;br&gt;- Webinar: Accelerate AV Development with NVIDIA DGX Cloud and NVIDIA AI Enterprise&lt;br&gt;- Podcast: Amdocs' Victoria Myers on How Employees See AI and ... - HCM Technology Report&lt;br&gt;- Functionality in Equitation: Eyes Are Important For The Movement - | Eurodressage&lt;br&gt;- Q&amp;A: White House AI advisor says US is 'catching up' to the tech, as Biden's new executive order demands transparency for the world's biggest AI models&lt;br&gt;- Vanguard CEO says asset-management giant won't pursue a bitcoin ETF, unlike rivals&lt;br&gt;- Japan's farmers are getting too old to work the land. 5G-powered smart tech is doing the heavy lifting for them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Coppell's Wiley relishing final season to coach son, Amari'a - Star Local Media&lt;br&gt;- Billionaire hedge fund boss Ken Griffin pays for 1,200 staff and family members to visit Disney Tokyo and hear performances by Maroon 5 and Calvin Harris&lt;br&gt;- Drugmakers Are Set to Pay 23andMe Millions to Access Consumer DNA&lt;br&gt;- McConnell fights for his legacy as he sells a divided GOP on Ukraine funding&lt;br&gt;- Biden's Education Department reveals the 4 groups of student-loan borrowers it's prioritizing for its second attempt at debt relief&lt;br&gt;- Dow soars more than 500 points as stocks jump amid easing Mideast conflict fears&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Sam Bankman-Fried can't get past the fundamental flaw in his defense strategy&lt;br&gt;- Judge pares down artists' AI copyright lawsuit against Midjourney, Stability AI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Lynvol Arthur Obituary - Wiley Funeral Home - Granbury - 2023 - Legacy.com&lt;br&gt;- Best Mortgage Lenders for Low or Bad Credit Scores of November 2023&lt;br&gt;- World Series live stream 2023: Where to watch Rangers vs. Diamondbacks Game 3 online from anywhere&lt;br&gt;- Noah Fifita Earns Third Pac-12 Freshman of the Week Honor ... - University of Arizona Athletics&lt;br&gt;- Best Cancel for Any Reason (CFAR) Travel Insurance Plans of November 2023&lt;br&gt;- Best Banks and Credit Unions for Military Members and Their Families, November 2023&lt;br&gt;- A tumultuous withdrawal from Afghanistan gave independents a reason to ditch Biden. The conflict in Israel and Gaza could do the same thing for Democrats.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The US military is looking to enhance its electronic warfare capabilities after observing the battles between Russia and Ukraine.&lt;br&gt;- NASA's James Webb Space Telescope has provided detailed images of a supernova remnant that were beyond the capabilities of the Hubble Space Telescope.&lt;br&gt;- There are concerns about the potential dangers of AI, with some accusing big tech companies of downplaying the risks.&lt;br&gt;- The AI industry is worried that Biden's AI executive order may hinder innovation.&lt;br&gt;- Vanguard CEO has stated that the company will not pursue a bitcoin ETF, setting it apart from its competitors.&lt;br&gt;- Japan's aging farming population is turning to smart technology, powered by 5G, to assist with agricultural work.&lt;br&gt;- Billionaire Ken Griffin treated his staff and their families to a trip to Disney Tokyo, featuring performances by Maroon 5 and Calvin Harris.&lt;br&gt;- The stock market experienced a significant increase, with the Dow soaring over 500 points, due to easing fears of conflict in the Middle East.&lt;br&gt;- Student loan borrowers and debt relief are a priority for Biden's Education Department.&lt;br&gt;- The withdrawal from Afghanistan and the conflict in Israel and Gaza have had political implications for both Democrats and Republicans.</summary></entry></feed>