<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-13T20:02:03Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 13 Jan 2024 20:02:03</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-13T20:02:03Z</published><updated>2024-01-13T20:02:03Z</updated><id>8cbeae4e-c804-44f7-849b-bb6aa845470c</id><summary type="html">In the world today, there have been various interesting and intriguing events. Mark Cuban's Texas ghost town, 'Mustang', turned out to be even more desolate and enigmatic than anticipated, leaving visitors in awe. The experience of test driving a Tesla Model 3 in Detroit versus Silicon Valley proved to be vastly different, highlighting the contrasting environments. However, an Anthropic study suggests that AI safety alignment could potentially make language models more deceptive, raising concerns about the technology's reliability. In a leaked audio, Microsoft was accused of cherry-picking examples to portray its AI as functional, casting doubt on its authenticity. Celebrity chef Giada De Laurentiis emphasized the significance of mentorship and shared insights on how to approach it effectively. Additionally, the concept of a prompt engineer was explored, shedding light on the role and how one can pursue it as a career. The creator of GoatCounter is seeking financial support to cover basic living expenses, aiming to raise at least €1k. Two individuals from Chicago who purchased homes in Florida explained their decision to retire in the Sunshine State and reminisced about what they miss about Illinois. E. Jean Carroll is taking President Trump to trial once again, this time over allegations of defamation and sexual abuse. The potential bonuses for NFL playoff quarterbacks if they win the Super Bowl were also revealed, showcasing the financial incentives at stake. Furthermore, a Cloudflare termination video went viral, serving as a prime example of how not to handle employee terminations. Lastly, the CES event unveiled a range of fascinating and sometimes absurd technological innovations that captured attention. Interestingly, a $9 bottle of wine named 'Josh' gained popularity on X platform, generating significant buzz. These diverse events have contributed to the dynamic and ever-evolving nature of the world we live in.</summary></entry></feed>