<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-20T10:05:25Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 20 Aug 2023 10:05:25</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-20T10:05:25Z</published><updated>2023-08-20T10:05:25Z</updated><id>5686e1ee-cbf8-4644-b92f-ce13ffa99040</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Self-driving car company Cruise to reduce driverless fleet by 50% after recent crashes.&lt;br&gt;- Mousetrap.jl: a GUI library for Julia and C++ that fully wrap GTK4.&lt;br&gt;- Cellebrite asks cops to keep its phone hacking tech 'hush hush'.&lt;br&gt;- Unlocking the Power of Context with Google AI: A Showdown Between prefixLM and causalLM in In-Context Learning.&lt;br&gt;- Apple devices spoofed, Musk eggs on Zuckerberg and Better.com goes public.&lt;br&gt;- This AI Paper Introduces A Comprehensive RDF Dataset With Over 26 Billion Triples Covering Scholarly Data Across All Scientific Disciplines.&lt;br&gt;- Air Force funds 'blended wing body' design for long-range, fuel-efficient flight.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Oil companies approaching influencers and enlisting PR firms to reach younger generations on social media.&lt;br&gt;- A nearly $200,000 fine threatening to shut down a Florida abortion clinic, but activists have already crowdfunded half of it.&lt;br&gt;- A former Giuliani mayoral staffer says Fani Willis will be talked about as a future Georgia governor or vice president if she convicts Trump.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Unlocking the Power of Context with Google AI: A Showdown Between prefixLM and causalLM in In-Context Learning.&lt;br&gt;- People like human art more than AI art - but it's complicated.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- W. H. Auden's 1954 review of The Fellowship of the Ring.&lt;br&gt;- The Rimac Nevera Has Broken the Production EV Nurburgring Lap Record.&lt;br&gt;- A new way to identify chiral molecules with light could vastly improve detection.&lt;br&gt;- Sleep ALL NIGHT to Heavy Rain | Black screen, 10 hrs, No ads.&lt;br&gt;- Today's Wordle #792 Hints, Clues And Answer For Sunday, August 20th.&lt;br&gt;- Stormzy at All Points East review: after a slow start the rapper gave fans a fast and furious thrill ride - Yahoo Canada Sports.&lt;br&gt;- Stormzy at All Points East review: after a slow start the rapper gave fans a fast and furious thrill ride - Yahoo Eurosport UK.&lt;br&gt;- The 3 Best Record Players for Enjoying Your Favorite Albums - The Wall Street Journal.&lt;br&gt;- Little Rock Nine members slam restrictions on AP African American Studies course in Arkansas.&lt;br&gt;- North Korea's new ICBM looks and works an awful lot like a Russian ICBM, experts say.&lt;br&gt;- Meta's news ban is preventing Canadians from sharing vital information about the wildfires ripping through western Canada.&lt;br&gt;- A judge dismissed a Wisconsin politician's defamation suit against a newspaper, but the legal fees may still shutter the paper.&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine continues to target Moscow with drone strikes, forcing the city to shut down its airports.&lt;br&gt;- First Hurricane to hit California in 84 years; 'catastrophic' flooding feared.&lt;br&gt;- 70 years ago, an Anglo-US coup condemned Iran to decades of oppression.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Self-driving car company Cruise's decision to reduce its driverless fleet by 50% after recent crashes highlights the challenges and safety concerns associated with autonomous vehicles.&lt;br&gt;- The use of AI in various fields, such as Google AI's research on in-context learning and the preference for human art over AI-generated art, showcases the advancements and complexities of artificial intelligence.&lt;br&gt;- The involvement of oil companies in influencer marketing and PR campaigns targeting younger generations reflects the changing landscape of advertising and the importance of social media in reaching audiences.&lt;br&gt;- The legal battles and controversies surrounding tech companies, such as Cellebrite's request for secrecy in its phone hacking technology and Apple devices being spoofed, demonstrate the ongoing challenges and ethical considerations in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of political decisions, such as the restrictions on AP African American Studies course in Arkansas and the potential conviction of Trump by Fani Willis, highlights the intersection of politics and education, as well as the potential future implications for individuals involved.&lt;br&gt;- The record-breaking achievements in various fields, such as the Rimac Nevera's production EV Nurburgring lap record and the comprehensive RDF dataset introduced by AI research, showcase the continuous advancements and innovations in technology and scientific disciplines.&lt;br&gt;- The natural disasters, such as the first hurricane to hit California in 84 years and the wildfires in western Canada, emphasize the environmental challenges and potential consequences faced by communities and the need for effective disaster management strategies.&lt;br&gt;- The historical events, such as the Anglo-US coup in Iran 70 years ago, shed light on the long-lasting impacts of political interventions and the importance of understanding historical contexts in shaping current situations.</summary></entry></feed>