<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-20T04:01:01Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 20 Aug 2023 04:01:01</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-20T04:01:01Z</published><updated>2023-08-20T04:01:01Z</updated><id>e4c9a89b-b367-4ec6-b951-9e539ae04d18</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Air Force funds ‘blended wing body’ design for long-range, fuel-efficient flight&lt;br&gt;- Helidon Níma: The first Java microservices framework based on virtual threads&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft retracts AI-written article advising tourists to visit a food bank&lt;br&gt;- Cellebrite asks cops to keep its phone hacking tech ‘hush hush’&lt;br&gt;- How SaaStr Built the World’s Largest Community for Business Software with Jason Lemkin&lt;br&gt;- A Comprehensive Guide to Creating a Scalable Folder Structure for Flutter Apps&lt;br&gt;- Get Notified in Slack for Every New User Sign Up With Authgear&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Spotify looked to ban white noise podcasts to become more profitable&lt;br&gt;- Kroger's secret weapon in the battle for your dining-out dollars is ... sushi&lt;br&gt;- Rupert Murdoch is urging Virginia Gov. Glenn Youngkin to jump into the Republican presidential race, report says&lt;br&gt;- TikTokers aren't McLovin' a 'trash' McDonald's clothing collaboration with skate brand Palace&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- People like human art more than AI art - but it's complicated&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft retracts AI-written article advising tourists to visit a food bank&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Others:&lt;br&gt;- Meta's news ban is preventing Canadians from sharing vital information about the wildfires ripping through western Canada&lt;br&gt;- A nearly $200,000 fine is threatening to shut down a Florida abortion clinic. But activists have already crowdfunded half of it.&lt;br&gt;- A former Giuliani mayoral staffer says Fani Willis will be talked about as a future Georgia governor or vice president if she convicts Trump&lt;br&gt;- First Hurricane to hit California in 84 years; ‘catastrophic’ flooding feared&lt;br&gt;- 70 years ago, an Anglo-US coup condemned Iran to decades of oppression&lt;br&gt;- July 4th is not the US's Birthday. A tale about how Ben Franklin invented the US&lt;br&gt;- 3 Reasons Why You’re Afraid To Show Your True Self In Relationships&lt;br&gt;- 3 ‘Must Know’ Messages For The Western U.S. About Hurricane Hilary&lt;br&gt;- Someone just paid almost $2 million for the rusted shell of a 1954 Ferrari&lt;br&gt;- Trump's PAC is doling out millions in legal fees over 2020 election investigations — just not to Rudy Giuliani&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine sends its US-supplied Stryker combat vehicles into battle for the first time in the counteroffensive against Russia, say reports&lt;br&gt;- Here's the full list of automakers who've said their cars will be able to use Tesla's Superchargers — and how to do it&lt;br&gt;- NC Files More Than 400 Charges Against Shelby Nissan Dealership Employees&lt;br&gt;- Striking writers have been in consistent talks with studios for over a week&lt;br&gt;- ‘Baldur’s Gate 3’ Lands An IGN 10/10, Metascore Has Ticked Down To Tie ‘Tears’</summary></entry></feed>