<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-13T04:01:23Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 13 Aug 2023 04:01:23</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-13T04:01:23Z</published><updated>2023-08-13T04:01:23Z</updated><id>9c1420c8-d4b7-4ca4-9ebc-88416e1ee13c</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Moderation on a popular AI image generator can be easily circumvented to create images that drive conspiracy theories, according to a new report.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers at Tel Aviv University propose ConceptLab, a creative generation platform that uses diffusion prior constraints to generate new concepts that have never been seen before.&lt;br&gt;- 'The most stunning demo I've ever seen in my life': ChatGPT impressed Bill Gates by acing the AP Bio exam.&lt;br&gt;- An Uber Eats rider and YouTuber claims to have stopped picking up from McDonald's due to mistreatment of delivery staff and issues with spilled drinks.&lt;br&gt;- Tracing the roots of the 8086 instruction set to the Datapoint 2200 minicomputer.&lt;br&gt;- Dissecting the UN Cybercrime Convention's threat to coders' rights at DEFCON.&lt;br&gt;- AI agent Dynalang could change the way we talk to robots.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- James Carville dismisses concerns that Democrats don't have a strong presidential bench for 2028, stating that there are many potential candidates.&lt;br&gt;- The once-mighty Iowa Democratic Party is struggling as the GOP dominates the onetime swing state.&lt;br&gt;- Congressmen call on Biden to stop Greg Abbott from transporting migrants to Democratic-led cities after a 3-year-old child died on a bus headed from Texas to Chicago.&lt;br&gt;- An American Airlines passenger paid for 3 seats to fly with his beloved Great Dane dog from LA to New York.&lt;br&gt;- Soccer fans caught burning or ripping money in Argentina face up to 30 days in prison as the country cracks down on those mocking its high inflation.&lt;br&gt;- Saving Our Rainforests - The Business Case For Acting On Nature.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Moderation on a popular AI image generator can be easily circumvented to create images that drive conspiracy theories, according to a new report.&lt;br&gt;- 'The most stunning demo I've ever seen in my life': ChatGPT impressed Bill Gates by acing the AP Bio exam.&lt;br&gt;- AI agent Dynalang could change the way we talk to robots.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Points:&lt;br&gt;- Moderation on AI image generators needs improvement to prevent the creation of conspiracy theory-driven images.&lt;br&gt;- Tel Aviv University's ConceptLab proposes a platform for generating new concepts using diffusion prior constraints.&lt;br&gt;- ChatGPT's impressive performance on the AP Bio exam caught the attention of Bill Gates.&lt;br&gt;- Mistreatment of delivery staff and spilled drinks have led an Uber Eats rider to stop picking up from McDonald's.&lt;br&gt;- The origins of the 8086 instruction set can be traced back to the Datapoint 2200 minicomputer.&lt;br&gt;- Concerns about coders' rights arise from the UN Cybercrime Convention.&lt;br&gt;- Dynalang, an AI agent, has the potential to revolutionize human-robot interactions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The need for better moderation tools and algorithms to prevent the spread of misinformation and conspiracy theories through AI-generated content.&lt;br&gt;- The potential of AI and creative generation platforms to push the boundaries of innovation and generate novel concepts.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of AI in various sectors, including education (ChatGPT's performance on exams) and customer service (Dynalang's potential in human-robot interactions).&lt;br&gt;- The importance of fair treatment and working conditions for gig economy workers, as highlighted by the Uber Eats rider's experience.&lt;br&gt;- The political landscape and challenges faced by different parties in the United States, as seen in the struggles of the Iowa Democratic Party and the transportation of migrants to Democratic-led cities.&lt;br&gt;- The intersection of technology and environmental conservation, as demonstrated by the business case for acting on nature and the potential of AI to contribute to sustainability efforts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The report highlights various topics under the broader categories of Tech, Business, and AI. It discusses the challenges and opportunities in each area, emphasizing the need for improved moderation in AI-generated content, the potential of creative generation platforms, and the impact of AI on different sectors. The report also touches on political and social issues, such as the struggles of political parties and the treatment of gig economy workers. Overall, it provides insights into the current landscape and future developments in these areas.</summary></entry></feed>