<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-03T08:03:55Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 03 Sep 2023 08:03:55</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-03T08:03:55Z</published><updated>2023-09-03T08:03:55Z</updated><id>d958fc9a-a4c0-4531-bdc4-2a336c45741e</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- The Para Method: The Simple System for Organizing Your Digital Life in Seconds&lt;br&gt;- Mini's new Cooper EV centers a giant circular OLED on the dash&lt;br&gt;- Show HN: I mirrored all the code from PyPI to GitHub and analyzed it&lt;br&gt;- Intel shows off 8-core, 528-thread processor with 1TB/s of co-packaged optics&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft PowerToys' Crop and Lock lets you make mini app windows&lt;br&gt;- Celebrating over 2 million pulls of pyaction from the GitHub Container Registry&lt;br&gt;- Building Simple and Customizable Image Classifier with Teachable Machine and Python&lt;br&gt;- Manipulate your Hyper-V Windows through Ansible running in a Docker container&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- The Para Method offers a simple system for organizing digital life efficiently.&lt;br&gt;- Mini's new Cooper EV features a large circular OLED display on the dashboard.&lt;br&gt;- A developer mirrored all the code from PyPI to GitHub and conducted an analysis.&lt;br&gt;- Intel showcased an impressive 8-core processor with high-speed co-packaged optics.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft PowerToys' Crop and Lock feature allows users to create mini app windows.&lt;br&gt;- The GitHub Container Registry reached over 2 million pulls of pyaction.&lt;br&gt;- Teachable Machine and Python can be used to build a customizable image classifier.&lt;br&gt;- Ansible running in a Docker container enables manipulation of Hyper-V Windows.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The Para Method provides a practical solution for organizing digital files and information.&lt;br&gt;- Mini's integration of a large circular OLED display enhances the user experience.&lt;br&gt;- Analyzing code from PyPI on GitHub can offer valuable insights and improvements.&lt;br&gt;- Intel's processor with co-packaged optics demonstrates advancements in high-speed computing.&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft PowerToys' Crop and Lock feature improves multitasking and window management.&lt;br&gt;- The GitHub Container Registry's milestone highlights the popularity of pyaction.&lt;br&gt;- Teachable Machine and Python offer accessible tools for creating image classifiers.&lt;br&gt;- Ansible running in a Docker container simplifies the management of Hyper-V Windows.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- John Wiley &amp; Sons: Still Too Much Risk, Too Little Return (NYSE:WLY) - Seeking Alpha&lt;br&gt;- A Look Back: Datadog's CMO Alex Rosemblat on Building Marketing Channels Slowly to Achieve Massive Scale (Pod and Video)&lt;br&gt;- Bill Richardson, the former New Mexico governor and UN ambassador just nominated for a Nobel Peace Prize for his work to free political prisoners, has died at 75&lt;br&gt;- One of Russia's richest oligarchs who now lives in Dubai says Putin's invasion of Ukraine made him a 'pariah'&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Seeking Alpha analyzes the risks and returns of John Wiley &amp; Sons.&lt;br&gt;- Datadog's CMO, Alex Rosemblat, discusses building marketing channels for massive scale.&lt;br&gt;- Bill Richardson, a former governor and UN ambassador, passed away after being nominated for a Nobel Peace Prize.&lt;br&gt;- A Russian oligarch living in Dubai expresses his disapproval of Putin's invasion of Ukraine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The analysis of John Wiley &amp; Sons highlights concerns regarding risk and return.&lt;br&gt;- Datadog's CMO emphasizes the importance of gradual marketing channel development.&lt;br&gt;- Bill Richardson's nomination for a Nobel Peace Prize recognizes his efforts in freeing political prisoners.&lt;br&gt;- The Russian oligarch's perspective sheds light on the impact of Putin's actions on his reputation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- This company thinks the future of education is virtual reality schools that offer students a more 'decentralized' experience&lt;br&gt;- Unlocking the Power of Diversity in Neural Networks: How Adaptive Neurons Outperform Homogeneity in Image Classification and Nonlinear Regression&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- A company believes that virtual reality schools can provide a decentralized educational experience.&lt;br&gt;- Research explores how diversity in neural networks improves image classification and regression.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Virtual reality schools have the potential to revolutionize education by offering decentralized learning opportunities.&lt;br&gt;- The study on diversity in neural networks highlights the advantages of adaptive neurons in various tasks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Burning Man access is closed as heavy rains muddy the playa&lt;br&gt;- Explosive Flash As Large Object Crashes Into Jupiter Captured By Cameras&lt;br&gt;- Republican lawmakers want to stop businesses in a small Florida town from displaying rainbow stickers to show they are a safe place for LGBTQ+ people&lt;br&gt;- Pennsylvania Democrats won big in 2022, holding the governorship, winning a US Senate seat, and flipping the state House. Now, the state party is being called a 'disaster.'&lt;br&gt;- Kentucky Gov. Andy Beshear won't say if he'd follow the state's new Senate vacancy law and appoint another Republican if McConnell steps down&lt;br&gt;- The surprising behavior of male fruit flies under intense light conditions&lt;br&gt;- Geoforensic search to crime scene: Remote sensing, geophysics... - onlinelibrary.wiley.com&lt;br&gt;- ‘Conserve food and water’: No way in or out of Burning Man after storm&lt;br&gt;- GOP lawmakers take aim at LGBTQ+ 'safe places' program in small Florida town&lt;br&gt;- ‘Destiny 2’ Turns ‘Dungeon Boss’ Crota Into A Monster In Reprised Raid&lt;br&gt;- One Dose Of Psychedelic Psilocybin Reduced Depression Symptoms For 6 Weeks&lt;br&gt;- MrBeast Announces Creator Esports League He’s Not Actually A Part Of&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Heavy rains have closed access to Burning Man due to muddy conditions.&lt;br&gt;- Cameras captured an explosive flash as a large object crashed into Jupiter.&lt;br&gt;- Republican lawmakers aim to prevent businesses in a small Florida town from displaying LGBTQ+ safe place stickers.&lt;br&gt;- Pennsylvania Democrats achieved significant victories in the 2022 elections but face criticism within the party.&lt;br&gt;- Kentucky Gov. Andy Beshear remains undecided on following the new Senate vacancy law.&lt;br&gt;- Male fruit flies exhibit surprising behavior under intense light conditions.&lt;br&gt;- Geoforensic search techniques are applied to crime scene investigations.&lt;br&gt;- Burning Man attendees are advised to conserve food and water due to limited access after a storm.&lt;br&gt;- GOP lawmakers target LGBTQ+ safe places program in a small Florida town.&lt;br&gt;- 'Destiny 2' introduces a reprised raid featuring a transformed dungeon boss.&lt;br&gt;- Psychedelic psilocybin shows promise in reducing depression symptoms for six weeks.&lt;br&gt;- MrBeast announces a creator esports league in which he is not directly involved.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Inclement weather can impact events like Burning Man, leading to access restrictions.&lt;br&gt;- The observation of a large object crashing into Jupiter provides valuable astronomical data.&lt;br&gt;- Opposition to LGBTQ+ safe place stickers highlights ongoing debates around inclusivity.&lt;br&gt;- Pennsylvania Democrats' electoral success is accompanied by internal challenges.&lt;br&gt;- Kentucky Gov. Andy Beshear faces a decision regarding the new Senate vacancy law.&lt;br&gt;- The behavior of male fruit flies under intense light conditions adds to our understanding of their biology.&lt;br&gt;- Geoforensic search techniques contribute to advancements in crime scene investigations.&lt;br&gt;- Limited access to Burning Man necessitates resource conservation for attendees.&lt;br&gt;- The targeting of LGBTQ+ safe places program raises concerns about inclusivity and acceptance.&lt;br&gt;- 'Destiny 2' introduces new gameplay experiences through reprised raids.&lt;br&gt;- Psychedelic psilocybin shows potential as a treatment for depression.&lt;br&gt;- MrBeast's announcement generates excitement within the creator community. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The report covers various topics including tech, business, AI, and others. In the tech section, key points include the Para Method for organizing digital life, Mini's new Cooper EV with a circular OLED display, code analysis on GitHub, Intel's impressive processor, Microsoft PowerToys' Crop and Lock feature, and milestones in the GitHub Container Registry. The business section discusses John Wiley &amp; Sons' risks and returns, Datadog's marketing channel development, the passing of Bill Richardson, and a Russian oligarch's perspective on Putin's actions. The AI section explores virtual reality schools and the power of diversity in neural networks. Other topics range from Burning Man access closure to political developments in Pennsylvania and Kentucky, surprising behavior of fruit flies, geoforensic search techniques, and various news and announcements. Overall, the report provides insights into the latest developments and trends across different fields.</summary></entry></feed>