<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-06T08:03:27Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:03:27</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-06T08:03:27Z</published><updated>2023-11-06T08:03:27Z</updated><id>101f23da-c9ef-4d5b-9a2f-17d16fc5457a</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- GPT-4 can pass the bar exam but has a decent chance of passing the CFA exams.&lt;br&gt;- Kai-Fu Lee's LLM startup, valued at $1B, unveils an open-source model.&lt;br&gt;- Together AI releases RedPajama v2, an open dataset for training large language models.&lt;br&gt;- New BeagleV Single Board Computer adopts Microchip's PolarFire SoC with FPGA.&lt;br&gt;- Imperial College London develops an AI method for few-shot imitation learning.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Trump plans to use the DOJ to investigate high-profile critics if he wins a second term.&lt;br&gt;- Bill Ackman calls on Harvard to take action against antisemitic and pro-Palestinian actions on campus.&lt;br&gt;- Consumers are paying more for streaming TV each month.&lt;br&gt;- Developing AI models or GPU clusters? Uncle Sam wants to talk.&lt;br&gt;- Tyson recalls 30,000 pounds of dinosaur-shaped chicken nuggets due to metal pieces.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- GPT-4 and ChatGPT have passed difficult exams.&lt;br&gt;- Imperial College London develops an AI method for few-shot imitation learning.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Others:&lt;br&gt;- 'Seven' takes place in Gotham, and David Fincher should make a 'Batman' movie.&lt;br&gt;- ULM falls at Southern Miss in a football game.&lt;br&gt;- 'Fear The Walking Dead' Season 8, Episode 9 review.&lt;br&gt;- Game report: Plymouth City Patriots defeat London Lions in the British Basketball League.&lt;br&gt;- Obituary for Moesha Shields.&lt;br&gt;- Pomerantz Law Firm investigates claims.&lt;br&gt;- Survivors and officials attend a state memorial honoring firefighters.&lt;br&gt;- Sheila E. and family honored for National Hispanic/Latinx Heritage Month celebration.&lt;br&gt;- Wiley College rebrands as Wiley University during homecoming.&lt;br&gt;- NAACP presents a ten-point voter action plan for a safer Oakland.&lt;br&gt;- Annemarie Wiley teases 'The Real Housewives of Beverly Hills.'&lt;br&gt;- US troops experience post-war trauma after battles with the Islamic State.&lt;br&gt;- Maryland Gov. Wes Moore brings a message of patriotism to Virginia's legislative elections.&lt;br&gt;- Middle-schooler wins $25,000 for inventing a faster fire-detection device.&lt;br&gt;- Russian troops face grueling conditions on the front line, according to UK intel.&lt;br&gt;- Console #182 features an interview with Alberto of Solidus, an open-source eCommerce framework.&lt;br&gt;- Q&amp;A with execs at Harlem's first legal dispensary.</summary></entry></feed>