<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-10T08:03:48Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 10 Nov 2023 08:03:48</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-10T08:03:48Z</published><updated>2023-11-10T08:03:48Z</updated><id>d5c2f236-fa98-41ea-ba2b-58166621ed75</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- The British navy's newest aircraft carrier collaborated with US pilots to launch F-35 jets in 'beast mode' for the first time.&lt;br&gt;- A $699 AI phone, powered by GPT-4, was unveiled by a husband and wife who previously worked at Apple. The phone projects information onto the user's hand.&lt;br&gt;- Google is under scrutiny for secret special app store deals, but has not disclosed if companies other than Spotify received such deals.&lt;br&gt;- Geely's Zeekr is preparing for a US IPO, but concerns about China's influence remain.&lt;br&gt;- Rocket Lab CEO states that launch contracts are not valuable until a rocket is proven and flying.&lt;br&gt;- Running virtual machines on Orange Pi 5 with Libvirt and Ubuntu is possible.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- United Airlines is temporarily increasing four of its credit card welcome offers by 10,000 miles.&lt;br&gt;- Amazon customers can learn how to find their recent orders and reorder previously purchased items.&lt;br&gt;- The best Black Friday mattress deals are available from Casper, Leesa, Nectar, and more.&lt;br&gt;- Meta allows users to shop on Amazon without leaving the app.&lt;br&gt;- The regulatory landscape in the pharma industry is shifting globally, requiring adjustments to the commercial model.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- The $699 AI phone, powered by GPT-4, projects information onto the user's hand.&lt;br&gt;- Twitter CEO expresses her wish for Elon Musk's AI to discuss sex with her kids.&lt;br&gt;- Cruise Robotaxis are forced to cease operations nationwide, impacting the industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The PlayStation 5 is considered a better buy than the Xbox Series X for most gamers.&lt;br&gt;- Wyoming's rare-earth discovery could be America's first new source since 1952.&lt;br&gt;- The first US commercial plant has started extracting carbon from the air, with plans for expansion.&lt;br&gt;- The 30-year Treasury yield rebounds amid sagging demand in the latest government bond auction.&lt;br&gt;- Former President Trump loses an early-win bid at a fraud trial with unconventional arguments.&lt;br&gt;- Bernie Sanders dismisses Dean Phillips' apology for dismissing his 'rigged' primary claims.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The tech section highlights advancements in aircraft carrier operations, AI phones, app store deals, IPO preparations, virtual machines, and rocket launch contracts. In the business section, there are updates on credit card offers, Amazon orders, Black Friday mattress deals, Meta's shopping integration, and the need for adjustments in the pharma commercial model. The AI section covers the AI phone's features, Twitter CEO's comments on AI and sex, and the impact of Cruise Robotaxis ceasing operations. Overall, the report provides insights into various tech, business, and AI-related topics, showcasing advancements, challenges, and market trends.</summary></entry></feed>