<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-11T16:01:27Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 11 Aug 2023 16:01:27</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-11T16:01:27Z</published><updated>2023-08-11T16:01:27Z</updated><id>edb5bc8a-744b-4182-93bc-b45e1af026ac</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from Stanford and Google have created an AI village with 25 bots that interact and engage in activities.&lt;br&gt;- Browsers do not prioritize the HTTP status code of web pages.&lt;br&gt;- A new Tetris game features blocks that are ARM instructions executed in the browser.&lt;br&gt;- VR in the workplace can lead to various health issues.&lt;br&gt;- Setting JavaScript framework standards and discussing the flaws of the React-set standard.&lt;br&gt;- Sensor Watch offers a board swap for the classic Casio F-91W wristwatch.&lt;br&gt;- Waymo and Cruise have received permits to operate robotaxis for money in SF, LA, and Silicon Valley.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Country Garden plans to pay its chairperson $28 million in dividends, attracting attention from bondholders due to her $5.3 billion fortune.&lt;br&gt;- X (formerly Twitter) has reduced requirements for its ad revenue sharing program.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's X Ads Revenue Sharing payments have been distributed.&lt;br&gt;- A Canadian woman received over 50 packages of women's shoes she never ordered and was asked to pay collect-on-delivery fees.&lt;br&gt;- Proposed Cybercrime Treaty's international cooperation provisions may have negative implications.&lt;br&gt;- Waymo and Cruise have obtained permits for full-day robotaxi operations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- The AI village created by researchers from Stanford and Google consists of 25 bots that engage in various activities.&lt;br&gt;- X (formerly Twitter) has made changes to its ad revenue sharing program.&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk's X Ads Revenue Sharing payments have been delivered.&lt;br&gt;- Robotaxis have received approval to operate 24/7 in California.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- An interactive story focused on self-exploration.&lt;br&gt;- Adults appreciate Van Gogh's art due to their infancy experiences.&lt;br&gt;- Free live stream of the Japan vs. Sweden Women's World Cup match.&lt;br&gt;- Websites and APIs on Render are currently unavailable due to Cloudflare network errors.&lt;br&gt;- Olivia Rodrigo has released a new song and a new Instagram feature.&lt;br&gt;- The Samsung Galaxy Flip 5 has made important design tweaks.&lt;br&gt;- The gig economy's impact on Covid-19.&lt;br&gt;- Comparing virtual vs in-person immersive leadership training.&lt;br&gt;- Arizona's Michael Wiley is considered the most underrated player in the Pac-12.&lt;br&gt;- Tips on earning, using, and maximizing United Miles.&lt;br&gt;- Solar flares have disrupted radio signals across the US.&lt;br&gt;- The potential implications of the proposed Cybercrime Treaty's international cooperation provisions.&lt;br&gt;- The Wordle game hints, clues, and answers for a specific date.&lt;br&gt;- Travel credit cards with benefits worth more than the annual fee.&lt;br&gt;- The drawbacks of building communities on Slack.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The development of AI villages showcases advancements in artificial intelligence and its potential applications.&lt;br&gt;- Changes in ad revenue sharing programs indicate evolving strategies in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of the gig economy on the post-pandemic recovery.&lt;br&gt;- The potential risks and benefits of virtual and in-person leadership training.&lt;br&gt;- The influence of childhood experiences on adult appreciation of art.&lt;br&gt;- The challenges and opportunities in the cybersecurity landscape.&lt;br&gt;- The disruption caused by solar flares on communication systems.&lt;br&gt;- The importance of user experience and design in technology products.&lt;br&gt;- The implications of international cooperation provisions in cybercrime treaties.&lt;br&gt;- The unexpected consequences of online shopping and delivery systems.&lt;br&gt;- The value and limitations of travel credit cards.&lt;br&gt;- The evolving landscape of transportation with the introduction of robotaxis.</summary></entry></feed>