<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-12T08:03:50Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 12 Dec 2023 08:03:50</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-12T08:03:50Z</published><updated>2023-12-12T08:03:50Z</updated><id>63c1d8ca-8a89-4934-94b0-1c9598a7da3b</id><summary type="html">In the world news, there have been several significant events and developments. The Android app that allowed users to send blue-bubble texts to iPhone users is back after being shut down by Apple, although there is a catch. Many major US companies, including Hasbro and Amazon, have been slashing staff this year. In a heated exchange, Katie Porter, a House Democrat, told a fellow Democrat to "go be a Republican" after the latter complained about Democratic amendments to a Trump-era immigration bill. A FISA "reform" bill is being proposed, which would expand the entities responsible for surveilling users. Ford has announced a cut in weekly production of the F-150 Lightning due to slowing demand. Google is bidding farewell to Google Play Movies &amp; TV. Helicity Space has raised $5 million to unlock fusion propulsion and enable fast travel in deep space. There is a discussion about STEM-themed gift or activity ideas for kids that go beyond books. A new study suggests that tonsillectomy can help improve the behavior of children who snore. Tragically, a married couple was killed in a plane crash in Oklahoma and will be deeply missed. George Santos is negotiating a plea deal with prosecutors following guilty pleas from two of his associates. The cofounder of Reddit claims that his Cybertruck is the first vehicle that feels comfortable to drive for tall people. Lawyers have criticized changes to the terms of service by 23andMe, calling them "cynical" and "self-serving." Asteroid mining startup AstroForge has faced setbacks and successes on its demonstration mission. Interestingly, department stores themselves have become the hottest Christmas items this year. CodiumAI's PR-Agent is in a battle with GitHub Copilot, both being Pull Request AI Assistants. Meta AI has introduced Relightable Gaussian Codec Avatars, an artificial intelligence method to build high-fidelity relightable head avatars. There is a discussion on enhancing machine learning reliability through atypicality. Puerto Rican boxing phenom Xander Zayas has been making waves in and out of the ring. The COP28 agreement does not include a fossil fuel phaseout, despite calls from the oil-rich host region. Apple has released an urgent update, iOS 17.2, for all iPhone users. ProPublica's investigation of Coast Guard detentions at sea has yielded five key takeaways. Wiley's transition year is unfolding amid strategic shifts, as discussed in an earnings call. Jeff Bezos is leaving behind a real estate empire in Seattle worth up to $190 million as he owns lavish properties across the US. Vintage photos showcase holiday decorations over the past century. NATO militaries are looking to assist Ukraine in building a navy, as it has been challenging Russia's Black Sea Fleet without one. Additionally, scientists have discovered a phenomenon called 'Steve,' which may be mistaken for aurora.</summary></entry></feed>