<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-18T20:03:00Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 18 Sep 2023 20:03:00</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-18T20:03:00Z</published><updated>2023-09-18T20:03:00Z</updated><id>631a8039-99b5-47ba-8dee-5fb9b474de9d</id><summary type="html">Effects and Safety of Vagus Nerve Stimulation on Upper Limb Function - Nature.com (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article discusses the effects and safety of vagus nerve stimulation on upper limb function.&lt;br&gt;- Vagus nerve stimulation has shown promising results in improving upper limb function in various conditions.&lt;br&gt;- The article highlights the potential benefits and risks associated with this treatment approach.&lt;br&gt;- Further research is needed to fully understand the mechanisms and optimize the use of vagus nerve stimulation in improving upper limb function.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zelenskyy said recent drone strikes on Russian soil are a message that its airspace is 'not as well protected' as it thinks (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Ukrainian President Zelenskyy commented on recent drone strikes on Russian soil, suggesting that it sends a message about the vulnerability of Russian airspace.&lt;br&gt;- The statement implies that Russia's air defense systems may not be as effective as they believe.&lt;br&gt;- This incident highlights the evolving nature of warfare and the increasing role of drones in modern conflicts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An amateur Scottish soccer club accuses Elon Musk's SpaceX of stealing its logo (Business)&lt;br&gt;- An amateur Scottish soccer club claims that Elon Musk's SpaceX has copied its logo.&lt;br&gt;- However, the club has stated that it does not plan to sue and would prefer if Musk buys the team instead.&lt;br&gt;- This case raises questions about intellectual property rights and the influence of high-profile individuals on smaller organizations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk criticizes short-sellers, while top investors bet against Tesla (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk has publicly criticized short-sellers, referring to them as bloodsuckers.&lt;br&gt;- However, prominent investors like Bill Gates and Michael Burry have placed bets against Tesla's success.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the ongoing debate and differing opinions regarding Tesla's future prospects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Savings Account and CD Rates Today | Savings Rates vs CD Rates (Business)&lt;br&gt;- This article compares the current savings account and certificate of deposit (CD) rates.&lt;br&gt;- It provides insights into the differences between these two types of accounts and their respective interest rates.&lt;br&gt;- The information can help individuals make informed decisions about where to invest their money.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Harry Potter' audiobook narrator Stephen Fry warns about AI-generated deepfake videos (AI)&lt;br&gt;- Stephen Fry, the narrator of the 'Harry Potter' audiobooks, claims that AI was used to steal his voice.&lt;br&gt;- He also warns about the potential for convincing deepfake videos of celebrities in the future.&lt;br&gt;- This raises concerns about the misuse of AI technology and the need for safeguards against deepfake manipulation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;US military seeks public help in finding missing F-35 fighter jet (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- The US military has asked the public for assistance in locating a missing F-35 fighter jet.&lt;br&gt;- The pilot had to eject while training over South Carolina, and the aircraft's whereabouts are currently unknown.&lt;br&gt;- This incident highlights the challenges and risks associated with military operations and the importance of advanced tracking systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Cook confirms Apple's Vision Pro release and shares his entertainment experience (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Apple CEO Tim Cook confirms that the Vision Pro headset is on track for an early 2024 release.&lt;br&gt;- He also mentions watching the entire third season of 'Ted Lasso' on the headset.&lt;br&gt;- This update provides insights into Apple's future plans and the potential impact of its augmented reality technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Softbank plans to invest in OpenAI, following CEO's endorsement of ChatGPT (Business, AI)&lt;br&gt;- Softbank is reportedly planning to invest in OpenAI, a leading artificial intelligence company.&lt;br&gt;- This comes after Softbank CEO Masayoshi Son expressed his daily use of OpenAI's ChatGPT.&lt;br&gt;- The investment highlights the growing interest and potential of AI technologies in various industries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leading economist warns of an AI-driven cataclysm (AI)&lt;br&gt;- A prominent economist warns that society is heading towards an AI-driven cataclysm.&lt;br&gt;- The article emphasizes the urgency to address the potential risks and consequences of AI advancements.&lt;br&gt;- This highlights the ongoing debate surrounding the ethical and societal implications of AI technologies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mortgage Interest Rates Today, September 18, 2023 | Rates Stable so far This Month (Business)&lt;br&gt;- This article provides an update on current mortgage interest rates as of September 18, 2023.&lt;br&gt;- It highlights the stability of rates throughout the month.&lt;br&gt;- The information can be useful for individuals considering mortgage options.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;US homebuyers await Fed's interest rate cuts (Business)&lt;br&gt;- US homebuyers are eagerly anticipating the Federal Reserve's decision to start cutting interest rates.&lt;br&gt;- The article presents insights from nine experts on when they believe the rate cuts will occur.&lt;br&gt;- This information can help individuals plan their homebuying strategies accordingly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nominations open for Rising Stars of Real Estate 2023 list (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Nominations are being sought for the Rising Stars of Real Estate 2023 list.&lt;br&gt;- The article provides instructions on how to apply for consideration.&lt;br&gt;- This opportunity highlights the recognition of young professionals in the real estate industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top economist warns of commercial real estate challenges (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Renowned economist Mohamed El-Erian warns of potential pain in the commercial real estate sector.&lt;br&gt;- He highlights the looming challenge of massive refinancing.&lt;br&gt;- This insight raises concerns about the stability and future prospects of the commercial real estate market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to cast Meta (Oculus) Quest devices to your TV, computer, or phone (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article provides a guide on how to cast Meta (Oculus) Quest devices to various screens.&lt;br&gt;- It offers step-by-step instructions for casting to TVs, computers, and phones.&lt;br&gt;- The information can be helpful for individuals looking to share their VR experiences with others.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unix shells are no longer viable access control mechanisms (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- The article discusses the diminishing viability of Unix shells as access control mechanisms.&lt;br&gt;- It highlights the need for more advanced and secure access control solutions.&lt;br&gt;- This insight reflects the evolving nature of cybersecurity and the importance of staying updated with modern technologies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bard provides a humorous critique of a landing page (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- The author shares their experience of asking Bard to provide a humorous critique of their landing page.&lt;br&gt;- The critique was entertaining and offered valuable insights for improvement.&lt;br&gt;- This anecdote highlights the importance of seeking feedback and continuously refining digital marketing strategies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creating a Language Server in Golang for Lama2 (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article explains the process of crafting a Language Server in Golang for Lama2, a programming language.&lt;br&gt;- It provides insights into the development of language servers and their role in enhancing programming experiences.&lt;br&gt;- This technical guide can be valuable for developers interested in creating their own language servers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 10 best features of Apple iOS 17 (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article highlights the top 10 features of Apple iOS 17 that users should take advantage of.&lt;br&gt;- It provides a brief overview of each feature and its benefits.&lt;br&gt;- The information can help iOS users maximize their experience with the latest software update.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wiz Khalifa launches a brand for growing mushrooms (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Wiz Khalifa, a popular musician, has launched a brand for growing mushrooms.&lt;br&gt;- However, it is clarified that the brand focuses on edible mushrooms, not psychedelic ones.&lt;br&gt;- This business venture reflects the growing interest in sustainable and alternative food sources.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mississippi courts criticized for lack of transparency in providing lawyers for poor clients (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Mississippi courts are facing criticism for their lack of transparency in providing lawyers for poor clients.&lt;br&gt;- The article highlights the importance of ensuring access to legal representation for all individuals, regardless of their financial status.&lt;br&gt;- This issue raises concerns about the fairness and effectiveness of the legal system in Mississippi.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cylindrical orifice testing in laminar flow with the orifice diameter - Nature.com (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- This article discusses cylindrical orifice testing in laminar flow, specifically focusing on the orifice diameter.&lt;br&gt;- It provides insights into the experimental setup and the impact of orifice diameter on flow characteristics.&lt;br&gt;- This research contributes to the understanding of fluid dynamics and engineering applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Macquarie Group reduces position in Gates Industrial Corp (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Macquarie Group has decreased its position in Gates Industrial Corp, a manufacturing company.&lt;br&gt;- The article highlights this investment decision and its potential implications.&lt;br&gt;- This update reflects the dynamic nature of investment strategies and the importance of monitoring market trends.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Topgun-trained fighter pilot discusses career choices (Business)&lt;br&gt;- A Topgun-trained fighter pilot shares insights into their career choice and compares it to being an airline pilot.&lt;br&gt;- While acknowledging the potential for higher earnings as an airline pilot, they emphasize the fulfillment derived from being a military pilot.&lt;br&gt;- This personal perspective sheds light on the considerations and motivations behind career decisions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI personal assistants and their impact on personal and work lives (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This article explores the potential impact of AI personal assistants on personal and work lives.&lt;br&gt;- It discusses the benefits and challenges associated with these technologies.&lt;br&gt;- This analysis highlights the transformative potential of AI personal assistants in various aspects of daily life.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tourism in NYC expected to become more challenging (Business)&lt;br&gt;- The article predicts that being a tourist in New York City will become more difficult in the future.&lt;br&gt;- It highlights factors such as overcrowding and increased regulations that may impact the tourist experience.&lt;br&gt;- This insight raises awareness of the evolving dynamics of tourism and the need for adaptive strategies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Review of Mercedes' EQE SUV, a Tesla rival (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- The author provides a review of Mercedes' EQE SUV, which is positioned as a rival to Tesla.&lt;br&gt;- While praising many aspects of the vehicle, they express reservations about its controversial design.&lt;br&gt;- This review offers insights into the competitive landscape of electric vehicles and consumer preferences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump comments on high interest rates and inflation (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Donald Trump claims that high interest rates are hindering people's ability to take action.&lt;br&gt;- He vows to tackle inflation and reduce borrowing costs.&lt;br&gt;- This statement reflects the ongoing debate surrounding monetary policies and their impact on the economy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;China Evergrande's volatile stock market performance (Business)&lt;br&gt;- China Evergrande, a real estate company, has experienced significant volatility in the stock market since trading resumed.&lt;br&gt;- The article highlights the fluctuations and uncertainties surrounding the company's financial situation.&lt;br&gt;- This development raises concerns about the stability of the Chinese real estate market and its potential ripple effects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wayve introduces LINGO-1, an AI model for commenting on driving scenes (AI)&lt;br&gt;- Wayve, an AI company, has introduced LINGO-1, a new AI model that can comment on driving scenes and respond to questions.&lt;br&gt;- This innovation showcases the advancements in natural language processing and computer vision technologies.&lt;br&gt;- The article emphasizes the potential applications of AI models in the automotive industry.</summary></entry></feed>