<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-01T08:03:51Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:03:51</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-01T08:03:51Z</published><updated>2023-12-01T08:03:51Z</updated><id>55dbdf21-f70b-45b1-a14e-fe11e16db0ff</id><summary type="html">In the world, Saudi Arabia is testing its new warships after years of building up its navy. Democrats have little praise for Henry Kissinger following his death, criticizing his actions. Scientists have confirmed that orcas killed a great white shark in Australia, leaving the sharks with one less place to hide. SpaceX rockets are causing concern among astronomers as they burn bright red holes in Earth's atmosphere. A top tech YouTuber claims that Tesla's Cybertruck is not living up to Elon Musk's promises. A 24-year-old man shares his experience with "softmaxxing," calling it a toxic scam. Broadcom plans to cut almost 1,300 VMware jobs in California after a takeover. A pen-and-paper game that is relatively unknown in the US and Europe is gaining attention. The United Nations summit in Dubai focuses on an oil executive, the climate crisis, and reparations. The CEO of defense startup Epirus is leaving to take a new job at a public company. Free events in December 2023 aim to educate people about the cloud. Bottlenose dolphins have been found to use dimples to locate food. Android devices are receiving new features before Christmas. Rokugan returns with a new Legend of the Five Rings art book. Generative AI strikes a chord with the Boomy/ADA deal, signaling a new era for music. The Senate committee authorizes subpoenas as part of a Supreme Court ethics probe. John Wiley &amp; Sons Inc releases press releases on the NYSE. A bill prohibiting foreign funding in state and local referenda is discussed. Meta's AI lab celebrates its 10th anniversary with new projects and a demo. A career coach highlights the need for constant stimulation among Millennials and Gen Z, while stability is desired by Millennials. Reddit cofounder Alexis Ohanian is among the first to get a Cybertruck. The Tesla Cybertruck will cost $20,000 more than initially promised, with a high-end option priced at $99,990. Tips for hiring and managing out-of-state and remote workers are shared. A new report suggests that the IDF's elite intelligence unit detected signs of a potential terror attack by Hamas. Tesla releases the official specifications of the Cybertruck. Henry Kissinger discusses AI, Israel, and the future of democracy before his death. George Santos faces a vote to expel him from Congress, which some consider to be bullying. Ukraine's air force shares a thrilling video of a MiG-29 flying at a shockingly low altitude. A GOP senator recounts choking on "woke policies" during a Senate lunch, where Rand Paul saved her life using the Heimlich maneuver.</summary></entry></feed>