<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-11T20:02:10Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 11 Sep 2023 20:02:10</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-11T20:02:10Z</published><updated>2023-09-11T20:02:10Z</updated><id>0d49a721-d392-4600-97ad-f83fa4e61e70</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Wiley's new advanced zyLabs help computer programming in higher education&lt;br&gt;- Meta is building an AI model as powerful as GPT-4&lt;br&gt;- Open Cosmos, a UK satellite startup focused on sustainability, raises $50M&lt;br&gt;- Meet Verba: An open-source tool to build your own RAG retrieval augmented generation pipeline and utilize LLMs for internal-based outputs&lt;br&gt;- AI, ML, Data Engineering News Roundup: Stable Chat, Vertex AI, ChatGPT, and Code Llama&lt;br&gt;- AI chatbots were tasked to run a tech company. They built software in under seven minutes for less than $1.&lt;br&gt;- Google heads to court in a landmark trial that puts its search business in the crosshairs. Here's what's at stake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- A boss who uses a 'coffee cup test' to filter candidates in job interviews is being accused by some social media users of playing 'mind games'&lt;br&gt;- The Fed may have beaten back inflation and skirted a recession for now, Goldman Sachs says&lt;br&gt;- The S&amp;P 500 could crash nearly 50% as a brutal recession takes hold, veteran technical analyst warns&lt;br&gt;- From body sensors to water coolers, here's how companies are watching how full their offices are&lt;br&gt;- A 'ferry house' made famous by Charles Dickens was converted into a 4-bedroom home with a private mooring. Now it's on the market for $2.8 million.&lt;br&gt;- A passenger on budget airline Ryanair was awarded over $30,000 in damages after she fell on 'narrow and steep' plane steps and broke her leg in 2 places&lt;br&gt;- From intern to strategic business partner: How to effectively promote your technology investment&lt;br&gt;- 3 Lessons Ray Dalio, Founder of the World's Largest Hedge Fund, Can Teach Us About Global Venture and Fintech Investing&lt;br&gt;- As Google turns 25, it faces the biggest tech antitrust trial of a generation&lt;br&gt;- Check out Toyota's new $170,000 SUV taking on Bentley and Rolls-Royce&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Meta is building an AI model as powerful as GPT-4&lt;br&gt;- AI, ML, Data Engineering News Roundup: Stable Chat, Vertex AI, ChatGPT, and Code Llama&lt;br&gt;- AI chatbots were tasked to run a tech company. They built software in under seven minutes for less than $1.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Wiley's new advanced zyLabs can greatly enhance computer programming education in higher education institutions.&lt;br&gt;- The use of mind games in job interviews, such as the 'coffee cup test', is being criticized by some on social media.&lt;br&gt;- Goldman Sachs believes that the Fed has successfully managed to control inflation and avoid a recession, at least for now.&lt;br&gt;- A veteran technical analyst warns of a potential 50% crash in the S&amp;P 500 due to an impending brutal recession.&lt;br&gt;- Companies are utilizing various technologies, such as body sensors and water coolers, to monitor the occupancy of their offices.&lt;br&gt;- The real estate market includes unique properties like the converted 'ferry house' from Charles Dickens' fame, now listed for $2.8 million.&lt;br&gt;- Ryanair was ordered to pay significant damages to a passenger who suffered injuries due to unsafe plane steps.&lt;br&gt;- Ray Dalio, the founder of the world's largest hedge fund, offers valuable lessons on global venture and fintech investing.&lt;br&gt;- Google faces a significant antitrust trial as it celebrates its 25th anniversary.&lt;br&gt;- AI continues to advance, with Meta working on a powerful AI model and AI chatbots demonstrating their ability to build software quickly and affordably.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The report covers various topics including tech, business, and AI. It highlights the advancements in computer programming education, the use of mind games in job interviews, the state of the economy, real estate market trends, and the impact of AI in various industries. Overall, the report emphasizes the importance of technological advancements and their influence on different sectors.</summary></entry></feed>