<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-12T04:01:30Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 12 Aug 2023 04:01:30</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-12T04:01:30Z</published><updated>2023-08-12T04:01:30Z</updated><id>03f246f7-701b-405f-9c10-9532c5f66df6</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Claude Instant 1.2 shows notable gains in math, coding, reasoning, and safety, says Anthropic&lt;br&gt;- Cybertruck fans are nitpicking Elon Musk's final design as Tesla gets ready to deliver the long-awaited truck&lt;br&gt;- Israeli startups are moving jobs and money out of the country. Here’s why&lt;br&gt;- I Fixed a 3-year-old bug in Windows Calculator and Microsoft Couldn't Care Less!&lt;br&gt;- ByteDance again looks to TikTok to promote its other social app, Lemon8&lt;br&gt;- How we scaled our App Store performance by approximately 200% in 1 year&lt;br&gt;- AI Is Now Better Than Humans at Solving Those Annoying "Prove You're a Human" Tests&lt;br&gt;- EA UFC 5: Release Info and 5 Smart Updates The New Game Needs&lt;br&gt;- ‘Overwatch 2’ Steam Purchases Aren’t Showing Up For Some Players, Others Can Use Illari Without Unlocking Her&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- Claude Instant 1.2 is a technology that has shown significant improvements in various areas such as math, coding, reasoning, and safety.&lt;br&gt;- The final design of the Cybertruck by Tesla has received criticism from fans who are nitpicking the details.&lt;br&gt;- Israeli startups are relocating jobs and funds out of the country due to certain reasons.&lt;br&gt;- A bug in Windows Calculator was fixed by an individual, but Microsoft did not show much interest in addressing it.&lt;br&gt;- ByteDance is leveraging TikTok to promote its other social app, Lemon8.&lt;br&gt;- A company shares its strategies on scaling App Store performance by 200% in one year.&lt;br&gt;- AI has surpassed humans in solving "Prove You're a Human" tests.&lt;br&gt;- The release of EA UFC 5 is anticipated, along with updates that are expected to enhance the game.&lt;br&gt;- Some players are experiencing issues with purchasing 'Overwatch 2' on Steam, while others can access a character without unlocking her.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Technology advancements like Claude Instant 1.2 and AI solving human tests highlight the progress made in the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- The criticism faced by Tesla's Cybertruck design and Microsoft's lack of response to a bug reveal the importance of user feedback and prompt bug fixes.&lt;br&gt;- The relocation of Israeli startups indicates the impact of various factors on the business environment.&lt;br&gt;- Leveraging popular platforms like TikTok can be an effective marketing strategy for promoting other apps.&lt;br&gt;- Strategies for scaling App Store performance can provide valuable insights for other developers.&lt;br&gt;- The challenges faced in game development, such as addressing purchase issues and ensuring a smooth gaming experience, require continuous improvement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Joint bank accounts vs. individual bank accounts: Which is better for you?&lt;br&gt;- Only one car model sold for under $20,000 in July — but experts say vehicle prices are stabilizing&lt;br&gt;- A 30-something who had $100,000 of student loan debt shares the steps she took to pay it off in 6 years&lt;br&gt;- Your neighbors might soon know when you order toilet paper, trash bags, and other items from Amazon&lt;br&gt;- The US government will hand out up to $1.2 billion for companies to suck greenhouse gases out of the air&lt;br&gt;- Prosecutors convinced a judge not to let Trump have his phone while reviewing trial documents because he has a 'tendency' to 'hold onto material' he shouldn't have&lt;br&gt;- Republicans are already delegitimizing the DOJ's newly-appointed special counsel to investigate Hunter Biden&lt;br&gt;- Hunter Biden's plea deal is dead as the DOJ appoints a special counsel to oversee its investigation&lt;br&gt;- The US housing market hits a record value of $47 trillion as the inventory shortage fuels a price boom&lt;br&gt;- As a recent college grad, I applied to nearly 90 jobs, and I never heard back from a majority of them. I didn't think it would be this difficult.&lt;br&gt;- Kentucky's largest school district had to cancel class for two days so it could overhaul a 'disastrous' new bus system that left kids on buses until 10 p.m.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- The comparison between joint bank accounts and individual bank accounts is discussed to determine which option is better.&lt;br&gt;- Vehicle prices are stabilizing, although there is limited availability of car models under $20,000.&lt;br&gt;- A person shares their journey of paying off $100,000 in student loan debt within six years.&lt;br&gt;- Amazon's potential feature of notifying neighbors about deliveries raises privacy concerns.&lt;br&gt;- The US government plans to allocate a significant amount of money for companies to develop technologies to remove greenhouse gases from the air.&lt;br&gt;- Legal proceedings involving Trump and Hunter Biden are being closely monitored, with concerns about potential misconduct and delegitimization.&lt;br&gt;- The US housing market has reached a record value due to an inventory shortage, leading to a price boom.&lt;br&gt;- Job hunting challenges are highlighted by a recent college graduate who faced a lack of response from the majority of job applications.&lt;br&gt;- A school district had to make changes to a problematic bus system that caused significant inconvenience for students.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The choice between joint and individual bank accounts depends on individual preferences and financial goals.&lt;br&gt;- The stabilization of vehicle prices and the housing market's record value reflect the dynamics of the economy.&lt;br&gt;- The burden of student loan debt and the challenges of job hunting after graduation are common concerns for individuals.&lt;br&gt;- The allocation of funds for greenhouse gas removal technologies demonstrates the government's commitment to addressing environmental issues.&lt;br&gt;- Legal proceedings involving high-profile individuals can raise questions about transparency and fairness.&lt;br&gt;- The impact of transportation systems on students' well-being and education highlights the importance of efficient infrastructure.</summary></entry></feed>