<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2024-01-28T15:09:20Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 28 Jan 2024 15:09:20</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-28T15:09:20Z</published><updated>2024-01-28T15:09:20Z</updated><id>d05e35f5-f219-4837-b3cc-671b718f8413</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xiayanzheng/xiayanzheng.github.io/main/voice/d05e35f5-f219-4837-b3cc-671b718f8413.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        
    &lt;script type="text/javascript"&gt;
        (function(c,l,a,r,i,t,y){
            c[a]=c[a]||function(){(c[a].q=c[a].q||[]).push(arguments)};
            t=l.createElement(r);t.async=1;t.src="https://www.clarity.ms/tag/"+i;
            y=l.getElementsByTagName(r)[0];y.parentNode.insertBefore(t,y);
        })(window, document, "clarity", "script", "kssf4cm8i9");
    &lt;/script&gt;
    
        In the world of technology, a new AI library called LangGraph has been introduced. This library allows for the creation of stateful, multi-actor applications using LLMs on top of LangChain. This advancement opens up possibilities for more complex and interactive AI applications. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of marine life, the decline of hammerhead sharks is being explored through the perspective of local divers. These divers are witnessing firsthand the dwindling numbers of these majestic creatures and are shedding light on the factors contributing to their decline. This insight is crucial for conservation efforts and understanding the impact of human activities on marine ecosystems. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking a nostalgic turn, there is a reflection on the history of Unix desktops and the lessons we can learn from them. Unix desktops have played a significant role in shaping the modern computing landscape, and understanding their evolution can provide valuable insights for future developments. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of data analysis, a Twitter user named @blackleitus shares that the data used in their visuals comes from SEC filings and company reports. They emphasize that the visuals are manually crafted in-house, highlighting the importance of accurate and reliable data sources in creating informative visual representations. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shifting gears back to AI, Adept AI has introduced a new multimodal model called Fuyu-Heavy. This model is specifically designed for digital agents, enabling them to process and understand various modes of communication. This advancement in AI technology enhances the capabilities of digital agents, making them more versatile and effective in their interactions. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, media literacy classes are gaining popularity, but some conservatives perceive a 'woke' agenda behind them. These classes aim to equip individuals with critical thinking skills and the ability to analyze media content effectively. However, some conservatives view this as an attempt to promote a particular ideological perspective, leading to debates and discussions about the purpose and content of media literacy education.
    </summary></entry></feed>