<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-03T20:02:01Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 03 Oct 2023 20:02:01</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-03T20:02:01Z</published><updated>2023-10-03T20:02:01Z</updated><id>e0aed7fd-a052-4b11-a0c6-17c737ae8eda</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Stability.AI's Stable LM 3B is a capable open-source LLM for mobile devices.&lt;br&gt;- Stable LM 3B is an open-source language model designed for mobile devices.&lt;br&gt;- It provides stable and reliable performance for various applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Beyond Rattling: Tetrahedrites as Incipient Ionic Conductors ... - John Wiley &amp; Sons.&lt;br&gt;- Tetrahedrites have been identified as potential ionic conductors.&lt;br&gt;- This discovery could have significant implications for various industries, including energy storage and electronics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. FTX cofounder Gary Wang is set to testify against his childhood friend Sam Bankman-Fried. Here's what we know.&lt;br&gt;- Gary Wang, co-founder of FTX, will testify against his childhood friend Sam Bankman-Fried.&lt;br&gt;- The details of the case are not provided, but it suggests a legal dispute between the two individuals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Hannagan Wins Chet Thomson Memorial Race at Antioch Speedway - Contra Costa News.&lt;br&gt;- Hannagan emerges as the winner of the Chet Thomson Memorial Race at Antioch Speedway.&lt;br&gt;- The event was held to honor the memory of Chet Thomson, and Hannagan's victory is highlighted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Former Abercrombie &amp; Fitch boss accused of exploiting men for sex.&lt;br&gt;- The former CEO of Abercrombie &amp; Fitch is facing accusations of exploiting men for sexual purposes.&lt;br&gt;- The details of the allegations are not provided, but it raises concerns about misconduct in the workplace.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. FTX told architects that its headquarters should look like Sam Bankman-Fried's hair.&lt;br&gt;- FTX, a company co-founded by Sam Bankman-Fried, instructed architects to design its headquarters to resemble Bankman-Fried's hair.&lt;br&gt;- This unusual request suggests a unique and personalized approach to the company's branding.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. An elite Russian unit's morale is at 'critical levels' after being sent to stop Ukraine's counteroffensive, analysts say.&lt;br&gt;- Analysts report that an elite Russian unit sent to stop Ukraine's counteroffensive is experiencing critical levels of morale.&lt;br&gt;- The situation highlights the challenges and potential consequences of military operations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Elon Musk was mocked by Ukraine's parliament after he posted a meme taunting Zelenskyy's calls for aid.&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine's parliament mocked Elon Musk after he shared a meme mocking President Zelenskyy's requests for aid.&lt;br&gt;- This incident reflects the intersection of politics and social media, with public figures facing criticism for their online actions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Beyond the Fitzpatrick Scale: This AI Paper From Sony Introduces a Multidimensional Approach to Assess Skin Color Bias in Computer Vision.&lt;br&gt;- Sony has published an AI paper that proposes a multidimensional approach to assess skin color bias in computer vision.&lt;br&gt;- The research aims to address the limitations of existing methods and promote fairness and accuracy in AI systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section highlights advancements in language models, potential applications of tetrahedrites, and a legal dispute between co-founders.&lt;br&gt;- The business section covers a race victory, allegations against a former CEO, and a unique architectural request.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section discusses the morale of a Russian unit, Elon Musk's social media controversy, and Sony's research on skin color bias.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report showcases a range of topics in the tech, business, and AI sectors, highlighting key developments and controversies.</summary></entry></feed>