<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-03T08:03:40Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 03 Dec 2023 08:03:40</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-03T08:03:40Z</published><updated>2023-12-03T08:03:40Z</updated><id>bdfeef94-3a61-4187-abdd-72fb7693a3b3</id><summary type="html">In recent news, two filmmakers made an unexpected discovery while operating an underwater drone in Lake Huron. They stumbled upon a 128-year-old shipwreck at the bottom of the lake, adding to the rich history of the area. Meanwhile, a concerning report reveals that some air traffic controllers, burdened by grueling work schedules, have resorted to alcohol and drugs as a means of coping instead of seeking professional help. This highlights the need for better support systems in high-stress professions. On a lighter note, fans of the popular video game series 'Halo' can rejoice as the release date and teaser trailer for the second season have been announced. Moving on to scientific advancements, a paper from Johns Hopkins University emphasizes the role of data science in accelerating probabilistic catalog matching for space discoveries across different time periods and telescopes. Additionally, an AI paper introduces 'ImMesh,' a technology that enables real-time mapping of large-scale scenes without the need for GPU acceleration, using advanced LiDAR-based localization and meshing techniques. In the realm of astronomy, a rare meteor shower is expected to illuminate the night skies tonight in a spectacular outburst, captivating stargazers around the world. However, it is important to remain cautious of misinformation, as a viral photo falsely claims to depict the man who stabbed Derek Chauvin, the former police officer involved in the George Floyd case. Shifting gears, Broadway enthusiasts can look forward to Rob Rokicki's release of the final cut song from 'The Lightning,' adding to the excitement surrounding the musical. In archaeology news, new claims of a 27,000-year-old Indonesian pyramid have sparked intrigue and further exploration into the ancient civilization. On the sports front, the Sports Illustrated Union responds to accusations of AI-generated articles by fake writers, raising concerns about the authenticity and credibility of sports journalism. Legal matters also come into play, as Bragar Eagel &amp; Squire, P.C. announces an investigation into John Wiley &amp; Sons Inc. Finally, after living in captivity at a Florida theme park since 1956, two manatees named Romeo and Juliet will finally be freed due to pressure from activists advocating for their release.</summary></entry></feed>