<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-11-19T08:03:58Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 19 Nov 2023 08:03:58</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-11-19T08:03:58Z</published><updated>2023-11-19T08:03:58Z</updated><id>9bcd514e-f644-487c-a9eb-0f6205bab509</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Ousted OpenAI CEO Sam Altman plans new AI venture with former president Greg Brockman&lt;br&gt;- The biggest challenges facing OpenAI’s Mira Murati, the newly minted most powerful woman in tech&lt;br&gt;- Altman was raising billions from Middle East sovereign funds for AI chip startup&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI fires CEO Sam Altman, Airbnb acquires GamePlanner.AI, and Epic battles Google over antitrust&lt;br&gt;- Here’s your quick primer on the latest with Sam Altman and ChatGPT-maker OpenAI&lt;br&gt;- Who is OpenAI chief scientist Ilya Sutskever, and what does he think about the future of AI and ChatGPT?&lt;br&gt;- Amazon cuts "hundreds" from its Alexa team to "maximize resources" on generative AI&lt;br&gt;- Palo Alto Networks Introduce the Cortex XSIAM 2.0 Platform: Featuring a Unique Bring-Your-Own-Machine-Learning (BYOML) Framework&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from Vanderbilt University and UC Davis Introduce PRANC: A Deep Learning Framework that is Memory-Efficient during both the Learning and Reconstruction Phases&lt;br&gt;- New Galaxy S24 Tech Solves The Worst Problem With Samsung Phones&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- How to Choose a Financial Advisor - When is a Financial Advisor Worth it for You?&lt;br&gt;- Tesorio (YC S15) Is Hiring a Senior Data Engineer in Latam&lt;br&gt;- 9 reasons you shouldn't check your investments more than once a month, according to financial advisors&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Ousted OpenAI CEO Sam Altman plans new AI venture with former president Greg Brockman&lt;br&gt;- The biggest challenges facing OpenAI’s Mira Murati, the newly minted most powerful woman in tech&lt;br&gt;- Altman was raising billions from Middle East sovereign funds for AI chip startup&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI fires CEO Sam Altman, Airbnb acquires GamePlanner.AI, and Epic battles Google over antitrust&lt;br&gt;- Here’s your quick primer on the latest with Sam Altman and ChatGPT-maker OpenAI&lt;br&gt;- Who is OpenAI chief scientist Ilya Sutskever, and what does he think about the future of AI and ChatGPT?&lt;br&gt;- Amazon cuts "hundreds" from its Alexa team to "maximize resources" on generative AI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Halftime: No. 17 Arizona football dominating Utah at half | National ... - KTBS&lt;br&gt;- 3 pedestrians hit by vehicles in Palos Heights, 1 dies - Southwest Regional Publishing&lt;br&gt;- Harvey man, woman charged in woman's murder in Worth - Southwest Regional Publishing&lt;br&gt;- Columbia administrators reportedly covertly changed the university's event policies just before suspending pro-Palestine student groups&lt;br&gt;- Ladies Bested By Wiley On Road, 69-35 - Centenary College Athletics&lt;br&gt;- Jenny Wiley Festival Car Show held | News | floydct.com - Floyd Chronicle &amp; Times&lt;br&gt;- Live coverage: No. 22 Utah trails No. 17 Arizona big in 2nd quarter - Yahoo News&lt;br&gt;- Alameda County D.A. Pamela Price delivers fiery rebuke to critics as she launches anti-recall campaign - Vallejo Times-Herald&lt;br&gt;- 'Workaholic' dad tragically told his eight-year-old son has died while on conference call - The Mirror&lt;br&gt;- Author's response - Thompson - Journal of Forensic Sciences - onlinelibrary.wiley.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The ousting of Sam Altman as CEO of OpenAI has caused controversy and speculation within the tech community.&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI is facing challenges in the AI industry, including competition, fundraising, and policy issues.&lt;br&gt;- Financial advisors provide guidance on choosing advisors and managing investments.&lt;br&gt;- Various AI developments and advancements are taking place, including new ventures, acquisitions, and research.&lt;br&gt;- News and events from different fields, such as sports, crime, education, and politics, are also covered in the content.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, the report highlights the ongoing developments and challenges in the tech, business, and AI sectors, as well as providing a glimpse into various news and events happening in different domains.</summary></entry></feed>