<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-03T08:03:38Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 03 Oct 2023 08:03:38</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-03T08:03:38Z</published><updated>2023-10-03T08:03:38Z</updated><id>eafc1b9f-91b1-4bd8-98c3-5b45fb5f5f4d</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Satya Nadella Confirms, Despite Distant Second Place, Bing is Still Profitable&lt;br&gt;- Tesla Autopilot arbitration win could set legal benchmark in auto industry&lt;br&gt;- Integrating Prometheus with SAP's Enterprise Software for Kubernetes Monitoring: A Step-by-Step Guide&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's Jaron Lanier says AI advancing without human dignity will 'undermine everything', including reality&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musk’s X Corp. faces trademark lawsuit from social media ad agency&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Taylor Swift and Beyoncé prove yet again why they're some of the world's best businesswomen&lt;br&gt;- Trump trial judge Arthur Engoron: Who is the quippy, Ivy league-educated judge deciding the fate of Trump's NY business empire?&lt;br&gt;- The US Air Force is buying a new missile as it makes plans to blast through enemy air defenses&lt;br&gt;- Taco Bell has the fastest drive-thru, and its latest tech could get customers their orders even faster&lt;br&gt;- Republicans still don’t know how to talk to young voters online&lt;br&gt;- Why The C-Suite Should Make Workforce Compliance And Risk Management A Priority&lt;br&gt;- 4 Ways Managed Service Providers Can Stabilize Labor Costs And Utilization In Healthcare&lt;br&gt;- Global Legal Weed Market Could Soar To $55 Billion In Four Years&lt;br&gt;- The cannabis industry still lacks diversity. Improving access is a joint effort&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft's Jaron Lanier says AI advancing without human dignity will 'undermine everything', including reality&lt;br&gt;- Cognitive scientists may have discovered a link between ‘Game of Thrones’ and the loneliness epidemic&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Others:&lt;br&gt;- ‘An Archeology of Silence’ Exhibit at De Young Museum is ... - Post News Group&lt;br&gt;- Watch the deposition tapes of Donald Trump, Don Jr., Eric Trump, Michael Cohen, and Allen Weisselberg in the NY civil fraud case&lt;br&gt;- U.S. avoids shutdown, but prospects for boosting science funding remain dim&lt;br&gt;- In 365 Days A ‘Ring Of Fire’ Solar Eclipse Will Visit Easter Island&lt;br&gt;- No, NASA’s Asteroid Visit This Week Won’t Make Us All Billionaires&lt;br&gt;- An orca pod has been harassing and killing porpoises for decades — but they don't eat them. Scientists still don't know why.&lt;br&gt;- First Blood Test for Dozens of Hereditary Cancers Approved by FDA&lt;br&gt;- Uncovered: Cover Art from Maverick Arts Studio 2019 - 2023 by Monte Michael Moore&lt;br&gt;- Pawly Door: The Intelligent Cat Door With Prey Detection by Pawly&lt;br&gt;- Faculty and Staff Notables | October 2023 - The Den - Mercer University&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Bing, despite being in second place, is still profitable, indicating its value in the market.&lt;br&gt;- Tesla's Autopilot arbitration win could have significant implications for the auto industry.&lt;br&gt;- The integration of Prometheus with SAP's Enterprise Software provides a step-by-step guide for Kubernetes monitoring.&lt;br&gt;- The lack of human dignity in AI advancements is a concern raised by Microsoft's Jaron Lanier.&lt;br&gt;- The cannabis industry's lack of diversity and the need for improved access are highlighted.&lt;br&gt;- The approval of the first blood test for hereditary cancers by the FDA is a significant development in healthcare.&lt;br&gt;- The potential growth of the global legal weed market to $55 billion in four years presents opportunities for the industry.&lt;br&gt;- The link between "Game of Thrones" and the loneliness epidemic, as discovered by cognitive scientists, is an interesting finding.&lt;br&gt;- The harassment and killing of porpoises by an orca pod without consumption raises questions for scientists.&lt;br&gt;- The intelligent cat door with prey detection by Pawly showcases advancements in pet technology.&lt;br&gt;- The October 2023 faculty and staff notables at Mercer University highlight notable achievements in academia.</summary></entry></feed>