<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-24T20:02:12Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 24 Oct 2023 20:02:12</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-24T20:02:12Z</published><updated>2023-10-24T20:02:12Z</updated><id>74a0544c-fff3-4100-ab64-e2cca2208772</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Midjourney has launched a new website and has a major update planned.&lt;br&gt;2. Automattic is acquiring Texts and focusing on the future of messaging.&lt;br&gt;3. Nvidia introduces Eureka, an AI agent powered by GPT-4 for training robots.&lt;br&gt;4. Incorporation of view sharing and KWIC filtering into GRASP-Pro.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The tech industry is constantly evolving with new updates, acquisitions, and advancements in AI technology. Companies like Midjourney, Automattic, and Nvidia are investing in the future of messaging, AI agents, and robot training. Incorporating view sharing and KWIC filtering into GRASP-Pro shows a focus on improving data analysis and research.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. 'Bond King' Bill Gross predicts a recession in the 4th quarter and shares his investment strategy.&lt;br&gt;2. Airline CEO who made controversial comments about women steps down after decades in the post.&lt;br&gt;3. Investors are repeating mistakes made before the 2008 crash, warns a top economist.&lt;br&gt;4. Sky requests government assistance to target pirate IPTV resellers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: The business sector is facing challenges such as economic predictions, leadership controversies, and potential financial mistakes. Bill Gross's recession prediction and investment strategy highlight the need for careful financial planning. The resignation of an airline CEO due to controversial comments emphasizes the importance of inclusive leadership. The warning from a top economist about repeating past mistakes serves as a reminder to learn from history. Sky's request for government assistance reflects the ongoing battle against piracy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. Nvidia introduces Eureka, an AI agent powered by GPT-4 for training robots.&lt;br&gt;2. Astrology 2.0 combines ancient wisdom with modern communication technology.&lt;br&gt;3. AI chatbots are creating targeted political ads.&lt;br&gt;4. The case for 3-D character creation using AI technology in game development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: AI continues to make advancements in various fields. Nvidia's Eureka AI agent focuses on training robots, showcasing the potential for AI in automation and robotics. Astrology 2.0 demonstrates the integration of ancient wisdom with modern technology. AI chatbots are being utilized for political advertising, highlighting the role of AI in influencing public opinion. The case for 3-D character creation using AI technology shows the potential for AI in enhancing game development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The report highlights various topics in the tech, business, and AI sectors. In tech, companies like Midjourney, Automattic, and Nvidia are making significant advancements. The business sector faces challenges such as economic predictions, leadership controversies, and potential financial mistakes. AI continues to evolve, with applications in robotics, astrology, political advertising, and game development. Overall, the insights gathered from these topics emphasize the importance of innovation, careful planning, inclusive leadership, and learning from past mistakes in order to succeed in the ever-changing landscape of technology and business.</summary></entry></feed>