<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-10-21T08:03:50Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 21 Oct 2023 08:03:50</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-10-21T08:03:50Z</published><updated>2023-10-21T08:03:50Z</updated><id>a4a61d09-155a-4b70-8718-5bcc316df2eb</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Photo released of 2 Americans - a mother and daughter - freed after being held hostage by Hamas for nearly 2 weeks&lt;br&gt;- Photos show the recently discovered wreck of a World War II-era submarine more than 80 years after a German sub sank it&lt;br&gt;- Chime vs Capital One 360: Which Is Better for Online Banking?&lt;br&gt;- Ally vs Capital One 360: Which Online Bank Accounts Are Better?&lt;br&gt;- Elon Musks Says He Unloaded a Tommy Gun Into a Cybertruck "Al Capone Style"&lt;br&gt;- Emerge (YC W21) is hiring a senior front end engineer (remote, small team)&lt;br&gt;- Pixel 8 Pro teardown exposes its temperature sensor and a sticky battery setup&lt;br&gt;- New York Bill Would Require a Background Check for 3D Printers, Like a Gun&lt;br&gt;- FCC Expands Audio Description Requirements to All Television ... - Wiley Rein&lt;br&gt;- Should You Think About Buying John Wiley &amp; Sons, Inc. (NYSE:WLY) Now? - Simply Wall St&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights: &lt;br&gt;- The tech section covers a range of topics including hostage release, World War II submarine discovery, online banking comparisons, Elon Musk's statement, job opportunities, smartphone teardown, 3D printer regulations, and stock market analysis.&lt;br&gt;- The release of hostages by Hamas and the discovery of a sunken submarine are significant events that highlight historical and security aspects.&lt;br&gt;- The comparison of online banking services and the discussion of a smartphone teardown provide insights into consumer choices and technological advancements.&lt;br&gt;- The proposed bill for background checks on 3D printers raises questions about the regulation of emerging technologies.&lt;br&gt;- The expansion of audio description requirements for television shows emphasizes the importance of accessibility in media.&lt;br&gt;- The stock market analysis and investment considerations provide insights into financial trends and potential opportunities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- UAW Says Talks With GM And Stellantis Progress While Criticizing Ford&lt;br&gt;- America First Credit Union review: High interest rates on CDs, and free savings and checking accounts&lt;br&gt;- Friday news dumps: all the news companies hoped you wouldn’t notice&lt;br&gt;- Facing customer backlash, Delta Air Lines CEO Ed Bastian unveils revised plan for SkyMiles changes&lt;br&gt;- Would you and your spouse make good business partners? Dwyane Wade was nervous about working with Gabrielle Union-Wade&lt;br&gt;- Charles Pillow Obituary - Wiley Funeral Home - Granbury - 2023 - Legacy.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The business section covers topics such as labor negotiations, financial services, news management, customer relations, and personal experiences in business partnerships.&lt;br&gt;- The updates on labor negotiations between UAW and automakers shed light on the state of the automotive industry and labor relations.&lt;br&gt;- The review of America First Credit Union provides insights into the offerings and benefits of the institution.&lt;br&gt;- The discussion of news dumps highlights media practices and the potential impact of hidden news stories.&lt;br&gt;- The revised plan for SkyMiles changes by Delta Air Lines reflects the importance of customer feedback and the need for adaptability in the business world.&lt;br&gt;- The personal experience of Dwyane Wade and Gabrielle Union-Wade raises questions about the dynamics of working with a spouse.&lt;br&gt;- The obituary of Charles Pillow showcases the human side of business and the impact individuals have on their communities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- How the creator of Alone in the Dark came back to games&lt;br&gt;- Jon Stewart's show on Apple TV+ is reportedly coming to an end amid disagreements around China and AI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The AI section focuses on the return of a game creator and the end of Jon Stewart's show on Apple TV+ due to disagreements related to China and AI.&lt;br&gt;- The return of the game creator highlights the evolving landscape of the gaming industry and the potential impact of AI on game development.&lt;br&gt;- The end of Jon Stewart's show raises questions about the influence of AI and China on media content and freedom of expression.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section covers a wide range of topics, highlighting advancements in online banking, smartphone technology, and emerging regulations.&lt;br&gt;- The business section provides insights into labor negotiations, customer relations, and personal experiences in business partnerships.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section explores the impact of AI on the gaming industry and media content, particularly in relation to China.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report showcases the diverse and interconnected nature of technology, business, and AI in today's world.</summary></entry></feed>