<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-10T10:15:31Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 10 Aug 2023 10:15:31</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-10T10:15:31Z</published><updated>2023-08-10T10:15:31Z</updated><id>6b9966ea-7965-44f0-a7cc-9abbed307c39</id><summary type="html">Vite Report on Thu, 10 Aug 2023 08:01:02&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Google opens eSignature beta for Google Docs and Google Drive&lt;br&gt;- China tech further severed from US fundings after Biden ban&lt;br&gt;- Krafton commits $150 million to India following BGMI trial approval&lt;br&gt;- Embarking on a Cloud Adventure: Unveiling the Magic of Cloud Computing&lt;br&gt;- InnovationRx: 70% Of U.S. Adults 'Concerned' About AI In Healthcare&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The introduction of Google's eSignature beta for Google Docs and Google Drive aims to streamline document signing processes.&lt;br&gt;- The Biden ban has resulted in further separation between China tech and US fundings, impacting the tech industry.&lt;br&gt;- Krafton's commitment of $150 million to India demonstrates the company's investment in the gaming market.&lt;br&gt;- Cloud computing continues to revolutionize the IT industry, offering scalability and flexibility to businesses.&lt;br&gt;- The concerns surrounding AI in healthcare highlight the need for ethical considerations and proper regulation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- 4 Best Banks and Credit Unions in California for August 2023&lt;br&gt;- Quorum Federal Credit Union Review 2023&lt;br&gt;- Digital Federal Credit Union Credit Builder Loan Review&lt;br&gt;- Seattle becomes first in U.S. to protect gig workers from sudden 'deactivation'&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The list of the best banks and credit unions in California provides options for individuals seeking financial services.&lt;br&gt;- The Quorum Federal Credit Union review offers insights into the institution's offerings and customer experiences.&lt;br&gt;- The Digital Federal Credit Union's Credit Builder Loan review highlights the benefits of their loan program.&lt;br&gt;- Seattle's initiative to protect gig workers from sudden 'deactivation' sets a precedent for worker rights in the gig economy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- Paul Graham on Conversations with Tyler&lt;br&gt;- 'What have I seen?': Joel Meyerowitz's life in photography - in pictures&lt;br&gt;- 'Humanity has fully decoded the human genome but cannot "understand" it: research findings&lt;br&gt;- Ai4 2023 Day Two Main Stage Recap&lt;br&gt;- 'Concerned' About AI In Healthcare&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Paul Graham's interview on Conversations with Tyler provides insights into the world of AI and technology.&lt;br&gt;- Joel Meyerowitz's photography showcases the power of visual storytelling and artistic expression.&lt;br&gt;- The research findings on the human genome highlight the complexity of understanding genetic information.&lt;br&gt;- The Ai4 2023 conference's main stage recap offers a glimpse into the latest advancements and discussions in AI.&lt;br&gt;- The concerns surrounding AI in healthcare emphasize the need for responsible and ethical implementation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech industry is experiencing significant developments, including eSignature beta, China-US tech separation, gaming investments, cloud computing, and concerns about AI in healthcare.&lt;br&gt;- The business sector focuses on the best banks and credit unions in California, credit union reviews, worker protection in the gig economy, and financial services.&lt;br&gt;- AI discussions cover interviews, photography, human genome research, conference recaps, and the ethical implications of AI in healthcare.</summary></entry></feed>