<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-16T08:03:28Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:03:28</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-16T08:03:28Z</published><updated>2024-01-16T08:03:28Z</updated><id>da0f5997-e208-4145-872d-218ebe5fc66a</id><summary type="html">In recent news, an Ireland court has granted permission to a former employee, allowing them to proceed with defamation claims against Elon Musk. The court's decision comes after the employee accused Musk of making defamatory statements about them. This development highlights the ongoing legal battles faced by high-profile individuals and the importance of accountability in the digital age. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, the Consumer Electronics Show (CES) 2024 showcased various transportation tech trends. The event witnessed the announcement of another merger in the micromobility sector, indicating the continued growth and consolidation within this industry. Additionally, Waymo, a leading autonomous vehicle company, made headlines as its robotaxis hit the highways, demonstrating the advancements in self-driving technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of smartphones, Oppo unveiled its latest model, the Find X7 Ultra. This smartphone stands out for featuring the first dual periscope zooms, promising enhanced photography capabilities. As smartphone technology continues to evolve, manufacturers strive to introduce innovative features to attract consumers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shifting gears, it has been revealed that Amazon's research and development (R&amp;D) spending surpasses that of all companies and the government of France. This staggering statistic underscores Amazon's commitment to innovation and its significant influence in the global tech landscape. The company's substantial R&amp;D investments enable it to continuously develop and improve its products and services, solidifying its position as a dominant player in the market.</summary></entry></feed>