<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager</id><updated>2024-01-06T08:03:24Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sat, 06 Jan 2024 08:03:24</title><link href="https://www.inoreader.com/stream/user/1004639937/tag/Voyager" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-06T08:03:24Z</published><updated>2024-01-06T08:03:24Z</updated><id>9551ea90-da34-44a5-88f5-ae640587e13e</id><summary type="html">In recent news, there have been several significant events happening around the world. Firstly, an intriguing conversation with Jill Lepore has shed light on the hold that the dead have over the living. This thought-provoking discussion has sparked contemplation on the impact of history on our present lives. Additionally, Niklaus Wirth's famous "Closing word" regarding the Algol 68 IFIP working group has garnered attention, highlighting the importance of collaboration and innovation in the field of computer science. On a different note, Apple has reignited an old dispute with Hey, a calendar app, after rejecting their new version. This clash between the tech giant and the app developers has raised questions about fairness and competition in the industry. In the realm of space exploration, United Launch Alliance and Astrobotic are preparing for an early Monday liftoff to the moon. This exciting mission signifies another step forward in our exploration of the cosmos. In a surprising turn of events, magician David Copperfield has reappeared in Jeffrey Epstein court documents, with a lawyer suggesting that he may have traded tickets for girls. This revelation has sparked outrage and further investigation into the alleged misconduct. Additionally, space photos have revealed that Japan's recent 7.6-magnitude earthquake has lifted land out of the sea, extending parts of its coastline by as much as 2 football fields. This natural phenomenon serves as a reminder of the immense power and unpredictability of our planet. Shifting our focus to the legal realm, Wayne LaPierre's lawyer has refused to discuss his client's resignation from the NRA for "health reasons" as the corruption trial begins. This trial has attracted significant attention and scrutiny, shedding light on the inner workings of the influential organization. Lastly, there has been a double-digit spike in Covid hospitalizations and deaths following the holiday season, amidst a surge in respiratory illnesses. This alarming trend emphasizes the ongoing challenges posed by the pandemic and the importance of adhering to safety measures. These events highlight the diverse and ever-changing nature of our world, reminding us of the need for awareness and engagement with global affairs.</summary></entry></feed>