<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-26T08:04:07Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Tue, 26 Sep 2023 08:04:07</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-26T08:04:07Z</published><updated>2023-09-26T08:04:07Z</updated><id>058b9d1a-1df4-4593-8de4-3d2fc66282c4</id><summary type="html">Online Educational Publishing Market 2024 Analysis, Trends, Size, Share | Industry Forecast Report 2031 - Benzinga (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- The report provides an analysis of the online educational publishing market, including trends, size, and share.&lt;br&gt;- It forecasts the industry's growth and provides insights into the future of the market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Air Force is using satellites and dirt runways to prepare its drones for a different kind of war (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- The US Air Force is utilizing satellites and dirt runways to train its drones for unconventional warfare.&lt;br&gt;- This approach allows the Air Force to simulate real-world scenarios and improve the capabilities of its drones.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US is planning its first fusion plant, and it could generate pollution-free power by 2035 (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- The US is developing plans for its first fusion plant, which has the potential to produce clean and sustainable energy by 2035.&lt;br&gt;- Fusion power has the advantage of being pollution-free and could revolutionize the energy industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intertwingled: Collection of videos to showcase the magic alchemy of computation (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Intertwingled is a collection of videos that demonstrate the fascinating combination of computation and creativity.&lt;br&gt;- The videos showcase the diverse applications of computation in various fields, highlighting its transformative power.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DJI Mini 4 Pro is the first mini with binocular vision in every direction (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- The DJI Mini 4 Pro is a groundbreaking mini drone that features binocular vision in all directions.&lt;br&gt;- This advanced technology enhances the drone's navigation and obstacle avoidance capabilities, making it safer and more efficient.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Amazon hardware boss Dave Limp will take over as CEO of Blue Origin (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Dave Limp, the former hardware boss at Amazon, has been appointed as the CEO of Blue Origin.&lt;br&gt;- This leadership change is expected to bring new strategies and innovations to the space exploration company.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ford halts work on $3.5B EV battery factory with China’s CATL (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Ford has temporarily suspended the construction of a $3.5 billion electric vehicle (EV) battery factory in partnership with China's CATL.&lt;br&gt;- The decision was made due to the global semiconductor shortage, which has impacted the automotive industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New SEC cybersecurity disclosure rules: What you need to know to stay in compliance (Business)&lt;br&gt;- The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has introduced new cybersecurity disclosure rules.&lt;br&gt;- This report provides essential information on these rules and offers guidance on how businesses can ensure compliance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Understanding Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) in TypeScript: Key Concepts and Practical Example (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This article explains the key concepts of Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) in TypeScript.&lt;br&gt;- It provides a practical example to demonstrate how OOP principles can be applied in TypeScript programming.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to Be a Good Open Source Contributor During Hacktoberfest and Beyond (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This guide offers tips on how to become a valuable open-source contributor during Hacktoberfest and beyond.&lt;br&gt;- It provides insights into the best practices and etiquette for contributing to open-source projects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Losing Human Users, Facebook Releasing Chatbots for Lonely to Talk To (AI)&lt;br&gt;- Facebook is developing chatbots to provide companionship for lonely users.&lt;br&gt;- This move comes as the social media platform experiences a decline in human users and aims to enhance user engagement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intel Closes the Gap &amp; Looks to the Future at Intel Innovation (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Intel has made significant progress in closing the technology gap and is focusing on future innovations.&lt;br&gt;- This report highlights Intel's achievements and provides insights into its future plans and strategies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ethics Expert: Episode 159 – Mita Mallick | Thomas Fox ... - JD Supra (Business)&lt;br&gt;- This episode of The Ethics Expert podcast features Mita Mallick, discussing ethical considerations in business.&lt;br&gt;- The conversation explores various topics related to ethics and provides valuable insights for business professionals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trends in separation science - 2023 - Journal of Separation Science - John Wiley (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- The Journal of Separation Science presents the latest trends in separation science for the year 2023.&lt;br&gt;- This article provides an overview of the advancements and innovations in the field of separation science.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Twitter Kills Circles, Instagram Continues Work on Similar Crew Private Sharing Feature (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- Twitter has discontinued its "Circles" feature, while Instagram is developing a similar private sharing feature called "Crew."&lt;br&gt;- This report highlights the evolving landscape of social media platforms and their efforts to enhance user experiences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood's writers strike is on the verge of ending. What happens next? (Business)&lt;br&gt;- The writers strike in Hollywood is nearing its end, raising questions about the future of the entertainment industry.&lt;br&gt;- This article explores the potential consequences and implications of the strike's resolution.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3 ChatGPT tips that have helped small-business owners nail their marketing copy &amp;mdash; and still keep the 'human touch' (AI)&lt;br&gt;- This article provides three tips for small-business owners to effectively use ChatGPT for their marketing copy.&lt;br&gt;- The tips focus on maintaining a human touch while leveraging AI technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's what needs to happen for Ukraine to make a breakthrough against Russia's defensive lines, according to war analysts (Business)&lt;br&gt;- War analysts provide insights into the necessary steps for Ukraine to achieve a breakthrough against Russia's defensive lines.&lt;br&gt;- The analysis considers various factors and strategies that could lead to a successful outcome.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold bars, cash found in home of senator charged with bribery (Business)&lt;br&gt;- A senator charged with bribery had gold bars and cash discovered in their residence.&lt;br&gt;- This report highlights the legal case and the evidence found during the investigation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's 'gobbledygook' math has lowballed, for a decade, how many fish he kills to cool his Chicago tower: AG (Business)&lt;br&gt;- Former President Trump's calculations regarding the number of fish killed to cool his Chicago tower have been criticized as inaccurate.&lt;br&gt;- This article discusses the controversy surrounding the environmental impact of the tower's cooling system.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How Much Does It Take to Be the Top% in Each U.S. State? (Business)&lt;br&gt;- This report examines the income thresholds required to be in the top percentage of earners in each U.S. state.&lt;br&gt;- It provides insights into the income disparities across states and the varying levels of wealth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study links blue light from smartphones or tablets to early puberty (AI)&lt;br&gt;- A study has found a correlation between exposure to blue light from smartphones or tablets and early puberty.&lt;br&gt;- This research highlights the potential health effects of excessive screen time, particularly in younger individuals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Romero on his book “Doom Guy” and developing games at a small scale (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- John Romero discusses his book "Doom Guy" and shares insights into game development at a small scale.&lt;br&gt;- The interview provides valuable perspectives on the gaming industry and the creative process.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Two Thangs Book: The whys of some weird paintings by Matthew Brennan aka Two Thangs (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- "The Two Thangs Book" explores the motivations and inspirations behind the unique paintings of Matthew Brennan, also known as Two Thangs.&lt;br&gt;- The book offers an in-depth look into the artist's creative process and the stories behind his artwork.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Juxtaposition: The Art of Karen Y. Buster by Karen Y. Buster (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- "Juxtaposition" showcases the art of Karen Y. Buster, highlighting her unique style and artistic vision.&lt;br&gt;- The book provides a collection of her artwork and offers insights into her creative journey.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOYS LOVE 2 + Yaoi Coloring Book + Art of Mizuyukiiro by The Yaoi Army (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- "BOYS LOVE 2" is a compilation of artwork and stories from The Yaoi Army, featuring a yaoi coloring book and the art of Mizuyukiiro.&lt;br&gt;- The book celebrates the yaoi genre and offers a visual feast for fans.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deluxe Collector's Hardbacks of Night of Death and Flowers by Rebecca L. Garcia (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- "Night of Death and Flowers" by Rebecca L. Garcia is a deluxe collector's hardback edition featuring captivating storytelling and stunning artwork.&lt;br&gt;- The book offers a unique reading experience and showcases the talent of the author and illustrator.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bold Venture (complete) 50's Radio Show w/ Bogart and Bacall by Carl Amari (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- "Bold Venture" is a complete collection of the 50's radio show featuring Humphrey Bogart and Lauren Bacall.&lt;br&gt;- The collection offers a nostalgic journey into the golden age of radio and showcases the iconic performances of the actors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Unexpected Soundscape &amp; A Soundscape of Eä by Jordan Rannells (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- "An Unexpected Soundscape" and "A Soundscape of Eä" are two audio projects by Jordan Rannells.&lt;br&gt;- These projects provide immersive sound experiences that transport listeners to different worlds and evoke emotions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hill of the Skull: A Photobook Memoir by Jeremy Bassetti by Jeremy Bassetti (Tech)&lt;br&gt;- "The Hill of the Skull" is a photobook memoir by Jeremy Bassetti, capturing his personal experiences and reflections.&lt;br&gt;- The book combines stunning photography with heartfelt storytelling, offering a unique perspective on life.</summary></entry></feed>