<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-12-03T20:01:58Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 03 Dec 2023 20:01:58</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-03T20:01:58Z</published><updated>2023-12-03T20:01:58Z</updated><id>12002a9e-6f8d-4121-a0f0-f6d0e72bdfd4</id><summary type="html">In the world this week, several notable events have taken place. In the Parsippany-Troy Hills area, the six most expensive homes were sold, showcasing the thriving real estate market in the region. Additionally, a new workflow has been introduced to investigate heart and muscle disorders, aiming to streamline the research process in these fields. However, Google has announced a delay in the release of its GPT-4 competitor, "Gemini," until next year, disappointing many eager users. On the academic front, concerns have been raised about the ethical publishing choices of women academics, highlighting potential downsides. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In economic news, after three years of struggle, America has finally achieved economic nirvana, marking a significant milestone for the country. However, not everyone has been fortunate, as a Gen Xer making $344,000 and secretly working three jobs recently got laid off from two of them, emphasizing the risks of being overemployed. The forever labor shortage continues to create tensions between parents and their childfree coworkers, further exacerbating workplace dynamics. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of science, a physicist has launched a crowdfunding campaign to fund an experiment that aims to determine if our universe is a giant simulation, sparking curiosity and intrigue. Meanwhile, a boomer couple who left Texas for their dream retirement destination shared their realization that they were misled about the state's appeal. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In international news, Russian President Vladimir Putin is reportedly concerned about potential protests from soldiers' wives and is attempting to "pay off" these individuals to prevent unrest. On a lighter note, an 11-year-old girl has gained viral fame on TikTok for showcasing her luxury outfits, including a $124,000 watch and a $31,000 handbag. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the tech world, a custom version of OpenAI's ChatGPT was created in just 15 minutes, demonstrating the accessibility and versatility of AI technology. Additionally, an IDF "rejuvenation complex" near Gaza has been established, offering amenities such as concerts, massage chairs, and buffets, providing a stark contrast to the horrors of the conflict zone. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of AI research, a 1960s chatbot named ELIZA has surpassed OpenAI's GPT-3.5 in a recent Turing test study, showcasing the advancements in conversational AI. Moreover, a new AI technique is revolutionizing 3D scene representation, enabling faster and more efficient rendering with reduced storage demands. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the medical field, Meditron, a suite of open-source medical large language models (LLMs) based on LLaMA-2, has been introduced, offering new possibilities for medical research and applications. Liver cancer rates are unfortunately rising with each successive generation, highlighting the need for increased awareness and prevention efforts. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In personal stories, a 40-year-old former teacher is retraining to enter the field of AI, expressing a desire for more people of their age to pursue similar paths. Additionally, the importance of admitting when one doesn't know something in a job interview has been discussed, emphasizing the significance of honesty and self-awareness. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In corporate news, a damning report has exposed a culture of abuse and toxicity within the union that defeated Uber, shedding light on the challenges faced by gig economy workers. Microsoft researchers have proposed MAIRA-1, a radiology-specific multimodal model for generating radiological reports from chest X-rays, showcasing advancements in medical imaging technology. Furthermore, a $2 billion unicorn startup has emerged as corporate America's secret weapon against Ozempic, a significant development in the pharmaceutical industry. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In entertainment, Sean Hannity's anti-woke Christmas movie, 'Jingle Smells,' has been released, although its timing has been criticized as unfortunate. Lastly, the obituary of Bennie Johnson has been published, commemorating their life and legacy. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amidst the diverse range of news stories, it is evident that the world continues to experience progress, challenges, and intriguing developments across various sectors.</summary></entry></feed>