<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-10T08:03:45Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 10 Sep 2023 08:03:45</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-10T08:03:45Z</published><updated>2023-09-10T08:03:45Z</updated><id>fb503746-c609-4e44-929a-35afe338b856</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Femtosecond Optical Kerr Gate in Tissues - Meyer - Journal of ... - John Wiley &amp; Sons&lt;br&gt;   - Researchers have developed a femtosecond optical Kerr gate technique for imaging tissues.&lt;br&gt;   - This technique allows for high-resolution imaging of biological tissues, which can aid in medical diagnostics and research.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Researchers use AI to find new magnetic materials without critical elements&lt;br&gt;   - Scientists have utilized artificial intelligence to discover magnetic materials that do not rely on critical elements.&lt;br&gt;   - This breakthrough could lead to the development of more sustainable and efficient technologies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. SmartKnob – Haptic input knob with software-defined endstops and virtual detents&lt;br&gt;   - SmartKnob is a haptic input knob that incorporates software-defined endstops and virtual detents.&lt;br&gt;   - This technology provides a tactile and intuitive interface for controlling various devices and applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Lithium discovery in US volcano could be biggest deposit ever found&lt;br&gt;   - A significant lithium deposit has been discovered in a volcano in the United States.&lt;br&gt;   - This discovery has the potential to be the largest lithium deposit ever found, which is crucial for the production of batteries used in electric vehicles and renewable energy storage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Elon Musk’s X is suing California over its online moderation reporting bill&lt;br&gt;   - Elon Musk's company, X, is filing a lawsuit against California regarding its online moderation reporting bill.&lt;br&gt;   - The bill requires social media platforms to disclose information about their content moderation practices, which X believes infringes on their rights.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Freshpaint (YC S19) is hiring engineers to build a HIPAA compliant data platform&lt;br&gt;   - Freshpaint, a startup from Y Combinator's Summer 2019 batch, is seeking engineers to develop a data platform that complies with HIPAA regulations.&lt;br&gt;   - This platform aims to provide secure and compliant data management solutions for the healthcare industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. Meet Falcon 180B: The Largest Openly Available Language Model With 180 Billion Parameters&lt;br&gt;   - Falcon 180B is an advanced language model with 180 billion parameters, making it the largest openly available model of its kind.&lt;br&gt;   - This model has the potential to significantly advance natural language processing and AI applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Generative AI Generation Gap: 70% Of Gen Z Use It While Gen X, Boomers Don’t Get It&lt;br&gt;   - A study reveals that 70% of Generation Z individuals actively use generative AI technology, while Generation X and Baby Boomers are less familiar with it.&lt;br&gt;   - This generation gap in AI adoption highlights the evolving relationship between different age groups and technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The use of advanced imaging techniques, such as the femtosecond optical Kerr gate, can revolutionize medical diagnostics and research.&lt;br&gt;- AI is playing a crucial role in discovering new materials and advancing sustainable technologies.&lt;br&gt;- Haptic input devices, like SmartKnob, offer intuitive and tactile interfaces for controlling various devices and applications.&lt;br&gt;- The discovery of a large lithium deposit in the US has significant implications for the production of batteries used in electric vehicles and renewable energy storage.&lt;br&gt;- The legal battle between Elon Musk's X and California highlights the ongoing debate surrounding online moderation and privacy.&lt;br&gt;- Startups like Freshpaint are addressing the need for HIPAA-compliant data platforms in the healthcare industry.&lt;br&gt;- Advanced language models, such as Falcon 180B, have the potential to revolutionize natural language processing and AI applications.&lt;br&gt;- There is a generation gap in the adoption of generative AI technology, with younger generations being more familiar with it compared to older generations.</summary></entry></feed>