<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-09T04:01:02Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 09 Aug 2023 04:01:02</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-09T04:01:02Z</published><updated>2023-08-09T04:01:02Z</updated><id>95d53e76-094d-490e-bc77-3ec2bcf7f409</id><summary type="html">Stable Diffusion, a startup, has launched a code generator called StableCode for LLM. Barcelona and Tottenham recently had a match. Noah Schnapp, Javier Loya, and Trevor Lawrence are mentioned, but no further details are provided. Wiley, a company, will be hosting an Investor Day on October 12, 2023. BNP PARIBAS ASSET MANAGEMENT Holding S.A. has reduced something, but the specifics are not mentioned. Sales have fallen in Q2 for Wiley, leading to a lowered sales forecast for the year. The US and its allies are training to avoid a fate similar to Ukrainian military commanders who were tracked down and killed by Russia. Ronald DeSantis, also known as Ron, is making Florida students obtain parental permission to use their nickname. The US Air Force has found unsafe levels of potentially cancer-causing chemicals in nuclear missile launch control centers. Millennials and Gen Zers in Asia are not interested in working in factories, which may lead to increased prices for clothes, furniture, and toys. Consumer credit card debt has surpassed $1 trillion for the first time ever. The sun's increased activity poses a threat to astronauts on the moon due to lethal doses of radiation. US companies are facing a $1.8 trillion wall of maturing corporate debt. The concept of an index fund is discussed. The workings of lotteries are explained, along with three key steps to take if one wins. Agentflow, a platform, allows for the execution of complex LLM workflows through simple JSON. ChimeraOS can turn any PC into a gaming console. Friendly Captcha offers GDPR-compliant bot protection. Project IDX is mentioned, but no details are provided. LCD, Please is a de-make of the game "Papers, please" celebrating its 10-year anniversary. Users are advised to uninstall the NightOwl macOS app. A simple XOR operation can cause a Microarchitectural Stack Overflow in the Inception project. Avoiding the news is becoming increasingly common. Mini paintings by Kimm Alfonso are showcased. CONSTRUCT by Anthony Luvera, a project by GRAIN Projects, is highlighted. Nvidia has unveiled a more powerful AI chip set to release next year. YouTube will display a blank homepage if the user has no watch history. Valve is selling refurbished Steam Decks. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insight: The news covers a wide range of topics, including technology, sports, finance, and global affairs. It highlights various events, developments, and trends happening around the world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conclusion: The news provides a snapshot of current events and offers insights into different industries and sectors. It showcases the diversity of topics and the interconnectedness of global issues.</summary></entry></feed>