<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-17T12:01:14Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 17 Aug 2023 12:01:14</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-17T12:01:14Z</published><updated>2023-08-17T12:01:14Z</updated><id>17bb30aa-e2c9-43f6-9030-4e183ffea109</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Ford is expanding its services, taking inspiration from Tesla.&lt;br&gt;- Madden 24, a video game, has responded to community feedback on-field audio.&lt;br&gt;- MIT and Harvard have developed an open-source system for object detection and tracking.&lt;br&gt;- CATL has developed a "Superfast Charging Battery" with a 250-mile range and 10-minute charge.&lt;br&gt;- Lenovo is rumored to be releasing a competitor to the Steam Deck.&lt;br&gt;- Acronym has partnered with Asus to create a new computer.&lt;br&gt;- dLocal, a payment platform, has rebounded from a short seller attack.&lt;br&gt;- Intel's 14th Gen processors, Raptor Lake Refresh, have confirmed performance and launch date.&lt;br&gt;- MLIR framework is being discussed in a series of articles for beginners.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers are teaching robots to open dishwashers and doors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- Nisa Investment Advisors has reduced its holdings in John Wiley &amp; Sons.&lt;br&gt;- Rupert Murdoch, aged 92, is dating again after breaking off his engagement.&lt;br&gt;- Splitit, a BNPL vendor, is seeking to go private in exchange for fresh funds.&lt;br&gt;- The New York Times is considering legal action against OpenAI over copyright issues.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- MIT and Harvard's open-source system enables real-time object detection, tracking, and following.&lt;br&gt;- Embroid is an AI method for stitching together models and correcting predictions without supervision.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Best money market accounts for August 2023 are offering up to 5.46% interest.&lt;br&gt;- The jail where Trump and co-defendants in the Georgia racketeering case will be booked is discussed.&lt;br&gt;- Terraform Industries Blog explains how to produce green hydrogen for $1/kg.&lt;br&gt;- Comet Nishimura may be visible to the naked eye in the coming weeks.&lt;br&gt;- The iconic flying boat from World War II is being revived.&lt;br&gt;- The Journal of the Association for Information Science and Technology is published by John Wiley.&lt;br&gt;- A correction has been made for a scientific paper on the inactivation of glyceraldehyde-3-phosphate dehydrogenase.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- Ford's move into services shows the influence of Tesla's successful business model.&lt;br&gt;- The development of a "Superfast Charging Battery" by CATL could revolutionize electric vehicle charging.&lt;br&gt;- The partnership between Acronym and Asus highlights the demand for high-performance computers.&lt;br&gt;- The rebound of dLocal after a short seller attack demonstrates the resilience of the company.&lt;br&gt;- The consideration of legal action by The New York Times against OpenAI reflects the ongoing copyright tensions in the industry.&lt;br&gt;- The advancements in AI, such as MIT and Harvard's open-source system and Embroid's AI method, showcase the potential for innovation in the field.&lt;br&gt;- The interest in green hydrogen production highlights the growing focus on sustainable energy solutions.&lt;br&gt;- The potential visibility of Comet Nishimura offers an exciting astronomical event for enthusiasts.&lt;br&gt;- The revival of the iconic flying boat from World War II showcases the preservation of historical artifacts.&lt;br&gt;- The correction made for the scientific paper emphasizes the importance of accuracy in research.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report highlights the latest developments in technology, business, and AI, providing insights into the trends and advancements in these fields. The diverse range of topics covered demonstrates the breadth of innovation and progress happening across industries.</summary></entry></feed>