<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-21T04:00:57Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 21 Aug 2023 04:00:57</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-21T04:00:57Z</published><updated>2023-08-21T04:00:57Z</updated><id>5f5d5730-1490-419e-9e5e-e588f446afcc</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- Run a macOS VM on Apple Silicon from a double-click with Vimy&lt;br&gt;- SwitchBot says its new smart curtain controller is stronger and quieter&lt;br&gt;- Demystifying EKS Authentication and Authorization: A Guide to Strengthening Network Security&lt;br&gt;- Comprehensive Walkthrough on How to Connect Your Flutter App to a REST API&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from Cornell Introduce Quantization with Incoherence Processing (QuIP): A New AI Method based on the Insight that Quantization Benefits from Incoherent Weight and Hessian Matrices&lt;br&gt;- Get your own WebRTC Audio and Video using Open Source, Self Hosted Coturn for your Turn Server!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- A fellow Yale secret society member said Ron DeSantis rolled his eyes when she talked about her upbringing as a Hispanic girl in Texas: 'It was like I wasn't worth listening to'&lt;br&gt;- A Marylander who hadn't recently traveled internationally caught malaria. Officials say it's the state's first 'locally acquired' case in 40 years.&lt;br&gt;- I was a USPS letter carrier for 44 years. To protect us from extreme heat, the postal service needs to provide more training and air-conditioned trucks.&lt;br&gt;- On 1-Year Anniversary Of Inflation Reduction Act’s Signing, Impact On Drug Prices And Out-Of-Pocket Spending Still To Be Determined&lt;br&gt;- The owner of a 1,900-square-foot house next to the Masters golf course kept turning down millions of dollars to sell&lt;br&gt;- GOP presidential candidate Vivek Ramaswamy says he can bring in 'voters of diverse shades of melanin' to the party by focusing on the economy&lt;br&gt;- A Maui restaurant owner is 'praying visitors will start to come back soon'&lt;br&gt;- Mexico replaced China as America's top trade buddy &amp;mdash; and it shows how the global economy is rapidly transforming&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- What happens to Salma Hayek in 'Black Mirror' might seem ridiculous &amp;ndash; but the way celebrities handle their AI rights could affect us all&lt;br&gt;- Researchers from Cornell Introduce Quantization with Incoherence Processing (QuIP): A New AI Method based on the Insight that Quantization Benefits from Incoherent Weight and Hessian Matrices&lt;br&gt;- ‘Baldur’s Gate 3’ Has Some Of The Best Romances In Gaming History, If Not The Best&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;- Pompeii find reveals the secrets of life as a slave in Ancient Rome, frozen in time for almost 2,000 years by volcanic eruption&lt;br&gt;- Data centres account for between 1.5% and 2% of global electricity consumption&lt;br&gt;- Adobe co-founder Dr. John Warnock has died — he was 82&lt;br&gt;- Tesla's massive data breach in May affected more than 75,000 people, carmaker says&lt;br&gt;- Ukraine lacks the drone capacity to strike enough targets in Russia to erode its 'will to fight,' retired US colonel says&lt;br&gt;- The Pentagon’s UFO Shop, the Hitchhiker Effect, and Models of Contagion [pdf]&lt;br&gt;- Ancient viruses could re-emerge as permafrost melts, posing 'unpredictable threats' to our communities, new study says&lt;br&gt;- X glitch wipes out most pictures and links tweeted before December 2014&lt;br&gt;- Video captures the terrifying moment a Russian ballistic missile slammed into a theatre in the Ukrainian city of Chernihiv killing 7, wounding 144&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The tech section highlights advancements in macOS VM, smart curtain controllers, network security, app development, and AI methods.&lt;br&gt;- The business section covers topics such as discrimination, public health, postal service, drug prices, real estate, politics, and tourism.&lt;br&gt;- The AI section explores the intersection of AI and celebrity rights, as well as its application in gaming.&lt;br&gt;- The other section includes historical discoveries, energy consumption, obituary, data breach, military capabilities, UFOs, permafrost risks, social media glitch, and international conflicts.&lt;br&gt;- Overall, the report showcases a diverse range of topics, highlighting technological advancements, societal issues, historical findings, and global events.</summary></entry></feed>