<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-08-13T02:01:33Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 13 Aug 2023 02:01:33</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-08-13T02:01:33Z</published><updated>2023-08-13T02:01:33Z</updated><id>a6bb4f82-c90a-48eb-82bd-61dfa19b00ed</id><summary type="html">Tech:&lt;br&gt;- NASA's Software Catalog offers hundreds of new software programs for free.&lt;br&gt;- iRobot’s Roomba j7 Plus, our favorite robot vacuum, has hit an all-time low.&lt;br&gt;- AI agent Dynalang could change the way we talk to robots.&lt;br&gt;- Google AI introduces Visually Rich Document Understanding (VRDU): A Dataset for Better Tracking of Document Understanding Task Progress.&lt;br&gt;- Setup your self-hosted, open-source, Matrix chat server for fully private and encrypted messaging.&lt;br&gt;- Can Large-Scale Language Models Replace Humans in Text Evaluation Tasks? This AI Paper Proposes to Use LLM for Evaluating the Quality of Texts to Serve as an Alternative to Human Evaluation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- NASA's Software Catalog provides access to a wide range of software programs for various purposes.&lt;br&gt;- The Roomba j7 Plus is a highly recommended robot vacuum that is currently available at a discounted price.&lt;br&gt;- Dynalang is an AI agent that has the potential to revolutionize human-robot interactions.&lt;br&gt;- Google AI's VRDU dataset aims to improve the tracking of document understanding task progress.&lt;br&gt;- Self-hosted Matrix chat servers offer secure and encrypted messaging options.&lt;br&gt;- Large-scale language models can be used to evaluate the quality of texts as an alternative to human evaluation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The availability of free software programs from NASA's Software Catalog can greatly benefit researchers and developers.&lt;br&gt;- The discounted price of the Roomba j7 Plus makes it an attractive option for those in need of a robot vacuum.&lt;br&gt;- AI agents like Dynalang have the potential to enhance the user experience in human-robot interactions.&lt;br&gt;- Google AI's VRDU dataset can contribute to advancements in document understanding technology.&lt;br&gt;- Self-hosted Matrix chat servers provide a secure and private messaging platform.&lt;br&gt;- Large-scale language models can be a valuable tool in evaluating the quality of texts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;- An American Airlines passenger paid for 3 seats to fly with his beloved Great Dane dog from LA to New York.&lt;br&gt;- Soccer fans caught burning or ripping money in Argentina face up to 30 days in prison as the country cracks down on those mocking its high inflation.&lt;br&gt;- A Ukrainian arms dealer accused of corruption is now one of the country's top weapons suppliers.&lt;br&gt;- Truth Social warned the FBI about a plot against Biden, highlighting the importance of platforms tracking such threats.&lt;br&gt;- Harvard University, the richest in the world, encourages students to go on food stamps.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- An American Airlines passenger went to great lengths to ensure the comfort of their pet during a flight.&lt;br&gt;- Argentina is taking strict measures to address the issue of high inflation and punish those who mock it.&lt;br&gt;- The Ukrainian arms dealer's alleged corruption raises concerns about the country's weapons supply.&lt;br&gt;- Truth Social's warning to the FBI emphasizes the need for platforms to actively track and address potential threats.&lt;br&gt;- Harvard University's encouragement of students to go on food stamps raises questions about income inequality and access to resources.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The story of the American Airlines passenger highlights the extent to which people are willing to go for their pets.&lt;br&gt;- Argentina's crackdown on those mocking high inflation reflects the government's efforts to address economic challenges.&lt;br&gt;- The Ukrainian arms dealer's rise as a top weapons supplier despite corruption allegations raises concerns about accountability and transparency.&lt;br&gt;- The incident involving Truth Social and the FBI underscores the importance of platforms taking responsibility for monitoring and reporting potential threats.&lt;br&gt;- Harvard University's encouragement of students to go on food stamps raises questions about the financial struggles faced by students and the need for greater support.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;- New finding boosts Panspermia theory that life on Earth originated in deep space.&lt;br&gt;- AI agent Dynalang could change the way we talk to robots.&lt;br&gt;- Can Large-Scale Language Models Replace Humans in Text Evaluation Tasks? This AI Paper Proposes to Use LLM for Evaluating the Quality of Texts to Serve as an Alternative to Human Evaluation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key points:&lt;br&gt;- The new finding supports the Panspermia theory, suggesting that life on Earth may have originated from outer space.&lt;br&gt;- Dynalang, an AI agent, has the potential to revolutionize human-robot interactions.&lt;br&gt;- Large-scale language models can be used to evaluate the quality of texts as an alternative to human evaluation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The new finding regarding the Panspermia theory adds to the ongoing discussion about the origins of life on Earth.&lt;br&gt;- Dynalang's potential impact on human-robot interactions highlights the advancements in AI technology.&lt;br&gt;- The use of large-scale language models for text evaluation tasks presents an alternative approach that can potentially improve efficiency and accuracy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary of overall insights:&lt;br&gt;- The availability of free software programs from NASA's Software Catalog and the discounted price of the Roomba j7 Plus offer practical benefits to consumers.&lt;br&gt;- AI agents like Dynalang and large-scale language models have the potential to transform various aspects of technology and human interactions.&lt;br&gt;- The incidents involving the American Airlines passenger, soccer fans in Argentina, the Ukrainian arms dealer, and Truth Social's warning to the FBI shed light on different societal and business issues.&lt;br&gt;- The encouragement of Harvard University students to go on food stamps raises questions about income inequality and access to resources.&lt;br&gt;- The new finding supporting the Panspermia theory adds to our understanding of the origins of life on Earth.</summary></entry></feed>