<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2023-09-13T20:02:33Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Wed, 13 Sep 2023 20:02:33</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-09-13T20:02:33Z</published><updated>2023-09-13T20:02:33Z</updated><id>c31100b3-803c-4948-824d-0c7d37c7cf54</id><summary type="html">Report:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech:&lt;br&gt;1. Coca-Cola introduces a futuristic, AI-generated "Y3000" flavored soda.&lt;br&gt;- Coca-Cola is embracing AI technology to create a new soda flavor called "Y3000."&lt;br&gt;- The AI-generated flavor aims to cater to future consumer preferences and trends.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Google invests $10 billion annually to maintain its position as the leading online search engine.&lt;br&gt;- The Department of Justice reveals that Google spends a significant amount of money each year to ensure its dominance in the online search market.&lt;br&gt;- This investment highlights Google's commitment to remaining the go-to search engine for users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. A deep learning method for keystroke detection in augmented reality (AR) enables typing on any surface.&lt;br&gt;- Researchers have developed a deep learning technique that allows users to type on any surface in AR environments.&lt;br&gt;- This advancement in technology enhances user experience and expands the possibilities of AR applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business:&lt;br&gt;1. Warren Buffett's fortune surpasses Larry Page's, and he is closing in on Bill Gates and Larry Ellison.&lt;br&gt;- Warren Buffett's wealth reaches $123 billion, making him richer than Larry Page.&lt;br&gt;- Buffett's growing fortune positions him to potentially surpass Bill Gates and Larry Ellison in wealth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. The impact of the pay gap between employees and CEOs on workers is discussed by experts.&lt;br&gt;- Experts analyze how the significant pay disparity between CEOs and employees affects workers.&lt;br&gt;- The discussion sheds light on the inequality within corporate structures and its consequences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Patagonia's success demonstrates that doing the right thing can be profitable in the long run.&lt;br&gt;- Patagonia's commitment to ethical practices has proven to be financially beneficial over its 50-year history.&lt;br&gt;- The company's success serves as a lesson that prioritizing sustainability and social responsibility can lead to profitability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI:&lt;br&gt;1. Goldman Sachs states that there is no bubble in AI stocks and predicts further outperformance.&lt;br&gt;- Goldman Sachs asserts that the current stage of AI stocks is not a bubble but rather the early stages of a tech cycle.&lt;br&gt;- The investment bank predicts that AI stocks will continue to outperform in the future.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. PyGraft, an open-source Python-based AI tool, generates highly customized schemas and knowledge graphs.&lt;br&gt;- PyGraft is an AI tool developed in Python that can create personalized schemas and knowledge graphs.&lt;br&gt;- This tool offers flexibility and adaptability for various domains and applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. A gathering of Silicon Valley leaders and lawmakers focuses on the future of AI.&lt;br&gt;- Prominent figures from Silicon Valley convene with lawmakers to discuss the implications and potential of AI.&lt;br&gt;- The meeting aims to shape policies and regulations surrounding AI technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insights:&lt;br&gt;- The integration of AI technology is prevalent across various industries, including food and beverage (Coca-Cola), internet services (Google), and AI development (PyGraft).&lt;br&gt;- Wealth distribution among business leaders continues to be a topic of discussion, with Warren Buffett's fortune surpassing that of Larry Page.&lt;br&gt;- The potential of AI stocks and their long-term performance is a subject of interest for investors, as highlighted by Goldman Sachs.&lt;br&gt;- Ethical practices and sustainability can lead to financial success, as demonstrated by Patagonia's 50-year journey.&lt;br&gt;- The collaboration between Silicon Valley leaders and lawmakers emphasizes the importance of shaping AI policies and regulations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, this report showcases the diverse applications of AI, highlights key developments in the business sector, and explores the impact of wealth distribution and ethical practices. The insights gathered emphasize the significance of AI technology and its potential for future growth and societal impact.</summary></entry></feed>